<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:36:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec 2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3823009</link><description>The December 2025 quarterly earnings season has delivered a nuanced picture across Indian equities, with 48.0% of companies reporting positive results, marking an improvement from the previous quarter’s 42.0%. Mid-cap stocks have emerged as the standout performers, driving aggregate profit growth amid a mixed performance from large and small caps.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>9b9aa0a751cffe6665cc2696477f2da9</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ind-Swift Labs Joins MomentumNow Stocks on Strong Financial Upswing</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/mojo-premium/ind-swift-labs-joins-momentumnow-stocks-on-strong-financial-upswing-3822998</link><description>Ind-Swift Labs., a micro-cap pharmaceutical company, has been added to the MomentumNow Stocks list as of 05 February 2026, reflecting a significant improvement in its financial performance and technical momentum. This inclusion highlights the company’s robust growth trajectory, underpinned by impressive quarterly results and a bullish outlook that aligns well with the MomentumNow strategy of capitalising on stocks exhibiting strong fundamental and technical momentum.
Time: 36 minutes ago</description><guid>87700df855709bc1f1377ac1755db444</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GRM Overseas Joins Hidden Turnarounds List on Strong Financial Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/mojo-premium/grm-overseas-joins-hidden-turnarounds-list-on-strong-financial-momentum-3822997</link><description>GRM Overseas, a small-cap player in the Other Agricultural Products sector, has been added to the Hidden Turnarounds list as of 5 February 2026, following a marked improvement in its financial performance and operational metrics. This inclusion reflects the company’s recent positive momentum and positions it as a compelling candidate for investors seeking early-stage turnaround opportunities.
Time: 36 minutes ago</description><guid>ea338fba1960513c9b128c2e4c70f10a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Blackbuck Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-blackbuck-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3822979</link><description>Blackbuck Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results show strong revenue growth with net sales up 53.02% year-on-year, but profitability declined with a 13.35% drop in net profit and reduced operating margins. While the company maintains a solid return on equity and a net cash position, rising costs and margin pressures present challenges moving forward.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>967e0feb1be04a2734de5fca0dc90882</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Shipping Corporation of India Land &amp; Assets Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-shipping-corporation-of-india-land-assets-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3822978</link><description>The latest results for Shipping Corporation of India Land &amp; Assets Ltd show a net profit of ₹11.13 crores, primarily driven by other income, but revenue declined by 7.83% and the operating margin remains negative at -88.32%, raising concerns about the sustainability of its earnings and overall financial health.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a35ebda9882b13a70ed614a4ef79cfee</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Inventurus Knowledge Solutions Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-inventurus-knowledge-solutions-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3822977</link><description>Inventurus Knowledge Solutions Ltd's Q3 FY26 results are strong, with net sales up 24.01% year-on-year and net profit increasing by 41.37%. However, the stock is trading at a premium valuation, which may pose risks for future performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>69e820fc5df9de9bf8240580f6f6b4e9</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Apeejay Surrendra Park Hotels Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-apeejay-surrendra-park-hotels-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3822976</link><description>Apeejay Surrendra Park Hotels Ltd reported record quarterly revenue of ₹200.06 crores, but net profit fell 24.75% to ₹24.20 crores due to rising interest expenses and tax burdens, indicating operational challenges despite strong revenue growth. Overall, the results reflect mixed performance with concerns about profitability and financial health.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>090221b2ff85e1f7827a0185757486b4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Emcure Pharmaceuticals Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-emcure-pharmaceuticals-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3822975</link><description>Emcure Pharmaceuticals Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show strong revenue growth with net sales at ₹2,363.48 crores, up 20.42% year-on-year, but a sequential profit decline raises concerns about margin sustainability. Overall, while revenue momentum is robust, the decrease in profit suggests caution moving forward.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5c5260162e7981b832b9b419f1ef7b08</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Rishabh Instruments Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-rishabh-instruments-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3822974</link><description>Rishabh Instruments Ltd's latest results show significant profit growth of 436.32% year-on-year, with net sales reaching a record ₹196.33 crores; however, concerns remain regarding low return on equity and slowing revenue growth, indicating mixed financial performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d6b57209526a98fe6f4f423cfab29111</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Avalon Technologies Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-avalon-technologies-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3822972</link><description>Avalon Technologies Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are strong, with a net profit of ₹32.60 crores (up 35.89% year-on-year) and record revenue of ₹417.54 crores (up 48.67% year-on-year), reflecting robust growth and improved operational efficiency. The company also reduced long-term debt, indicating prudent financial management.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>461a4b766fdc812e134b82b67c228cb0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Keystone Realtors Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-keystone-realtors-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3822971</link><description>Keystone Realtors Ltd's latest results are concerning, with a 77.57% decline in net profit and a 42.64% drop in net sales year-on-year, indicating significant operational challenges and financial deterioration. The company's ability to cover interest expenses has also weakened, raising doubts about its future prospects.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b48fb1aaf8b284c987aab9495864c4cc</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Tracxn Technologies Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-tracxn-technologies-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3822970</link><description>Tracxn Technologies Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results are concerning, showing a net loss of ₹5.56 crores and stagnating revenue, indicating operational inefficiencies and a lack of growth momentum. The company faces significant challenges, including high employee costs and a deteriorating operating margin, which may require strategic reassessment to improve profitability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f1661f75c900fa4150179fd2b7d0b929</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Kaynes Technology India Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-kaynes-technology-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3822969</link><description>Kaynes Technology India Ltd's Q2 FY26 results are strong, with net sales up 58.40% year-on-year and net profit up 101.64%, indicating robust growth. However, high valuation metrics may raise concerns about sustainability despite the company's solid operational performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e7a7eca2d0169f69b45340a47d60c867</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Global Health Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-global-health-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3822968</link><description>Global Health Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth with net sales up 18.83% year-on-year, but net profit fell significantly by 33.51%, indicating challenges in profitability and operational efficiency. The company needs to improve cost management to enhance future performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2d63b60b9678039774be7a77befc46a6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Archean Chemical Industries Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-archean-chemical-industries-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3822967</link><description>Archean Chemical Industries Ltd's latest results show modest revenue growth of 5.06% year-on-year, but a significant net profit decline of 50.72%, indicating serious profitability challenges and margin compression. Investors should be cautious and monitor future performance for signs of recovery.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f7bd83c4fcdb3265819c4fe2a4a1ce08</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Data Patterns (India) Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-data-patterns-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3822966</link><description>Data Patterns (India) Ltd reported strong revenue growth of 209.53% quarter-on-quarter, reaching ₹307.46 crores, and a net profit increase of 92.90% to ₹49.19 crores. However, margin compression raises concerns about profitability sustainability, despite effective capital deployment and a zero-debt balance sheet.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5cb42ea89996b86dab8ead07ed5a7e0f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Venus Pipes &amp; Tubes Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-venus-pipes-tubes-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3822965</link><description>Venus Pipes &amp; Tubes Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 27.34% year-on-year, reaching ₹291.54 crore, but net profit declined by 10.25% and operating margins contracted, indicating rising cost pressures and operational challenges. Overall, while revenue performance is positive, concerns about profitability persist.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>935d7b08c208eb4972998b81b055de01</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Harsha Engineers International Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-harsha-engineers-international-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3822964</link><description>Harsha Engineers International Ltd's latest results show mixed performance: net sales grew by 7.31% year-on-year, but net profit declined sequentially despite a 25.83% year-on-year increase, highlighting ongoing operational challenges and margin pressures. Investors should monitor how the company addresses these issues in future quarters.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0764c95479e0e18bdba9d715d7a410f9</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Aptus Value Housing Finance India Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-aptus-value-housing-finance-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3822963</link><description>Aptus Value Housing Finance India Ltd's latest results show a mixed performance, with a net profit increase and strong capital efficiency, but rising operational costs and significant promoter shareholding reduction have pressured the stock, leading to underperformance in the market. Future quarters will be key to assessing if operational strengths can improve market sentiment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>dc1d80e9e50f637514b6fbc7674a7837</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Metropolis Healthcare Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-metropolis-healthcare-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3822962</link><description>Metropolis Healthcare Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results show strong revenue growth of 22.70% year-on-year, with net profit increasing by 13.22%. However, while operational metrics are solid, profitability margins are under pressure, indicating a mixed performance overall.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>46528280a038fc57811e9bb8b1f3ea12</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:36:41 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>