<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 06:26:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>IDBI Bank Ltd. Surges to Intraday High with 5.25% Gain on 2 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/idbi-bank-ltd-surges-to-intraday-high-with-525-gain-on-2-jan-2026-3778980</link><description>IDBI Bank Ltd. surged to an intraday high of Rs 109.7 on 2 Jan 2026, marking a robust 5.73% increase during the trading session and outperforming its sector peers significantly.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>fa0a83fd2a0e9d54255045851cc4f9cf</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 06:26:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Piramal Finance Ltd Hits Intraday High with 3.81% Surge on 2 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/piramal-finance-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-381-surge-on-2-jan-2026-3778979</link><description>Piramal Finance Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 2 Jan 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 1700, marking a 3.55% rise. The stock outpaced the broader market and its sector, reflecting sustained buying momentum and positive trading action throughout the session.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>73e303b734e6d22d320deffe7029c94b</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 06:26:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NTPC Ltd. Hits Intraday High with Strong 3.14% Surge on 2 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ntpc-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-strong-314-surge-on-2-jan-2026-3778981</link><description>NTPC Ltd. demonstrated robust intraday performance on 2 Jan 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 346.9, marking a 3.15% increase. The stock outpaced the broader Sensex and its sector peers, continuing its upward momentum for the third consecutive day.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>29dcc6cf938239d3265ae6e730c525c8</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 06:26:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aavas Financiers Ltd. Stock Hits 52-Week Low at Rs.1431.05</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aavas-financiers-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-at-rs143105-3778975</link><description>Aavas Financiers Ltd., a key player in the housing finance sector, has recorded a fresh 52-week low of Rs.1431.05, marking a significant decline amid a broader market rally. The stock has underperformed its sector and benchmark indices, reflecting a series of challenges impacting its valuation and market sentiment.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>d7f297e0bfb25a42287754658ff83e4f</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 06:26:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Samrat Forgings Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.226 Amidst Weak Financial Metrics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/samrat-forgings-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs226-amidst-weak-financial-metrics-3778974</link><description>Samrat Forgings Ltd, a player in the Castings &amp; Forgings sector, has touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.226 today, marking a significant decline amid ongoing downward momentum. The stock’s performance contrasts sharply with broader market gains, reflecting persistent pressures on the company’s financial and operational metrics.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>b20f80cdd5fb632a46284a39e6c02f6c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 06:26:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Energy Solutions Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.1061.9</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-energy-solutions-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs10619-3778976</link><description>Adani Energy Solutions Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.1061.9 on 2 Jan 2026, marking a notable surge in the power sector amid a broadly positive market environment.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>509f4da235916c34fb464ce4bcfeaa9a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 06:26:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Unipro Technologies Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.9.95</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/unipro-technologies-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs995-3778969</link><description>Unipro Technologies Ltd reached a significant milestone today by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.9.95, marking a notable surge in its stock price and reflecting sustained momentum over the past week.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>98f704b3aeed765f5b67cbb75f27ff2e</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 06:26:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Unison Metals Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/unison-metals-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3778977</link><description>Unison Metals Ltd, a player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, touched a new 52-week and all-time low of Rs.1.44 on 2 Jan 2026, marking a significant decline amid ongoing market pressures and company-specific factors. The stock underperformed its sector by 2.06% on the day, reflecting persistent challenges in its financial and operational metrics.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>68867ae01911ac4891de8a98adc896a9</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 06:26:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Frontline Corporation Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/frontline-corporation-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3778971</link><description>Frontline Corporation Ltd, a player in the Transport Services sector, recorded a fresh 52-week low of Rs.34.71 today, marking a significant decline amid ongoing downward momentum. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting persistent pressures on its valuation and financial metrics.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>cce6e6e649d126057661d0866f090903</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 06:26:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>3M India Ltd. Hits New 52-Week High of Rs 37,384.85</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/3m-india-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-of-rs-3738485-3778973</link><description>3M India Ltd. has reached a significant milestone by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs. 37,384.85, marking a strong rally driven by sustained momentum and robust financial performance. The stock has outperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting investor confidence in its recent results and operational metrics.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>1e672a3bb6c2f2ceda771b49af27ba56</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 06:26:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oil Country Tubular Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Financial Strains</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/oil-country-tubular-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-financial-strains-3778972</link><description>Oil Country Tubular Ltd’s stock has declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing near Rs 59.8, marking a significant downturn amid persistent financial headwinds and underperformance relative to the broader market and sector peers.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>c4c7aabafb10e8b09b3fcf008a41f4e1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 06:26:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IDBI Bank Ltd. Hits New 52-Week High of Rs 109.7, Marking Significant Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/idbi-bank-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-of-rs-1097-marking-significant-milestone-3778970</link><description>IDBI Bank Ltd. has surged to a fresh 52-week high of Rs.109.7, reflecting robust momentum and sustained gains over recent sessions. This milestone underscores the bank’s impressive performance amid a broadly positive market backdrop.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>30fa97b2c44c8fab6d7a8d1652287220</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 06:26:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Covidh Technologies Ltd Hits New 52-Week High of Rs.17.65</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/covidh-technologies-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-of-rs1765-3778978</link><description>Covidh Technologies Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.17.65 today, marking a notable surge in its stock price and reflecting sustained momentum over the past month.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>1316a19589f2409b0e4e09c23dd56ede</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 06:26:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NIBE Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.6% Surge on 2 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nibe-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-76-surge-on-2-jan-2026-3778965</link><description>NIBE Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 2 Jan 2026, surging 7.6% to touch a day’s high of Rs 1,215.6, significantly outperforming the broader Sensex and its Aerospace &amp; Defense sector peers.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>ef8325a132e6693f22295c5ea0f58dfa</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 06:26:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GE Power India Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.22% Surge on 2 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ge-power-india-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-722-surge-on-2-jan-2026-3778967</link><description>GE Power India Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 2 January 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 350.7, marking a 7.74% increase. The stock outpaced its sector and broader market indices, reflecting strong trading momentum and sustained gains over recent sessions.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>f449a6b4b3d28cb392faa5b04c671808</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 06:26:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JBM Auto Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.05% Surge on 2 January 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jbm-auto-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-705-surge-on-2-january-2026-3778966</link><description>JBM Auto Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 2 Jan 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 673.2, marking a 7.56% increase from its previous close. This notable rally outpaced the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector and broader market indices, reflecting a significant rebound after two days of decline.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>bde1bd120cf95e47b8450b3e63d52c7e</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 06:26:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SJVN Ltd. Hits Intraday High with 5.1% Surge on 2 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sjvn-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-51-surge-on-2-jan-2026-3778964</link><description>SJVN Ltd. demonstrated robust intraday strength on 2 Jan 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 78.89, marking a 5.57% increase from its previous close. This performance notably outpaced the broader Sensex and the power sector, reflecting significant trading momentum within the stock.
Time: 38 minutes ago</description><guid>4221a63aa4b65550876cdc6efe4b4bcd</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 06:26:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Senores Pharmaceuticals Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.864.65</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/senores-pharmaceuticals-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs86465-3778963</link><description>Senores Pharmaceuticals Ltd has surged to a fresh 52-week and all-time high of Rs.864.65, marking a significant milestone in its stock performance amid a broadly positive market environment.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>03a501ecc4582824e2b20d8e89219a90</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 06:26:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ruchi Infrastructure Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.6 Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ruchi-infrastructure-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs6-amid-continued-downtrend-3778962</link><description>Ruchi Infrastructure Ltd’s stock touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.6 today, marking a significant decline amid ongoing underperformance relative to the broader market and its sector peers. The stock has now fallen for three consecutive sessions, accumulating a loss of 8.81% over this period, reflecting persistent pressures on the company’s valuation and investor sentiment.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>6e01125fdf886946970394e511c26957</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 06:26:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kalpataru Ltd Hits Intraday High with 5.09% Surge on 2 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kalpataru-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-509-surge-on-2-jan-2026-3778960</link><description>Kalpataru Ltd, a key player in the realty sector, demonstrated robust intraday performance on 2 January 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 369.6, marking a 6.28% increase from its previous close. The stock outperformed the broader market and its sector peers, registering a day gain of 5.09% amid a generally positive market environment.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>b963224345652f20f529e1a07ba8d62d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 06:26:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 06:26:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>