<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:46:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Ratnaveer Precision Engineering Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ratnaveer-precision-engineering-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3860611</link><description>Ratnaveer Precision Engineering Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>49fea6cee6c35ce17cb15c4a2c8efaf4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:46:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Supriya Lifescience Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/supriya-lifescience-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3860607</link><description>Supriya Lifescience Ltd has recently experienced a significant technical development as its 50-day moving average (DMA) crossed below the 200-day moving average, forming a Death Cross. This event is widely regarded by market analysts as a bearish signal, indicating a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raising concerns about its medium to long-term price prospects.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>08243ee2d7296812ff478676ccd39464</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:46:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ashika Credit Capital Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ashika-credit-capital-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3860610</link><description>Ashika Credit Capital Ltd (Stock ID: 630303), a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross—a significant technical event where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses above the 200-DMA. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout, indicating a possible shift in long-term momentum and trend reversal for the stock.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>cc8826e79b63da51b7c5d6a011bf5a8e</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:46:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IFCI Ltd. Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ifci-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3860608</link><description>IFCI Ltd., a prominent player in the finance sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross—a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, attracting renewed investor interest despite the company’s current Mojo Grade of Sell.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>da2fd2d83313b4324d675246cba6883b</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:46:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vistar Amar Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vistar-amar-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3860609</link><description>Vistar Amar Ltd, a micro-cap player in the FMCG sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses above the 200-DMA. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, marking a possible trend reversal for the stock after a period of mixed performance.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>784f39e073754935fc0d81cd28b4e213</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:46:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec 2025 Results Reveal Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-reveal-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3860606</link><description>The December 2025 quarter results season has unfolded with a nuanced picture across Indian equities, as 4,094 companies declared their earnings. While the proportion of companies reporting positive results has inched up to 46.0%, this reflects only a modest improvement compared to the preceding quarters, underscoring persistent challenges in the broader economic environment.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>795dba682d6ad473ab80b8007a5a78d1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:46:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pashupati Cotspin Ltd Hits New 52-Week High of Rs.1025 on 27 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pashupati-cotspin-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-of-rs1025-on-27-feb-2026-3860547</link><description>Pashupati Cotspin Ltd achieved a significant milestone on 27 Feb 2026, reaching a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs.1025. This marks a notable moment for the garment and apparel company as it continues its upward momentum, outperforming its sector peers and demonstrating sustained strength over the past several weeks.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>d1c7eaf99d1ccc15d491179206215ccc</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:46:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ashirwad Steels &amp; Industries Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.22</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ashirwad-steels-industries-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs22-3860549</link><description>Ashirwad Steels &amp; Industries Ltd has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.22 today, marking a significant decline in its share price amid broader market pressures and company-specific performance issues. This fresh low comes after a brief two-day rally, signalling a continuation of the stock’s downward trajectory within the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>941307331c4a66203c3cd390a390b0e8</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:46:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Procter &amp; Gamble Hygiene &amp; Health Care Ltd. Stock Hits 52-Week Low at Rs.11,253.75</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/procter-gamble-hygiene-health-care-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-at-rs1125375-3860548</link><description>Procter &amp; Gamble Hygiene &amp; Health Care Ltd. has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.11253.75, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid broader market pressures and company-specific valuation concerns.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>321924393bc5c6e0ae0c9ee86600eef1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:46:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bartronics India Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.10.14 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bartronics-india-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs1014-amidst-continued-downtrend-3860546</link><description>Bartronics India Ltd, a player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.10.14 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing pressures on its valuation and performance metrics.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>0f0b1c63be1d4aba04d23d007121854f</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:46:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TeleCanor Global Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.48.5</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/telecanor-global-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs485-3860545</link><description>TeleCanor Global Ltd, a key player in the Software Products sector, reached a significant milestone today by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.48.5. This achievement marks a continuation of the stock’s robust momentum, reflecting strong market performance amid a broader sector downturn.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>724b068444f66d119f1316ec448bffe5</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:46:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Euro Leder Fashion Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Market Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/euro-leder-fashion-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-market-pressure-3860536</link><description>Euro Leder Fashion Ltd’s stock declined sharply to a new 52-week low of Rs.16.5 on 27 Feb 2026, marking a significant drop amid broader market weakness and sectoral pressures. The stock’s recent performance reflects ongoing challenges within the Gems, Jewellery And Watches industry and highlights persistent concerns over the company’s financial metrics and valuation.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>4e1fb308a8201ff0cb1b1211612d51e0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:46:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AD Manum Finance Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ad-manum-finance-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3860543</link><description>AD Manum Finance Ltd, a Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC), touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.50.05 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trajectory over recent sessions. The stock has now fallen for four consecutive days, registering a cumulative loss of 5.6% during this period, reflecting ongoing pressures within the sector and company-specific performance concerns.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>818839a167646ccb581d43aee6dbc385</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:46:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arex Industries Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.118 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/arex-industries-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs118-amidst-continued-downtrend-3860542</link><description>Shares of Arex Industries Ltd, a player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.118 on 27 Feb 2026, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory. This new low reflects a continuation of the stock’s underperformance relative to its sector and broader market indices over the past year.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>c5ec8e97752544982ba34e650840d254</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:46:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Primo Chemicals Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.18.5</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/primo-chemicals-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs185-3860537</link><description>Primo Chemicals Ltd, a player in the commodity chemicals sector, has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.18.5 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid a broader market downturn and persistent underperformance relative to its peers and benchmarks.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>4e794528e0a505a5a9adcf44cfd9fc02</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:46:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Everest Industries Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.382.4</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/everest-industries-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs3824-3860538</link><description>Everest Industries Ltd has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.382.4 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid ongoing financial pressures and subdued market sentiment. The stock has been on a downward trajectory, reflecting persistent challenges in its performance metrics and valuation concerns.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>a5e75c722e2ee3d8f44c33755ba33efb</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:46:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wim Plast Ltd. Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.372 Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/wim-plast-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs372-amidst-prolonged-downtrend-3860541</link><description>Wim Plast Ltd., a player in the diversified consumer products sector, has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.372, marking a significant downturn in its stock performance. The stock has been on a downward trajectory for eight consecutive trading sessions, culminating in a cumulative loss of 9.16% over this period.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>186dbd48464b2821ccf358fe9186204c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:46:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spectrum Foods Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.12.6 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/spectrum-foods-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs126-amidst-continued-downtrend-3860539</link><description>Spectrum Foods Ltd, a player in the FMCG sector, recorded a fresh 52-week low of Rs.12.6 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid a broader market downturn and persistent underperformance relative to its peers and benchmarks.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>4666dea02e2982baa99bf4a3351e3f35</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:46:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Evexia Lifecare Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/evexia-lifecare-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3860540</link><description>Evexia Lifecare Ltd, a player in the edible oil sector, recorded a fresh 52-week low today, with its share price declining to Rs.1.48. This marks a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory, reflecting persistent pressures on its financial and market performance.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>4c6a4ec4d951117e9a5cf12542f60386</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:46:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:46:31 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>