<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 04:06:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Vishwas Agri Seeds Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vishwas-agri-seeds-ltd-fallingrising-3790786</link><description>On 13-Jan, Vishwas Agri Seeds Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 8.15% to ₹43.80 by 09:15 PM, outperforming its sector and broader market indices despite a challenging longer-term performance backdrop.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>43f3a2252844e3f291d413dd4bc27ee3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 04:06:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vikram Aroma Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vikram-aroma-ltd-fallingrising-3790785</link><description>On 13-Jan, Vikram Aroma Ltd’s stock price fell by 3.15% to close at ₹70.04, reflecting ongoing concerns about the company’s financial health and market performance despite an initially positive start to the trading day.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>696567e45119b6e6198a998238c88289</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 04:06:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-awfis-space-solutions-ltd-fallingrising-3790784</link><description>On 13-Jan, AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, continuing a sustained downward trajectory that has seen the stock underperform both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>289f2dbe6f094dfb6951369ce971cc48</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 04:06:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Italian Edibles Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-italian-edibles-ltd-fallingrising-3790783</link><description>On 13-Jan, Italian Edibles Ltd witnessed a significant drop in its share price, falling by 7.17% to close at ₹27.85. This decline reflects a continuation of the stock's underperformance relative to key benchmarks and technical indicators, signalling persistent challenges for the company’s equity in the current market environment.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>dd0c2ad20d396fcaf0a73f4e25f938b1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 04:06:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Jasch Gauging Technologies Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-jasch-gauging-technologies-ltd-fallingrising-3790782</link><description>On 13-Jan, Jasch Gauging Technologies Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling 4.16% to close at ₹533.10. This drop reflects a continuation of recent negative momentum, with the stock underperforming both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>30b6401501d3444e268154bec59d98a3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 04:06:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Yasons Chemex Care Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-yasons-chemex-care-ltd-fallingrising-3790780</link><description>On 13-Jan, Yasons Chemex Care Ltd witnessed a significant drop in its share price, falling by 11.54% to close at ₹11.50, marking a new 52-week and all-time low of ₹10.55 during the trading session. This decline notably outpaced the broader market, with the Sensex falling only 1.71% over the past week.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>b984f5d97522e687cd7ae0fe0d403edc</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 04:06:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Kalyani Cast-Tech Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-kalyani-cast-tech-ltd-fallingrising-3790781</link><description>On 13-Jan, Kalyani Cast-Tech Ltd witnessed a notable surge in its share price, closing at ₹485.85, up ₹23.5 or 5.08% from the previous close. This rise reflects a combination of strong short-term performance and heightened investor participation, positioning the stock favourably against its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>23ec01d14fca46f1abe409adb0aaab70</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 04:06:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is C P S Shapers Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-c-p-s-shapers-ltd-fallingrising-3790779</link><description>As of 13-Jan, C P S Shapers Ltd’s stock price has experienced a slight decline, reflecting a complex interplay of recent performance trends and investor behaviour that has influenced its market standing.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>8599f67ef4139eddf8a496077e867477</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 04:06:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ameya Precision Engineers Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ameya-precision-engineers-ltd-fallingrising-3790778</link><description>On 13-Jan, Ameya Precision Engineers Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 3.19% to close at ₹94.00. This drop reflects a broader pattern of underperformance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices, compounded by technical indicators signalling bearish momentum.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>6b430ec1c973b9546827cfbd9f6f1c70</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 04:06:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is QMS Medical Allied Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-qms-medical-allied-services-ltd-fallingrising-3790777</link><description>As of 13 Jan, QMS Medical Allied Services Ltd has experienced a decline in its stock price, trading at ₹87.00 with a decrease of 0.57%. This article examines the underlying factors contributing to this downward movement despite some positive fundamentals.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>0d2e4990d7896cee4f9ca152de244846</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 04:06:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Cohance Lifesciences Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-cohance-lifesciences-ltd-fallingrising-3790775</link><description>As of 13-Jan, Cohance Lifesciences Ltd’s stock price has continued its downward trajectory, reflecting a combination of disappointing financial results, poor long-term growth prospects, and market concerns over promoter share pledging.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>73af43f072f03e08495d0b07840fc2e4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 04:06:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Happiest Minds Technologies Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-happiest-minds-technologies-ltd-fallingrising-3790776</link><description>On 13-Jan, Happiest Minds Technologies Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, closing at ₹429.55, down by ₹3.90 or 0.9%. This drop continues a broader downtrend that has seen the stock underperform both its sector and benchmark indices over multiple time frames.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>3890a7bf1728daafed8e7469bce3958d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 04:06:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Pearl Green Clubs and Resorts Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-pearl-green-clubs-and-resorts-ltd-fallingrising-3790774</link><description>On 13-Jan, Pearl Green Clubs and Resorts Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, closing at ₹112.05, down by ₹12.4 or 9.96%. This marks a continuation of a pronounced downward trend that has persisted over recent weeks and months, significantly underperforming the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>23be67252c1b97b3ee6d4e0fa4760d84</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 04:06:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is The Anup Engineering Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-the-anup-engineering-ltd-fallingrising-3790773</link><description>On 13-Jan, The Anup Engineering Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.26% to close at ₹2,072.00. This drop reflects a continuation of a downward trend that has persisted over the past week, driven by valuation pressures and underwhelming recent performance relative to the broader market.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>d771fdf0e573c6971bb5045ac0cf226c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 04:06:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Focus Lighting &amp; Fixtures Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-focus-lighting-fixtures-ltd-fallingrising-3790772</link><description>As of 13-Jan, Focus Lighting &amp; Fixtures Ltd’s stock price has declined to ₹72.60, reflecting ongoing challenges in its financial performance and market sentiment despite some long-term growth indicators.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>37f53dfe39755cc99b85cb78a60e0701</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 04:06:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 04:06:25 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>