<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:02:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Sensex and Nifty Advance as Metal Sector Leads Gains; Jupiter Wagons Tops BSE500</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-advances-055-as-metal-sector-leads-broad-market-rally-3765302</link><description>The Indian equity markets witnessed broad-based gains on 22 December 2025, with the Sensex climbing 468.33 points to trade at 85,397.69, reflecting a 0.55% rise. The Nifty followed suit, supported by strong sectoral performance, particularly in metals, while small caps led the market advance. Jupiter Wagons emerged as the top gainer among BSE500 stocks, underscoring selective buying interest amid positive global cues and steady foreign institutional investor activity.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>6da061236b918be395f9e36dd437691c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eternal Ltd: Nifty 50 Membership and Market Performance Analysis</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eternal-ltd-faces-sell-downgrade-amidst-mixed-market-performance-and-nifty-50-membership-impact-3765301</link><description>Eternal Ltd, a prominent player in the E-Retail and E-Commerce sector, continues to hold its position as a constituent of the Nifty 50 index, underscoring its significance in India’s benchmark equity market. Despite recent market fluctuations and sectoral pressures, the company’s market capitalisation and trading patterns reflect its ongoing relevance to institutional investors and index trackers alike.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>81f6d0890fce74fc2fb47f4b1bb2d49a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Max Healthcare Institute: Navigating Market Dynamics as a Nifty 50 Constituent</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/max-healthcare-institutes-market-performance-and-nifty-50-membership-a-comprehensive-analysis-3765299</link><description>Max Healthcare Institute, a prominent player in the hospital sector and a constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to attract investor attention amid evolving market conditions. Despite recent fluctuations in its share price and performance metrics, the company’s role within the benchmark index underscores its significance in India’s healthcare landscape and the broader equity market.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>a83b976fc1cb0c0f31052ac5790dd954</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SBI Life Insurance Company: Navigating Market Dynamics as a Nifty 50 Constituent</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sbi-life-insurance-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-3765300</link><description>SBI Life Insurance Company continues to hold a significant position within the Nifty 50 index, reflecting its stature in India’s insurance sector. Recent market activity and performance metrics highlight the company’s evolving role amid broader sector trends and benchmark influences.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>ac72647f3dd7d93a454275d911f38292</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maruti Suzuki India: A Key Nifty 50 Constituent Demonstrating Robust Market Presence</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/maruti-suzuki-india-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-shifts-amid-robust-performance-3765298</link><description>Maruti Suzuki India continues to assert its significance within the Nifty 50 index, reflecting a strong market capitalisation and consistent performance across multiple time frames. The company’s standing as a large-cap automobile stock is underscored by its proximity to a 52-week high and its trading levels above key moving averages, signalling sustained investor interest and institutional confidence.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>8df3daa6592719a3e75ed7029b2dbda4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Finance: Nifty 50 Constituent Strengthens Benchmark Role Amid Market Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-finance-sustained-outperformance-reinforces-nifty-50-benchmark-status-3765297</link><description>Bajaj Finance continues to assert its prominence within the Nifty 50 index, reflecting its significant market capitalisation and sectoral influence in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) space. Recent trading patterns and comparative performance metrics underscore its role as a key benchmark constituent amid evolving market conditions.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>5b108355fe1f2f0ffe39fc1b6fdf40bd</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles: Navigating Market Dynamics as a Nifty 50 Constituent</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-motors-passenger-vehicles-navigating-challenges-amidst-nifty-50-membership-3765296</link><description>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles continues to command attention within the Indian equity landscape as a prominent Nifty 50 constituent. Despite recent market headwinds reflected in its year-to-date and one-year returns, the stock’s role within the benchmark index and its valuation metrics offer a nuanced perspective for investors and market watchers alike.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>109e0f028cc7d266929147ef85f4758d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries: Navigating Market Dynamics as a Nifty 50 Constituent</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sun-pharmaceutical-industries-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-mixed-performance-3765295</link><description>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries continues to hold a pivotal position within the Nifty 50 index, reflecting its stature in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector. Recent market movements and institutional holding patterns underscore the stock’s evolving role amid broader benchmark trends and sectoral performance.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>d9436a04f439c6bf9d3b93da95961db8</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JSW Steel: Navigating Market Dynamics as a Key Nifty 50 Constituent</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jsw-steels-nifty-50-membership-reinforces-market-standing-amid-mixed-sector-performance-3765293</link><description>JSW Steel continues to hold a pivotal position within the Nifty 50 index, reflecting its stature in India’s ferrous metals sector. Recent market data highlights the company’s performance relative to benchmarks and sector peers, underscoring its role as a large-cap stock with significant institutional interest and benchmark influence.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>084a739f1657dae012086fce754f384d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra: Navigating Market Dynamics as a Nifty 50 Constituent</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mahindra-mahindras-nifty-50-status-reinforces-market-leadership-amid-mixed-sector-trends-3765292</link><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra continues to hold a pivotal position within the Nifty 50 index, reflecting its stature in the Indian automobile sector. Recent market data reveals nuanced shifts in its performance relative to benchmarks and sector peers, underscoring the importance of its index membership and institutional shareholding patterns in shaping investor sentiment.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>a5eb56409203b5a71fb9ff0c0ce37863</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Larsen &amp; Toubro: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Holding Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/larsen-toubro-strengthens-position-as-key-nifty-50-constituent-amid-robust-performance-3765294</link><description>Larsen &amp; Toubro, a cornerstone of India's construction sector and a prominent Nifty 50 constituent, continues to demonstrate resilience and steady performance amid evolving market conditions. Its role within the benchmark index and shifts in institutional holdings underscore its significance for investors tracking large-cap Indian equities.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>409de724793a3dffdd77ed18e1d120f3</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Finserv: Navigating Market Dynamics as a Key Nifty 50 Constituent</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-finservs-nifty-50-membership-reinforces-market-standing-amid-mixed-performance-3765289</link><description>Bajaj Finserv continues to hold a pivotal position within the Nifty 50 index, reflecting its stature as a leading holding company in India’s financial sector. Recent market activity and performance metrics highlight the stock’s nuanced trajectory amid broader sectoral and benchmark movements.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>a09d5988a82df4db6db748ba700d78fe</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Enterprises: Navigating Market Challenges Amid Nifty 50 Membership</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-enterprises-faces-strong-sell-rating-amid-mixed-market-performance-and-nifty-50-membership-3765288</link><description>Adani Enterprises continues to hold its position as a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, underscoring its significance in India’s diversified sector. Despite recent market headwinds and a complex performance trajectory, the company’s role within the benchmark index remains pivotal for institutional investors and market watchers alike.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>16bc2825e38df0f0607093927528fdc7</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Mahindra's Market Position and Institutional Holding Dynamics Amid Nifty 50 Membership</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tech-mahindras-nifty-50-membership-reinforces-market-standing-amid-mixed-performance-3765290</link><description>Tech Mahindra continues to hold a significant position within the Nifty 50 index, reflecting its stature in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector. Recent market data reveals nuanced shifts in its performance metrics and institutional holdings, underscoring the complexities of maintaining benchmark status in a competitive large-cap environment.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>276c956ea0eb2162b9fbde16880736f9</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Unilever’s Market Position and Institutional Holding Trends Amidst Nifty 50 Benchmark Status</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-unilevers-market-challenges-highlight-nifty-50-membership-significance-3765291</link><description>Hindustan Unilever, a cornerstone of India’s FMCG sector and a prominent Nifty 50 constituent, continues to navigate a challenging market environment as its recent performance metrics reveal a divergence from benchmark indices and sector peers. The company’s standing within the index and shifts in institutional holdings underscore its ongoing significance in India’s equity landscape.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>d5c67bab2f5f5dc2a2f4e9244ca4d4f8</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dr Reddys Laboratories: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amid Sector and Market Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dr-reddys-laboratories-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-mixed-performance-and-institutional-shifts-3765285</link><description>Dr Reddys Laboratories continues to hold its position as a significant constituent of the Nifty 50 index, reflecting its stature within the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector. Despite mixed performance metrics relative to the broader market, the company’s role within the benchmark index and evolving institutional holdings remain key factors influencing investor sentiment and market dynamics.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>fb1f3d60de6a8663bc0f72ee806fe2f3</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Ports &amp; Special Economic Zone: Nifty 50 Constituent Shows Robust Market Presence Amid Sector Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-ports-special-economic-zone-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-3765287</link><description>Adani Ports &amp; Special Economic Zone continues to assert its significance within the Nifty 50 index, reflecting a strong market capitalisation and notable performance metrics that underscore its role in India's transport infrastructure sector. The stock's recent market activity and comparative performance against benchmarks highlight its evolving position amid sectoral and institutional shifts.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>78dd7b0fd95ed288b38e301f01d4a70f</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Grasim Industries: Cement Sector Stalwart Maintains Strong Benchmark Presence Amid Market Fluctuations</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/grasim-industries-strengthens-position-amid-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-shifts-3765286</link><description>Grasim Industries continues to hold a pivotal position within the Nifty 50 index, reflecting its stature as a leading player in the Cement &amp; Cement Products sector. Recent market activity and performance metrics underscore the company’s sustained relevance amid evolving sector dynamics and benchmark movements.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>a488420ce805fca8f59e099b358f8598</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oil &amp; Natural Gas Corporation: Navigating Market Dynamics as a Nifty 50 Constituent</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/oil-natural-gas-corporations-nifty-50-status-highlights-institutional-shifts-and-market-challenges-3765282</link><description>Oil &amp; Natural Gas Corporation (ONGC), a key player in India’s oil sector and a prominent Nifty 50 constituent, continues to attract investor attention amid evolving market conditions. Despite recent fluctuations in its share price and performance metrics, ONGC’s role within the benchmark index and its substantial institutional holdings underscore its significance in the broader equity landscape.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>d4a3f47f890f9afa52c3484bab190733</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kotak Mahindra Bank: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Holding Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kotak-mahindra-bank-strengthens-position-as-nifty-50-constituent-amid-institutional-confidence-3765283</link><description>Kotak Mahindra Bank continues to assert its presence as a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, reflecting its stature within India’s private sector banking landscape. Recent market movements and institutional holding patterns underscore the bank’s evolving role amid broader benchmark trends and sectoral shifts.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>d205795de4b5c593589f93e50ebd34ca</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 04:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>