<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:16:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Shilchar Technologies Ltd Falls 11.60%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Sharp Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shilchar-technologies-ltd-falls-1160-2-key-factors-driving-the-sharp-decline-3789008</link><description>Shilchar Technologies Ltd endured a challenging week, with its share price declining 11.60% from Rs.3,840.30 to Rs.3,395.00, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 2.62% fall over the same period. The stock faced sustained selling pressure amid bearish technical signals and heightened intraday volatility, culminating in a sharp drop on 9 January 2026 that underscored the prevailing negative momentum.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>0457deaf4e3740badc6fa1fc17637865</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:16:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hinduja Global Solutions Ltd Falls 4.66% Amid Intensified Bearish Momentum and 52-Week Low</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hinduja-global-solutions-ltd-falls-466-amid-intensified-bearish-momentum-and-52-week-low-3789007</link><description>Hinduja Global Solutions Ltd (HGS) experienced a challenging week ending 09 January 2026, with its share price declining 4.66% from Rs.453.00 to Rs.431.90. This underperformance was sharper than the Sensex’s 2.62% fall over the same period, reflecting intensified bearish momentum amid technical deterioration and a fresh 52-week low. The stock’s weakness was driven by both company-specific financial pressures and broader sector headwinds, signalling a difficult outlook for investors.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>40b096b10cfed1d0ebf514b6523d6321</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:16:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bosch Ltd Falls 3.74%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bosch-ltd-falls-374-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3789006</link><description>Bosch Ltd’s stock declined by 3.74% over the week ending 9 January 2026, underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62%. The week was marked by a sharp surge in derivatives open interest amid mixed market signals, a shift to a mildly bullish technical momentum, and a notable valuation re-rating to expensive territory. Despite strong historical returns and technical resilience, the stock faced selling pressure in the latter half of the week, reflecting cautious investor sentiment amid broader market weakness.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>491f0393ad6dc6eeb2828ec126a86357</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:16:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tribhovandas Bhimji Zaveri Ltd Gains 0.90%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tribhovandas-bhimji-zaveri-ltd-gains-090-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3789005</link><description>Tribhovandas Bhimji Zaveri Ltd (TBZ) closed the week ending 9 January 2026 with a modest gain of 0.90%, rising from Rs.166.85 to Rs.168.35. This performance notably outpaced the BSE Sensex, which declined 2.62% over the same period, reflecting a mixed but ultimately resilient week for the stock amid volatile market conditions and sector-specific pressures.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>56a960fc16e2e8583f08ca93ba0fb97d</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:16:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Filtron Engineers Ltd Gains 10.37%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/filtron-engineers-ltd-gains-1037-5-key-factors-driving-the-rally-3789004</link><description>Filtron Engineers Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, surging 10.37% from Rs.95.46 to Rs.105.36 between 5 and 9 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 2.62% over the same period. The stock hit consecutive new 52-week and all-time highs each trading day, reflecting sustained momentum amid a cautious broader market environment.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>d4bd0a02c9592481ef1a6f2395ec071d</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:16:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ajanta Pharma Declines 5.75%: Technical Momentum and Market Volatility Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ajanta-pharma-declines-575-technical-momentum-and-market-volatility-shape-the-week-3789003</link><description>Ajanta Pharma Ltd. experienced a challenging week on the bourses, closing at Rs.2,767.65 on 9 Jan 2026, down 5.75% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.2,936.65. This decline notably outpaced the Sensex’s 2.62% fall over the same period, reflecting heightened volatility and mixed technical signals amid evolving market sentiment.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>b868c85d37acb9f9dfe6a32e325b4b87</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:16:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biocon Ltd Falls 3.46%: 2 Key Factors Driving This Week’s Market Moves</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/biocon-ltd-falls-346-2-key-factors-driving-this-weeks-market-moves-3789002</link><description>Biocon Ltd’s shares declined by 3.46% over the week ending 9 January 2026, underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62%. The stock faced mixed technical momentum and a surge in derivatives open interest amid subdued price action, reflecting a complex interplay of cautious investor positioning and sector headwinds.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>94a7e84b13594660e7ad47115e3ece47</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:16:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Murudeshwar Ceramics Declines 4.91%: Downgrade and Valuation Shifts Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/murudeshwar-ceramics-declines-491-downgrade-and-valuation-shifts-shape-the-week-3789001</link><description>Murudeshwar Ceramics Ltd experienced a challenging week on the bourses, with its share price declining 4.91% from Rs.35.42 on 2 January to Rs.33.68 on 9 January 2026. This underperformance contrasted with the broader Sensex, which fell 2.62% over the same period. The week was marked by a significant downgrade to a Strong Sell rating and notable shifts in valuation metrics, reflecting a complex interplay of deteriorating fundamentals and evolving market sentiment.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>de679b4cdce8b836c14a7883ff4bcf88</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:16:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mihika Industries Ltd Drops 10.61%: Key Factors Behind the Steep Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mihika-industries-ltd-drops-1061-key-factors-behind-the-steep-decline-3789000</link><description>Mihika Industries Ltd endured a difficult week ending 9 January 2026, with its share price declining 10.61% from Rs.14.98 to Rs.13.39, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 2.62% fall over the same period. The stock hit both a 52-week and an all-time low on 8 January, reflecting ongoing financial and operational challenges amid volatile market conditions.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>d01dd8776411d62111f22cf2faf2c4f2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:16:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kernex Microsystems Falls 3.38%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kernex-microsystems-falls-338-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3788999</link><description>Kernex Microsystems (India) Ltd experienced a volatile week ending 9 January 2026, closing at Rs.1,204.80, down 3.38% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.1,247.00. Despite this decline, the stock outperformed the Sensex, which fell 2.62% over the same period. The week was marked by a strong initial surge, technical momentum shifts, and mixed signals amid price volatility, reflecting a complex market environment for the mid-cap stock.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>ccce60540c1b16d031fdedc65459d916</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:16:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gujarat State Fertilizers &amp; Chemicals Ltd Declines 3.62%: Technical and Valuation Concerns Weigh</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gujarat-state-fertilizers-chemicals-ltd-declines-362-technical-and-valuation-concerns-weigh-3788998</link><description>Gujarat State Fertilizers &amp; Chemicals Ltd (GSFC) experienced a challenging week ending 9 January 2026, with its share price declining 3.62% to close at ₹177.15, underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The week was marked by a significant downgrade in the company’s mojo rating to Sell, driven by deteriorating technical indicators and a shift in valuation from attractive to fair. Despite some operational strengths, the stock faced sustained bearish momentum amid broader market weakness and sector-specific concerns.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>cf102989b286211f8401c8fec622faf9</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:16:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>EID Parry Falls 6.92%: Technical Weakness and Valuation Concerns Weigh</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eid-parry-falls-692-technical-weakness-and-valuation-concerns-weigh-3788988</link><description>EID Parry (India) Ltd experienced a challenging week on the bourses, with its share price declining by 6.92% from ₹1,009.25 to ₹939.40 between 5 and 9 January 2026. This underperformance was notably sharper than the Sensex’s 2.62% fall over the same period, reflecting a combination of technical momentum deterioration and valuation concerns that weighed on investor sentiment despite the company’s strong underlying fundamentals.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>cdceca318bf78464b4a38d99de6a0f4f</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:16:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Navkar Urbanstructure Ltd Falls 3.95%: 5 Key Factors Behind the Volatile Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/navkar-urbanstructure-ltd-falls-395-5-key-factors-behind-the-volatile-week-3788987</link><description>Navkar Urbanstructure Ltd experienced a volatile week from 5 to 9 January 2026, closing down 3.95% at Rs.1.70 despite early strong gains. The stock initially surged with three consecutive upper circuit hits, outperforming the Sensex which declined 2.62% over the same period. However, heavy selling pressure on the last two trading days triggered lower circuit limits, erasing much of the week's earlier gains and signalling heightened investor caution amid mixed technical and fundamental signals.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b90d3b153d82d0b04cb2e9262fa86224</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:16:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tavernier Resources Ltd Falls 3.52%: 2 Key Events Shaping the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tavernier-resources-ltd-falls-352-2-key-events-shaping-the-week-3788986</link><description>Tavernier Resources Ltd experienced a volatile week ending 09 Jan 2026, with its share price declining by 3.52% from Rs.75.00 to Rs.72.36, slightly outperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The stock’s journey was marked by a new 52-week and all-time high on 07 Jan, followed by a sharp correction amid broader market weakness, reflecting mixed investor sentiment and sector-specific dynamics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e8b5f0d651fa65017c2eb43be6d89725</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:16:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Balaji Amines Ltd Gains 4.67%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/balaji-amines-ltd-gains-467-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3788985</link><description>Balaji Amines Ltd experienced a volatile trading week from 5 to 9 January 2026, closing with a 4.67% gain to Rs.1,163.85, outperforming the Sensex which declined 2.62% over the same period. The stock’s journey was marked by a fresh 52-week low early in the week, followed by a sharp intraday surge amid heavy trading activity, reflecting mixed investor sentiment and significant price swings.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a26fd9454415084974e021542bef7516</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:16:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nestle India Gains 1.51%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Resilience</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nestle-india-gains-151-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-resilience-3788984</link><description>Nestle India Ltd delivered a modest gain of 1.51% over the week ending 9 January 2026, closing at Rs.1,298.95 compared to Rs.1,279.60 the previous Friday. This performance notably outpaced the Sensex, which declined 2.62% during the same period, underscoring the stock’s resilience amid a broadly weak market. The week was marked by multiple new 52-week highs, strong derivatives activity, and sustained technical momentum, reflecting investor confidence despite some profit pressures and mixed market conditions.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6b057c307512b7af318c9611ed292400</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:16:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vaghani Techno-Build Ltd Gains 10.35%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vaghani-techno-build-ltd-gains-1035-5-key-factors-driving-the-rally-3788983</link><description>Vaghani Techno-Build Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, surging 10.35% from Rs.194.75 to Rs.214.90 between 5 and 9 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 2.62% over the same period. The stock consistently hit new 52-week and all-time highs each trading day, reflecting strong investor demand and sustained momentum despite a broadly weak market backdrop.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>50b194d6cc6395f35d293e641b457af1</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:16:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vascon Engineers Declines 2.28%: Technical Weakness and Flat Financials Weigh</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vascon-engineers-declines-228-technical-weakness-and-flat-financials-weigh-3788982</link><description>Vascon Engineers Ltd experienced a challenging week on the BSE, closing at Rs.45.39 on 9 January 2026, down 2.28% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.46.45. This decline slightly outperformed the Sensex’s 2.62% fall over the same period, reflecting a mixed but predominantly bearish sentiment amid deteriorating technical indicators and flat financial results.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ae4e00ff173a635fcfe0b37a03d5dcc2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:16:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MT Educare Ltd Falls 3.41%: 5 Key Events Highlight Persistent Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mt-educare-ltd-falls-341-5-key-events-highlight-persistent-downtrend-3788981</link><description>MT Educare Ltd’s shares declined by 3.41% over the week ending 9 January 2026, closing at Rs.1.70 from Rs.1.76. This underperformance slightly exceeded the broader Sensex’s 2.62% fall, reflecting intensified selling pressure amid deteriorating fundamentals and weak market sentiment. The stock hit multiple all-time lows and lower circuit limits during the week, underscoring persistent bearish momentum and liquidity challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e4ad3e1611baa3892c384f5d5534d487</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:16:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SG Finserve Ltd Falls 0.89%: Mixed Signals Amid Technical Momentum Shift</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sg-finserve-ltd-falls-089-mixed-signals-amid-technical-momentum-shift-3788980</link><description>SG Finserve Ltd experienced a turbulent trading week from 5 to 9 January 2026, closing marginally lower by 0.89% at Rs.411.40, while the Sensex declined more sharply by 2.62%. The stock showed notable intraday strength midweek, surging over 7% on 7 January, before retreating in the final sessions amid mixed technical signals and a recent rating downgrade to Hold by MarketsMOJO.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c61f45d52a168c22d5afc7be4bf01eee</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:16:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:16:30 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>