<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:24:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Has Canara Robeco declared dividend?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/has-canara-robeco-declared-dividend-3762955</link><description>Yes, Canara Robeco has declared a 15% dividend, with an ex-date of December 22, 2025. While specific total return figures for different periods were not provided, the dividend reflects the company's commitment to enhancing shareholder value.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>6fbbb5d998ad5e75f2ea2c3da020d1d1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When is the next results date for Vidya Wires?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-vidya-wires-3762950</link><description>The next results date for Vidya Wires is 22 December 2025.
Time: 38 minutes ago</description><guid>63163d2c0894f4f26465684066673290</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What is the bonus history of A-1?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/what-is-the-bonus-history-of-a-1-3762947</link><description>A-1's recent bonus history includes a 3:1 bonus announced on December 31, 2025, and a 3:20s bonus issued on August 19, 2021, with an ex-date of August 17, 2021.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>48fcf680f3f4c9e8fa7e9ed8b5aa34b2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MAS FINANC SER Joins Market Coverage Backed by Strong Quarterly Financials</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/mojo-premium/mas-financ-ser-joins-mojo-stocks-list-on-strong-quarterly-performance-3762933</link><description>MAS FINANC SER, a small-cap player in the Non-Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has been added to market coverage following a series of robust quarterly financial results. The company’s latest performance metrics highlight significant operational scale and profitability, positioning it as a noteworthy contender within the NBFC space.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>d0fa6ff1142fb749cc56385075310d24</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SG Finserve Joins MomentumNow Stocks Amid Strong Quarterly Financials</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/mojo-premium/sg-finserve-joins-momentumnow-stocks-following-robust-q3-financials-3762931</link><description>SG Finserve, a small-cap Non-Banking Financial Company (NBFC), has been added to the MomentumNow Stocks list as of 18 December 2025, reflecting its notable financial performance in the September 2025 quarter. The company’s recent quarterly results highlight significant growth across key metrics, positioning it as a compelling candidate for investors seeking momentum-driven opportunities in the NBFC sector.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>5e8e9cc8b0fe26ec226fe9f64a29bbe7</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IFCI Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ifci-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-amid-weakening-momentum-3762923</link><description>IFCI Ltd., a key player in the finance sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting potential long-term weakness and a deterioration in price momentum.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>b70398f718b1edaba066c12ed27d3803</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Bijlee Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-bijlee-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3762922</link><description>Bharat Bijlee, a key player in the Other Electrical Equipment sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a potential weakening in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>3a023eaf239020d19088026ca0b23fe5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deepak Builders &amp; Engineers India Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/deepak-builders-engineers-india-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3762920</link><description>Deepak Builders &amp; Engineers India has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting potential long-term weakness in the stock’s price movement amid broader market challenges.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>b72b48c0ed6bf50190720db95a0d3ec0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Premier Energies Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/premier-energies-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3762919</link><description>Premier Energies, a mid-cap player in the Other Electrical Equipment sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>09866352728237e3b6189a3512ee775e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>J.G.Chemicals Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jgchemicals-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3762921</link><description>J.G.Chemicals, a player in the Commodity Chemicals sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>85c66f52348b6e4940df9a6504bddd6e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Veranda Learning Solutions Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/veranda-learning-solutions-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3762918</link><description>Veranda Learning Solutions has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting potential long-term weakness in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>a6b871d5193a313764a2052e84115254</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UTI Asset Management Company Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/uti-asset-management-company-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3762917</link><description>UTI Asset Management Company has recently experienced a significant technical development as its 50-day moving average crossed below the 200-day moving average, a pattern commonly referred to as a Death Cross. This event often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>9ab1e508ec2e880e5c3869c40b8c1a72</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:24:52 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>