<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:54:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>R R Kabel Ltd is Rated Buy by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/r-r-kabel-ltd-is-rated-buy-by-marketsmojo-3834759</link><description>R R Kabel Ltd is rated Buy by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 31 January 2026. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 12 February 2026, providing investors with the latest comprehensive analysis.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>d6c7748ff4ab6e49a5b127c4b5888913</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Grauer &amp; Weil (India) Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/grauer-weil-india-ltd-is-rated-sell-3834757</link><description>Grauer &amp; Weil (India) Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 07 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 12 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>76f09d97f94105336a9455596ea1dc07</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PTC Industries Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ptc-industries-ltd-is-rated-sell-3834749</link><description>PTC Industries Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 05 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 12 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>dca51dc14ce2a96f758859a94be5ee82</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ashirwad Capital Ltd is Rated Sell by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ashirwad-capital-ltd-is-rated-sell-by-marketsmojo-3834756</link><description>Ashirwad Capital Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 13 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 12 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>d8c1de92f2a9c738d659ac0ff7593554</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sustainable Energy Infra Trust is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sustainable-energy-infra-trust-is-rated-strong-sell-3834753</link><description>Sustainable Energy Infra Trust is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 01 February 2026. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 12 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date analysis.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>2b61ba218eb874301734977f436e277e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indus Infra Trust is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/indus-infra-trust-is-rated-strong-sell-3834754</link><description>Indus Infra Trust is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 09 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 12 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date perspective on its performance and outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>1a23b17b9cfbb83919711ba29afbd468</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Akums Drugs &amp; Pharmaceuticals Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/akums-drugs-pharmaceuticals-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3834752</link><description>Akums Drugs &amp; Pharmaceuticals Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 17 Nov 2025, reflecting a shift from the previous 'Sell' grade. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here represent the stock's current position as of 12 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>c5fae9310d6795ee61d044e97e536827</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Timex Group India Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/timex-group-india-ltd-is-rated-hold-3834750</link><description>Timex Group India Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 03 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 12 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>d128d694307d8f53914e1cf8ddf19c41</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Newgen Software Technologies Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/newgen-software-technologies-ltd-is-rated-sell-3834743</link><description>Newgen Software Technologies Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 05 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 12 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date perspective on the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>70a3976ab099f1b5e1c26c18ee21e1ad</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanathan Textiles Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sanathan-textiles-ltd-is-rated-sell-3834744</link><description>Sanathan Textiles Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 11 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 12 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the stock’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>1debbd5e525d305ed9e175878a2abad5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahamaya Steel Industries Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/mahamaya-steel-industries-ltd-is-rated-sell-3834739</link><description>Mahamaya Steel Industries Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 20 January 2026. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 12 February 2026, providing investors with the latest comprehensive analysis.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>c5cce6f39d5359e8ee417bb78dfa7e1b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jeena Sikho Lifecare Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/jeena-sikho-lifecare-ltd-is-rated-hold-3834740</link><description>Jeena Sikho Lifecare Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 09 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed below reflect the stock's current position as of 12 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>9a8f4d7ee3f4729a5a2d7d5cf8d92d4c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rallis India Ltd is Rated Sell by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/rallis-india-ltd-is-rated-sell-by-marketsmojo-3834733</link><description>Rallis India Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 15 Oct 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 12 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>cf5a2b4a1d1716f85dcd716295b7202f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Parag Milk Foods Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/parag-milk-foods-ltd-is-rated-sell-3834734</link><description>Parag Milk Foods Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 05 Feb 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 12 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>7d054563c5c2643462c123835655005e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ASK Automotive Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ask-automotive-ltd-is-rated-sell-3834735</link><description>ASK Automotive Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 19 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 12 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market standing.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>cdfd301650c02e91c2240f30d154928b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mastek Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/mastek-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3834730</link><description>Mastek Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 19 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 12 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>68228c5b6a8ce00e78d3da33ff84384a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Monarch Networth Capital Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/monarch-networth-capital-ltd-is-rated-sell-3834731</link><description>Monarch Networth Capital Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 22 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 12 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>d6c7b06d9d886ccc76cc5646b29fa2b5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Va Tech Wabag Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/va-tech-wabag-ltd-is-rated-sell-3834729</link><description>Va Tech Wabag Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 03 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 12 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market standing.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>925a5f97ec3bf6381d17e05957b88d8a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Saregama India Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/saregama-india-ltd-is-rated-sell-3834728</link><description>Saregama India Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 01 August 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock's current position as of 12 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market performance.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>1723c33a3b26e23a40e546b50cb4a481</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NDR INVIT Trust is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ndr-invit-trust-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3834724</link><description>NDR INVIT Trust is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 10 February 2026. While the rating change occurred on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 12 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date perspective on its performance and outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>c273339559609b3a76057a51bda6e0f0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:54:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>