<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:55:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Fortis Healthcare Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/fortis-healthcare-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3832918</link><description>Fortis Healthcare Ltd has witnessed a notable 17.7% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite the stock’s recent underperformance relative to its sector, the sustained increase in open interest alongside rising volumes suggests evolving directional bets that merit close attention from market participants.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>ef631d5da6d12c1ea48d6d5715aa9d8a</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>L&amp;T Finance Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lt-finance-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-price-action-3832917</link><description>L&amp;T Finance Ltd (LTF), a prominent player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has witnessed a notable 10.66% surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this, the stock has underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting a complex interplay of market sentiment and technical factors.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>3ee80fc2402d0101767e2a4da1c55145</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jubilant Foodworks Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jubilant-foodworks-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3832916</link><description>Jubilant Foodworks Ltd (JUBLFOOD) has witnessed a significant 32.14% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite the stock opening with a 2.8% gain, it underperformed its sector and reversed gains after two consecutive days of upward momentum, reflecting a complex interplay of bullish and bearish sentiments among traders.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>5070e68bee6894f996789b7af1768891</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Torrent Power Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/torrent-power-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3832915</link><description>Torrent Power Ltd. has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, with a 25.08% increase to 24,630 contracts from the previous 19,692. This sharp rise, coupled with elevated volumes and shifting price dynamics, suggests evolving market positioning and potential directional bets among traders, despite the stock’s underperformance relative to its sector and broader indices.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>b36dca8632ed5724493750f22637195f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kaynes Technology India Ltd Sees Surge in Call Option Activity Amid Bullish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kaynes-technology-india-ltd-sees-surge-in-call-option-activity-amid-bullish-momentum-3832914</link><description>Kaynes Technology India Ltd has emerged as the most active stock in call options trading, reflecting heightened bullish sentiment among investors. With a significant volume of contracts traded at the 4,200 strike price expiring on 24 February 2026, the stock’s recent price performance and option market dynamics suggest a growing optimism despite a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>9a5e51bc090fe8d9bc84ef037776385f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec 2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3832903</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has unfolded with a nuanced picture across market capitalisations, sectors and individual companies. With 2,234 stocks having declared results, the proportion of positive outcomes has edged higher to 47.0%, signalling a modest improvement in corporate profitability compared to recent quarters. However, the divergence between large, mid and small caps remains pronounced, reflecting varied sectoral dynamics and company-specific factors.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>867dbff7c4575c68febfb7c169f8e1e9</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kavveri Defence &amp; Wireless Technologies Ltd Hits Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kavveri-defence-wireless-technologies-ltd-hits-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-momentum-3832910</link><description>Kavveri Defence &amp; Wireless Technologies Ltd surged to its upper circuit limit on 11 Feb 2026, registering a maximum daily gain of 9.99% to close at ₹83.24. The stock demonstrated robust buying interest, outpacing its sector and broader market indices, while triggering a regulatory freeze due to unfilled demand and heightened investor participation.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>e241c3d30dbb548930f501964aa08f1f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Persistent Systems Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/persistent-systems-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-price-action-3832911</link><description>Persistent Systems Ltd (PERSISTENT), a mid-cap player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has witnessed a notable 13.03% increase in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s recent underperformance. This surge in OI, coupled with declining price momentum and volume patterns, suggests evolving market positioning and potential directional bets among traders.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>60d40abc2e4a0bab1930174ab83fd03d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NACL Industries Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nacl-industries-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-robust-buying-pressure-3832912</link><description>NACL Industries Ltd, a key player in the Pesticides &amp; Agrochemicals sector, surged to hit its upper circuit price limit on 11 Feb 2026, propelled by robust buying interest and a significant intraday gain. The stock closed at ₹152.22, marking a 4.99% increase, outperforming its sector and broader market indices amid heightened investor participation and unfilled demand.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>26de2953b954586e284f186096c54e3a</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kaynes Technology India Ltd Sees Robust Trading Activity Amid Mixed Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kaynes-technology-india-ltd-sees-robust-trading-activity-amid-mixed-technical-signals-3832913</link><description>Kaynes Technology India Ltd (KAYNES), a mid-cap player in the industrial manufacturing sector, emerged as one of the highest value traded stocks on 11 Feb 2026, registering a significant intraday price surge and strong volume turnover. Despite a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade to Sell, the stock has demonstrated notable resilience with a four-day consecutive gain, outperforming its sector and broader market indices.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>6c594b252d55f6b4483bcbb81d2d6a59</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vivimed Labs Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vivimed-labs-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3832909</link><description>Vivimed Labs Ltd witnessed a sharp decline on 11 Feb 2026, hitting its lower circuit limit as intense selling pressure gripped the stock. The share price fell by 4.9% to close at ₹6.80, just 1.18% above its 52-week low, signalling heightened investor anxiety and a deteriorating market sentiment towards the micro-cap pharmaceutical player.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>84d92bd32b5bc173163f7d5a4c0ed6dc</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Small-Cap Segment Surges 2.5% Amid Mixed Breadth and Sectoral Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/small-cap-segment-surges-25-amid-mixed-breadth-and-sectoral-shifts-3832906</link><description>The BSE Smallcap index has demonstrated notable resilience in recent trading sessions, advancing 2.52% on the day and posting a 1.95% gain over the past five days. Despite this upward momentum, the segment’s breadth remains subdued, reflecting a complex market environment where a handful of stocks have driven gains amid broader weakness.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>0d24dca73d4fc21975262552c63460e7</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Large-Cap Segment Edges Higher Amid Mixed Stock Movements and Upcoming Earnings</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/large-cap-segment-edges-higher-amid-mixed-stock-movements-and-upcoming-earnings-3832905</link><description>The large-cap segment, represented by the BSE 100 index, has exhibited modest gains in recent sessions, reflecting a cautious but steady investor sentiment. While the index rose by 0.15% on the day and has advanced 1.25% over the past five trading days, the underlying stock movements reveal a nuanced picture of sectoral rotations and divergent performances among heavyweight constituents.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>190dca285110348f9df3d1ae3578ff5d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mid-Cap Segment Surges 1.64% as Sectoral Breadth Remains Mixed</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/mid-cap-segment-surges-164-as-sectoral-breadth-remains-mixed-3832904</link><description>The BSE Midcap index advanced by 1.64% on 11 Feb 2026, continuing its strong momentum with a 1.79% gain over the past five trading sessions. Despite a broader market environment marked by mixed sectoral performances, the mid-cap segment emerged as a relative outperformer, buoyed by technical upgrades and selective stock rallies.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>78c325647860c10dae7d15d3d689975c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rolex Rings Ltd Hits Intraday High with 8.22% Surge on 11 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rolex-rings-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-822-surge-on-11-feb-2026-3832897</link><description>Rolex Rings Ltd demonstrated robust intraday momentum on 11 Feb 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 142.95, marking an 8.79% increase from its previous close. This strong performance outpaced the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector by 7.77%, underscoring notable buying interest and positive trading dynamics throughout the session.
Time: 37 minutes ago</description><guid>4c1f0da4fb1846eb368fb2773e419786</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gala Global Products Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gala-global-products-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amid-prolonged-downtrend-3832895</link><description>Gala Global Products Ltd has reached an all-time low in its stock price, reflecting a sustained period of decline and underperformance relative to market benchmarks. The stock closed just 4.38% above its 52-week low of ₹1.53, marking a significant milestone in its downward trajectory within the miscellaneous sector.
Time: 44 minutes ago</description><guid>652cc15757fff2aef38675a3523ef3e2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>APL Apollo Tubes Ltd Hits All-Time High, Marking a Milestone in Market Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/apl-apollo-tubes-ltd-hits-all-time-high-marking-a-milestone-in-market-performance-3832894</link><description>APL Apollo Tubes Ltd, a prominent player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, has reached a significant milestone by hitting its all-time high stock price, reflecting sustained robust performance and market confidence. This achievement underscores the company’s strong fundamentals and consistent growth trajectory over recent years.
Time: 44 minutes ago</description><guid>25093540cf685b25ad3d1d7c50163419</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blue Star Ltd. Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/blue-star-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3832891</link><description>Blue Star Ltd., a prominent player in the Electronics &amp; Appliances sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross—a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-DMA. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout, suggesting a shift in long-term momentum and a possible trend reversal for the stock.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>e7d6c597b05f2c13a5c37d8f2ae9c5d6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arihant Foundations &amp; Housing Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/arihant-foundations-housing-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3832886</link><description>Arihant Foundations &amp; Housing Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum and raising concerns about sustained weakness in the Realty sector micro-cap.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>c63e4109eb16b0531c4589b0cc2b7597</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>B2B Software Technologies Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/b2b-software-technologies-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3832889</link><description>B2B Software Technologies Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a long-term momentum shift for the micro-cap software products company, which has demonstrated strong relative performance against the broader market over multiple time frames.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>567becd69b87ea68913d12722bbe8550</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:55:42 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>