<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 03:52:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Indegene’s Market Assessment Reflects Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/indegene-downgraded-to-sell-by-marketsmojo-amid-technical-and-financial-concerns-3760875</link><description>Indegene, a key player in the healthcare services sector, has recently experienced a shift in market evaluation driven by a combination of financial performance, valuation metrics, and technical indicators. This article analyses the factors influencing the current market perspective on Indegene, highlighting the interplay between its operational results, stock price movements, and broader market trends.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>a975831f4c7447c56151b36117a0dcf8</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 03:52:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manoj Vaibhav Gems N Jewellers: Analytical Review Highlights Key Market and Financial Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/manoj-vaibhav-gems-n-jewellers-downgraded-to-sell-amid-technical-weakness-and-long-term-growth-concerns-3760874</link><description>Manoj Vaibhav Gems N Jewellers has recently undergone a revision in its market assessment, reflecting shifts across multiple evaluation parameters including quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. This article explores the underlying data and market context shaping the current perspective on this player in the Gems, Jewellery and Watches sector.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>601a96234a65aae54896de8bcd8b801c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 03:52:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NIIT Learning Systems: Analytical Perspective Shifts Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/niit-learning-systems-downgraded-to-sell-amid-technical-and-financial-concerns-3760873</link><description>NIIT Learning Systems has experienced a revision in its market assessment following a detailed analysis of its quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. The company’s recent performance data and market behaviour have prompted a nuanced re-evaluation of its investment profile within the Other Consumer Services sector.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>a19c5510c7f4447cbf64d68f009d96ee</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 03:52:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Senco Gold's Market Assessment Reflects Mixed Signals Amid Sector Challenges</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/senco-gold-upgraded-to-hold-by-marketsmojo-amid-mixed-financial-and-technical-signals-3760871</link><description>Senco Gold's recent market evaluation reveals a nuanced picture shaped by shifts in technical indicators, valuation metrics, financial trends, and quality parameters. Despite a challenging year marked by significant stock price declines, the company’s underlying fundamentals and sector context offer a complex backdrop for investors analysing its prospects within the gems and jewellery industry.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>5c1af6525a8d1d40851710f908158dd6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 03:52:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anand Rathi Wealth Sees Shift in Market Assessment Amid Technical and Financial Developments</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/anand-rathi-wealth-upgraded-to-buy-by-marketsmojo-on-strong-technical-and-financial-performance-3760872</link><description>Anand Rathi Wealth has experienced a notable revision in its market evaluation, reflecting changes across technical indicators, financial trends, valuation metrics, and overall quality parameters. This shift highlights evolving investor perspectives and the company’s recent performance within the capital markets sector.
Time: 58 minutes ago</description><guid>77e0c6cc24a96bf86a4ae4296e398a45</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 03:52:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jeena Sikho Lifecare Sees Shift in Market Assessment Amid Technical and Financial Developments</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/jeena-sikho-lifecare-upgraded-to-hold-by-marketsmojo-amid-improving-technicals-and-solid-financials-3760870</link><description>Jeena Sikho Lifecare, a key player in the hospital sector, has experienced a notable revision in its market evaluation, reflecting changes across technical indicators, financial trends, valuation metrics, and overall quality parameters. This article analyses the factors influencing the recent shift in the company’s assessment and what it means for investors navigating the healthcare services industry.
Time: 58 minutes ago</description><guid>55ebe070722389d2fed6ce6484e5c619</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 03:52:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Electronics Mart India Faces Challenging Market Conditions Amidst Revised Evaluation Metrics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/electronics-mart-india-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-weak-financials-and-bearish-technicals-3760867</link><description>Electronics Mart India, a key player in the diversified retail sector, is currently navigating a complex market environment as recent assessment changes reflect shifts across quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. The company’s stock performance and financial results reveal a cautious outlook amid ongoing headwinds in the consumer durables segment.
Time: 58 minutes ago</description><guid>7292286dea16103b2fb7ab63ad63df9d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 03:52:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tips Films Evaluation Sees Shift Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/tips-films-stock-upgraded-to-sell-amid-mixed-technicals-and-weak-financials-3760869</link><description>Tips Films, a key player in the Media &amp; Entertainment sector, has experienced a revision in its market assessment driven by a combination of technical indicators and financial performance metrics. While the company’s stock price has shown some short-term resilience, underlying financial trends and valuation considerations continue to present challenges for investors.
Time: 58 minutes ago</description><guid>a9af1b262d561a90b411d983f080299a</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 03:52:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uniparts India: Analytical Revision Reflects Mixed Signals Across Quality, Valuation, Financial Trend and Technicals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/uniparts-india-downgraded-to-hold-amid-mixed-financial-and-technical-signals-3760868</link><description>Uniparts India, a key player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has undergone a revision in its market assessment reflecting nuanced shifts across multiple evaluation parameters. The recent analytical perspective highlights a blend of positive financial results, valuation considerations, and technical indicators that collectively influence the stock’s current standing.
Time: 58 minutes ago</description><guid>77687d661b3b71640a6b1cb551f29532</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 03:52:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Medplus Health Services: Analytical Perspective Shifts Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/medplus-health-services-downgraded-to-sell-amid-mixed-fundamentals-and-technicals-3760866</link><description>Medplus Health Services has experienced a revision in its market assessment following a detailed evaluation of its quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. This reassessment reflects a nuanced view of the company’s current position within the retailing sector, highlighting both strengths and vulnerabilities amid fluctuating market conditions.
Time: 59 minutes ago</description><guid>b6b6cc026edf4da922cfe9fec0071ecc</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 03:52:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ellenbarrie Industrial Gases Sees Shift in Market Assessment Amid Mixed Technical and Financial Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ellenbarrie-industrial-gases-upgraded-to-hold-on-technical-and-financial-improvements-3760865</link><description>Ellenbarrie Industrial Gases, a key player in the Other Chemical products sector, has experienced a notable revision in its market evaluation following recent developments across technical indicators, financial trends, valuation metrics, and quality parameters. This shift reflects a nuanced picture of the company’s current standing and prospects within the industrial gases industry.
Time: 59 minutes ago</description><guid>cb8d1a65cda0108214db9273f606b108</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 03:52:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gland Pharma's Market Assessment Reflects Mixed Signals Amidst Flat Financials</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/gland-pharma-upgraded-to-hold-as-technicals-improve-amid-mixed-financials-3760864</link><description>Gland Pharma's recent market evaluation reveals a nuanced picture shaped by a combination of technical indicators, valuation metrics, financial trends, and quality parameters. Despite flat quarterly financial performance and subdued long-term growth, shifts in technical trends and institutional confidence have influenced the current market assessment of this pharmaceutical and biotechnology company.
Time: 59 minutes ago</description><guid>a21cc7c83fbb944e52dbe770defdbf8c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 03:52:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Craftsman Automation Sees Shift in Market Assessment Amid Strong Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/craftsman-automation-upgraded-to-strong-buy-on-robust-financials-and-bullish-technicals-3760862</link><description>Craftsman Automation, a key player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has experienced a notable revision in its market evaluation, reflecting a combination of robust financial results and evolving technical indicators. This shift highlights the company's sustained growth trajectory and its positioning relative to industry peers and broader market benchmarks.
Time: 59 minutes ago</description><guid>6c0bed03b5eb12492bae208ed562daa0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 03:52:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mangalam Global Enterprise: Analytical Perspective Shift Reflects Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/mangalam-global-enterprise-upgraded-to-hold-on-technical-and-valuation-improvements-3760863</link><description>Mangalam Global Enterprise has experienced a revision in its market assessment, reflecting nuanced changes across quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. This shift highlights a complex interplay of factors influencing the stock’s outlook within the Other Agricultural Products sector.
Time: 59 minutes ago</description><guid>1cd23007e1ae94b3db574975d4a9e457</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 03:52:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kapil Cotex Faces Challenging Market Conditions Amidst Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/kapil-cotex-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-weak-fundamentals-and-bearish-technicals-3760861</link><description>Kapil Cotex, a player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, is currently navigating a complex market environment marked by subdued financial performance and shifting technical indicators. Recent assessment changes reflect a cautious market stance as the company’s stock price trends lower amid broader sector challenges and internal operational factors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9d940896f0127ad970e216b706762df6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 03:52:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries: Analytical Perspective Shift Amid Mixed Technical and Financial Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sun-pharmaceutical-industries-downgraded-to-buy-by-marketsmojo-amid-mixed-technical-signals-3760860</link><description>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries has experienced a revision in its market assessment, reflecting nuanced changes across technical indicators, valuation metrics, financial trends, and overall quality parameters. This article examines the factors influencing the recent analytical perspective shift, providing investors with a comprehensive understanding of the company’s current standing within the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>948517c0c8c5dfed3ad54f700e685d15</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 03:52:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apex Frozen Foods Sees Shift in Market Assessment Amid Strong Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/apex-frozen-foods-upgraded-to-buy-on-strong-financial-and-technical-performance-3760859</link><description>Apex Frozen Foods has experienced a notable revision in its market evaluation, driven by a combination of robust financial results, evolving technical indicators, and valuation metrics that suggest a more favourable outlook. This article analyses the key factors influencing the recent shift in the company's assessment across quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical parameters.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5ead3d2bf4e76f5111957504e70d43e5</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 03:52:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KPIT Technologies Faces Mixed Signals Amidst Market Underperformance and Technical Challenges</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/kpit-technologies-downgraded-to-sell-amid-technical-weakness-and-flat-financials-3760858</link><description>KPIT Technologies, a key player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, is currently navigating a complex market environment marked by subdued financial results, technical indicators signalling caution, and valuation metrics that suggest a nuanced investment landscape. Recent shifts in analytical perspectives reflect a reassessment of the company’s standing amid broader market trends and sector dynamics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>112c3380dfcd5855a59e4132dae57840</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 03:52:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cochin Shipyard Faces Challenging Market Conditions Amid Revised Evaluation Metrics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/cochin-shipyard-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-weak-financials-and-bearish-technicals-3760857</link><description>Cochin Shipyard, a key player in the Aerospace &amp; Defense sector, has experienced a shift in market assessment following recent financial disclosures and technical indicators. The company’s performance across quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical parameters has prompted a revision in its evaluation, reflecting the complex environment it currently navigates.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f4c89ba8c5f238e9b7d87cb31b11ec05</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 03:52:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gulf Oil Lubricants India Sees Shift in Market Assessment Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/gulf-oil-lubricants-india-upgraded-to-hold-on-technical-and-valuation-improvements-3760856</link><description>Gulf Oil Lubricants India has experienced a revision in its market assessment, reflecting nuanced changes across quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. The stock’s recent performance and underlying fundamentals present a complex picture for investors navigating the oil sector landscape.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ef0aed520b79cfdf60427efd87cf51b8</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 03:52:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 03:52:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>