<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:15:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Integrity Infrabuild Developers Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-integrity-infrabuild-developers-ltd-fallingrising-3774044</link><description>On 29 Dec, Integrity Infrabuild Developers Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, closing at ₹130.10, down by ₹2.00 or 1.51%. This movement reflects a combination of short-term market dynamics and investor behaviour, despite the stock’s relatively strong position against longer-term moving averages.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>8815966b65fb5f5f537af2f2c1bfe0e6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:15:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Rapid Fleet Management Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-rapid-fleet-management-services-ltd-fallingrising-3774043</link><description>On 29-Dec, Rapid Fleet Management Services Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 4.69% to close at ₹183.00. This drop reflects a broader underperformance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices, signalling investor caution and a challenging trading environment for the stock.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>c09dde72e483633eaca20fb922bf97c6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:15:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Solarium Green Energy Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-solarium-green-energy-ltd-fallingrising-3774042</link><description>On 29-Dec, Solarium Green Energy Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 6.86% to close at ₹235.00. This drop comes amid heightened volatility and subdued investor engagement, marking a continuation of recent downward momentum.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>ea1e4c936525723dcc9478d42381d441</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:15:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Royal Arc Electrodes Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-royal-arc-electrodes-ltd-fallingrising-3774041</link><description>On 29-Dec, Royal Arc Electrodes Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, closing at ₹142.00, down ₹8.00 or 5.33% from the previous session. This drop reflects a broader pattern of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and technical indicators.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>d787278caf9e2313337732d256b3e9a9</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:15:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sanathan Textiles Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sanathan-textiles-ltd-fallingrising-3774040</link><description>As of 29-Dec, Sanathan Textiles Ltd’s stock price has fallen sharply, reflecting mounting concerns over its long-term fundamentals, rising debt levels, and recent underperformance relative to benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>6888e49736743dcbf0654df345327c06</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:15:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is EMA Partners India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ema-partners-india-ltd-fallingrising-3774039</link><description>On 29-Dec, EMA Partners India Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, closing at ₹96.50 with a gain of ₹5.50, representing a 6.04% increase. This upward movement reflects a strong short-term performance that significantly outpaces the broader market benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>334e0fcfdd3ba94b2512c93dfe99a955</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:15:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Transrail Lighting Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-transrail-lighting-ltd-fallingrising-3774038</link><description>On 29-Dec, Transrail Lighting Ltd experienced a significant decline in its share price, falling by 5.71% to close at ₹563.55. This drop comes amid heightened volatility and underperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market indices.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>7dfe9974204e384a81e93a0201f83c1f</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:15:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Happy Forgings Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-happy-forgings-ltd-fallingrising-3774037</link><description>On 29-Dec, Happy Forgings Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 2.54% to ₹1,114.00, reflecting a positive market response driven by robust quarterly results and sustained outperformance against benchmarks.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>6c8cc98b957cbb4d2878460f7f3cd8ea</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:15:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is R R Kabel Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-r-r-kabel-ltd-fallingrising-3774036</link><description>As of 29-Dec, R R Kabel Ltd’s stock price has declined by 1.75% to ₹1,448, reflecting a short-term correction despite the company’s robust financial performance and healthy growth indicators.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>8f1b9b77a0d39be0a5e9392ce80f7178</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:15:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Retina Paints Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-retina-paints-ltd-fallingrising-3774035</link><description>On 29-Dec, Retina Paints Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, falling by 0.86% to close at ₹69.40. This movement reflects a continuation of recent downward pressure despite the stock’s positive performance over the past month.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>0e0897ca9d17372e6fca6c1a04cab627</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:15:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Dharni Capital Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-dharni-capital-services-ltd-fallingrising-3774034</link><description>As of 29-Dec, Dharni Capital Services Ltd has recorded a slight increase in its share price, continuing a robust upward trajectory that has significantly outpaced the broader market indices over the past year.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>23937bf6913179bcceac7f26d9fd7afb</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:15:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Annapurna Swadisht Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-annapurna-swadisht-ltd-fallingrising-3774033</link><description>On 29-Dec, Annapurna Swadisht Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, closing at ₹190.00, down ₹16.95 or 8.19% from the previous session. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s underperformance relative to broader market benchmarks and sector peers, driven by a combination of technical weakness and subdued investor participation.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>15948528b21ce3d38882abf4f7386afc</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:15:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Anand Rathi Wealth Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-anand-rathi-wealth-ltd-fallingrising-3774032</link><description>As of 29-Dec, Anand Rathi Wealth Ltd's stock price has surged by 1.82% to ₹3,087.40, reflecting a sustained upward trajectory driven by impressive financial performance and growing institutional participation.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>b8a2fd9eba871a9c76ef8c99fad00604</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:15:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Gateway Distriparks Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gateway-distriparks-ltd-fallingrising-3774031</link><description>As of 29-Dec, Gateway Distriparks Ltd’s stock price has fallen by 2.01% to ₹59.84, continuing a downward trend that has seen the share lose over 6% in the past three days. Despite some positive operational metrics, the stock’s performance remains under pressure due to long-term growth concerns and sustained underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>9c2750a3dcb3b77a88cdc2a430eb4c7f</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:15:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ameya Precision Engineers Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ameya-precision-engineers-ltd-fallingrising-3774030</link><description>On 29-Dec, Ameya Precision Engineers Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.51% to close at ₹99.00. This drop reflects a broader trend of underperformance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices, compounded by weakening investor participation and technical indicators signalling bearish momentum.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>afd58d5dff73d8b78e3f626228471c45</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:15:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Pearl Green Clubs and Resorts Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-pearl-green-clubs-and-resorts-ltd-fallingrising-3774029</link><description>On 29-Dec, Pearl Green Clubs and Resorts Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, falling by 10.0% to close at ₹121.50. This significant drop reflects a continuation of the stock's underperformance relative to broader market indices and sector peers.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>df73db3a66319e1cf5fb9b202d2989f6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:15:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Nazara Technologies Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-nazara-technologies-ltd-fallingrising-3774028</link><description>On 29 Dec, Nazara Technologies Ltd witnessed a significant price increase of 6.68%, closing at ₹253.05, driven by robust quarterly performance and a notable rebound after two days of decline.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>87e3a77a31839ee5092223fb82b786f3</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:15:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Seacoast Ship. falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-seacoast-ship-fallingrising-3774027</link><description>On 29-Dec, Seacoast Shipping Services Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, falling 20.69% to hit a new 52-week and all-time low of ₹0.92. This steep drop reflects ongoing concerns about the company’s fundamentals and market performance despite some recent positive earnings data.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>ac8cf224df60e82f92feb2393c4ca88d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:15:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Happiest Minds Technologies Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-happiest-minds-technologies-ltd-fallingrising-3774026</link><description>On 29-Dec, Happiest Minds Technologies Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, closing at ₹475.00, down by ₹2.7 or 0.57%. This movement continues a recent pattern of weakness, reflecting broader challenges despite some underlying strengths in the company’s fundamentals.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>fadc407f1c7ee2b55130df147d0c0ff9</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:15:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Mercury EV-Tech Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-mercury-ev-tech-ltd-fallingrising-3774025</link><description>On 29-Dec, Mercury EV-Tech Ltd’s stock price fell sharply to ₹37.00, marking a 4.42% decline as the share hit a fresh 52-week low of ₹36 during intraday trading. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s recent downward trajectory, significantly underperforming both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>14197ea4b245ba3af49fcc892e75e8eb</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:15:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:15:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>