<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:53:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>TGV Sraac Ltd is Rated Sell by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/tgv-sraac-ltd-is-rated-sell-by-marketsmojo-3816078</link><description>TGV Sraac Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 20 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 02 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trend, and technical outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>61e693e2495fd430bae6ea70997a3fa6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:53:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Automobile Corporation Of Goa Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/automobile-corporation-of-goa-ltd-is-rated-sell-3816076</link><description>Automobile Corporation Of Goa Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 21 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 02 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trend, and technical outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>a0a7a9e6e00c10999b301e3c00dc936a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:53:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SPML Infra Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/spml-infra-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3816069</link><description>SPML Infra Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 21 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 02 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>7ece71423a37d21fc1cf2f73ff7f0ae6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:53:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indo Amines Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/indo-amines-ltd-is-rated-sell-3816074</link><description>Indo Amines Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 19 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 02 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date view of the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>8e74a1acb4dfc698ef0d1bca3cd18e42</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:53:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Modi Naturals Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/modi-naturals-ltd-is-rated-sell-3816065</link><description>Modi Naturals Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 21 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 02 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>d88f3f1762ca8810eea12091cb0e424c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:53:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nahar Spinning Mills Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/nahar-spinning-mills-ltd-is-rated-sell-3816070</link><description>Nahar Spinning Mills Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 30 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 02 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>81aa9fb90817dc3185436ce9fd65e900</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:53:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cords Cable Industries Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/cords-cable-industries-ltd-is-rated-sell-3816063</link><description>Cords Cable Industries Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 19 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 02 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trend, and technical outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>c3589f14b46e95df3bc8518a671d68d1</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:53:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Electrosteel Castings Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/electrosteel-castings-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3816066</link><description>Electrosteel Castings Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 21 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 02 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market performance.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>f6155f61f427989e4451a6865d1104be</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:53:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Loyal Equipments Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/loyal-equipments-ltd-is-rated-sell-3816062</link><description>Loyal Equipments Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 27 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 02 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>d21539994915a2916977d78991043222</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:53:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Veritas (India) Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/veritas-india-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3816061</link><description>Veritas (India) Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 19 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock’s current position as of 02 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>736a185944a8b7a984a0f6fadca4f0f9</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:53:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kuantum Papers Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/kuantum-papers-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3816060</link><description>Kuantum Papers Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 19 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 02 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>21f0ce938036f0af2f3c7f5764a5b94d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:53:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deepak Builders &amp; Engineers India Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/deepak-builders-engineers-india-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3816059</link><description>Deepak Builders &amp; Engineers India Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 18 December 2025, reflecting a change from the previous 'Sell' grade. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed below represent the stock’s current position as of 02 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>7e690b74d5740cef76d2df2dccabeeed</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:53:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mercantile Ventures Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/mercantile-ventures-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3816054</link><description>Mercantile Ventures Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 08 January 2026, reflecting a shift from the previous 'Sell' grade. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed below represent the stock's current position as of 02 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>39171d24dee45f77bfebb8d4be7e46a8</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:53:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gillanders Arbuthnot &amp; Company Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/gillanders-arbuthnot-company-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3816048</link><description>Gillanders Arbuthnot &amp; Company Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 19 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock's current position as of 02 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>0e633e97a53eb484daad095815737e53</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:53:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indag Rubber Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/indag-rubber-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3816049</link><description>Indag Rubber Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 08 January 2026, reflecting a shift from the previous 'Sell' grade. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed below represent the stock's current position as of 02 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>a19f396044149d5141da1b8fa296f1cc</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:53:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Delton Cables Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/delton-cables-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3816046</link><description>Delton Cables Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 01 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 02 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date insight into the stock’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>3fe059f658a158fb9816157df38b1ffd</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:53:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hazoor Multi Projects Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/hazoor-multi-projects-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3816043</link><description>Hazoor Multi Projects Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 21 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock's current position as of 02 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>5a892fdd6e7a843570160f334e974462</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:53:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>V-Mart Retail Ltd. is Rated Sell by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/v-mart-retail-ltd-is-rated-sell-by-marketsmojo-3816045</link><description>V-Mart Retail Ltd. is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 27 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 02 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>e918806a84580050f20ee75e04d256eb</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:53:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anuh Pharma Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/anuh-pharma-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3816042</link><description>Anuh Pharma Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 08 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 02 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>939268d69d361cbe0975e63047033530</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:53:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Venkys (India) Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/venkys-india-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3816047</link><description>Venkys (India) Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 10 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 02 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>e61801e64bf951add7303576d577f9a0</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:53:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:53:55 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>