<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:43:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Anzen India Energy Yield Plus Trust Hits All-Time High on 4 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/anzen-india-energy-yield-plus-trust-hits-all-time-high-on-4-feb-2026-3820665</link><description>Anzen India Energy Yield Plus Trust has reached an all-time high, underscoring a notable achievement in its market journey. This milestone reflects the company’s sustained performance over recent years, highlighted by a robust one-year return that outpaces the broader Sensex index.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>d5107f379475e0a5ee835c0a481f21e7</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gillanders Arbuthnot &amp; Company Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Weak Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gillanders-arbuthnot-company-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-weak-performance-3820667</link><description>Gillanders Arbuthnot &amp; Company Ltd has touched a fresh 52-week low, closing just 1.14% above its lowest price of Rs 87, marking a significant downturn in the stock’s performance amid broader market fluctuations and company-specific factors.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>60eb7ad2c42d415a9ee4f631e657dcdd</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zodiac Ventures Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/zodiac-ventures-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3820668</link><description>Zodiac Ventures Ltd, a player in the Commercial Services &amp; Supplies sector, has recently touched a 52-week low, marking a significant decline in its stock price to ₹1.74. This new low reflects ongoing challenges faced by the company, as it continues to underperform relative to its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>4c1e3574c7976723e6c59bf470480111</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sandesh Ltd. Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.973.5 Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sandesh-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs9735-amidst-continued-underperformance-3820666</link><description>Sandesh Ltd., a key player in the Media &amp; Entertainment sector, recorded a fresh 52-week low of Rs.973.5 today, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing price decline. Despite a modest rebound over the past three days, the stock remains under pressure, reflecting persistent challenges in its financial performance and market positioning.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>58df60417fcb1a9fc5db3ce5fd729ff9</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>APL Apollo Tubes Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.2177</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/apl-apollo-tubes-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs2177-3820669</link><description>APL Apollo Tubes Ltd, a prominent player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, reached a fresh 52-week high of Rs.2177 today, marking a significant milestone in its market performance. This achievement underscores the stock’s robust momentum amid a mixed broader market environment.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>0cbe2b1b144704afe90f5eadbb00ec04</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Power Ltd Hits Intraday High with Strong 3.45% Surge on 4 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-power-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-strong-345-surge-on-4-feb-2026-3820661</link><description>Adani Power Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 4 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 148.4, marking a 3.31% increase. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, continuing its upward momentum with a third consecutive day of gains.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>624ea63f042143c9b5cd4ab6f19c70cb</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IDBI Bank Ltd. Hits Intraday High with 8.46% Surge on 4 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/idbi-bank-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-846-surge-on-4-feb-2026-3820663</link><description>IDBI Bank Ltd. demonstrated robust intraday performance on 4 Feb 2026, surging 8.46% to touch a day’s high of Rs 108.15, significantly outperforming its sector and broader market indices amid mixed market conditions.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>8e2b46cd07190d2b36ce557a77310412</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd Hits Intraday High with 3.0% Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/power-grid-corporation-of-india-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-30-surge-3820662</link><description>Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd demonstrated robust intraday strength on 4 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 291.1, marking a 2.77% increase and outperforming its sector and the broader market amid mixed market conditions.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>094cb98d84697391a333233a0812de62</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trent Ltd. Hits Intraday High with 3.11% Surge on 4 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/trent-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-311-surge-on-4-feb-2026-3820659</link><description>Trent Ltd. demonstrated robust intraday performance on 4 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 3,945.35, marking a 3.21% increase. This advance outpaced the broader Sensex, which traded lower by 0.13%, underscoring Trent’s relative strength in a subdued market environment.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>cba5864ed816410fa934a1996919c407</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mankind Pharma Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mankind-pharma-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-market-signals-3820654</link><description>Mankind Pharma Ltd has witnessed a significant 26.8% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this spike, the stock underperformed its sector and broader indices, trading near its 52-week low and reflecting bearish sentiment among traders.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>25ab2ad114a7c38de6d19060c8cef581</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Varun Beverages Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/varun-beverages-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-price-action-3820657</link><description>Varun Beverages Ltd (VBL) has witnessed a notable 10.24% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s recent underperformance. This surge in open interest, coupled with rising volumes and a persistent downtrend, suggests evolving market positioning and potential directional bets among traders.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>b8445e38f3e53e609271346e3e68f1de</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>LTI Mindtree Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Market Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lti-mindtree-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-market-weakness-3820658</link><description>LTI Mindtree Ltd (LTIM), a prominent player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment on 4 Feb 2026, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning amid a challenging market backdrop. The stock underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting a complex interplay of bearish sentiment and speculative bets.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>56e456338d2147729fb277e23b7e2219</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Info Edge (India) Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/info-edge-india-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-price-action-3820656</link><description>Info Edge (India) Ltd, a prominent player in the E-Retail and E-Commerce sector, witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment on 4 February 2026, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this, the stock underperformed sharply, closing near its 52-week low, reflecting a complex interplay of bearish sentiment and speculative bets in the derivatives market.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>bc5be2449967f5b6290a36b1f3fe6498</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Mahindra Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Market Downturn</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tech-mahindra-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-market-downturn-3820655</link><description>Tech Mahindra Ltd. (TECHM), a prominent player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has witnessed a notable 10.5% surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s recent underperformance. This development comes amid a broader sectoral decline and increased investor participation, raising questions about evolving market positioning and potential directional bets.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>0addfaf0582de9cadada7d8adad66120</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Solar Industries India Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/solar-industries-india-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3820660</link><description>Solar Industries India Ltd (SOLARINDS), a key player in the Other Chemical products sector, has witnessed a notable surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and evolving investor positioning. Despite a recent dip in share price, the stock’s derivatives market reveals intriguing directional bets that merit close attention from investors and analysts alike.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>a7b21279f38c71f4e0dc0b0c7e6b0330</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oracle Financial Services Software Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/oracle-financial-services-software-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-price-action-3820652</link><description>Oracle Financial Services Software Ltd (OFSS) witnessed a notable 12.7% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment on 4 Feb 2026, signalling heightened market activity and shifting positioning despite the stock’s bearish price movement. This surge in open interest, coupled with volume patterns and technical indicators, offers critical insights into investor sentiment and potential directional bets in the mid-cap software products stock.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>30523916c09074f5e9ba5e4f7fba2286</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mphasis Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mphasis-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-market-momentum-3820650</link><description>Mphasis Ltd., a mid-cap player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, witnessed a notable 12.8% surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment on 4 Feb 2026, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s underperformance and sector-wide weakness. This sudden spike in OI, coupled with increased volume and a sharp price decline, suggests a significant shift in market positioning and potential directional bets among traders.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>2ecdd7fe226e256eb33fca40eb8cc9b1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wipro Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/wipro-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-market-volatility-3820653</link><description>Wipro Ltd. has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite the stock hitting a fresh 52-week low, the increase in open interest by over 18% alongside rising volumes suggests a complex interplay of directional bets and hedging strategies amid a broader sector downturn.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>a37a1c36d5797fc188936313f27bf7ed</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kotyark Industries Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit on Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kotyark-industries-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-on-robust-buying-pressure-3820649</link><description>Kotyark Industries Ltd, a micro-cap player in the power sector, surged to hit its upper circuit limit on 4 February 2026, registering a maximum daily gain of 9.99% to close at ₹211.95. This sharp rally was driven by strong buying interest and a significant rise in investor participation, signalling renewed market confidence despite the company’s recent downgrade to a Sell rating by MarketsMOJO.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>b77ec865d6a952cf924c6505f4469e16</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Synoptics Technologies Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/synoptics-technologies-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3820651</link><description>Synoptics Technologies Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, surged to hit its upper circuit price limit on 4 Feb 2026, registering a maximum daily gain of 4.98%. This sharp rally was driven by robust buying interest despite subdued trading volumes, signalling a significant unfilled demand and a regulatory freeze on further price movement.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>3ab94eb5af3d0f5d0cdb4c174ef0c771</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:43:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>