<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:15:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>eClerx Services Ltd Gains 0.97%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eclerx-services-ltd-gains-097-4-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3780301</link><description>eClerx Services Ltd closed the week ending 2 January 2026 with a modest gain of 0.97%, rising from Rs.4,679.80 to Rs.4,725.00. This performance, while positive, lagged behind the Sensex’s 1.35% advance over the same period. The week was marked by a series of technical momentum shifts, a significant upgrade to a Strong Buy rating, and evolving valuation metrics that together shaped investor sentiment and price action.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>87de835cc35044ddda0411d6534cbf45</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:15:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mangalore Refinery &amp; Petrochemicals Ltd. Gains 4.45%: Mixed Technical Signals Shape Weekly Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mangalore-refinery-petrochemicals-ltd-gains-445-mixed-technical-signals-shape-weekly-momentum-3780300</link><description>Mangalore Refinery &amp; Petrochemicals Ltd. (MRPL) closed the week ending 2 January 2026 with a 4.45% gain, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.35% rise over the same period. The stock exhibited notable volatility, including a sharp rebound on 31 December 2025, driven by heavy trading volumes and institutional interest, despite a recent downgrade to a Sell rating by MarketsMOJO. Mixed technical signals and sectoral headwinds characterised the week’s price action, reflecting a complex market environment for MRPL.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>b45a37b739b4a7b764e8782f967f25c6</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:15:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pankaj Polymers Gains 27.46%: 8 Key Factors Driving the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pankaj-polymers-gains-2746-8-key-factors-driving-the-rally-3780299</link><description>Pankaj Polymers Ltd delivered a remarkable weekly performance, surging 27.46% from Rs.35.10 on 29 December 2025 to Rs.44.74 on 2 January 2026. This rally vastly outpaced the Sensex’s modest 1.35% gain over the same period, underscoring the stock’s strong momentum and resilience amid a mixed market backdrop. The week was marked by a series of new 52-week and all-time highs, sustained buying interest, and consistent outperformance relative to both the packaging sector and broader market indices.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>f73982dacfb8d715b3abbd228ce0d672</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:15:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maithan Alloys Gains 2.55%: Valuation Shift and Mixed Technical Signals Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/maithan-alloys-gains-255-valuation-shift-and-mixed-technical-signals-shape-the-week-3780296</link><description>Maithan Alloys Ltd delivered a modest weekly gain of 2.55%, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.35% rise over the same period. The stock showed resilience amid mixed technical signals and a notable valuation upgrade, closing the week at Rs.1,016.30 from Rs.991.00. Despite some intraday volatility and a brief dip on 1 January, the overall trend reflected cautious optimism supported by improving fundamentals and attractive price multiples.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>aa9a3a261fd71f8e9173bc050c0c01b7</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:15:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Filatex Fashions Ltd Falls 8.57%: 5 Key Factors Behind the Volatile Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/filatex-fashions-ltd-falls-857-5-key-factors-behind-the-volatile-week-3780298</link><description>Filatex Fashions Ltd’s stock endured a turbulent week from 29 December 2025 to 2 January 2026, closing down 8.57% at Rs.0.32 despite a strong Sensex rally of 1.35%. The stock hit multiple 52-week and all-time lows early in the week before staging a sharp rebound on 1 January, surging 14.81% to hit its upper circuit. However, the overall weekly performance reflects ongoing financial challenges and bearish momentum amid volatile trading.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>ff7d4c818ef860608d5485bc418eb6c0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:15:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GHV Infra Projects Ltd Falls 3.44%: Technical Weakness and Valuation Concerns Weigh</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ghv-infra-projects-ltd-falls-344-technical-weakness-and-valuation-concerns-weigh-3780297</link><description>GHV Infra Projects Ltd closed the week down 3.44% at Rs.287.90, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.35% over the same period. The stock faced a mildly bearish technical shift amid mixed momentum signals and a downgrade to a Sell rating by MarketsMOJO, reflecting concerns over valuation and long-term growth despite recent positive quarterly financials.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>0676692e2b880e49f79c7a64088045ac</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:15:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>City Union Bank Ltd: 1.05% Weekly Decline Amidst Valuation Shift and Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/city-union-bank-ltd-105-weekly-decline-amidst-valuation-shift-and-market-volatility-3780293</link><description>City Union Bank Ltd experienced a mixed week ending 2 Jan 2026, with its stock price declining by 1.05% from Rs.291.85 to Rs.288.80, underperforming the Sensex which rose 1.35% over the same period. The week was marked by new 52-week and all-time highs on 29 and 30 Dec 2025, followed by a gradual pullback amid valuation reassessments and subdued market conditions. Despite the weekly decline, the bank’s strong fundamentals and institutional backing remain key pillars supporting its market position.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>c49a8215c809589dceed38569ccc350e</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:15:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Panama Petrochem Ltd Gains 7.59%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/panama-petrochem-ltd-gains-759-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3780295</link><description>Panama Petrochem Ltd closed the week with a notable 7.59% gain, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.35% rise from 29 December 2025 to 2 January 2026. The stock experienced a volatile week marked by a bearish technical shift early on, mixed momentum signals midweek, and a sharp surge on the first trading day of 2026. Despite the positive weekly return, the stock’s technical indicators and volume patterns suggest cautious optimism amid ongoing sector challenges.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>9537bf78c4872f0b6953d7d85a1e2213</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:15:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Graphite India Ltd Gains 13.17%: 4 Key Drivers Behind the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/graphite-india-ltd-gains-1317-4-key-drivers-behind-the-rally-3780292</link><description>Graphite India Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, gaining 13.17% from Rs.583.10 to Rs.659.90 between 29 December 2025 and 2 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.35% rise over the same period. The stock’s rally was marked by multiple new 52-week highs, heavy institutional interest, and robust technical momentum, underscoring sustained investor confidence as it closed the week near its peak levels.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>c64a5696218fbd545e128e33ad2fa5e1</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:15:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Garware Hi Tech Films Ltd Gains 0.89%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/garware-hi-tech-films-ltd-gains-089-3-key-factors-driving-the-week-3780294</link><description>Garware Hi Tech Films Ltd recorded a modest weekly gain of 0.89%, closing at Rs.3,166.00 on 2 January 2026, despite underperforming the Sensex which rose 1.35% over the same period. The week was marked by a downgrade to a Sell rating amid valuation and technical concerns, a notable shift in technical momentum from mildly bullish to bearish, and mixed price movements reflecting investor caution in a challenging market environment.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>d4df1c932bfe975815a95efe9a6623b3</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:15:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indraprastha Medical Corporation’s 1.07% Weekly Decline: Mixed Technical Signals and Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indraprastha-medical-corporations-107-weekly-decline-mixed-technical-signals-and-valuation-concerns-3780291</link><description>Indraprastha Medical Corporation Ltd experienced a modest decline of 1.07% over the week ending 2 January 2026, closing at ₹453.30 from ₹458.20 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s 1.35% gain during the same period, reflecting mixed technical signals and valuation concerns that tempered investor enthusiasm despite the company’s strong long-term fundamentals.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>30896d4aa00908e22c96da4dbbc17a4c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:15:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:15:06 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>