<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:18:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Seacoast Shipping Services Opens with Sharp Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/seacoast-shipping-services-opens-with-sharp-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3773774</link><description>Seacoast Shipping Services witnessed a significant gap down at market open today, plunging 20.69% to hit a new 52-week and all-time low of ₹0.92. This sharp decline reflects heightened market concerns following overnight developments, with the stock underperforming its sector and broader benchmarks amid persistent bearish technical signals.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>2fcb78e1e980546700c01407739b27a2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kartik Investments Trust Opens with Strong Gap Up, Reflecting Positive Market Sentiment</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kartik-investments-trust-opens-with-strong-gap-up-reflecting-positive-market-sentiment-3773776</link><description>Kartik Investments Trust Ltd witnessed a robust start to trading on 29 Dec 2025, opening with a significant gap up of 15.47%, reaching a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs.1196.25. This sharp rise outpaced the broader market and sector performance, signalling strong overnight catalysts and sustained momentum at the market open.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>2c711e2ca6df9d68c9bc6b87a4f5ef92</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>United Textiles Opens with Strong Gap Up Reflecting Positive Market Sentiment</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/united-textiles-opens-with-strong-gap-up-reflecting-positive-market-sentiment-3773775</link><description>United Textiles Ltd witnessed a significant gap up at the opening bell today, surging by 21.61% to open at Rs 17.95. This robust start outpaced the broader Sensex, which declined by 0.41%, signalling a distinct positive sentiment towards the garment and apparel sector stock.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>55ec04b53242b086ca96fdb23dba0a2a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vijay Textiles Opens with Sharp Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vijay-textiles-opens-with-sharp-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3773772</link><description>Vijay Textiles commenced trading today with a significant gap down, opening at a price 24.57% lower than its previous close, reflecting heightened market apprehension following overnight developments. The stock’s sharp decline has triggered notable volatility and underperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>93655cb222e666e0e0221bcb1a510010</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gopal Snacks Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gopal-snacks-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3773773</link><description>Gopal Snacks Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action amid challenging market conditions.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>3184c374a1c54aa12ec1113a62578189</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stove Kraft Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/stove-kraft-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3773767</link><description>Stove Kraft Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>d5755d1f41ba11c2d29e950770f4b1c6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mipco Seamless Rings (Gujarat) Ltd Opens with Strong Gap Up, Reflecting Positive Market Sentiment</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mipco-seamless-rings-gujarat-ltd-opens-with-strong-gap-up-reflecting-positive-market-sentiment-3773768</link><description>Mipco Seamless Rings (Gujarat) Ltd witnessed a robust start to the trading session on 29 Dec 2025, opening with a significant gap up of 9.0%, signalling positive market sentiment despite its overall cautious technical outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b369285d809928c790cd724b099fe436</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Clenon Enterprises Ltd Opens Strong with 10.25% Gap Up on 29 Dec 2025</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/clenon-enterprises-ltd-opens-strong-with-1025-gap-up-on-29-dec-2025-3773769</link><description>Clenon Enterprises Ltd, a player in the Telecom - Equipment &amp; Accessories sector, opened the trading session on 29 Dec 2025 with a significant gap up, surging 10.25% to hit a new 52-week and all-time high of ₹57.12. This robust start outpaced the broader market and sector indices, signalling strong overnight momentum and positive sentiment among market participants.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>33f2013a0d4d67e761f01e60bd0a83cc</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Aeronautics Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-aeronautics-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3773771</link><description>Hindustan Aeronautics Ltd (HAL) has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's near- to medium-term outlook amid broader market pressures.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>367172e5047fbd36b3bab026e0780807</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hiliks Technologies Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hiliks-technologies-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3773770</link><description>Hiliks Technologies Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about its long-term prospects amid already challenging fundamentals.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>34332511b00166ae6177cf86aabd839a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Capfin India Ltd Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/capfin-india-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3773766</link><description>Capfin India Ltd experienced a significant gap down at market open today, reflecting heightened market concerns and a weak start for the non-banking financial company (NBFC). The stock opened 5.5% lower, hitting a new 52-week low of Rs.149.7, underperforming its sector and broader indices amid bearish technical signals and volatile trading patterns.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>c2f41d20faba56071ae388ad3efcb233</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hawkins Cookers Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hawkins-cookers-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3773765</link><description>Hawkins Cookers Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum. Investors should carefully analyse this event in the context of Hawkins Cookers’ recent performance and broader market conditions.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>a07b8565b861516e007d521f646e9282</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Control Print Ltd. Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/control-print-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3773762</link><description>Control Print Ltd., a micro-cap player in the IT - Hardware sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s near to medium-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b49fe777c47f4f3f4c50a238ad61ee7a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sunrakshakk Industries India Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sunrakshakk-industries-india-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3773764</link><description>Sunrakshakk Industries India Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential shift towards a bearish trend, raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term momentum and investor sentiment.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>c41a823518ac92594fa75ab669aea277</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baron Infotech Opens with Strong Gap Up, Reflecting Positive Market Sentiment</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/baron-infotech-opens-with-strong-gap-up-reflecting-positive-market-sentiment-3773761</link><description>Baron Infotech Ltd witnessed a significant gap up at the opening bell on 29 Dec 2025, surging by 19.84% to hit a new 52-week high of ₹1.51. This sharp rise outpaced the broader market and sector indices, signalling robust overnight developments and sustained bullish momentum in the software products sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>6d3281b150a6957584f4de46e8ff097e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BEML Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/beml-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3773763</link><description>BEML Ltd, a key player in the Indian automobile sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s near- to medium-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>f4cbb479a2c993633a5fc38e92dfd0c8</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Union Quality Plastics Ltd Opens with Strong Gap Up, Reflecting Positive Market Sentiment</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/union-quality-plastics-ltd-opens-with-strong-gap-up-reflecting-positive-market-sentiment-3773757</link><description>Union Quality Plastics Ltd witnessed a significant gap up at market open on 29 Dec 2025, surging by 40.79% from its previous close. The stock’s robust start was accompanied by an intraday high of Rs. 17.41, marking a new 52-week peak and signalling strong positive momentum in the packaging sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>64a96c5be941772f85f70d4730a4c3db</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GHCL Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ghcl-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3773759</link><description>GHCL Ltd, a key player in the Commodity Chemicals sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s near- to medium-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ef37b590d149ada9f4f9642a4a616803</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sika Interplant Systems Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sika-interplant-systems-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3773756</link><description>Sika Interplant Systems Ltd, a small-cap player in the Aerospace &amp; Defense sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term momentum despite its impressive historical returns.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>0efb73c9dbed917c953cf638a20ceac3</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shri Niwas Leasing &amp; Finance Ltd Opens with Sharp Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shri-niwas-leasing-finance-ltd-opens-with-sharp-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3773760</link><description>Shri Niwas Leasing &amp; Finance Ltd commenced trading today with a significant gap down, opening at Rs 9.90, marking an 18.59% decline from its previous close. This sharp drop reflects heightened market concerns following overnight developments, with the stock underperforming its sector and broader indices amid subdued trading activity.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>8344371ff70ae31cae0b65df20edefd3</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:18:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>