<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:15:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Standard Glass Lining Technology Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-standard-glass-lining-technology-ltd-fallingrising-3795072</link><description>On 19-Jan, Standard Glass Lining Technology Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹134.30, down ₹2.80 or 2.04% from the previous close. This movement reflects a continuation of the stock’s underperformance relative to broader market benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>97fd8945f455539d9549e3ec003c76f0</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Suraksha Diagnostic Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-suraksha-diagnostic-ltd-fallingrising-3795071</link><description>As of 19-Jan, Suraksha Diagnostic Ltd’s stock price has been under pressure, declining by 1.17% to ₹261.55, continuing a downward trend that has persisted over the past week and year. This article analyses the factors behind the stock’s recent fall, contrasting its performance with broader market benchmarks and examining key financial indicators.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0050192a5e6f54d4532e872c20f9be6d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Gajanand International Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gajanand-international-ltd-fallingrising-3795070</link><description>On 19-Jan, Gajanand International Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 10.62% to close at ₹10.10. This sharp drop reflects a broader pattern of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and sector peers, compounded by weak investor participation and technical indicators signalling bearish momentum.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d333956692c18751db546b0693b9d6e4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Arkade Developers Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-arkade-developers-ltd-fallingrising-3795069</link><description>On 19-Jan, Arkade Developers Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, closing at ₹120.80, down ₹4.25 or 3.4% during the trading session. This drop marks a fresh 52-week and all-time low for the stock, reflecting ongoing challenges despite some positive operational metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c6517d5256310238698ff9f90bc3e698</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Bajaj Housing Finance Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-bajaj-housing-finance-ltd-fallingrising-3795068</link><description>On 19-Jan, Bajaj Housing Finance Ltd's stock price fell to a new 52-week and all-time low of ₹91.37, reflecting ongoing challenges despite the company’s strong fundamental growth and recent positive quarterly results.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8d4ea09110c6fa7817748ac90149ba59</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Quest Laboratories Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-quest-laboratories-ltd-fallingrising-3795067</link><description>As of 19-Jan, Quest Laboratories Ltd’s stock price has fallen to ₹99.00, down by 2.08% on the day, reflecting a broader trend of underperformance against market benchmarks despite strong underlying profitability metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6621d631d772b41154dd47f5ccb1a944</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Gopal Snacks Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gopal-snacks-ltd-fallingrising-3795065</link><description>As of 19-Jan, Gopal Snacks Ltd’s stock price has fallen sharply, reflecting a combination of disappointing financial performance, underwhelming growth prospects, and waning institutional interest.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>40b6f536173fd746fe4f1b0e50f0e934</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Enser Communications Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-enser-communications-ltd-fallingrising-3795066</link><description>On 19-Jan, Enser Communications Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling 9.06% to ₹14.55 by 09:16 PM. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s underwhelming performance relative to broader market benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>76ea59f9ed7983f906b1ecf8e9b9b33f</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Epack Durable Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-epack-durable-ltd-fallingrising-3795064</link><description>As of 19-Jan, Epack Durable Ltd’s stock price has fallen to ₹262.75, down 1.96% on the day, continuing a downward trend driven by disappointing financial results and sustained underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1ef292b968ee04816bcfebecfb7095ad</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Medi Assist Healthcare Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-medi-assist-healthcare-services-ltd-fallingrising-3795063</link><description>On 19-Jan, Medi Assist Healthcare Services Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling 3.0% to close at ₹423.00. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s downward trajectory amid concerns over profitability metrics and valuation pressures, despite the company’s strong long-term fundamentals.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>147a6637d9a2c134d653ad272225107b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Yatra Online Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-yatra-online-ltd-fallingrising-3795062</link><description>On 19-Jan, Yatra Online Ltd’s stock price fell sharply by 4.82% to close at ₹153.10, continuing a recent downward trend amid broader sector weakness and short-term technical pressures despite the company’s strong long-term fundamentals.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8dd1875dc19bf447f12f0fbcca38aff0</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Jio Financial Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-jio-financial-services-ltd-fallingrising-3795061</link><description>As of 19-Jan, Jio Financial Services Ltd’s stock price has experienced a notable decline, falling 1.22% to ₹275.50 by 09:14 PM. This downward movement reflects a combination of disappointing quarterly results, valuation pressures, and underperformance relative to market benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>391a884a40e6620ec158f3fcf423ed41</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Mankind Pharma Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-mankind-pharma-ltd-fallingrising-3795060</link><description>As of 19-Jan, Mankind Pharma Ltd’s stock price has fallen sharply, reflecting a combination of disappointing profit growth, valuation pressures, and underperformance relative to key benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>25463b3ca8a774a450d4bef551750659</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vedant Fashions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vedant-fashions-ltd-fallingrising-3795059</link><description>On 19-Jan, Vedant Fashions Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹512.40, down ₹16.3 or 3.08% from the previous session. This drop marks a continuation of a downward trend that has seen the stock hit a new 52-week and all-time low of ₹510.3 during intraday trading, reflecting mounting investor concerns over the company’s recent performance and valuation metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>906b0a49434421d6bc038a4eae5f881c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is HP Adhesives Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-hp-adhesives-ltd-fallingrising-3795058</link><description>On 19-Jan, HP Adhesives Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, closing at ₹38.24, down ₹1.69 or 4.23% for the day. This drop reflects ongoing challenges faced by the company, including poor recent financial results and sustained underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a97f5c34e2bb0b75251e1083981109aa</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is EKI Energy Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-eki-energy-services-ltd-fallingrising-3795057</link><description>As of 19-Jan, EKI Energy Services Ltd’s stock price has fallen to ₹95.01, down 2.56% on the day, continuing a downward trend driven by persistent weak financial results and deteriorating investor confidence.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9acddaf26542c2fb8f87274c237289cc</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Cohance Lifesciences Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-cohance-lifesciences-ltd-fallingrising-3795056</link><description>On 19-Jan, Cohance Lifesciences Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹415.75, down ₹9.90 or 2.33%. This drop reflects a continuation of a downward trend driven by disappointing financial results, weak investor participation, and valuation concerns, compounded by broader market underperformance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>34375ca5933322ae7f2d7bca57594c90</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Nila Spaces Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-nila-spaces-ltd-fallingrising-3795055</link><description>On 19-Jan, Nila Spaces Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.62% to close at ₹13.75. This drop reflects a continuation of recent downward trends, with the stock underperforming both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4fab111026af9b7afe2eb53352f830a5</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Solara Active Pharma Sciences Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-solara-active-pharma-sciences-ltd-fallingrising-3795054</link><description>On 19-Jan, Solara Active Pharma Sciences Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling 2.32% to close at ₹532.70. This drop reflects a continuation of recent underperformance driven by weak financial metrics, subdued investor participation, and broader market pressures.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c331db1b542d70230e8d6a9ea79d7d64</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Affordable Robotic &amp; Automation Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-affordable-robotic-automation-ltd-fallingrising-3795053</link><description>On 19-Jan, Affordable Robotic &amp; Automation Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹180.80, down ₹5.20 or 2.8%. This drop reflects a continuation of a prolonged downward trend driven by weak financial performance, deteriorating investor sentiment, and diminishing promoter confidence.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>05857080aed5059a4f682b945874b58c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>