<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 18:45:40 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>When is the next results date for Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-sanofi-consumer-healthcare-india-ltd-3846119</link><description>The next results date for Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd is 25 February 2026.
Time: Feb 18 2026 11:15 PM IST</description><guid>268aa92e3ed4053417a0051469f692b4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 18:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When is the next results date for DIC India Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-dic-india-ltd-3846118</link><description>The next results date for DIC India Ltd is 24 February 2026.
Time: Feb 18 2026 11:15 PM IST</description><guid>b7d38a7423fdf02e9e4b6725946c8d76</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 18:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When is the next results date for AJC Jewel Manufacturers Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-ajc-jewel-manufacturers-ltd-3846117</link><description>The next results date for AJC Jewel Manufacturers Ltd is 25 February 2026.
Time: Feb 18 2026 11:15 PM IST</description><guid>76a51b1478df303df6ccc4b68f459b7e</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 18:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When is the next results date for Sattva Sukun Lifecare Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-sattva-sukun-lifecare-ltd-3846116</link><description>The next results date for Sattva Sukun Lifecare Ltd is 19 February 2026.
Time: Feb 18 2026 11:15 PM IST</description><guid>e026f297fdbc59612dd795a089934d99</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 18:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When is the next results date for Remedium Lifecare Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-remedium-lifecare-ltd-3846115</link><description>The next results date for Remedium Lifecare Ltd is 25 February 2026.
Time: Feb 18 2026 11:15 PM IST</description><guid>8e370969b604c03d112719cb0a60574c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 18:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Creative Eye Ltd Q3 FY26: Mounting Losses Signal Deepening Operational Crisis</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/creative-eye-ltd-q3-fy26-mounting-losses-signal-deepening-operational-crisis-3846113</link><description>Creative Eye Ltd., the Mumbai-based television content producer, reported a staggering quarterly loss of ₹3.68 crores in Q3 FY26, marking a dramatic deterioration from the ₹0.65 crore loss recorded in Q2 FY26. The company, with a diminished market capitalisation of just ₹15.00 crores, continues to struggle with zero revenue generation for the third consecutive quarter, raising serious questions about its operational viability. Shares plummeted 6.42% to ₹7.00 following the results, reflecting investor alarm over the accelerating cash burn and absence of any meaningful business activity.
Time: Feb 18 2026 09:16 PM IST</description><guid>0269f0b2d20bf84e538b19946a73c174</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 18:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3846101</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has revealed a nuanced picture across Indian equities, with 4,080 companies reporting results. While the overall proportion of positive earnings has inched up to 46.0%, the data highlights divergent trends across market capitalisation segments and sectors, underscoring the varied pace of recovery and growth in the economy.
Time: Feb 18 2026 09:00 PM IST</description><guid>a85fc27ae7ffb0d60a2a117a463039b8</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 18:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Evexia Lifecare Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-evexia-lifecare-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3846089</link><description>Evexia Lifecare Ltd's latest results show revenue growth of 16.31% year-on-year to ₹25.24 crores, but profitability remains a concern with a net profit of only ₹0.29 crores and declining margins, indicating significant operational challenges and high leverage risks.
Time: Feb 18 2026 07:11 PM IST</description><guid>3c357b4ef35d25281d6fab144b09f678</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 18:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Impex Ferro Tech Q3 FY26: Operations Remain Suspended as Losses Mount</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/impex-ferro-tech-q3-fy26-operations-remain-suspended-as-losses-mount-3846092</link><description>Impex Ferro Tech Ltd., a Kolkata-based manufacturer of manganese-based ferrous alloys, reported continued operational suspension in Q3 FY26, with quarterly losses persisting at ₹1.81 crores. The micro-cap company, with a market capitalisation of just ₹16.00 crores, has generated zero revenue for six consecutive quarters, reflecting prolonged operational challenges. The stock, trading at ₹1.77, has declined 35.16% over the past year, significantly underperforming the Sensex's 10.22% gain during the same period.
Time: Feb 18 2026 06:21 PM IST</description><guid>4dee062d5d6fcfdc882eb8f5ed469e50</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 18:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nimbus Projects Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Outlook</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nimbus-projects-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-outlook-3846086</link><description>Nimbus Projects Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Realty sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: Feb 18 2026 06:20 PM IST</description><guid>38d85bedaaabf7cc4f4719de44826dbc</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 18:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Poonawalla Fincorp Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/poonawalla-fincorp-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3846085</link><description>Poonawalla Fincorp Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a long-term momentum shift for the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC), reinforcing the stock’s positive trajectory amid strong fundamentals and improving market sentiment.
Time: Feb 18 2026 06:20 PM IST</description><guid>e2bbd78b43a6f6025fff8eba03187b01</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 18:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Inox Green Energy Services Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/inox-green-energy-services-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3846080</link><description>Inox Green Energy Services Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: Feb 18 2026 06:00 PM IST</description><guid>b5fc9f87e59617d8f054e7c13f62b7ca</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 18:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indigo Paints Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indigo-paints-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3846081</link><description>Indigo Paints Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: Feb 18 2026 06:00 PM IST</description><guid>51619af0d93d17f3ecb0f5d7236518df</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 18:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Moksh Ornaments Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/moksh-ornaments-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3846079</link><description>Moksh Ornaments Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Gems, Jewellery And Watches sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term outlook.
Time: Feb 18 2026 06:00 PM IST</description><guid>fe5677081db722272b119d4a3d426e33</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 18:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Yash Chemex Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/yash-chemex-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3846076</link><description>Yash Chemex Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: Feb 18 2026 06:00 PM IST</description><guid>bc53557ce80b028998dba2ab3bc99fbf</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 18:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Narayana Hrudayalaya Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/narayana-hrudayalaya-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3846075</link><description>Narayana Hrudayalaya Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s short- to medium-term momentum and raising concerns about long-term weakness despite its strong historical performance.
Time: Feb 18 2026 06:00 PM IST</description><guid>88442ac51752483b40eece0f4e18ed10</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 18:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Carysil Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/carysil-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3846078</link><description>Carysil Ltd, a prominent player in the Electronics &amp; Appliances sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, raising concerns about the stock’s near-term momentum and long-term strength despite its impressive historical performance.
Time: Feb 18 2026 06:00 PM IST</description><guid>f2d798affa2faf5f9bfc3518022552f4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 18:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Haria Apparels Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/haria-apparels-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3846073</link><description>Haria Apparels Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has recently formed a Death Cross as its 50-day moving average (DMA) crossed below the 200-DMA. This technical development is widely regarded as a bearish signal, indicating a potential deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term trend. Investors should carefully consider this shift amid mixed fundamental and technical indicators.
Time: Feb 18 2026 06:00 PM IST</description><guid>79468739cba2524d0b017677a04b4523</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 18:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hitachi Energy India Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hitachi-energy-india-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3846072</link><description>Hitachi Energy India Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout, signalling a shift in long-term momentum and a possible trend reversal for the heavy electrical equipment company.
Time: Feb 18 2026 06:00 PM IST</description><guid>2f4a89f0ae7512c56a9aef30c75e7def</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 18:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 18:45:40 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>