<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:36:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Allcargo Terminals Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/allcargo-terminals-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3785840</link><description>Allcargo Terminals Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development highlights a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raises concerns about its long-term prospects amid already challenging market conditions.
Time: 3 minutes ago</description><guid>70792367ebc7dd39b9681628dcbad7e3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/orissa-bengal-carrier-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3785842</link><description>Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a prolonged bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 3 minutes ago</description><guid>801b2dee7bba67d22467c5822bc474bc</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>We Win Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/we-win-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3785839</link><description>We Win Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Commercial Services &amp; Supplies sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about long-term weakness amid already challenging market conditions.
Time: 3 minutes ago</description><guid>95506a9e27ec9e6300d205a5ad00081a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Balkrishna Paper Mills Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/balkrishna-paper-mills-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3785838</link><description>Balkrishna Paper Mills Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a prolonged bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>781bb4a1f61540d2b0cfb15f1084c187</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kemistar Corporation Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kemistar-corporation-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3785835</link><description>Kemistar Corporation Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Specialty Chemicals sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>75e87904e04ce36fac830ee294114a20</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Orient Bell Ltd. Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/orient-bell-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3785834</link><description>Orient Bell Ltd., a micro-cap player in the diversified consumer products sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>ff0f216a09b6ad3efd524cef980ee6c1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zenith Steel Pipes &amp; Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/zenith-steel-pipes-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3785833</link><description>Zenith Steel Pipes &amp; Industries Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and suggests a bearish outlook for investors amid ongoing sectoral and company-specific challenges.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>55c50883d6fbf8a701764a573a7bc4c9</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kunststoffe Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kunststoffe-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3785832</link><description>Kunststoffe Industries Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend and long-term weakness in the stock’s price momentum.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>3dbde42e524b0a33962537db2f3a1e57</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Western India Plywoods Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/western-india-plywoods-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3785836</link><description>Western India Plywoods Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term prospects.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>91a4c7a9b4442c95adeced9ba999cbbe</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Utique Enterprises Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/utique-enterprises-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3785831</link><description>Utique Enterprises Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non - Ferrous Metals sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>a5dd8e135ba7bb9d2e24ac1e9a3fdfbc</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Best Agrolife Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/best-agrolife-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3785837</link><description>Best Agrolife Ltd, a player in the Pesticides &amp; Agrochemicals sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross—a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, offering investors a fresh perspective on the stock’s future trajectory.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>682faae1272e68808979496a31ded5f8</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MM Forgings Ltd. Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mm-forgings-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3785828</link><description>MM Forgings Ltd., a key player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross—a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-DMA. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, offering investors a fresh perspective on the stock’s trajectory amid mixed recent performances.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>ab7c335d1ee5db66979dd758659dd294</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vascon Engineers Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vascon-engineers-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3785829</link><description>Vascon Engineers Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>9c9a4e973202925a54e1496d638e9e23</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pradeep Metals Ltd. Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pradeep-metals-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3785830</link><description>Pradeep Metals Ltd., a micro-cap player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross—a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, attracting investor attention despite the stock’s current mixed fundamentals and recent price volatility.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>62f382dbfd5f02e31574b3b6f70fe26b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eimco Elecon Q3 FY26: Sharp Profit Surge Masks Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/eimco-elecon-q3-fy26-sharp-profit-surge-masks-valuation-concerns-3785807</link><description>Eimco Elecon (India) Limited, a specialised manufacturer of underground and opencast mining equipment, has reported mixed signals in its December 2025 quarter results, with strong sequential profit growth offset by concerning valuation metrics and deteriorating technical trends. The stock surged 8.67% on January 08, 2026, trading at ₹1,768.80, yet remains 41.06% below its 52-week high of ₹3,001.10, reflecting investor uncertainty about the company's premium valuation amidst modest operational performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1622b1307cb44181ac9e7935794018ea</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Transformers &amp; Rectifiers India Q3 FY26: Strong Profit Surge Masks Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/transformers-rectifiers-india-q3-fy26-strong-profit-surge-masks-valuation-concerns-3785806</link><description>Transformers &amp; Rectifiers India Ltd. (TARIL) delivered a robust performance in Q3 FY26, with consolidated net profit surging 117.78% quarter-on-quarter to ₹73.85 crores, driven by exceptional revenue growth and improved operational efficiency. However, the stock's dramatic 9.15% decline following the results announcement reflects deepening investor concerns about stretched valuations and a prolonged technical downtrend that has eroded over half of shareholder value in the past year.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>32233ef52c51b22842533d8aca644d19</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tejas Networks Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.440 Amid Weak Financial Metrics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tejas-networks-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs440-amid-weak-financial-metrics-3785803</link><description>Tejas Networks Ltd, a key player in the Telecom - Equipment &amp; Accessories sector, has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.440 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid ongoing financial headwinds and subdued market performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>42027cefaeeacaa532cb417533488a50</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Xchanging Solutions Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.78.8 Amidst Market Downturn</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/xchanging-solutions-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs788-amidst-market-downturn-3785804</link><description>Shares of Xchanging Solutions Ltd, a player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, declined sharply to a new 52-week low of Rs.78.8 on 8 Jan 2026, marking a significant downturn amid broader market weakness and company-specific performance concerns.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>735deb73afbea177b4a13c164d2852f7</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahanagar Gas Ltd. Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.1051</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mahanagar-gas-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs1051-3785802</link><description>Mahanagar Gas Ltd. has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.1051 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid a series of underwhelming financial results and sectoral pressures. The stock has been on a downward trajectory, reflecting challenges in maintaining growth momentum within the gas sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0f042fbc697438ee204f6375e706250d</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mercury EV-Tech Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Market Downturn</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mercury-ev-tech-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-market-downturn-3785798</link><description>Mercury EV-Tech Ltd’s stock price declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.35.75 on 8 Jan 2026, reflecting ongoing pressures within the automobile sector and broader market weakness. The stock has been on a downward trajectory, underperforming both its sector and key market indices over the past year.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>40fec3c27162932f8b06e560ef8eed99</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:36:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>