<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:11:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>GE Power Joins MomentumNow Stocks on Strong Financial Footing</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/mojo-premium/ge-power-added-to-momentumnow-stocks-on-strong-financial-upswing-3767433</link><description>GE Power, a small-cap player in the Heavy Electrical Equipment sector, has been added to the MomentumNow Stocks list as of 23 December 2025, reflecting its recent financial performance and alignment with momentum-driven investment strategies.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>4a3ec0be88645ee89470ddf7a979f334</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:11:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>D B Corp Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/d-b-corp-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3767426</link><description>D B Corp, a key player in the Media &amp; Entertainment sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ce6e1d8869f2e5690a408bf24e79ac1c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:11:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Indian Wood Products Company Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/the-indian-wood-products-company-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3767425</link><description>The Indian Wood Products Company has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests potential long-term weakness in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8a74b5840edb984a0fd6177c24abeeda</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:11:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Akme Fintrade (India) Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/akme-fintrade-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3767424</link><description>Akme Fintrade (India), a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>94512392ebca78129eaf6ee91f6e9c89</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:11:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pritika Engineering Components Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pritika-engineering-components-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3767423</link><description>Pritika Engineering Components has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price action over the longer term.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ee4544028b2f85025a00f4660edae3eb</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:11:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paradeep Phosphates Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/paradeep-phosphates-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3767422</link><description>Paradeep Phosphates, a key player in the fertilisers sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a potential weakening in the stock's medium to long-term momentum.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>091963857633bf9025e62963b7c92c80</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:11:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prudent Corporate Advisory Services Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/prudent-corporate-advisory-services-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3767421</link><description>Prudent Corporate Advisory Services has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price action over the longer term.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ed386464a790e84ae2b01673b110d654</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:11:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Greenpanel Industries Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/greenpanel-industries-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3767417</link><description>Greenpanel Industries has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests potential long-term weakness in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a00340533ad24da29ed1686ab6821e76</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:11:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Akshar Spintex Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/akshar-spintex-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3767419</link><description>Akshar Spintex, a micro-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory over the longer term.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4a4a4dcc1ab458f6f37b40a444d34190</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:11:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Power &amp; Instrumentation (Gujarat) Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/power-instrumentation-gujarat-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3767415</link><description>Power &amp; Instrumentation (Gujarat) Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical event where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price over the longer term.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>07296ef3e149c2a1f85d21c94999d388</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:11:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>J K Cements Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/j-k-cements-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3767416</link><description>J K Cements has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend, indicating potential weakness in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum. Investors and market watchers are closely analysing this event amid mixed performance metrics and sector dynamics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>43604eaf07c43a4c08d5a28e2998f202</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:11:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Williamson Magor &amp; Company Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/williamson-magor-company-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3767418</link><description>Williamson Magor &amp; Company, a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6702798beb4e247975f68c201848ed3b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:11:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blue Star Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/blue-star-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3767413</link><description>Blue Star, a prominent player in the Electronics &amp; Appliances sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory over the medium to long term.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>99dc62db32979aa7952ecbc9fd99bad0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:11:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Balu Forge Industries Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/balu-forge-industries-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3767420</link><description>Balu Forge Industries, a key player in the Castings &amp; Forgings sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting potential long-term weakness and a deterioration in the stock’s momentum.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9dcdfebd139929b622e0e64581d5ae98</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:11:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cinevista Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cinevista-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3767414</link><description>Cinevista, a micro-cap player in the Media &amp; Entertainment sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>eeb6de647ea45aeeb8e35733fb47f69f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:11:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ABans Enterprises Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/abans-enterprises-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3767409</link><description>ABans Enterprises, a micro-cap player in the Non-Ferrous Metals sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and may indicate a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory over the medium to long term.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9e379a921b63c986397abf258e16a93c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:11:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Central Bank of India Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/central-bank-of-india-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3767407</link><description>Central Bank of India has recently experienced a significant technical development as its 50-day moving average crossed above the 200-day moving average, a formation widely recognised as a Golden Cross. This event often signals a potential shift in long-term momentum and a possible bullish breakout for the stock, attracting attention from market participants and technical analysts alike.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>61e20b297eee916d9b845ed71e8e6da6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:11:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lee &amp; Nee Software (Exports) Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lee-nee-software-exports-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3767405</link><description>Lee &amp; Nee Software (Exports), a player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock's price trajectory.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d3094f7ca7b6359a53e24996e3d902a1</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:11:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>United Spirits Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/united-spirits-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3767404</link><description>United Spirits has recently experienced a significant technical event known as the Golden Cross, where its 50-day moving average has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development is widely regarded as a bullish signal, indicating a possible shift in long-term momentum and a potential trend reversal for the stock within the beverages sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>06532197b1626676843bb0e9c91d757e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:11:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Automotive Stampings &amp; Assemblies Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/automotive-stampings-assemblies-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3767411</link><description>Automotive Stampings &amp; Assemblies has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests potential long-term weakness in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>73470ac053e83e76665984b030320af5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:11:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:11:27 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>