<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:37:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Virtual Galaxy Infotech Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-virtual-galaxy-infotech-ltd-fallingrising-3832100</link><description>On 10-Feb, Virtual Galaxy Infotech Ltd’s stock price rose by 3.84% to ₹147.35, outperforming both its sector and the broader market benchmarks, reflecting a positive short-term momentum despite some mixed longer-term trends.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a6be8a15b224a0377c99a7dc51558fa3</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:37:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Chamunda Electrical Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-chamunda-electrical-ltd-fallingrising-3832099</link><description>On 10-Feb, Chamunda Electrical Ltd’s stock price rose by 2.29% to ₹47.00, reflecting a modest recovery despite a challenging recent performance record and subdued investor participation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>38c504f313db136beebc18c7dac9bee3</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:37:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is National Peroxide Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-national-peroxide-ltd-fallingrising-3832098</link><description>On 10-Feb, National Peroxide Ltd’s stock price rose by 2.06% to close at ₹435.00, reflecting a notable short-term recovery despite a challenging longer-term performance relative to the broader market.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>bf25946b19feed2590927ad589492fc1</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:37:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-awfis-space-solutions-ltd-fallingrising-3832097</link><description>On 10-Feb, AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 3.22% to close at ₹386.00. This movement reflects a complex interplay of strong operational growth overshadowed by concerns over management efficiency and financial leverage.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>317f187c33918e7e9b4c902e56210516</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:37:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Azad Engineering Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-azad-engineering-ltd-fallingrising-3832096</link><description>On 10-Feb, Azad Engineering Ltd's stock price rose by 1.64% to ₹1,592.40, reflecting growing investor confidence driven by robust quarterly performance and heightened market participation.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>460d27af4fb5eb8d793dad5e9a9eed35</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:37:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Crop Life Science Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-crop-life-science-ltd-fallingrising-3832095</link><description>On 10-Feb, Crop Life Science Ltd’s stock price fell sharply by 5.05% to close at ₹47.00, reflecting a continuation of a downward trend that has persisted over recent weeks and months, significantly underperforming the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>8cf0f33528a2a03d3303b05638238ed7</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:37:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Enser Communications Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-enser-communications-ltd-fallingrising-3832094</link><description>On 10-Feb, Enser Communications Ltd recorded a 2.39% rise in its share price, closing at ₹12.85. This modest gain comes despite a backdrop of sustained underperformance relative to key benchmarks and a notable decline in investor participation.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>999fbe475799418f7178ac2d1cc1e7c4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:37:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Divgi Torqtransfer Systems Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-divgi-torqtransfer-systems-ltd-fallingrising-3832093</link><description>On 10-Feb, Divgi Torqtransfer Systems Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, closing at ₹647.70 with a gain of ₹23.35 or 3.74%. This upward movement reflects a combination of robust quarterly financial results, sustained market outperformance, and positive technical indicators that have bolstered investor confidence.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>9a42b8b76820e125e55433601d26fe1c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:37:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Mega Flex Plastics Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-mega-flex-plastics-ltd-fallingrising-3832092</link><description>On 10-Feb, Mega Flex Plastics Ltd's stock price rose by 1.87% to ₹119.70, reflecting a notable outperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>2209efe86d624b31b64578e1601a8981</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:37:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vijaya Diagnostic Centre Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vijaya-diagnostic-centre-ltd-fallingrising-3832091</link><description>On 10-Feb, Vijaya Diagnostic Centre Ltd’s stock price rose by 3.0% to ₹1,023.60, reflecting a notable short-term rally driven by increased investor participation and strong technical indicators despite mixed long-term fundamentals.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>d9fe20a9fae388a9d643862478e7d91b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:37:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Venus Pipes &amp; Tubes Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-venus-pipes-tubes-ltd-fallingrising-3832090</link><description>On 10-Feb, Venus Pipes &amp; Tubes Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 4.31% to ₹1,238.00 by 9:15 PM. This upward movement reflects a combination of strong quarterly financial performance, favourable long-term growth indicators, and positive investor sentiment despite some mixed volume signals.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>3670d72b6646f4c6225436e38e4b1c76</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:37:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shyam Metalics &amp; Energy Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shyam-metalics-energy-ltd-fallingrising-3832089</link><description>As of 10-Feb, Shyam Metalics &amp; Energy Ltd has recorded a notable rise in its stock price, reflecting strong investor confidence driven by robust long-term returns and increasing market participation despite some recent financial headwinds.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ecb3ec4ff782ef7651871cdd4ac2f3dc</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:37:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is NDR Auto Components Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ndr-auto-components-ltd-fallingrising-3832088</link><description>On 10-Feb, NDR Auto Components Ltd witnessed a significant price rise of 5.13%, closing at ₹799.80, driven by strong short-term momentum and robust long-term growth metrics despite some valuation concerns and recent flat results.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>d596df98c6ce2a22c7feaf005f76b6a0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:37:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is The Anup Engineering Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-the-anup-engineering-ltd-fallingrising-3832087</link><description>On 10-Feb, The Anup Engineering Ltd witnessed a notable intraday price increase of 4.36%, closing at ₹2,110.60. This rise comes despite the company’s recent quarterly results showing some softness, reflecting a complex interplay of short-term market dynamics and longer-term fundamentals.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>309865b6990bf610ed2073f9b5af5323</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:37:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Affordable Robotic &amp; Automation Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-affordable-robotic-automation-ltd-fallingrising-3832086</link><description>On 10-Feb, Affordable Robotic &amp; Automation Ltd witnessed a notable uptick in its share price, rising by 2.29% to close at ₹210.00. This increase reflects a continuation of positive momentum over recent sessions, supported by robust trading volumes and outperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>214ddd9c01e9d8a1503f2e3956a5bd4e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:37:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ashapuri Gold Ornament Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ashapuri-gold-ornament-ltd-fallingrising-3832085</link><description>On 10-Feb, Ashapuri Gold Ornament Ltd's stock price rose by 3.61% to ₹5.46, continuing a short-term upward trend despite a challenging longer-term performance relative to the broader market.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>0506f284d3c1814f739bf015c0e68e6a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:37:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ambani Orgochem Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ambani-orgochem-ltd-fallingrising-3832084</link><description>On 10-Feb, Ambani Orgochem Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, closing at ₹130.20 with a gain of ₹4.35 or 3.46%. This upward movement reflects a broader trend of robust performance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>d10600f5b8ba09022db0983b51f3f1e5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:37:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is KKV Agro Powers Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-kkv-agro-powers-ltd-fallingrising-3832083</link><description>On 10-Feb, KKV Agro Powers Ltd witnessed a significant rise in its share price, closing at ₹693.00, up ₹32.55 or 4.93% from the previous session. This marks a new 52-week high for the stock, reflecting robust investor interest and notable outperformance relative to both its sector and broader market benchmarks.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>6b9d2a0946ee0dfbce6e61ec98fc9388</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:37:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Zota Health Care Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-zota-health-care-ltd-fallingrising-3832082</link><description>On 10-Feb, Zota Health Care Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 4.52% to ₹1,388.60 by 9:08 PM. This upward movement comes despite the company’s ongoing operational challenges and mixed financial performance, reflecting a complex interplay of investor sentiment and market dynamics.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>3322cd235d9c5b066d5bc5cf02f4bcd8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:37:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Advik Capital Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-advik-capital-ltd-fallingrising-3832081</link><description>On 10-Feb, Advik Capital Ltd's stock price rose by 3.36% to ₹1.54, reflecting a notable short-term rally that outpaces broader market benchmarks and sector performance.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>507056419930315bb20d05e1215ea626</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:37:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 21:37:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>