<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:35:36 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Airan Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/airan-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3783542</link><description>Airan Ltd, a player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has reached a new 52-week low, reflecting ongoing pressures on its share price. The stock’s latest decline underscores a challenging period marked by subdued financial performance and valuation concerns.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>205e283bb27f7e6b6210225fb848a9a0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sensex and Nifty Slip Amid Mixed Sectoral Trends; Pharma Leads Gains</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-and-nifty-slip-amid-mixed-sectoral-trends-pharma-leads-gains-3783541</link><description>Indian equity markets closed lower on 6 Jan 2026, with the Sensex retreating 376.28 points (-0.44%) to 85,063.34 and the Nifty 50 shedding 71.6 points (-0.27%) to finish at 26,178.70. Despite the modest declines, the Nifty remains within striking distance of its 52-week high, trading just 0.74% below the peak of 26,373.20. Market breadth was weak, with declines outnumbering advances across the BSE500 index, reflecting cautious investor sentiment amid mixed sectoral trends and subdued foreign institutional activity.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b74c69dd4ffa866eca0591ed1c648150</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AWL Agri Business Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/awl-agri-business-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3783540</link><description>AWL Agri Business Ltd has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.229.75 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has underperformed its sector and benchmark indices, reflecting a challenging period for the edible oil company.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>4f98e0d62c11d92e39a1a4a1db3816d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lupin Ltd. Hits Intraday High with 3.78% Surge on 6 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lupin-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-378-surge-on-6-jan-2026-3783534</link><description>Lupin Ltd. demonstrated robust intraday strength on 6 Jan 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 2,157.95, marking a 3.84% increase. This performance notably outpaced the broader Sensex, which declined by 0.44% amid a negative market opening and ongoing volatility.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>2c22d3794fb9f7ec8f36aa977bcc1660</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gorani Industries Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.58.03 Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gorani-industries-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs5803-amid-continued-downtrend-3783533</link><description>Shares of Gorani Industries Ltd, a player in the Electronics &amp; Appliances sector, declined sharply to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.58.03 on 6 January 2026, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s recent performance trajectory.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ae4b65602b71276f4ec19c837f3e2009</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>XPRO India Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/xpro-india-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3783537</link><description>XPRO India Ltd’s share price declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.922.4 on 6 Jan 2026, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory. The packaging sector stock has underperformed its peers and broader market indices, reflecting persistent pressures on its financial performance and valuation metrics.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b8375f34673e3a6b812c0a63d8987135</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bliss GVS Pharma Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.190.95</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bliss-gvs-pharma-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs19095-3783538</link><description>Bliss GVS Pharma Ltd has surged to a fresh 52-week high of Rs.190.95, marking a significant milestone in its stock performance. This new peak reflects robust momentum driven by strong intraday gains and sustained buying interest, outpacing its sector and broader market indices.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>48419407183df576d5574f41b12e4fd5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SMT Engineering Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.211.8</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/smt-engineering-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs2118-3783539</link><description>SMT Engineering Ltd, a key player in the Trading &amp; Distributors sector, surged to a fresh 52-week and all-time high of Rs.211.8 on 6 Jan 2026, reflecting robust market momentum and sustained gains over the past several weeks.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b2adf549fdc55d004e672c0620310813</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>P. H. Capital Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.463</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/p-h-capital-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs463-3783535</link><description>P. H. Capital Ltd, a prominent player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, reached a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs.463 today, underscoring a remarkable rally and sustained momentum in its share price over the past year.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>062aa3199a3daac86fce362237c9d7e4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RDB Infrastructure and Power Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.70.3</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rdb-infrastructure-and-power-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs703-3783532</link><description>RDB Infrastructure and Power Ltd has surged to a fresh 52-week high of Rs.70.3, marking a significant milestone in its stock performance amid a sustained rally over the past fortnight.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>dd30124017ff8c6d64dbff1e9b8c3578</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I G Petrochemicals Ltd Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/i-g-petrochemicals-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3783530</link><description>I G Petrochemicals Ltd commenced trading on 6 Jan 2026 with a pronounced gap down, opening at Rs 371, reflecting a 6.55% decline from its previous close. This weak start underscores prevailing market apprehensions surrounding the commodity chemicals sector and the stock’s recent performance metrics.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>442f7c66cf92676e58ab17a57a6c3b65</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bluegod Entertainment Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.5.1</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bluegod-entertainment-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs51-3783536</link><description>Bluegod Entertainment Ltd, a key player in the Fertilizers sector, reached a significant milestone today by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.5.1. This achievement underscores the stock’s strong momentum, driven by sustained gains and robust trading above all major moving averages.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ad62f75f7192911eb82fe8fd602cb181</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Money Masters Leasing &amp; Finance Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.0.7</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/money-masters-leasing-finance-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs07-3783531</link><description>Money Masters Leasing &amp; Finance Ltd has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.0.7, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid a challenging year for the company and the broader market environment.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>a48c42279df535fb50f6290e629c580f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Small and Micro Cap Stocks Deliver Exceptional Half-Year Returns Amid Bullish Market Sentiment</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/small-and-micro-cap-stocks-deliver-exceptional-half-year-returns-amid-bullish-market-sentiment-3783517</link><description>In a remarkable display of resilience and growth, select small and micro cap stocks have outperformed the broader market indices over the past six months, delivering returns well above benchmark levels. These stocks, spanning sectors from FMCG to healthcare and metals, have been propelled by strong fundamentals, bullish technicals, and favourable sectoral tailwinds, rewarding investors with exceptional gains.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>bd25f615a969c1f61eb7218a9077055a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Small Cap Stocks Deliver Exceptional Returns: Cupid Leads with 436.5% Gain in One Year</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/small-cap-stocks-deliver-exceptional-returns-cupid-leads-with-4365-gain-in-one-year-3783516</link><description>In a remarkable display of market outperformance, several small and micro cap stocks have delivered extraordinary returns over the past year, significantly outpacing benchmark indices. Leading the pack is Cupid, a small cap FMCG company, which has surged by an astonishing 436.51%, underscoring the potential for high-growth opportunities within niche sectors.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>c4a3132048bafc79128220ffc4d20537</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bluegod Entertainment Ltd Hits All-Time High at Rs.5.1 on 6 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bluegod-entertainment-ltd-hits-all-time-high-at-rs51-on-6-jan-2026-3783529</link><description>Bluegod Entertainment Ltd, a key player in the Fertilizers sector, reached a new all-time high of Rs.5.1 on 6 Jan 2026, underscoring a remarkable ascent in its market valuation and investor confidence. This milestone reflects the company’s sustained performance and significant outperformance relative to broader market indices and sector peers.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>0bccd5945e0aeb5e725a4390cfcbe8ca</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Parmeshwari Silk Mills Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.81.92</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/parmeshwari-silk-mills-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs8192-3783528</link><description>Parmeshwari Silk Mills, a key player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, surged to a fresh 52-week and all-time high of Rs.81.92 today, marking a significant milestone in its stock performance amid a mixed market backdrop.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>8e4f922a993f6ef901333821da134d6f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dhruv Consultancy Services Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dhruv-consultancy-services-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3783523</link><description>Dhruv Consultancy Services Ltd has declined to a fresh 52-week low, reflecting ongoing difficulties in its financial and market performance. The stock’s latest low price underscores a challenging period for the company within the Commercial Services &amp; Supplies sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>1f8a932a018e920d94d71e5e811e4343</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flexituff Ventures International Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/flexituff-ventures-international-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3783521</link><description>Flexituff Ventures International Ltd, a player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.12.02 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid broader market fluctuations and company-specific financial pressures.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>3740efa255b917162a542ac83747122f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spectrum Electrical Industries Ltd Hits Day Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/spectrum-electrical-industries-ltd-hits-day-low-amid-price-pressure-3783524</link><description>Spectrum Electrical Industries Ltd experienced a notable decline today, hitting its day low as price pressures intensified amid a broadly cautious market environment. The stock underperformed significantly against its sector and key benchmarks, reflecting immediate selling pressure and subdued investor sentiment.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>d3f131afdf7c7d06cabf7926212f6bc0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:35:36 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>