<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:33:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Robust Earnings Growth Marks Dec-2025 Quarter as Majority of Stocks Report Positive Results</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/robust-earnings-growth-marks-dec-2025-quarter-as-majority-of-stocks-report-positive-results-3804336</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has unfolded with a notable improvement in positive results, as 55.0% of the 428 companies reporting have posted favourable outcomes, marking a significant uptick from the preceding quarters. While mid and small caps continue to outperform large caps in terms of positive earnings surprises, sectoral leaders and individual standouts have emerged, painting a nuanced picture of corporate profitability and growth trends.
Time: 3 minutes ago</description><guid>6b08c44ceb35959d9ec9ab21022ee5ef</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Loyal Equipments Ltd Drops 6.87%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/loyal-equipments-ltd-drops-687-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3804333</link><description>Loyal Equipments Ltd’s shares declined by 6.87% over the week ending 23 January 2026, closing at Rs.176.95 from Rs.190.00 the previous Friday. This underperformance came despite the Sensex falling 3.31% over the same period, indicating a sharper drop for the stock amid weak financial results, technical deterioration, and waning institutional interest.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b2e67f0d3a550979252706fccc3a6fc9</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shanthi Gears Surges 10.88% Amid Volatility and Earnings Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shanthi-gears-surges-1088-amid-volatility-and-earnings-pressure-3804332</link><description>Shanthi Gears Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, gaining 10.88% from Rs.407.15 to Rs.451.45 between 19 and 23 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 3.31% over the same period. The stock’s rally was marked by a notable intraday high of Rs.472.70 on 22 January, driven by a surge in buying interest despite mixed financial results and technical signals. This review analyses the key events and price movements shaping the stock’s volatile week.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>85e5037644e2c0c4907e6aa26999d709</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Praj Industries Falls 8.76% This Week: 5 Key Factors Behind the Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/praj-industries-falls-876-this-week-5-key-factors-behind-the-decline-3804331</link><description>Praj Industries Ltd’s stock endured a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, falling 8.76% to close at Rs.283.95, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 3.31% decline over the same period. The stock repeatedly hit fresh 52-week lows amid persistent earnings pressure and bearish technical signals, reflecting ongoing financial headwinds and subdued market sentiment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6da5c6033e78e6935d45afcdb35a83b6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>eClerx Services Ltd Falls 6.88%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eclerx-services-ltd-falls-688-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3804330</link><description>eClerx Services Ltd experienced a turbulent week, closing at Rs.4,314.50 on 23 January 2026, down 6.88% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.4,633.40. This decline notably outpaced the Sensex’s 3.31% fall over the same period, reflecting a week marked by technical momentum shifts, a sharp gap up midweek, and a valuation reassessment amid broader market volatility.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>19a93e45a95e3e0568a8a3345d094640</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crimson Metal Engineering Company Ltd Falls 14.24%: Key Factors Behind the Sharp Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/crimson-metal-engineering-company-ltd-falls-1424-key-factors-behind-the-sharp-weekly-decline-3804328</link><description>Crimson Metal Engineering Company Ltd experienced a significant reversal this week, closing at Rs.50.11 on 23 Jan 2026, down 14.24% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.58.43. This decline notably outpaced the Sensex’s 3.31% fall over the same period, reflecting a sharper correction in the stock amid volatile market conditions and shifting investor sentiment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ccb3898c91cececd7253014654e402d4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mangalore Refinery &amp; Petrochemicals Ltd Gains 2.51%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mangalore-refinery-petrochemicals-ltd-gains-251-5-key-factors-driving-the-week-3804329</link><description>Mangalore Refinery &amp; Petrochemicals Ltd. (MRPL) closed the week ending 23 January 2026 with a modest gain of 2.51%, rising from Rs.151.55 to Rs.155.35. This performance notably outpaced the broader Sensex, which declined by 3.31% over the same period, reflecting MRPL’s relative resilience amid a volatile market environment. The week was marked by a mix of technical shifts, strong trading volumes, and renewed investor interest, culminating in a cautious but positive momentum for the stock.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>bc91416487a26793d9b3711946d35f34</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>City Union Bank Gains 1.03%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/city-union-bank-gains-103-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3804327</link><description>City Union Bank Ltd. recorded a modest weekly gain of 1.03%, closing at Rs.275.70 on 23 January 2026, outperforming the Sensex which declined 3.31% over the same period. The stock’s performance was shaped by a series of technical momentum shifts, a significant upgrade in its rating by MarketsMOJO, and strong financial results, all contributing to a cautiously optimistic market sentiment despite some volatility in the final session.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7833206296a3d1139cdc7f0627056120</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Colgate-Palmolive Gains 2.99%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/colgate-palmolive-gains-299-2-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3804326</link><description>Colgate-Palmolive (India) Ltd recorded a 2.99% gain over the week ending 23 Jan 2026, closing at Rs.2,164.95, outperforming the Sensex which declined 3.31% during the same period. The stock’s performance was shaped by a mix of technical momentum shifts and a sharp surge in derivatives open interest, reflecting a complex but cautiously optimistic market stance amid broader sector and market volatility.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8be5157d583eaa398dfa7b84ba9aad32</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Axis Bank Ltd. Declines 2.66% Despite Derivatives Surge: 5 Key Factors Driving Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/axis-bank-ltd-declines-266-despite-derivatives-surge-5-key-factors-driving-volatility-3804325</link><description>Axis Bank Ltd. closed the week ending 23 January 2026 at Rs.1,260.10, down 2.66% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.1,294.55. Despite this decline, the stock outperformed the Sensex, which fell 3.31% over the same period. The week was marked by a new 52-week high, robust derivatives activity, and mixed price action amid a volatile market backdrop.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>adeb4743803145b9e5e21f76ed8663a4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Symphony Ltd. Falls 5.04%: Downgrade and Bearish Momentum Shape Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/symphony-ltd-falls-504-downgrade-and-bearish-momentum-shape-weekly-decline-3804324</link><description>Symphony Ltd. experienced a challenging week on the bourses, closing at Rs.849.50 on 23 January 2026, down 5.04% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.894.60. This decline outpaced the Sensex’s 3.31% fall over the same period, reflecting intensified selling pressure amid a downgrade to Strong Sell and a shift towards bearish technical momentum. Despite a brief midweek recovery, the stock struggled to sustain gains, ending the week near its recent lows.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0f01bb067722636c1cd60bb6bb37d6db</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Steelcast Ltd Falls 9.85%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/steelcast-ltd-falls-985-5-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3804323</link><description>Steelcast Ltd endured a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its share price declining by 9.85% to close at Rs.183.50, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. Despite a brief midweek rebound, the stock faced persistent selling pressure amid deteriorating technical indicators and a downgrade to a Sell rating by MarketsMOJO, reflecting growing caution among investors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e6a3a8357a0c87d7ce7fd96a1e8cf99c</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Karur Vysya Bank’s 0.77% Weekly Dip Amid Valuation Reset and Q3 Earnings</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/karur-vysya-banks-077-weekly-dip-amid-valuation-reset-and-q3-earnings-3804322</link><description>Karur Vysya Bank Ltd. closed the week ending 23 Jan 2026 at Rs.265.35, down 0.77% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.267.40. This modest decline came amid a broader market sell-off, with the Sensex falling 3.31% over the same period. Despite the weekly dip, the bank’s share price outperformed the benchmark index, reflecting resilience supported by a significant valuation reset and strong quarterly profit growth announced during the week.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ffb9c1d0e5dea0261ea7d9b1cee565b7</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JTL Industries Gains 5.39% This Week: Key Price Swings and Market Context</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jtl-industries-gains-539-this-week-key-price-swings-and-market-context-3804321</link><description>JTL Industries Ltd closed the week at Rs.76.19, marking a 5.39% gain from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.72.29, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 3.31% over the same period. The stock’s week was marked by sharp intraday swings, including a steep drop on 20 January followed by a strong rebound on 22 January, reflecting a volatile trading environment amid mixed market conditions.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3b50e53b523e3695772f5bdc0ef564f3</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Goa Carbon Ltd Falls 8.55%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/goa-carbon-ltd-falls-855-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3804320</link><description>Goa Carbon Ltd’s stock endured a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, declining 8.55% to close at Rs.359.05, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 3.31% fall over the same period. The stock repeatedly hit fresh 52-week lows amid mounting financial pressures, negative earnings, and subdued market sentiment, despite brief intraday recoveries. This review analyses the key events and market dynamics shaping the stock’s performance during the week.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>173b1db79358742dea039beddad8fb0a</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pankaj Polymers Gains 27.56%: 8 Key Days Driving the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pankaj-polymers-gains-2756-8-key-days-driving-the-rally-3804319</link><description>Pankaj Polymers Ltd delivered a remarkable weekly performance, surging 27.56% from Rs.56.74 to Rs.72.38 between 19 and 23 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 3.31% over the same period. The stock hit consecutive new 52-week and all-time highs each trading day, reflecting strong momentum amid a broadly weak market backdrop.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6e19632972913aad8e5146c1c93d2c62</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rajratan Global Wire Ltd Falls 13.20%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rajratan-global-wire-ltd-falls-1320-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3804318</link><description>Rajratan Global Wire Ltd experienced a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its share price declining 13.20% to close at Rs.455.85, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 3.31% fall over the same period. The stock faced intense selling pressure early in the week, followed by a sharp intraday rebound on 21 January, before succumbing to renewed weakness by week’s end. Key events including intraday lows, a strong recovery rally, and a robust quarterly earnings report shaped the stock’s volatile performance amid a broadly cautious market environment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a64d3e419146ca2aec6cbdd2caa986cb</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Azad India Mobility Ltd Falls 22.49%: 2 Key Technical Factors Driving the Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/azad-india-mobility-ltd-falls-2249-2-key-technical-factors-driving-the-decline-3804306</link><description>Azad India Mobility Ltd experienced a steep decline of 22.49% over the week ending 23 January 2026, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% in the same period. The stock’s slide was marked by a series of bearish technical signals, including the formation of a Death Cross and deteriorating momentum indicators, which coincided with heavy selling pressure and increased volatility. Despite the sharp weekly fall, the stock’s long-term performance remains strong, though near-term risks have intensified.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>0cf58d28d38109577e26cd4e2f358f3d</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hathway Cable &amp; Datacom Ltd Drops 15.10%: 8 Key Factors Behind the Steep Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hathway-cable-datacom-ltd-drops-1510-8-key-factors-behind-the-steep-decline-3804307</link><description>Hathway Cable &amp; Datacom Ltd’s stock endured a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, plunging 15.10% from Rs.12.05 to Rs.10.23, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 3.31% decline over the same period. The stock repeatedly hit fresh 52-week lows, culminating in an all-time low of Rs.10.6 on 23 January, amid deteriorating financial fundamentals, weak profitability, and subdued market sentiment within the media and entertainment sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>2585c3c999dfbca82fe3a5b4b5717f68</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GHV Infra Projects Ltd Gains 6.17%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ghv-infra-projects-ltd-gains-617-2-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-rally-3804309</link><description>GHV Infra Projects Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, rising 6.17% from ₹231.10 to ₹245.35 between 19 and 23 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 3.31% over the same period. The stock’s upward momentum was supported by a technical upgrade to a Hold rating and strong quarterly financial results, despite mixed signals from some technical indicators and a cautious market environment.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>4db4c7248da28a7eb2aa2ce42156ac72</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:33:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>