<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:42:58 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Saurashtra Cement Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.67 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/saurashtra-cement-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs67-amidst-continued-downtrend-3835363</link><description>Saurashtra Cement Ltd’s stock price declined sharply to hit a new 52-week low of Rs.67 on 12 Feb 2026, marking a significant downturn amid broader market fluctuations and company-specific performance concerns.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>4d57fd5ac355e3c8b4b898592b8380d4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:42:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Precision Wires India Ltd Hits New 52-Week High of Rs.279</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/precision-wires-india-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-of-rs279-3835362</link><description>Precision Wires India Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.279, marking a notable surge in the stock’s performance amid a mixed market environment. This achievement underscores the stock’s strong momentum, outpacing its sector and broader indices over the recent period.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>57edb71c6046365012f9e0f77aafa52e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:42:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lumax Auto Technologies Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.1823.75</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lumax-auto-technologies-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs182375-3835361</link><description>Lumax Auto Technologies Ltd has surged to a fresh 52-week and all-time high of Rs.1823.75, marking a significant milestone in its stock performance. This achievement underscores the company’s robust momentum amid a mixed market backdrop, with the stock outperforming its sector and demonstrating sustained gains over recent sessions.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>1f60017c4476d65eb6a9b09e5e7a6c39</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:42:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Garuda Construction and Engineering Ltd Reports Outstanding Quarterly Performance Amid Market Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/garuda-construction-and-engineering-ltd-reports-outstanding-quarterly-performance-amid-market-rally-3835359</link><description>Garuda Construction and Engineering Ltd has delivered an outstanding quarterly performance for December 2025, marking a significant improvement in its financial trend from very positive to outstanding. The company recorded its highest-ever quarterly net sales and profitability metrics, reflecting robust operational execution amid a challenging construction sector backdrop.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>e1aebf8dda6a911421e298d0faf1de65</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:42:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IRB Infrastructure Trust Reports Outstanding Quarterly Performance Amid Financial Trend Upgrade</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/irb-infrastructure-trust-reports-outstanding-quarterly-performance-amid-financial-trend-upgrade-3835358</link><description>IRB Infrastructure Trust has delivered an exceptional quarterly performance for the period ended December 2025, prompting a significant upgrade in its financial trend rating from flat to outstanding. The construction sector player recorded record-breaking revenue and profitability metrics, signalling robust operational efficiency and strong market positioning amid a challenging macroeconomic backdrop.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>62af70e50bc3a35b6ff3bd9937af9b7d</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:42:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KPIT Technologies Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Weak Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kpit-technologies-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-weak-price-action-3835355</link><description>KPIT Technologies Ltd has witnessed a significant 18.0% rise in open interest in its derivatives segment, coinciding with a sharp decline in its share price to a fresh 52-week low of ₹890.1. This surge in open interest, coupled with heavy volume near the day’s low, signals a notable shift in market positioning and investor sentiment within the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>12966d6460392160896e9d22b8aef86b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:42:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>LTI Mindtree Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amidst Weak Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lti-mindtree-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amidst-weak-price-action-3835357</link><description>LTI Mindtree Ltd (LTIM) has witnessed a significant 26.2% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, rising from 30,611 to 38,631 contracts, even as the stock price declined by over 5% on 12 Feb 2026. This divergence between rising open interest and falling prices signals a complex shift in market positioning, warranting a closer examination of volume patterns, investor sentiment, and potential directional bets in the software consulting sector.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>18b5dde6de3d8170406b8649ceb886ef</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:42:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alkem Laboratories Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/alkem-laboratories-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3835356</link><description>Alkem Laboratories Ltd has witnessed a notable 10.05% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this surge, the stock underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting a complex interplay of bullish and bearish sentiments among traders.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>c7b2697030d07d12ecfdd49cb931647c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:42:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Elxsi Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amidst Weak Price Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-elxsi-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amidst-weak-price-performance-3835354</link><description>Tata Elxsi Ltd., a key player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, rising by 16.78% to 45,472 contracts. This spike comes amid a broader market decline, with the stock underperforming its sector and the Sensex, signalling notable shifts in market positioning and investor sentiment.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>29a7a31b649c97c4d6ccfe774e327911</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:42:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Forge Ltd Sees Sharp Surge in Open Interest Signalling Strong Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-forge-ltd-sees-sharp-surge-in-open-interest-signalling-strong-market-positioning-3835353</link><description>Bharat Forge Ltd., a leading player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and potential directional bets. The stock’s recent price action, combined with robust volume and rising investor participation, underscores a bullish sentiment that is attracting increased attention from traders and investors alike.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>6603e564d5c310cb3828a6bc5809f19a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:42:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Heavy Electricals Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-heavy-electricals-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-price-action-3835352</link><description>Bharat Heavy Electricals Ltd. (BHEL) has witnessed a notable 12.4% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a recent two-day price decline, the stock’s rising open interest and volume patterns suggest evolving directional bets among traders in the heavy electrical equipment sector.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>230103988a66d785f58bbe0b6ebf7c69</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:42:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Happy Forgings Ltd Hits Upper Circuit Amid Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/happy-forgings-ltd-hits-upper-circuit-amid-robust-buying-pressure-3835351</link><description>Happy Forgings Ltd, a key player in the Castings &amp; Forgings sector, surged to hit its upper circuit limit on 12 Feb 2026, propelled by strong investor demand and sustained buying momentum. The stock closed at ₹1,286.6, marking a 9.99% gain on the day and setting a fresh 52-week high, underscoring renewed market confidence despite broader sector and benchmark declines.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>1d5881c967621d6d2985ce96c499b9c2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:42:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Mahindra Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Price Decline and Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tech-mahindra-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-price-decline-and-market-volatility-3835350</link><description>Tech Mahindra Ltd. has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling a shift in market positioning despite the stock’s recent underperformance. The sudden increase in open interest, coupled with volume patterns and price action, suggests investors are recalibrating their directional bets amid a broader sectoral and market decline.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>1f7412fcec93185d813c4894a54fd4c3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:42:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oracle Financial Services Software Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Price Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/oracle-financial-services-software-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-price-weakness-3835346</link><description>Oracle Financial Services Software Ltd (OFSS) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, rising by 17.87% to 37,839 contracts from the previous 32,102. This increase comes amid a pronounced downtrend in the stock price, which recently hit a new 52-week low of ₹6,787, reflecting growing market positioning shifts and directional bets by traders.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>da557045ff88dd02797250f2160b1ade</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:42:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SML Mahindra Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit, Hits Record High on Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sml-mahindra-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-hits-record-high-on-robust-buying-pressure-3835345</link><description>SML Mahindra Ltd, a prominent player in the automobile sector, witnessed a remarkable surge on 12 Feb 2026, hitting its upper circuit limit of 10% to close at a new 52-week and all-time high of ₹4,862.8. This sharp rally was driven by robust buying interest, significant unfilled demand, and a notable increase in investor participation, positioning the stock well above key moving averages and outperforming both its sector and the broader market indices.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>8d3c2b81c5a472546d6ce192b49e45e8</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:42:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quicktouch Technologies Ltd Plunges to Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/quicktouch-technologies-ltd-plunges-to-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3835343</link><description>Quicktouch Technologies Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, witnessed a sharp decline on 12 Feb 2026, hitting its lower circuit limit as panic selling gripped the stock. The share price plunged by 4.92%, closing at ₹33.80, marking the maximum permissible daily loss and reflecting intense selling pressure amid subdued investor participation.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>b2afea3994f815a935cb2e393429c3c9</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:42:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wipro Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Price Decline and Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/wipro-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-price-decline-and-market-volatility-3835348</link><description>Wipro Ltd. has experienced a notable 13.7% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock hitting a fresh 52-week low of ₹218.5. This surge in open interest, coupled with declining prices and volume patterns, suggests a complex interplay of investor positioning and potential directional bets in the large-cap IT software sector.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>4234745f62fccc132776142b385a1e3a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:42:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ratnamani Metals &amp; Tubes Ltd Surges 20% to Hit Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ratnamani-metals-tubes-ltd-surges-20-to-hit-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3835349</link><description>Ratnamani Metals &amp; Tubes Ltd witnessed a remarkable surge on 12 Feb 2026, hitting its upper circuit limit of 20% to close at ₹2,335.60. This sharp rally was driven by intense buying interest, resulting in a significant intraday price range and a substantial increase in trading volumes, signalling renewed investor confidence after a prolonged downtrend.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>cd14cec0521082c920efeb2c7d932f9b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:42:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lexus Granito (India) Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lexus-granito-india-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3835341</link><description>Shares of Lexus Granito (India) Ltd plunged to their lower circuit limit on 12 Feb 2026, reflecting intense selling pressure and panic among investors. The stock closed at ₹33.57, down 4.41% intraday and registering a maximum daily loss of 3.87%, significantly underperforming its sector and the broader market indices.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>d42fa572d6c0625e2bb6dd8b4512c2f1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:42:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Biocon Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/biocon-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3835344</link><description>Biocon Ltd., a key player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, has witnessed a notable 11.4% surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a modest decline in the stock price, the increase in OI alongside rising volumes suggests evolving directional bets and a complex interplay of bullish and bearish sentiments among traders.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>6e3c76fb181e8fc203f76d9c8c96eded</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:42:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:42:58 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>