<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:15:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Solarium Green falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-solarium-green-fallingrising-3759231</link><description>On 15 Dec, Solarium Green Energy Ltd's stock price fell by 3.07% to close at ₹234.00, continuing a sustained downward trajectory that has seen the share lose over 21% in the past eight days amid weakening investor participation and underperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d62897ea7571915e864a6ce4c178308c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vikram Aroma falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vikram-aroma-fallingrising-3759230</link><description>On 15-Dec, Vikram Aroma Ltd’s stock price surged by 4.4% to close at ₹74.98, marking a notable rebound after a period of volatility and weak financial performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>369401905d60721ce2488927a6a36824</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Unimech Aero. falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-unimech-aero-fallingrising-3759229</link><description>On 15 Dec, Unimech Aerospace and Manufacturing Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, falling by 1.19% to close at ₹935.85. This drop follows a recent trend reversal after two days of gains, reflecting ongoing challenges in the stock’s performance relative to broader market benchmarks and technical indicators.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>11c7925b27fc75dd3e28fa911cbe0cc8</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Transrail Light falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-transrail-light-fallingrising-3759228</link><description>On 15-Dec, Transrail Lighting Ltd’s stock price rose by 3.48% to ₹604, reflecting a combination of robust financial performance and increased investor participation that has driven the share price higher over recent sessions.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4716ee4bc03c219e036eaa170c0a7024</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Unilex Colour &amp;C falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-unilex-colour-c-fallingrising-3759227</link><description>On 15-Dec, Unilex Colour &amp; Chemical Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 6.76% to close at ₹34.50. This downturn reflects a combination of underwhelming recent returns, weak technical indicators, and diminishing investor participation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2571f56140cf10911c2ecd6c8ab659bc</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Dindigul Farm falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-dindigul-farm-fallingrising-3759226</link><description>On 15-Dec, Dindigul Farm Product Ltd’s stock price fell sharply to ₹15.20, marking a 5.0% decline on the day and hitting a new 52-week and all-time low. This drop continues a sustained downward trajectory that has seen the stock underperform both its sector and the broader market benchmarks over multiple timeframes.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>27f6b2c92db445c5cae636a2b0c10dfa</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is GP Eco Solutions falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gp-eco-solutions-fallingrising-3759225</link><description>On 15-Dec, GP Eco Solutions India Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.83% to close at ₹433.70. This drop comes amid a backdrop of strong year-to-date performance but recent short-term underperformance relative to benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>959dc015f9667f506dbfbd3297040e1d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Kronox Lab falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-kronox-lab-fallingrising-3759224</link><description>On 15-Dec, Kronox Lab Sciences Ltd witnessed a notable uptick in its share price, rising by 2.46% to close at ₹143.80. This increase comes after a three-day consecutive gain, reflecting a short-term positive momentum despite the company’s challenging long-term performance metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>cce734fd6aecb6f3ce5ff8fe8abc2678</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vibhor Steel falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vibhor-steel-fallingrising-3759223</link><description>On 15 Dec, Vibhor Steel Tubes Ltd witnessed a notable intraday price increase of 5.97%, closing at ₹134.10, reflecting a significant rebound despite the stock's challenging year-to-date and one-year performance metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2c588343b2af75cb9b5017ed7c19f7e7</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Exicom Tele-Sys. falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-exicom-tele-sys-fallingrising-3759222</link><description>On 15-Dec, Exicom Tele-Systems Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 2.38% to ₹113.90 by 09:20 PM, reflecting a short-term positive momentum despite persistent long-term financial difficulties.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5fb81d338c86b91bb1cf68da45ad798f</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Digidrive Dist. falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-digidrive-dist-fallingrising-3759221</link><description>On 15-Dec, Digidrive Distributors Ltd witnessed a notable uptick in its share price, rising by 3.29% to close at ₹27.62. This gain comes despite the stock's challenging year-to-date and one-year performance, reflecting a short-term positive momentum amid broader market headwinds.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c85e31e506becdfc27136762e90a0143</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Australian Prem falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-australian-prem-fallingrising-3759220</link><description>On 15-Dec, Australian Premium Solar (India) Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.21% to close at ₹377.90. This drop reflects a combination of underwhelming market performance, subdued investor participation, and a disconnect between strong operational results and market valuation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>125afb2c6c5945a5bf98fb278d79211b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Maitreya Medica. falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-maitreya-medica-fallingrising-3759219</link><description>As of 15 Dec, Maitreya Medicare Ltd’s stock price has fallen sharply, reflecting a combination of deteriorating financial results, weak investor participation, and underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>95238d4c3516b17e5fd0a9cba42ef830</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is ESAF Small Fin falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-esaf-small-fin-fallingrising-3759218</link><description>On 15-Dec, ESAF Small Finance Bank Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 3.89% to close at ₹26.70. This increase comes despite the bank's ongoing financial challenges and underperformance relative to broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c468e0262fccf0187d9afb327cdb5d47</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is C P S Shapers falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-c-p-s-shapers-fallingrising-3759217</link><description>On 15 Dec, C P S Shapers Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 5.0% to ₹944.70 by 09:18 PM. This upward movement reflects a continuation of the stock’s robust performance over the past year, significantly outpacing benchmark indices and demonstrating strong technical positioning despite some signs of waning investor participation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7ffeab9f557c199fd491510a0f882e18</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is R R Kabel falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-r-r-kabel-fallingrising-3759216</link><description>On 15-Dec, R R Kabel Ltd's stock price rose by 2.34% to ₹1,456.00, reflecting growing investor confidence driven by robust financial performance and positive market momentum.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c3915889a96f71a738034ab2639af383</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Aeroflex falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-aeroflex-fallingrising-3759215</link><description>On 15 Dec, Aeroflex Industries Ltd witnessed a notable share price increase of 4.12%, closing at ₹183.20. This rise comes despite the company’s challenging long-term performance and valuation concerns, reflecting a complex interplay of short-term market dynamics and underlying fundamentals.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8f8087b1280e4f709f55f951b90f5555</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is TransIndia Real falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-transindia-real-fallingrising-3759214</link><description>On 15-Dec, TransIndia Real Estate Ltd’s stock price rose by 4.43% to ₹28.98, marking a notable short-term rally amid persistent long-term fundamental weaknesses and underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c02fde0f71b0d2c8728a339c3718499c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Krishca Strapp. falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-krishca-strapp-fallingrising-3759213</link><description>As of 15 Dec, Krishca Strapping Solutions Ltd’s stock price has fallen sharply, continuing a trend of significant underperformance relative to the broader market and its sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>05192d2127d7a7663c3f1a6b4de08ca1</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Aarti Pharma falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-aarti-pharma-fallingrising-3759212</link><description>On 15 Dec, Aarti Pharmalabs Ltd saw its share price rise by 2.7% to ₹760.85, reflecting a notable outperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices despite recent financial challenges and declining promoter confidence.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4866a4c5bf456aebb97a4a34233f440a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:15:32 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>