<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:01:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Sensex and Nifty Edge Higher as Midcaps Lead Market Rally; FMCG Sector Faces Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-and-nifty-edge-higher-as-midcaps-lead-market-rally-fmcg-sector-faces-pressure-3778505</link><description>Indian equity markets opened flat on 2 January 2026 but gradually gained momentum, with the Sensex rising 0.21% to trade at 85,365.61 and the Nifty following suit. Midcap stocks led the advance, supported by broad sectoral participation, while the FMCG sector lagged amid profit-taking. Market breadth remained healthy, and foreign institutional investors showed cautious buying, signalling a positive start to the new year.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>3d6c2a37169f5506aabf1782cce22d9c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Max Healthcare Institute Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amidst Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/max-healthcare-institute-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amidst-mixed-market-signals-3778501</link><description>Max Healthcare Institute Ltd, a prominent player in the hospital sector and a constituent of the Nifty 50 index, has recently undergone notable changes in its institutional holding patterns and market perception. Despite its large-cap status and inclusion in India’s premier benchmark, the stock faces challenges reflected in its recent downgrade and subdued price performance relative to the broader market.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>3b2a95dde31376fec9562b380e7d656a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HDFC Life Insurance: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hdfc-life-insurance-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-3778502</link><description>HDFC Life Insurance Company Ltd continues to hold its position as a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, underscoring its significance in India’s insurance sector and broader equity markets. Despite recent mixed performance metrics and a cautious rating upgrade, the company’s large-cap status and institutional interest remain pivotal factors influencing investor sentiment and benchmark index dynamics.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>25882dd984cee27bdd3c7c506ff90ad7</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SBI Life Insurance: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sbi-life-insurance-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-3778503</link><description>SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd continues to assert its prominence within the Nifty 50 index, demonstrating robust performance metrics and institutional interest that underscore its pivotal role in India’s insurance sector. Despite a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade to Hold, the stock’s sustained gains and market cap stature reinforce its benchmark significance and investor appeal.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>1beb20037bbe3b6238f9f5730e947d84</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Auto Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-auto-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-3778504</link><description>Bajaj Auto Ltd., a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to demonstrate resilience and steady growth within the Indian automobile sector. Despite a slight dip in its latest trading session, the company’s sustained gains over recent months and its strategic market positioning underscore its significance as a benchmark stock for investors and institutions alike.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>06006b7e7c8ac9011a6302a0c97cc7c8</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Finance Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-finance-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-3778500</link><description>Bajaj Finance Ltd, a stalwart in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, continues to command significant attention as a Nifty 50 constituent. Despite recent short-term price pressures, the company’s robust fundamentals, institutional interest, and benchmark status underpin its pivotal role in India’s equity markets.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>e44ade02320f3b8340eb9769942b2d87</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd: Navigating Challenges as a Nifty 50 Constituent</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-motors-passenger-vehicles-ltd-navigating-challenges-as-a-nifty-50-constituent-3778495</link><description>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd, a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to face a complex market environment marked by mixed performance metrics and evolving institutional interest. Despite its large-cap status and significant sector presence, the stock’s recent downgrade and valuation challenges underscore the nuanced dynamics investors must consider amid benchmark index membership.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>5b44ea4eb506175a4b21c34f05b49711</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sun-pharmaceutical-industries-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-3778499</link><description>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd, a stalwart in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, continues to assert its significance as a Nifty 50 constituent. Despite recent market headwinds, the stock’s institutional holding dynamics and benchmark status remain pivotal factors influencing investor sentiment and valuation trajectories.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>fb7f5299432a095242b2635b33fede59</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JSW Steel Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Shifts Amid Market Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jsw-steel-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-shifts-amid-market-dynamics-3778498</link><description>JSW Steel Ltd., a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to demonstrate resilience and strategic significance within the ferrous metals sector. Despite a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade from Buy to Hold, the company’s robust market capitalisation and sustained outperformance relative to the Sensex underscore its pivotal role in India’s benchmark equity index. Institutional investors are closely monitoring shifts in holdings as JSW Steel balances valuation pressures with long-term growth prospects.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>8982751551d7c63ba9470f9b77c9e637</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Ltd Strengthens Position as Nifty 50 Constituent Amid Robust Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mahindra-mahindra-ltd-strengthens-position-as-nifty-50-constituent-amid-robust-performance-3778496</link><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Ltd (M&amp;M), a stalwart in the Indian automobile sector, continues to consolidate its stature within the Nifty 50 index, buoyed by robust institutional holdings and a recent upgrade in its investment grade. The company’s sustained outperformance relative to the benchmark Sensex and its sector peers underscores its growing appeal among investors navigating a dynamic market environment.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>3b88a7bc48af2f10b1103636e94c2a83</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Larsen &amp; Toubro Ltd: Strengthening Its Position as a Nifty 50 Powerhouse Amid Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/larsen-toubro-ltd-strengthening-its-position-as-a-nifty-50-powerhouse-amid-institutional-shifts-3778497</link><description>Larsen &amp; Toubro Ltd. (L&amp;T), a cornerstone of India’s construction sector and a prominent Nifty 50 constituent, continues to demonstrate resilience and growth potential. Recent upgrades in its Mojo Grade to ‘Buy’ from ‘Hold’ alongside sustained institutional buying highlight the company’s strengthening market position and its critical role within the benchmark index.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>c88c8bc8c729f11d78c51c07d496f614</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Finserv Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-finserv-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-mixed-market-signals-3778493</link><description>Bajaj Finserv Ltd, a prominent holding company and a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to command significant attention from investors amid evolving institutional holdings and benchmark dynamics. Despite a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade to 'Hold', the company’s market capitalisation and historical performance underscore its enduring influence within India’s large-cap universe.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>da5efe18f2056f57f602beb3e31dff17</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Enterprises Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amid Mixed Performance and Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-enterprises-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-mixed-performance-and-institutional-shifts-3778491</link><description>Adani Enterprises Ltd, a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to navigate a challenging market environment marked by subdued performance relative to benchmarks and evolving institutional holdings. Despite recent modest gains, the stock’s valuation and rating adjustments underscore the complexities investors face in assessing its future prospects within the diversified sector.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>5678fe27806040928e309d129fd406b0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Ports &amp; SEZ: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-ports-sez-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-3778492</link><description>Adani Ports &amp; Special Economic Zone Ltd (APSEZ), a pivotal constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to demonstrate resilience and strategic importance within India’s transport infrastructure sector. With a market capitalisation exceeding ₹3.42 lakh crore and a recent upgrade in its Mojo Grade from Sell to Hold, the stock’s evolving institutional holding patterns and benchmark status underscore its critical role in portfolio allocations and market sentiment.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>aee21de85c5dfbef9d84491fd6dfd97d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Grasim Industries Ltd Strengthens Position as Key Nifty 50 Constituent Amid Institutional Interest</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/grasim-industries-ltd-strengthens-position-as-key-nifty-50-constituent-amid-institutional-interest-3778490</link><description>Grasim Industries Ltd, a key player in the Cement &amp; Cement Products sector, continues to solidify its stature within the Nifty 50 index, buoyed by robust institutional holdings and a recent upgrade in its investment grade. The company’s sustained outperformance relative to the benchmark Sensex underscores its growing appeal among investors and its critical role in India’s large-cap landscape.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>da586205575aeafa0ecccec92c504f52</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oil &amp; Natural Gas Corporation Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amid Mixed Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/oil-natural-gas-corporation-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-mixed-performance-3778494</link><description>Oil &amp; Natural Gas Corporation Ltd (ONGC), a cornerstone of India’s oil sector and a prominent Nifty 50 constituent, continues to command investor attention amid evolving market conditions. Despite recent downgrades and mixed performance metrics, its benchmark status and institutional holding patterns remain critical factors shaping its market trajectory.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>7b0b45753c0de912bfd5242d54e3128b</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd: Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Dynamics Shape Outlook</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kotak-mahindra-bank-ltd-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-shape-outlook-3778486</link><description>Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd continues to solidify its position as a key player in India’s private banking sector, buoyed by its status as a Nifty 50 constituent. The bank’s recent upgrade to a ‘Buy’ Mojo Grade, coupled with robust market capitalisation and consistent outperformance against the Sensex, underscores growing institutional confidence and highlights the strategic importance of its benchmark index membership.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>99d57055dd2692d65e546e20efdb14bf</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reliance Industries Ltd Strengthens Position as Nifty 50 Heavyweight Amid Robust Institutional Interest</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/reliance-industries-ltd-strengthens-position-as-nifty-50-heavyweight-amid-robust-institutional-interest-3778482</link><description>Reliance Industries Ltd (RIL), a cornerstone of the Indian equity market and a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to demonstrate robust performance and growing institutional confidence. With a recent upgrade to a 'Buy' rating and sustained gains, the oil sector giant is reinforcing its benchmark status, reflecting both its market leadership and strategic importance to investors.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>674da05336d8dce6218bbea7547ef377</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cipla Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amid Shifting Institutional Holdings</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cipla-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-shifting-institutional-holdings-3778487</link><description>Cipla Ltd., a stalwart in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector and a prominent Nifty 50 constituent, continues to face a challenging market environment as it balances its benchmark status with evolving institutional holdings and a nuanced performance record. Despite recent downgrades and subdued returns relative to the broader market, Cipla remains a key player whose movements warrant close attention from investors and market analysts alike.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>57cce60e29f97c387b393c4fe7e933a8</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HDFC Bank Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hdfc-bank-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-3778484</link><description>HDFC Bank Ltd continues to solidify its stature as a cornerstone of the Indian equity market, maintaining its position as a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index. With a market capitalisation exceeding ₹15 lakh crore and a recent Mojo Grade adjustment to 'Buy', the private sector banking giant demonstrates resilience amid evolving institutional holdings and sector dynamics, underscoring its benchmark status and investor appeal.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>9d21243100a6d3572b8927636040ff52</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:01:23 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>