<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:58:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Atlantaa Ltd Q2 FY26: Operating Losses Deepen as Infrastructure Firm Struggles</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/atlantaa-ltd-q2-fy26-operating-losses-deepen-as-infrastructure-firm-struggles-3829008</link><description>Atlantaa Ltd., a micro-cap infrastructure development company, reported a consolidated net loss of ₹20.81 crores for Q2 FY26, marking a sharp deterioration from the ₹1.71 crore loss in the previous quarter. The company, which operates in road construction, highways, bridges, and real estate development, has seen its operating performance collapse with an alarming operating margin of -135.18%, signalling severe operational distress. With a market capitalisation of ₹363 crores and the stock trading at ₹44.41 following a 3.65% decline, investors are grappling with mounting concerns about the company's ability to return to profitability.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>17723061c042b691dac270c67045fc3a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:58:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mold-Tek Packaging Q3 FY26: Profit Decline Amid Volume Pressures</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/mold-tek-packaging-q3-fy26-profit-decline-amid-volume-pressures-3829007</link><description>Mold-Tek Packaging Ltd., India's leading rigid plastic packaging manufacturer with a market capitalisation of ₹1,803 crores, has reported challenging quarterly results for Q3 FY26, with net profit declining 14.60% quarter-on-quarter to ₹14.35 crores. The company's stock, currently trading at ₹546.30, has fallen 38.62% from its 52-week high of ₹890.00, reflecting investor concerns over deteriorating operational metrics and sustained volume pressures across key segments.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>1762880c1525b76178737dc5cd1e2c8d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:58:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>QMS Medical Allied Services Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/qms-medical-allied-services-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3829004</link><description>QMS Medical Allied Services Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>a335dbb62548a40e91e4c25c7841026f</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:58:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trident Texofab Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/trident-texofab-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3829001</link><description>Trident Texofab Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>8d93dff4339ae13eebd9daa7cadb6703</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:58:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>L&amp;T Technology Services Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lt-technology-services-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3829002</link><description>L&amp;T Technology Services Ltd (Stock ID: 1002656) has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action within the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>300538de39a9e39046b6c607dc1b661a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:58:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KIOCL Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kiocl-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3828998</link><description>KIOCL Ltd, a key player in the ferrous metals industry, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term momentum and underlying market sentiment.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>d454654869f0734f9983196aaccdb08e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:58:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Machino Plastics Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/machino-plastics-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3828997</link><description>Machino Plastics Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s near- to medium-term outlook.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>2fd215cfdd37d8bb9df9c41f3be19bef</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:58:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Safari Industries Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/safari-industries-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3828996</link><description>Safari Industries (India) Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>edeb6c3651a987ce5aeb40ce155274f3</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:58:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>La Tim Metal &amp; Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/la-tim-metal-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3829000</link><description>La Tim Metal &amp; Industries Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non-Ferrous Metals sector, has recently formed a Death Cross—a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average—indicating a potential shift towards a bearish trend and signalling long-term weakness in the stock’s price momentum.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>6034457600845c481b7a0cb59b762eb7</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:58:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>India Home Loans Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/india-home-loans-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3828995</link><description>India Home Loans Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about long-term weakness amid already challenging market conditions for the housing finance sector.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>db28f23cb19d5123764f6284c1db2d3c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:58:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Olympic Cards Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/olympic-cards-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3829003</link><description>Olympic Cards Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-DMA. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, offering investors a fresh perspective on the stock’s future trajectory amid its current market challenges.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>46df40bb144151fd53a94bf5dfa1b069</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:58:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Mixed Results Mark Dec-2025 with Mid Caps Leading Profit Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-mixed-results-mark-dec-2025-with-mid-caps-leading-profit-growth-3828994</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has unfolded with a nuanced picture across Indian equities, as 1,813 companies declared results reflecting a modest improvement in profitability and sales growth. While mid-cap stocks led the charge with a 52.0% positive result ratio, large caps lagged behind at 39.0%, underscoring divergent sectoral and market cap dynamics amid evolving macroeconomic conditions.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>fdbc5fbf8f51c3cea642ed22a02b95f1</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:58:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aditya Birla Capital Ltd Delivers Multibagger Returns Amid Strong Fundamentals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aditya-birla-capital-ltd-delivers-multibagger-returns-amid-strong-fundamentals-3828999</link><description>Aditya Birla Capital Ltd has emerged as a standout performer in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, delivering multibagger returns exceeding 100% over the past year. This remarkable growth significantly outpaces the broader market, with the stock appreciating 108.26% compared to the Sensex’s modest 7.97% gain. Investors and analysts alike are closely examining the drivers behind this surge and assessing the sustainability of its momentum amid evolving market conditions.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>2311c2c7ecfa64996237686e8e567dcb</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:58:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ceigall India Q3 FY26: Revenue Surge Masks Margin Erosion Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/ceigall-india-q3-fy26-revenue-surge-masks-margin-erosion-concerns-3828992</link><description>Ceigall India Ltd., a Punjab-based construction company with a market capitalisation of ₹5,162 crores, reported consolidated net profit of ₹74.11 crores for Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), representing a robust sequential growth of 27.80% from ₹57.99 crores in Q2 FY26. However, year-on-year growth remained anaemic at just 1.24%, raising questions about the sustainability of the company's earnings trajectory. The stock declined 2.81% to ₹284.10 following the results announcement, as investors digested mixed signals from the quarterly performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1a5a91c930a88553a4b85cb3486fb24b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:58:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Electronics Mart India Q3 FY26: Profit Surge Masks Margin Pressures and Mounting Debt Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/electronics-mart-india-q3-fy26-profit-surge-masks-margin-pressures-and-mounting-debt-concerns-3828991</link><description>Electronics Mart India Ltd., one of India's leading multi-brand electronics retailers with a market capitalisation of ₹3,651 crores, posted a consolidated net profit of ₹29.65 crores for Q3 FY26, marking an impressive 83.71% quarter-on-quarter surge from ₹16.14 crores in Q2 FY26. However, the year-on-year comparison reveals a concerning 11.49% decline from ₹33.50 crores in Q3 FY25, highlighting the company's struggle to match prior-year profitability levels despite strong sequential recovery.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2dafbb929d941e67e54fa3b7755c5949</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:58:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Northern Spirits Q3 FY26: Margin Compression Clouds Revenue Growth Story</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/northern-spirits-q3-fy26-margin-compression-clouds-revenue-growth-story-3828990</link><description>Northern Spirits Limited, a pan-India distributor of imported wines, liquors, and beverages, reported a net profit of ₹7.18 crores for Q3 FY26, representing a sequential decline of 5.40% from the previous quarter's ₹7.59 crores. Despite posting healthy year-on-year revenue growth of 12.89%, the company's profitability metrics reveal concerning margin erosion that has weighed on investor sentiment. The stock, currently trading at ₹135.25, has declined 24.02% over the past year and remains in a confirmed bearish technical trend.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a4119562b2adf008051f64e59afacabf</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:58:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fredun Pharmaceuticals Q3 FY26: Margin Expansion Drives Stellar Profit Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/fredun-pharmaceuticals-q3-fy26-margin-expansion-drives-stellar-profit-growth-3828989</link><description>Fredun Pharmaceuticals Ltd., a Mumbai-based pharmaceutical formulations manufacturer, delivered an impressive third-quarter performance for FY2026, posting net profit of ₹10.48 crores—an 11.13% sequential improvement and the highest quarterly profit in the company's recent history. The ₹922-crore market cap company demonstrated robust operational efficiency, with operating margins expanding to 16.47% from 15.56% in the previous quarter, signalling strengthening pricing power and cost management discipline.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>19c47244f670bc0acd1f5b6e2a724783</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:58:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Electricals Q3 FY26: Steep Losses Mount as Margins Collapse</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/bajaj-electricals-q3-fy26-steep-losses-mount-as-margins-collapse-3828988</link><description>Bajaj Electricals Ltd., a prominent player in India's electronics and appliances sector, reported a consolidated net loss of ₹34.10 crores for Q3 FY26, marking a dramatic reversal from the ₹9.86 crores profit recorded in the previous quarter. The steep decline of 445.84% quarter-on-quarter and a staggering 202.22% year-on-year deterioration has sent alarm bells ringing amongst investors, with the stock trading at ₹408.95 and down 43.77% over the past year.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ba2b7ee4fbd215ad0df1656a9828136d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:58:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kaira Can Q3 FY26: Profit Turns Negative as Tax Anomaly and Margin Pressure Bite</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/kaira-can-q3-fy26-profit-turns-negative-as-tax-anomaly-and-margin-pressure-bite-3828987</link><description>Kaira Can Company Ltd., a micro-cap packaging manufacturer with a market capitalisation of ₹127.00 crores, reported a troubling Q3 FY26 performance, slipping into negative profitability territory for the first time in recent quarters. The company posted a net loss of ₹0.14 crores for the quarter ended December 2025, a sharp reversal from the ₹0.40 crores profit in Q2 FY26 and the ₹0.64 crores profit in the corresponding quarter last year. The stock reacted positively on February 9, 2026, gaining 5.00% to close at ₹1,448.00, though this appears disconnected from the underlying quarterly fundamentals.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d4531fa77c720bdc36d84e329a5afe02</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:58:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cholamandalam Financial Holdings Q3 FY26: Profit Growth Slows Amid Rising Costs and Margin Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/cholamandalam-financial-holdings-q3-fy26-profit-growth-slows-amid-rising-costs-and-margin-pressure-3828986</link><description>Cholamandalam Financial Holdings Ltd., the Chennai-based non-banking financial company and part of the diversified Murugappa Group, reported a consolidated net profit of ₹549.92 crores for Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), marking a decline of 4.94% quarter-on-quarter and a modest growth of 4.64% year-on-year. With a market capitalisation of ₹31,985 crores, the mid-cap NBFC faces mounting challenges as rising employee costs and interest expenses weigh on profitability despite steady revenue growth.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ac31313dfbc7a7f32a70f09cc551937d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:58:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:58:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>