<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:24:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Maruti Suzuki India Ltd is Rated Buy</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/maruti-suzuki-india-ltd-is-rated-buy-3772231</link><description>Maruti Suzuki India Ltd is rated Buy by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 22 December 2025. While the rating was revised on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 28 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market standing.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6766284f331af37a1b27917af3bbd158</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:24:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Medplus Health Services Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/medplus-health-services-ltd-is-rated-hold-3772230</link><description>Medplus Health Services Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 22 December 2025. While the rating change occurred on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 28 December 2025, providing investors with the most up-to-date view of the stock’s fundamentals, returns, and technical outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e4de7a984e673ab7f98eb48d0e4ea901</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:24:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sbi-life-insurance-company-ltd-is-rated-hold-3772229</link><description>SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 30 July 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 28 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c4e7babb27874a32b945b30122e321ba</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:24:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Overseas Bank is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/indian-overseas-bank-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3772227</link><description>Indian Overseas Bank is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 04 Aug 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 28 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the bank's performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>db13e21155b09ce02c2a060b1a6a8ed3</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:24:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Embassy Office Parks REIT is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/embassy-office-parks-reit-is-rated-sell-3772228</link><description>Embassy Office Parks REIT is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 02 Sep 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock's current position as of 28 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of its fundamentals, returns, and overall outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ee7f045edec722b23752df8b57f03f28</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:24:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Oil Corporation Ltd is Rated Strong Buy</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/indian-oil-corporation-ltd-is-rated-strong-buy-3772222</link><description>Indian Oil Corporation Ltd is rated Strong Buy by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 22 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 28 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b3c031c4e446c58ca6e93e8f4d0a5f68</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:24:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jeena Sikho Lifecare Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/jeena-sikho-lifecare-ltd-is-rated-sell-3772226</link><description>Jeena Sikho Lifecare Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 22 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 28 December 2025, providing investors with the most up-to-date view of the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f07413e8613067aa86ca056d9d2baa9e</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:24:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Union Bank of India is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/union-bank-of-india-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3772224</link><description>Union Bank of India is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 04 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 28 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of its fundamentals, returns, and market performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9e8626e227db819b1cad14b1a90c93f0</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:24:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PNGS Gargi Fashion Jewellery Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/pngs-gargi-fashion-jewellery-ltd-is-rated-hold-3772225</link><description>PNGS Gargi Fashion Jewellery Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 25 Nov 2025. While the rating was revised on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 28 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c58c8415159cb91331dcda62ebdc0939</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:24:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nexus Select Trust is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/nexus-select-trust-is-rated-sell-3772223</link><description>Nexus Select Trust is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 22 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 28 December 2025, providing investors with the most up-to-date view of its performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>938b70e5b4c8306ae11a65a5ba7ddfce</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:24:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/rail-vikas-nigam-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3772221</link><description>Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 12 Aug 2025, reflecting a shift from the previous 'Sell' grade. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here represent the stock's current position as of 28 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company's performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>71b89a467908900c8daa790483b24ba4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:24:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BSE Ltd is Rated Strong Buy</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/bse-ltd-is-rated-strong-buy-3772220</link><description>BSE Ltd is rated Strong Buy by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 22 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 28 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3e79879b58a23810dc34f6762193926a</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:24:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Redington Ltd is Rated Buy</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/redington-ltd-is-rated-buy-3772217</link><description>Redington Ltd is rated 'Buy' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 16 Dec 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock’s current position as of 28 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>bf760c15f2eb543a16e886795371b367</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:24:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Energy Solutions Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/adani-energy-solutions-ltd-is-rated-sell-3772219</link><description>Adani Energy Solutions Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 07 Oct 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 28 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market standing.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f6530cb0b1120b1d6c3ee03b8905ecb2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:24:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Finance Ltd is Rated Buy</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/bajaj-finance-ltd-is-rated-buy-3772215</link><description>Bajaj Finance Ltd is rated 'Buy' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 17 Mar 2025. While the rating was revised on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 28 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of its fundamentals, returns, and market standing.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3b137eed9f13789b3a3de74547f605e4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:24:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nalwa Sons Investments Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/nalwa-sons-investments-ltd-is-rated-sell-3772218</link><description>Nalwa Sons Investments Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 24 December 2025. While the rating change occurred on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 28 December 2025, providing investors with the most up-to-date insight into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d6aeb1f512ffeb7b55a284a47741219e</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:24:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mindspace Business Parks REIT is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/mindspace-business-parks-reit-is-rated-hold-3772216</link><description>Mindspace Business Parks REIT is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 15 Sep 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 28 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of its fundamentals, returns, and market standing.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6d841d0e223414cff1cad51d420e6c50</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:24:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Godrej Consumer Products Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/godrej-consumer-products-ltd-is-rated-sell-3772210</link><description>Godrej Consumer Products Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 23 September 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 28 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into the company's performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8ba6cecb0862f3d30d7c3503ec233eed</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:24:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hero MotoCorp Ltd. is Rated Buy</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/hero-motocorp-ltd-is-rated-buy-3772213</link><description>Hero MotoCorp Ltd. is rated 'Buy' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 16 December 2025. While the rating change occurred on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 28 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>fa656dc595986913779d0dd62e485021</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:24:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Noida Toll Bridge Company Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/noida-toll-bridge-company-ltd-is-rated-sell-3772212</link><description>Noida Toll Bridge Company Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 22 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 28 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0f7dd2391bcbef2af26a5d6faa997ab9</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:24:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:24:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>