<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:24:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Italian Edibles Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-italian-edibles-ltd-fallingrising-3861828</link><description>On 27-Feb, Italian Edibles Ltd witnessed a significant price surge, closing at ₹44.55, marking a 10.0% increase and establishing a new 52-week high. This sharp rise reflects the stock’s robust performance relative to both its sector and broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>70cf9df2c80af2ca933cb8baf80175ae</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:24:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Maiden Forgings Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-maiden-forgings-ltd-fallingrising-3861827</link><description>On 27-Feb, Maiden Forgings Ltd recorded a modest rise in its share price, climbing 0.46% to ₹86.95 by 9:15 PM. This increase follows a two-day decline and reflects a nuanced market response amid broader sector and benchmark movements.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f26f8f708e19f2400cc7a0dc497b39ea</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:24:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ujjivan Small Finance Bank Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ujjivan-small-finance-bank-ltd-fallingrising-3861826</link><description>On 27-Feb, Ujjivan Small Finance Bank Ltd’s stock price fell sharply by 5.62% to close at ₹58.09, marking a notable reversal after two consecutive days of gains. This decline comes amid a broader context of strong long-term performance but short-term underperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9b5a508ce48fadd27cb9d341ba8e8287</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:24:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vinny Overseas Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vinny-overseas-ltd-fallingrising-3861825</link><description>On 27-Feb, Vinny Overseas Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, falling by 1.82% to close at ₹1.08. This movement reflects a continuation of a broader downtrend, with the stock underperforming both its sector and benchmark indices over multiple time frames.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0ac3950f80e4960948025de93b663fe2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:24:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ashapuri Gold Ornament Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ashapuri-gold-ornament-ltd-fallingrising-3861824</link><description>On 27-Feb, Ashapuri Gold Ornament Ltd recorded a notable intraday price increase of 5.57%, rising by ₹0.26 to close at ₹4.93. This gain marks a reversal after six consecutive days of decline, yet the stock remains entrenched in a broader downtrend when compared to market benchmarks and its own historical performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>58f37b0f01de1d2d17d15d5c9bf35e69</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:24:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Rajnandini Metal Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-rajnandini-metal-ltd-fallingrising-3861823</link><description>As of 27-Feb, Rajnandini Metal Ltd’s stock price has continued its downward trajectory, closing at ₹3.83 with a decline of 0.78% on the day. This fall reflects a broader pattern of underperformance driven by weak financial metrics and persistent operational challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9318f6d94b1b7340cb511ad39eb0415c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:24:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-orissa-bengal-carrier-ltd-fallingrising-3861822</link><description>On 27-Feb, Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd’s stock price rose by 5.44% to ₹58.00, marking a notable short-term gain despite ongoing fundamental challenges and declining profitability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f087b38c31333dd2bc17b711b307670c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:24:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Archidply Decor Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-archidply-decor-ltd-fallingrising-3861821</link><description>On 27-Feb, Archidply Decor Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 4.92% to close at ₹69.13. This drop reflects a broader pattern of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and sector peers, driven by weak financial metrics and subdued investor interest.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>caf5903c02dcd31f117b509ea927e70a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:24:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ritco Logistics Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ritco-logistics-ltd-fallingrising-3861820</link><description>As of 27-Feb, Ritco Logistics Ltd’s stock price has declined by 1.08% to ₹220.10, continuing a downward trend influenced by debt servicing challenges, underwhelming recent performance, and a significant divergence from broader market gains.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>be18c726aeb40438fd5a8a2aab85a0b4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:24:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Computer Age Management Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-computer-age-management-services-ltd-fallingrising-3861819</link><description>On 27-Feb, Computer Age Management Services Ltd (CAMS) experienced a notable decline in its share price, falling by 4.3% to close at ₹678.00. This drop reflects a continuation of recent underperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>de347ae57e84e24a101055ca6e3fdbb0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:24:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Crystal Business System Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-crystal-business-system-ltd-fallingrising-3861818</link><description>On 27-Feb, Crystal Business System Ltd’s stock price fell by 4.95% to ₹1.73, marking a new 52-week low of ₹1.56 during the trading session. This decline reflects ongoing challenges faced by the company, including weak financial metrics, consistent underperformance relative to benchmarks, and deteriorating profitability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>262071c3d5dceea469edc5bbb954b937</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:24:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is The Indian Wood Products Company Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-the-indian-wood-products-company-ltd-fallingrising-3861817</link><description>On 27-Feb, The Indian Wood Products Company Ltd experienced a notable intraday price surge of 7.93%, reversing a four-day decline and outperforming its sector by 8.59%, despite underlying long-term fundamental challenges and subdued profitability trends.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7ec8f3fa0cca579ec9c3dbd4d371c852</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:24:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Welspun Enterprises Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-welspun-enterprises-ltd-fallingrising-3861816</link><description>On 27-Feb, Welspun Enterprises Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, falling by 1.45% to close at ₹484.70. This drop comes amid a backdrop of mixed financial performance indicators and recent negative quarterly results, despite the company’s strong long-term growth trajectory and rising promoter confidence.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8e78f569c685ffcd707084b41c9a9856</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:24:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Rishi Techtex Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-rishi-techtex-ltd-fallingrising-3861815</link><description>On 27-Feb, Rishi Techtex Ltd’s stock price fell sharply by 3.78% to close at ₹40.00, marking a continuation of recent downward momentum and underperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b08eefb4594420158709ac32f81b5173</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:24:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Enkei Wheels India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-enkei-wheels-india-ltd-fallingrising-3861814</link><description>On 27-Feb, Enkei Wheels India Ltd saw its share price rise by 0.51% to close at ₹460.00, continuing a short-term upward trend despite mixed longer-term returns and subdued investor participation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>cd399154bcff0f20b1e80d2b26106b25</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:24:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vikram Kamats Hospitality Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vikram-kamats-hospitality-ltd-fallingrising-3861813</link><description>On 27-Feb, Vikram Kamats Hospitality Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, closing at ₹55.78, down ₹1.21 or 2.12% from the previous session. This drop reflects a continuation of recent negative momentum driven by weak financial performance and underwhelming market returns compared to benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1da3a8d72f177254e862627fe402161c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:24:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Enbee Trade &amp; Finance Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-enbee-trade-finance-ltd-fallingrising-3861812</link><description>On 27-Feb, Enbee Trade &amp; Finance Ltd witnessed a significant price rise, climbing 18.6% to ₹0.51, driven by robust trading volumes, sustained gains, and notable outperformance against both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e23c595a77955db320a708d0940c8fb0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:24:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Dhanuka Agritech Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-dhanuka-agritech-ltd-fallingrising-3861811</link><description>On 27-Feb, Dhanuka Agritech Ltd’s stock price fell sharply, closing at ₹1,019.70, down ₹36.00 or 3.41%, marking a continuation of a downward trend that has seen the share price hit a new 52-week low.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1f3ffd27b5e8bcec831129c080d8153b</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:24:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Kama Holdings Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-kama-holdings-ltd-fallingrising-3861810</link><description>As of 27-Feb, Kama Holdings Ltd’s stock price has fallen by 1.65% to ₹2,636.50, continuing a downward trend over the past week despite the company’s robust long-term financial performance and positive quarterly results.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2c466cca9ead704e9e4049f692666737</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:24:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is The Bombay Burmah Trading Corporation Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-the-bombay-burmah-trading-corporation-ltd-fallingrising-3861809</link><description>On 27-Feb, The Bombay Burmah Trading Corporation Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.12% to close at ₹1,690.10. This drop reflects a continuation of recent negative momentum, driven by a combination of underwhelming financial performance and market sentiment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c229f3a47b91857e5bcce748dd7eda6a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:24:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 21:24:27 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>