<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:21:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Ken Enterprises Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ken-enterprises-ltd-fallingrising-3799260</link><description>As of 21-Jan, Ken Enterprises Ltd has experienced a notable decline in its share price, reflecting broader challenges in its market performance and investor engagement despite marginal outperformance relative to its sector today.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>8a2f8d36a32b48eb8c8b84d4181d8aee</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:21:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Chamunda Electrical Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-chamunda-electrical-ltd-fallingrising-3799259</link><description>As of 21-Jan, Chamunda Electrical Ltd’s stock price has fallen by 3.23% to ₹46.45, reflecting a broader trend of underperformance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>85b84ba8326dc2d3d661fc618f35adae</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:21:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Mamata Machinery Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-mamata-machinery-ltd-fallingrising-3799258</link><description>As of 21-Jan, Mamata Machinery Ltd’s stock price has fallen sharply, reflecting a combination of disappointing quarterly financial results and sustained underperformance relative to broader market benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>a822e8e3e5c24b75c8f34599ca05f147</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:21:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is EMA Partners India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ema-partners-india-ltd-fallingrising-3799256</link><description>On 21-Jan, EMA Partners India Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 5.88% to close at ₹83.30. This drop reflects a broader trend of underperformance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices, compounded by weakening investor participation and technical indicators signalling bearish momentum.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>2c90c581dc1088df284ad690d370be51</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:21:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Standard Glass Lining Technology Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-standard-glass-lining-technology-ltd-fallingrising-3799257</link><description>On 21-Jan, Standard Engineering Technology Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, hitting a new 52-week and all-time low of ₹121.1. The stock has been under pressure for several sessions, reflecting a broader trend of underperformance relative to the benchmark indices and its sector peers.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>90fee71c18848d8d742031cd7952f8cb</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:21:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Suraksha Diagnostic Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-suraksha-diagnostic-ltd-fallingrising-3799255</link><description>On 21-Jan, Suraksha Diagnostic Ltd’s stock price rose by 4.47% to ₹269.00, marking a notable recovery after five consecutive days of decline. This upward movement reflects a combination of short-term technical factors and underlying fundamental strengths that have supported investor confidence despite the stock’s longer-term challenges.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>1fd2d426060fd9360f0d047dc01fa5cf</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:21:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Afcons Infrastructure Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-afcons-infrastructure-ltd-fallingrising-3799254</link><description>On 21-Jan, Afcons Infrastructure Ltd’s stock price fell sharply, continuing a downward trend driven by weak financial performance, poor debt servicing ability, and significant promoter share pledging, resulting in sustained investor caution and selling pressure.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>c2b5e0456634ebe06190cbfaad7a1c28</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:21:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Gajanand International Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gajanand-international-ltd-fallingrising-3799253</link><description>On 21-Jan, Gajanand International Ltd’s stock price fell sharply to ₹9.15, marking a new 52-week and all-time low as the share declined by 9.85% during the trading session, reflecting sustained weakness and underperformance relative to broader market benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>d0fadae8d09655d6c3c0ab7e26e05d38</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:21:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Quest Laboratories Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-quest-laboratories-ltd-fallingrising-3799252</link><description>On 21-Jan, Quest Laboratories Ltd saw its share price rise by 6.32% to ₹103.50, reflecting a notable intraday recovery despite a challenging recent performance record and mixed financial indicators.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>570374ad90233a4b894491cdf17cb373</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:21:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Go Digit General Insurance Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-go-digit-general-insurance-ltd-fallingrising-3799251</link><description>On 21-Jan, Go Digit General Insurance Ltd’s stock price declined by 0.77% to ₹320.70, continuing a five-day losing streak amid valuation pressures despite robust long-term growth and strong quarterly results.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>3fb79841a8d99d3e2b94e942fb63232a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:21:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shipping Corporation of India Land &amp; Assets Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shipping-corporation-of-india-land-assets-ltd-fallingrising-3799250</link><description>As of 21-Jan, Shipping Corporation of India Land &amp; Assets Ltd has seen its share price fall by 2.52% to ₹44.06, continuing a downward trend driven by poor financial performance and sustained underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>5818c30528b9a6027289ad451858b58b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:21:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Entero Healthcare Solutions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-entero-healthcare-solutions-ltd-fallingrising-3799249</link><description>On 21-Jan, Entero Healthcare Solutions Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 3.35% to close at ₹1,106.00. This drop comes despite the company’s strong underlying fundamentals and recent positive quarterly results, reflecting a complex interplay of short-term market dynamics and investor sentiment.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>7416367e8d6997cee181901da6968710</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:21:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Nova Agritech Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-nova-agritech-ltd-fallingrising-3799248</link><description>On 21-Jan, Nova Agritech Ltd’s stock price fell to ₹34.21, down 1.5% as the company hit a new 52-week and all-time low of ₹33.16, reflecting ongoing challenges in profitability and sustained underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>0e6f5cf2b1fee9995b0ba33504d24116</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:21:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is GHCL Textiles Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ghcl-textiles-ltd-fallingrising-3799247</link><description>As of 21-Jan, GHCL Textiles Ltd's stock price has fallen to ₹69.25, reflecting a 2.13% decline on the day and continuing a downward trend over recent weeks. This decline is underpinned by a combination of disappointing returns relative to benchmarks, flat recent financial results, and technical indicators signalling weakness.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>058418d45b4e962ba17ae3c079052358</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:21:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vinyas Innovative Technologies Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vinyas-innovative-technologies-ltd-fallingrising-3799246</link><description>On 21-Jan, Vinyas Innovative Technologies Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, falling by 1.63% to close at ₹1,089.00. This drop reflects a broader short-term weakness despite the stock's strong one-year performance relative to the Sensex.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>bc6d15a5609e61920554081f724d7811</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:21:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-nuvama-wealth-management-ltd-fallingrising-3799245</link><description>On 21-Jan, Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 3.95% to close at ₹1,365.35. This drop comes amid a broader short-term underperformance relative to the market and sector benchmarks, despite the company’s robust long-term fundamentals and market-beating returns over the past year.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>7f8951e5a64cff50e38dbf08f337834c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:21:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is BEML Land Assets Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-beml-land-assets-ltd-fallingrising-3799244</link><description>As of 21-Jan, BEML Land Assets Ltd’s stock price has fallen sharply, reflecting persistent underperformance against benchmarks and deteriorating fundamental indicators that have weighed heavily on investor sentiment.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>c9b822bf02c9468050a68031551d6844</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:21:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Harsha Engineers International Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-harsha-engineers-international-ltd-fallingrising-3799243</link><description>As of 21-Jan, Harsha Engineers International Ltd’s stock price has fallen sharply, reflecting a combination of disappointing financial results, sustained underperformance relative to benchmarks, and negative market sentiment.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>2dd525d297bbafc2a727b2f77497be98</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:21:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Dollex Agrotech Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-dollex-agrotech-ltd-fallingrising-3799242</link><description>As of 21-Jan, Dollex Agrotech Ltd’s stock price has fallen sharply, reflecting a combination of deteriorating quarterly financial performance, high leverage, and sustained underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>1a9371a6e584d2c51becd943aeade0a2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:21:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is AGS Transact Technologies Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ags-transact-technologies-ltd-fallingrising-3799241</link><description>On 21-Jan, AGS Transact Technologies Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, closing at ₹3.70, down 4.15% for the day and hitting a new 52-week and all-time low of ₹3.67. This drop reflects a continuation of a downward trend driven by deteriorating financial performance, weak fundamentals, and waning investor confidence.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>ec111938e9e458f788e628bf30f68b0c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:21:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:21:06 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>