<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:44:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Has Naperol Investments Ltd declared dividend?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/has-naperol-investments-ltd-declared-dividend-3859383</link><description>Naperol Investments Ltd has declared a 30% dividend, with an ex-date of March 4, 2026. However, the company has experienced significant losses in total returns across various periods, indicating a challenging financial environment.
Time: Feb 26 2026 11:30 PM IST</description><guid>ac2a6e3cd0f616dbebe833cf5a9ab724</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:44:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Has Eighty Jewellers Ltd declared dividend?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/has-eighty-jewellers-ltd-declared-dividend-3859382</link><description>Eighty Jewellers Ltd has declared a 1% dividend, with an ex-date of March 6, 2026. However, total returns over various periods have been largely negative, indicating poor performance despite the dividend announcement.
Time: Feb 26 2026 11:30 PM IST</description><guid>59c8400223515fb22041b99578cd094d</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:44:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When is the next results date for Remedium Lifecare Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-remedium-lifecare-ltd-3859379</link><description>The next results date for Remedium Lifecare Ltd is March 9, 2026.
Time: Feb 26 2026 11:15 PM IST</description><guid>3455773fd3f65deeeaaf2d1ec63918cb</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:44:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Reveal Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-reveal-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3859371</link><description>The December 2025 quarterly earnings season has wrapped up for 4,090 stocks, revealing a nuanced landscape of corporate performance marked by modest profit growth and sector-specific disparities. While the proportion of companies reporting positive results has inched up to 46.0%, the data underscores a cautious optimism amid ongoing macroeconomic challenges.
Time: Feb 26 2026 09:00 PM IST</description><guid>3e552eb8549376f06bff5033b0ef9428</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:44:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Foseco India Ltd. latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-foseco-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3859357</link><description>Foseco India Ltd. reported strong net sales growth of 24.03% but faced a 23.59% decline in net profit due to higher depreciation and tax rates, raising concerns about profitability sustainability. While operational metrics are solid, the reduction in promoter holding may signal caution for investors.
Time: Feb 26 2026 07:11 PM IST</description><guid>d3d1108dc4dea3704461e9234195b47c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:44:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-sanofi-consumer-healthcare-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3859356</link><description>Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are strong, showing a 47.04% year-on-year increase in net sales to ₹251.00 crores and a net profit rise of 50.11% to ₹66.50 crores, despite slight margin pressures. The company remains financially robust with a debt-free balance sheet and high return on equity, though investors should watch for future margin stability.
Time: Feb 26 2026 07:11 PM IST</description><guid>801e786249309a64f28305a3176ae403</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:44:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are KSB Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-ksb-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3859355</link><description>KSB Ltd's latest results are generally positive, with a 7.93% increase in net sales and a 10.81% rise in net profit, although profit growth is slowing compared to previous years. The company maintains strong operational metrics and a debt-free balance sheet, but faces valuation concerns in the market.
Time: Feb 26 2026 07:11 PM IST</description><guid>5ff7900011a93402ed982e9956d7b234</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:44:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>L&amp;T Finance Ltd: A Multibagger Stock Delivering Exceptional Returns Amid Market Challenges</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lt-finance-ltd-a-multibagger-stock-delivering-exceptional-returns-amid-market-challenges-3858929</link><description>L&amp;T Finance Ltd has emerged as a standout performer in the Non-Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, delivering multibagger returns of 125.82% over the past year, vastly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 10.25% gain. This remarkable surge has attracted significant investor attention, prompting a detailed analysis of the key drivers behind its stellar performance and the sustainability of its momentum going forward.
Time: Feb 26 2026 06:05 PM IST</description><guid>089913f14865788a79918088caaf4fe9</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:44:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tega Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tega-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3858858</link><description>Tega Industries Ltd, a key player in the Industrial Manufacturing sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term momentum despite its strong historical performance.
Time: Feb 26 2026 06:00 PM IST</description><guid>618d51d97b9d4dab38d4987e967f55be</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:44:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Krishana Phoschem Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/krishana-phoschem-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3858856</link><description>Krishana Phoschem Ltd, a notable player in the Fertilizers sector, has recently formed a Death Cross as its 50-day moving average (DMA) crossed below the 200-day moving average. This technical development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend, indicating potential long-term weakness and a deterioration in the stock’s momentum. Investors and market watchers should carefully analyse the implications of this event amid the company’s broader financial and market context.
Time: Feb 26 2026 06:00 PM IST</description><guid>013b310652bde6b4eddb158d54f90b37</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:44:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Calcom Vision Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/calcom-vision-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3858855</link><description>Calcom Vision Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Electronics &amp; Appliances sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development is widely regarded as a bearish signal, indicating a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raising concerns about its medium to long-term outlook.
Time: Feb 26 2026 06:00 PM IST</description><guid>8d37ffdd0b980066402ddb3b49727cd2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:44:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Goyal Aluminiums Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Indicating Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/goyal-aluminiums-ltd-forms-golden-cross-indicating-potential-bullish-breakout-3858854</link><description>Goyal Aluminiums Ltd has recently experienced a significant technical event known as the Golden Cross, where its 50-day moving average has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development is widely regarded as a bullish signal, indicating a potential trend reversal and a shift towards long-term upward momentum for the stock.
Time: Feb 26 2026 06:00 PM IST</description><guid>42ec53b1ac92353b84e9a763ae025442</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:44:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fedders Holding Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/fedders-holding-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3858859</link><description>Fedders Holding Ltd (Stock ID: 532434) has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s near- to medium-term outlook within the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector.
Time: Feb 26 2026 06:00 PM IST</description><guid>a666497c46a5409de9385b6c141b2eac</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:44:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sukhjit Starch &amp; Chemicals Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sukhjit-starch-chemicals-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3858857</link><description>Sukhjit Starch &amp; Chemicals Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout, indicating a shift in long-term momentum and a possible trend reversal for the micro-cap stock in the Other Agricultural Products sector.
Time: Feb 26 2026 06:00 PM IST</description><guid>2a4b590cf25650a2b0fd90fc1e7bbca6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:44:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arvind Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/arvind-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3858853</link><description>Arvind Ltd, a prominent player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross—a technical event where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average—indicating a potential bullish breakout and a significant shift in long-term momentum for the stock.
Time: Feb 26 2026 06:00 PM IST</description><guid>fce892714750b49ecb454ed798efd64c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:44:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CIE Automotive India Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cie-automotive-india-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3858852</link><description>CIE Automotive India Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses above the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential bullish breakout and a long-term momentum shift for the auto components company, suggesting renewed investor confidence and a possible trend reversal in the stock’s trajectory.
Time: Feb 26 2026 06:00 PM IST</description><guid>99c65eac0f9c380a3b26b56d4012384e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:44:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dec-2025 Quarterly Earnings Reveal Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/dec-2025-quarterly-earnings-reveal-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3858826</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has unfolded with a nuanced picture across Indian equities, as 4,089 companies declared results reflecting a modest improvement in profitability and revenue growth. While mid-cap firms led the charge with a 53.0% positive results ratio, large caps lagged behind at 43.0%, signalling divergent sectoral and market cap dynamics amid a challenging macroeconomic backdrop.
Time: Feb 26 2026 06:00 PM IST</description><guid>dd48659640663c6b1a9bc990d87f4a5f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:44:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:44:42 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>