<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:16:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Premium Plast Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-premium-plast-ltd-fallingrising-3792464</link><description>On 14-Jan, Premium Plast Ltd's stock price declined by 0.52% to close at ₹38.00, reflecting a modest pullback amid subdued investor interest and short-term technical pressures despite outperforming the broader market over the past month.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>3faf0fad427ac5ee1e929fcf25b0410c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is SPP Polymer Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-spp-polymer-ltd-fallingrising-3792463</link><description>On 14-Jan, SPP Polymer Ltd's stock price rose by 4.93% to ₹15.95, outperforming both its sector and the broader market indices despite a challenging long-term performance record.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>c444e32ea5ae3d7fac2fa5ad34bf2ea1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is P N Gadgil Jewellers Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-p-n-gadgil-jewellers-ltd-fallingrising-3792462</link><description>On 14-Jan, P N Gadgil Jewellers Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 1.9% to close at ₹587.55. This drop reflects a broader trend of underperformance relative to both its sector and the benchmark Sensex index, amid subdued investor participation and technical weaknesses.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>9f278dfcd449d5f8d5e7c519041c4603</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sati Poly Plast Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sati-poly-plast-ltd-fallingrising-3792461</link><description>On 14-Jan, Sati Poly Plast Ltd’s stock price fell sharply to ₹51.90, marking a new 52-week and all-time low as the company continues to underperform both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>24d652172f9725bd37a5fa6d7c1538dc</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Divine Power Energy Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-divine-power-energy-ltd-fallingrising-3792460</link><description>On 14-Jan, Divine Power Energy Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, falling by 1.99% to close at ₹305.00. This movement comes despite the stock's strong longer-term performance, reflecting a complex interplay of short-term market dynamics and investor behaviour.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>07ba80c7147ffc6438501c9f0cf95be1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Bharti Hexacom Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-bharti-hexacom-ltd-fallingrising-3792459</link><description>On 14-Jan, Bharti Hexacom Ltd’s stock price fell by 2.27% to close at ₹1,641.10, continuing a downward trend over the past three days amid broader market pressures and technical weaknesses, despite the company’s robust financial performance and healthy long-term growth indicators.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>2aefdc9b2ec6381fe03184293a86022e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Credo Brands Marketing Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-credo-brands-marketing-ltd-fallingrising-3792458</link><description>On 14-Jan, Credo Brands Marketing Ltd's stock price continued its downward trajectory, closing at ₹94.00 with a marginal decline of 0.27%. The stock's persistent underperformance relative to the broader market and sector benchmarks highlights ongoing challenges for the company’s shares.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>ebe9f42bb312fea527935f494bb522d6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Harshdeep Hortico Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-harshdeep-hortico-ltd-fallingrising-3792457</link><description>On 14-Jan, Harshdeep Hortico Ltd's stock price surged by 5.44% to close at ₹100.00, reflecting robust investor interest and significant outperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>22de00a94455c7d0459760c1886b9de5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Fedbank Financial Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-fedbank-financial-services-ltd-fallingrising-3792456</link><description>On 14-Jan, Fedbank Financial Services Ltd witnessed a significant price surge, rising by 8.82% to close at ₹176.40, reaching a new 52-week and all-time high of ₹178.4. This remarkable performance stands in stark contrast to the broader market, with the Sensex declining by 2.16% year-to-date, underscoring the stock’s robust momentum.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>2e324e81d8d324369a59751798c1da15</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is IRM Energy Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-irm-energy-ltd-fallingrising-3792455</link><description>On 14-Jan, IRM Energy Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 5.66% to close at ₹258.20. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s recent downward trend, underperforming both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>925d1d0ffa72e4c57bc20ed7d99280d3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Aarti Pharmalabs Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-aarti-pharmalabs-ltd-fallingrising-3792454</link><description>On 14-Jan, Aarti Pharmalabs Ltd witnessed a notable share price increase of 3.42%, closing at ₹793.05. This rise comes despite the company’s recent financial challenges, reflecting a complex interplay of market performance, valuation metrics, and investor sentiment.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>87103e2c2af7bc595f0f1ed21e16b9d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Retina Paints Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-retina-paints-ltd-fallingrising-3792453</link><description>On 14-Jan, Retina Paints Ltd witnessed a significant price increase of 7.25%, closing at ₹72.50, reflecting robust short-term performance that outpaced both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>5070d5dca0e6af282c866321c26a6a6c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is ITCONS E-Solutions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-itcons-e-solutions-ltd-fallingrising-3792452</link><description>On 14-Jan, ITCONS E-Solutions Ltd experienced a sharp decline in its share price, falling by 19.99% to close at ₹312.90, marking a new 52-week low and continuing a prolonged period of underperformance relative to the broader market and its sector peers.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>3557e6b97ae5a05878bae5cf4d36effa</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is AWL Agri Business Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-awl-agri-business-ltd-fallingrising-3792451</link><description>On 14-Jan, AWL Agri Business Ltd's stock price declined to ₹217.95, marking a fall of 0.86% and hitting a new 52-week and all-time low. This downward trend reflects a combination of disappointing recent financial results, diminishing promoter confidence, and sustained underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>cff4cacf975b79e43dfc64b20dbd6ede</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Uma Exports Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-uma-exports-ltd-fallingrising-3792450</link><description>On 14-Jan, Uma Exports Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, closing at ₹33.75, down by ₹1.25 or 3.57%. This drop reflects ongoing challenges faced by the company, including deteriorating financial performance and weak investor sentiment.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>cceb53f70839009b12f4c8d5721523e2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Classic Leasing &amp; Finance Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-classic-leasing-finance-ltd-fallingrising-3792449</link><description>On 14-Jan, Classic Leasing &amp; Finance Ltd witnessed a notable increase in its share price, rising by 4.99% to close at ₹42.29. This surge outpaced the broader market and sector indices, reflecting strong investor interest despite some signs of volatility and declining participation.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>612def5f4eee213e15f2c4fd68dee449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ethos Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ethos-ltd-fallingrising-3792448</link><description>On 14-Jan, Ethos Ltd’s stock price fell by 1.68% to ₹2,666.00, continuing a downward trend that has seen the share underperform both its sector and the broader market benchmarks in recent weeks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>814a99c21b8a7761ef55ca7147231f83</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is G R Infraprojects Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-g-r-infraprojects-ltd-fallingrising-3792447</link><description>On 14-Jan, G R Infraprojects Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, closing at ₹930.40, down ₹11.40 or 1.21% from the previous session. This drop reflects a continuation of a downward trend influenced by both short-term market pressures and longer-term fundamental challenges.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>ccd5739492d5dc85cab98bcb8289141b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Rajeshwari Cans Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-rajeshwari-cans-ltd-fallingrising-3792446</link><description>On 14-Jan, Rajeshwari Cans Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, closing at ₹28.12 with a gain of 4.96%. This upward movement reflects a strong short-term performance despite the company’s longer-term challenges.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>79a2d0aa10b133a175367c548f826f24</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Macpower CNC Machines Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-macpower-cnc-machines-ltd-fallingrising-3792445</link><description>On 14-Jan, Macpower CNC Machines Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.02% to close at ₹934.50. This drop reflects a continuation of recent underperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>d64b2e2a728d98b6e69b2fcb91d65cf0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:16:55 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>