<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:24:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Mankind Pharma Ltd Hits Intraday High with Strong 3.2% Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mankind-pharma-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-strong-32-surge-3784757</link><description>Mankind Pharma Ltd demonstrated robust intraday strength on 7 Jan 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 2,320.35, marking a 3.5% increase from its previous close. This performance notably outpaced the broader Sensex, which traded lower by 0.31% during the session.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>14563091c264c5f24ae306822425ff20</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:24:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KPIT Technologies Ltd Hits Intraday High with Strong 5.38% Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kpit-technologies-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-strong-538-surge-3784755</link><description>KPIT Technologies Ltd demonstrated robust intraday strength on 7 Jan 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 1,208.5, marking a 6.05% increase from its previous close. This performance notably outpaced the broader sector and the Sensex, reflecting a significant rebound after two days of decline.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>5bbe258cf20f7cc0f3ecb7fdef041d7c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:24:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Solar Industries India Ltd Hits Intraday High with 3.32% Surge on 7 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/solar-industries-india-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-332-surge-on-7-jan-2026-3784756</link><description>Solar Industries India Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 7 January 2026, surging 3.32% to touch a day’s high of ₹13,210.95, outperforming its sector and broader market indices amid mixed market conditions.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>0ac4c79441e9b76f41d320b1ae9d9b20</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:24:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Epigral Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.1150 Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/epigral-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs1150-amid-continued-downtrend-3784751</link><description>Epigral Ltd, a key player in the Specialty Chemicals sector, has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.1150 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has underperformed both its sector and the broader market indices, reflecting ongoing pressures on its financial performance and valuation metrics.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>321bd5a0fce0b115988218a53a6556d6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:24:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stanley Lifestyles Ltd Surges to Intraday High with 7.76% Gain</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/stanley-lifestyles-ltd-surges-to-intraday-high-with-776-gain-3784754</link><description>Stanley Lifestyles Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 7 Jan 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 209.1, marking an 8.85% increase from its previous close. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting notable trading momentum amid a mixed market backdrop.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>18e197f9805480db30aa4d5ca6435321</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:24:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tiger Logistics (India) Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.32.11</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tiger-logistics-india-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs3211-3784750</link><description>Tiger Logistics (India) Ltd has touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.32.11 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trajectory. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing pressures on its valuation and market sentiment.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>6a9bd76389c21fffde0efc93c8046443</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:24:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Super Sales India Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.650 Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/super-sales-india-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs650-amidst-continued-underperformance-3784749</link><description>Super Sales India Ltd, a player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.650 today, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing price decline. Despite a volatile trading session with an intraday high of Rs.800, the stock closed near its lowest point, reflecting persistent pressures on its valuation and performance metrics.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>59c08b71a8199804486b6034a2fdc256</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:24:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ERP Soft Systems Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.65.6 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/erp-soft-systems-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs656-amidst-continued-downtrend-3784752</link><description>ERP Soft Systems Ltd, a player in the Diversified Commercial Services sector, has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.65.6 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid a sustained downward trend over recent sessions.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>375648e64d8793dc980da616e75e3c63</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:24:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Samrat Pharmachem Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.222.05</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/samrat-pharmachem-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs22205-3784753</link><description>Samrat Pharmachem Ltd’s stock declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.222.05 on 7 January 2026, marking a significant downturn amid persistent underperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices. The pharmaceutical and biotechnology company’s shares have been trading below all key moving averages, reflecting ongoing pressures on its valuation and financial metrics.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>2c497ba9d11f301bab7c3dd8cf0b0837</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:24:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Swiggy Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amidst Weak Price Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/swiggy-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amidst-weak-price-performance-3784747</link><description>Swiggy Ltd, a prominent player in the E-Retail and E-Commerce sector, has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this spike, the stock continues to underperform its sector peers, reflecting cautious sentiment amid a sustained downtrend.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>aa351fe80d21e482ec99150779dc92dc</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:24:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Premier Energies Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Price Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/premier-energies-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-price-weakness-3784746</link><description>Premier Energies Ltd has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, rising by 16.87% to 17,088 contracts, even as the stock price continues to slide to fresh 52-week lows. This divergence between rising market participation and falling prices signals a complex shift in investor positioning and potential directional bets in the Other Electrical Equipment sector.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>7d5a0967205ed7021f80730d8dc3239e</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:24:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Technologies Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-technologies-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-momentum-3784745</link><description>Tata Technologies Ltd (TATATECH) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling a notable shift in market sentiment. The stock outperformed its sector and broader indices on 7 Jan 2026, with a 4.21% gain, driven by increased volumes and fresh positioning by traders. This article analyses the recent OI spike, volume trends, and the implications for directional bets on this small-cap software and consulting company.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>21fe6e2e20f79e28a1753074b266cd6a</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:24:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Piramal Pharma Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/piramal-pharma-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3784744</link><description>Piramal Pharma Ltd (PPLPHARMA) has witnessed a notable 10.25% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a modest 0.47% price gain, the surge in open interest alongside volume patterns suggests evolving directional bets amid a backdrop of mixed technical and fundamental indicators.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>efc120437092d5b7fc531f6dd212bb69</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:24:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mankind Pharma Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Derivatives Activity</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mankind-pharma-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-derivatives-activity-3784743</link><description>Mankind Pharma Ltd has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. The pharmaceutical giant’s stock outperformed its sector peers, buoyed by increased volumes and a notable uptick in delivery volumes, reflecting growing investor confidence despite a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>43ecbf37d5e12a66ad27112db141dc1f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:24:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kalyan Jewellers Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kalyan-jewellers-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3784740</link><description>Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd (KALYANKJIL) has witnessed a significant 22.13% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite the stock underperforming its sector by 0.83% today, the spike in open interest alongside rising volumes suggests a complex interplay of directional bets and hedging strategies among traders.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>79d8952fb1814e96ec2be2b60843a844</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:24:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hitachi Energy India Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Signalling Bullish Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hitachi-energy-india-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-signalling-bullish-market-positioning-3784739</link><description>Hitachi Energy India Ltd (POWERINDIA) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, reflecting a marked shift in market sentiment and positioning. The stock outperformed its sector and broader indices on 7 Jan 2026, buoyed by increased volumes and a notable 25.9% rise in open interest, signalling fresh directional bets among traders and investors.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>635231648b495124045faf2e3c8525a2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:24:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Polycab India Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/polycab-india-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-market-momentum-3784742</link><description>Polycab India Ltd has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market participation and potential directional bets. The stock hit a new 52-week and all-time high of ₹7,935, outperforming its sector and broader indices, while trading volumes and futures values indicate heightened investor interest and positioning ahead of upcoming market catalysts.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>17db0aca56f8c3bc2283146feff84628</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:24:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SBI Life Insurance Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sbi-life-insurance-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3784741</link><description>SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd (SBILIFE) has witnessed a notable 12.8% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite the stock hitting a new 52-week high of ₹2,109.6, the share price slipped by 0.97% on 7 Jan 2026, underperforming its sector and the broader Sensex. This article analyses the implications of the open interest surge, volume trends, and potential directional bets shaping the stock’s near-term outlook.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>20ea0f0cd5537154f4c82eb5ce024c75</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:24:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Elxsi Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Market Outperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-elxsi-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-market-outperformance-3784738</link><description>Tata Elxsi Ltd., a prominent player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment on 7 Jan 2026, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. The stock outperformed its sector peers and broader indices, reflecting renewed bullish sentiment despite a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>7ccd3fd7c67132c833c3c5dcc60bb08d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:24:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amidst Steady Price Gains</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sun-pharmaceutical-industries-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amidst-steady-price-gains-3784736</link><description>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market participation and potential directional bets. The stock’s recent price momentum, combined with rising volumes and shifting investor positioning, suggests a cautiously optimistic outlook within the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>20c5d550690d2c016d8bad2c89429987</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:24:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:24:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>