<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 09:22:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Vishnu Prakash R Punglia Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vishnu-prakash-r-punglia-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-3762770</link><description>Shares of Vishnu Prakash R Punglia touched an intraday low of Rs 66.5 today, marking a fresh 52-week and all-time low as the stock faced significant price pressure. The construction sector stock underperformed the broader market, reflecting persistent downward momentum amid volatile trading conditions.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>015fd980fbbd4edbc1de1d3cc9984439</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 09:22:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Astron Paper &amp; Board Mill Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/astron-paper-board-mill-stock-hits-52-week-low-amid-continued-weakness-3762769</link><description>Astron Paper &amp; Board Mill has reached a new 52-week low, closing just 1.68% above its lowest price of Rs 5.85, reflecting a year marked by significant declines and persistent challenges within the Paper, Forest &amp; Jute Products sector.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>a39f597d29fdbf25685a5d22ddb2f04f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 09:22:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Afcons Infrastructure Stock Hits All-Time Low Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/afcons-infrastructure-stock-hits-all-time-low-amidst-prolonged-downtrend-3762768</link><description>Afcons Infrastructure has reached a new all-time low of Rs.381.1, marking a significant point in its recent market performance. The stock has experienced a sustained decline over the past several sessions, reflecting ongoing pressures within the construction sector and broader market conditions.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>60a32868abf1e33703d43769f65183e0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 09:22:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wonder Electricals Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure and Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/wonder-electricals-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-18-dec-2025-3762767</link><description>Wonder Electricals experienced a notable decline today, touching an intraday low of Rs 143, reflecting significant price pressure amid heightened volatility. The stock underperformed its sector and broader market indices, continuing a recent trend of subdued performance.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>0c2901ac04e75cf307a0bf5991197ab2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 09:22:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MT Educare Stock Hits All-Time Low Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mt-educare-stock-hits-all-time-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3762766</link><description>MT Educare’s shares have reached an unprecedented low, reflecting a sustained period of subdued performance and financial strain within the Other Consumer Services sector. The stock’s recent trading activity underscores the challenges faced by the company amid broader market pressures and sector dynamics.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>f11c02f9db2c5c98f54ebd892958379d</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 09:22:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nuvama Wealth Management Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nuvama-wealth-management-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-momentum-3762761</link><description>Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd has experienced a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling a shift in market positioning and investor sentiment. This development coincides with the stock outperforming its sector and reversing a short-term downtrend, highlighting increased activity and potential directional bets among traders.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>90039af80ba41e5d2e98974ddc31b777</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 09:22:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Life Insurance Corporation of India Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/life-insurance-corporation-of-india-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3762765</link><description>Life Insurance Corporation of India (LICI) has experienced a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and evolving investor positioning. This development comes amid a backdrop of subdued price performance and shifting volume dynamics, offering insights into potential directional bets and market sentiment.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>632070cce14a230e7840ed44bf930e34</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 09:22:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hitachi Energy India Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hitachi-energy-india-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amidst-weak-price-action-3762762</link><description>Hitachi Energy India has experienced a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and evolving investor positioning. This development comes amid a period of price softness and increased trading volumes, reflecting a complex interplay of market sentiment and strategic bets on the stock’s near-term trajectory.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>3ec8f42957ff2d9ab3469f7db6e2a872</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 09:22:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HDFC Asset Management Company Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hdfc-asset-management-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-signalling-renewed-market-confidence-3762760</link><description>HDFC Asset Management Company Ltd has experienced a notable surge in open interest within its derivatives segment, coinciding with a strong intraday price performance and increased trading volumes. This development reflects evolving market positioning and potential directional bets by investors amid a backdrop of sector outperformance and shifting liquidity patterns.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>556cb41bcf12d4452e08db1a6d20ac67</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 09:22:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Infosys Sees Robust Trading Activity Amid Sector Outperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/infosys-leads-high-value-trading-amid-institutional-interest-and-positive-momentum-3762763</link><description>Infosys Ltd has emerged as one of the most actively traded stocks by value on 18 Dec 2025, reflecting significant investor interest and liquidity within the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector. The stock's performance today has outpaced its sector peers, supported by strong volume and value metrics that underscore its prominence in the large-cap space.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>d51826e6a5922b981877a3d27a9d351b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 09:22:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Supreme Infrastructure India Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/supreme-infrastructure-india-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3762759</link><description>Supreme Infrastructure India Ltd witnessed a sharp decline on 18 Dec 2025, hitting its lower circuit limit as intense selling pressure gripped the stock. The construction sector company recorded a maximum daily loss of 5.0%, closing at ₹89.73, reflecting a day marked by panic selling and unfilled supply that weighed heavily on investor sentiment.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>04d361d6eb1256344c2002b0c158883f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 09:22:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UltraTech Cement Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ultratech-cement-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-market-signals-3762758</link><description>UltraTech Cement Ltd has experienced a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, reflecting a shift in market positioning and investor sentiment. Despite the stock underperforming its sector and trading below key moving averages, the surge in open interest suggests increased speculative activity and potential directional bets by market participants.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>a540a18a13e697b50f774a0fd2859e15</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 09:22:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bhagyanagar India Hits Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bhagyanagar-india-hits-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3762764</link><description>Bhagyanagar India Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non-Ferrous Metals sector, witnessed robust market activity on 18 Dec 2025 as its stock price surged to hit the upper circuit limit. The stock closed at ₹137.58, marking a 5.0% gain on the day, driven by intense buying interest and a notable outperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>4a263b3946642d5c0893dda38c6efe80</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 09:22:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sensex Edges Higher Amid Mixed Sector Performance; HDFC AMC Leads Gains</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-edges-higher-as-it-sector-leads-gains-amid-mixed-market-breadth-3762757</link><description>The Indian equity market displayed a cautious tone on 18 Dec 2025, with the Sensex inching up by 72.97 points to trade at 84,632.62, reflecting a modest 0.09% gain. Market breadth remained subdued as declines outnumbered advances across the BSE500, while sectoral trends showed a divergence between technology and power stocks. HDFC AMC emerged as the top large-cap gainer, underscoring selective buying interest amid mixed investor sentiment.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>b2a747415775b95ae6e5d4eba4d06d35</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 09:22:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aavas Financiers Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.1447.55 Amid Market Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aavas-financiers-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3762756</link><description>Aavas Financiers, a prominent player in the housing finance sector, has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.1447.55 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid broader market dynamics and company-specific factors.
Time: 56 minutes ago</description><guid>1b1d9c0f017b6b2c832ee8c15e12e92f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 09:22:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DCM Nouvelle Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dcm-nouvelle-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3762755</link><description>Shares of DCM Nouvelle have declined to their lowest level in the past 52 weeks, marking a significant price point for the garment and apparels company. The stock’s recent trading activity reflects ongoing challenges in financial performance and market positioning within its sector.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>d1437ac9835dcabe0545f0856c41eac5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 09:22:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shiva Mills Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shiva-mills-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-underperformance-3762754</link><description>Shares of Shiva Mills have reached a fresh 52-week low, reflecting ongoing challenges within the garments and apparels sector. The stock's recent price movement highlights a significant decline, with the current trading level marking a notable point in its year-long performance.
Time: 58 minutes ago</description><guid>2c515adfd1a03920f012897dcb2aea65</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 09:22:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Confidence Futuristic Energetech Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.35.9 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/confidence-futuristic-energetech-stock-hits-52-week-low-at-rs359-3762753</link><description>Confidence Futuristic Energetech has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.35.9 today, marking a significant decline in its share price amid a sustained downward trend over the past week. The stock has recorded a cumulative loss of 5.91% over the last five trading sessions, reflecting ongoing pressures within the Trading &amp; Distributors sector.
Time: 58 minutes ago</description><guid>c6eccacdb7d80f3338e95fa1b6a586d1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 09:22:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Allcargo Logistics Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.10.8 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/allcargo-logistics-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-108-amid-continued-downtrend-3762749</link><description>Shares of Allcargo Logistics have reached a new 52-week low of Rs.10.8, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend over the past week. The stock has recorded a cumulative return of -14.81% over the last seven trading sessions, reflecting ongoing pressures within the transport services sector.
Time: 59 minutes ago</description><guid>1948dcc24addab350085ca3ca0362352</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 09:22:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Integra Essentia Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.1.55 Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/integra-essentia-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs155-3762752</link><description>Integra Essentia, a player in the FMCG sector, touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.1.55 today, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing price decline. This new low comes amid a broader underperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices, reflecting persistent challenges in both its financial metrics and market positioning.
Time: 59 minutes ago</description><guid>18860aff384ed0e1e6645e904e85baa0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 09:22:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 09:22:06 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>