<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:59:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Sensex Dips 0.23% Amid Broad Market Weakness; Realty Sector Leads Declines</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-dips-023-amid-broad-market-weakness-realty-sector-leads-declines-3774555</link><description>Indian equity markets closed lower on 30 Dec 2025, with the Sensex retreating 0.23% to 84,501.95 and the Nifty following suit amid widespread sectoral declines. Market breadth was notably weak, reflecting cautious investor sentiment as large caps traded largely flat and mid and small caps faced selling pressure. The Realty sector emerged as the top laggard, while select stocks in metals and pharmaceuticals bucked the trend with modest gains.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>7680bde918a117ac301f6405c8e00249</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:59:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jio Financial Services Ltd Faces Mixed Fortunes Amid Nifty 50 Inclusion</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jio-financial-services-ltd-faces-mixed-fortunes-amid-nifty-50-inclusion-3774554</link><description>Jio Financial Services Ltd, a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to face headwinds amid a challenging market environment. Despite its large-cap status and inclusion in India’s premier benchmark, the stock has underperformed the Sensex over multiple time horizons, reflecting sectoral pressures and valuation concerns. Institutional investors are closely monitoring the company’s evolving fundamentals as it navigates the complexities of the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>96acb9fffc5a297375a48f9fe7266712</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:59:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eternal Ltd Faces Downgrade Amidst Nifty 50 Membership and Market Challenges</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eternal-ltd-faces-downgrade-amidst-nifty-50-membership-and-market-challenges-3774553</link><description>Eternal Ltd, a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index and a major player in the E-Retail and E-Commerce sector, has recently undergone a significant rating downgrade from Hold to Sell. This shift comes amid a backdrop of underwhelming price performance relative to the broader market, evolving institutional holdings, and the stock’s critical role within benchmark indices.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>6fbbbf6d88593809dd60868429166875</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:59:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Max Healthcare Institute Ltd Faces Headwinds Despite Nifty 50 Inclusion</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/max-healthcare-institute-ltd-faces-headwinds-despite-nifty-50-inclusion-3774552</link><description>Max Healthcare Institute Ltd, a prominent hospital sector stock and a constituent of the Nifty 50 index, has recently undergone a downgrade from a Hold to a Sell rating, reflecting growing concerns over its valuation and performance relative to the broader market and sector benchmarks.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>f077110abfde3637bc67009f60a0d9e2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:59:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HDFC Life Insurance: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hdfc-life-insurance-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-mixed-market-signals-3774551</link><description>HDFC Life Insurance Company Ltd continues to assert its significance as a Nifty 50 constituent, reflecting both its market stature and the evolving institutional interest. Despite recent trading pressures and valuation concerns, the company’s benchmark status and large-cap credentials underpin its pivotal role in India’s insurance sector and broader equity markets.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>6938c3b986b17935c93474e9816c94bd</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:59:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Market Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sbi-life-insurance-company-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-market-dynamics-3774550</link><description>SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd continues to assert its prominence within the Nifty 50 index, reflecting robust market capitalisation and sustained investor interest despite recent rating adjustments. The stock’s performance relative to benchmarks and sector peers underscores its strategic importance in India’s insurance sector and highlights evolving institutional holding patterns that could influence future market trajectories.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>38d53537e9de5a2825d4fc20a0863c3f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:59:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Auto Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Dynamics Amid Sectoral Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-auto-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-amid-sectoral-trends-3774549</link><description>Bajaj Auto Ltd., a stalwart in the Indian automobile sector and a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to command significant attention amid evolving market dynamics. Despite a modest decline of 0.43% on 30 Dec 2025, the stock’s strategic position within the benchmark index and recent upgrades in its investment grade underscore its enduring relevance for institutional investors and market watchers alike.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>9b3921d9a42f5b14f8712a9c01fd9e02</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:59:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Finance Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-finance-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-mixed-market-signals-3774547</link><description>Bajaj Finance Ltd continues to assert its prominence within the Nifty 50 index, reflecting its stature as a leading Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) in India. Despite recent short-term price pressures, the stock’s robust long-term performance and institutional interest underscore its critical role in the benchmark and the broader financial sector.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>f0db0710578b31a98a7263fd92e984e5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:59:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd: Navigating Challenges Amidst Nifty 50 Membership</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-motors-passenger-vehicles-ltd-navigating-challenges-amidst-nifty-50-membership-3774548</link><description>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd, a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, has experienced notable volatility and downward pressure in recent trading sessions, reflecting broader challenges in the automobile sector and shifts in institutional holdings. Despite its large-cap status and significant market presence, the stock’s recent performance contrasts sharply with benchmark indices, raising questions about its near-term outlook and strategic positioning within the Nifty 50 framework.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>bd10170d583191f7fc30250ea7a4ce1a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:59:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amidst Market Headwinds</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sun-pharmaceutical-industries-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amidst-market-headwinds-3774546</link><description>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd, a stalwart in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector and a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, is currently facing a challenging phase marked by subdued price performance and shifting institutional holdings. Despite recent setbacks, the company’s large-cap status and benchmark inclusion continue to underpin its market significance, warranting a detailed analysis of its current standing and future prospects.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>f5a1768ec3af796e01c884db085dbbf4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:59:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JSW Steel Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amid Shifting Institutional Holdings</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jsw-steel-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-shifting-institutional-holdings-3774545</link><description>JSW Steel Ltd., a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to demonstrate resilience amid evolving market conditions. Despite a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade from Buy to Hold, the steel giant’s long-term performance and institutional interest underscore its significance within India’s benchmark equity index.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>427fe000ea1eeebec9a7f3261696c53a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:59:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Ltd: Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Dynamics Shape Market Outlook</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mahindra-mahindra-ltd-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-shape-market-outlook-3774542</link><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Ltd (M&amp;M), a stalwart in the Indian automobile sector, continues to demonstrate resilience and strategic significance as a Nifty 50 constituent. With a recent upgrade in its Mojo Grade to 'Buy' and a market capitalisation exceeding ₹4.46 lakh crores, the company’s evolving institutional holdings and benchmark status underscore its pivotal role in shaping market sentiment and investor portfolios.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>2dd1b7f4e003f661e88f37576b3b52c9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:59:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Larsen &amp; Toubro Ltd: Nifty 50 Membership Reinforces Market Standing Amid Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/larsen-toubro-ltd-nifty-50-membership-reinforces-market-standing-amid-institutional-shifts-3774543</link><description>Larsen &amp; Toubro Ltd. (L&amp;T), a cornerstone of India’s construction sector and a prominent Nifty 50 constituent, continues to demonstrate resilience amid sectoral headwinds and market volatility. Recent upgrades in its Mojo Grade to ‘Buy’ from ‘Hold’ reflect growing investor confidence, supported by robust long-term performance and strategic institutional interest.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>74516b7ac59814a5031c2fb485b7ebb8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:59:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Finserv Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-finserv-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-mixed-market-signals-3774544</link><description>Bajaj Finserv Ltd, a prominent holding company and a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, has experienced a nuanced performance trajectory in recent trading sessions. Despite a strong year-to-date return of 27.86%, the stock has faced short-term headwinds, reflecting broader sectoral pressures and shifting institutional holdings. This article analyses the implications of its index membership, recent market movements, and evolving investor sentiment.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>72714a6bc0ea6e751f68e28b10d35db6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:59:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Enterprises Ltd Faces Strong Sell Rating Amidst Nifty 50 Membership Impact</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-enterprises-ltd-faces-strong-sell-rating-amidst-nifty-50-membership-impact-3774541</link><description>Adani Enterprises Ltd, a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to grapple with significant headwinds as it navigates a challenging market environment. Despite its large-cap status and diversified business model, the stock has underperformed the benchmark Sensex over multiple time frames, reflecting growing concerns among institutional investors and analysts alike.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>7d3fb8fa21a6fa1423a83ecced23e7d3</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:59:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Mahindra Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amid Mixed Performance and Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tech-mahindra-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-mixed-performance-and-institutional-shifts-3774540</link><description>Tech Mahindra Ltd., a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to demonstrate a complex performance trajectory amid evolving institutional holdings and sector dynamics. Despite recent downward pressure, the company’s large-cap status and benchmark inclusion underscore its significance in India’s software and consulting landscape.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>3b19a99a7e95ef61e0de1118c5566afb</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:59:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Unilever Ltd Faces Downgrade Amidst Challenging FMCG Sector and Nifty 50 Implications</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-unilever-ltd-faces-downgrade-amidst-challenging-fmcg-sector-and-nifty-50-implications-3774538</link><description>Hindustan Unilever Ltd (HUL), a flagship constituent of the Nifty 50 index and a dominant player in the FMCG sector, has recently undergone a notable downgrade in its Mojo Grade from Hold to Sell as of 3 December 2025. This shift reflects mounting concerns over the company’s subdued performance relative to the broader market and sectoral headwinds, raising questions about its future trajectory and implications for institutional investors and index benchmarks.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>a34d7c19deb72333eda1759037dec42f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:59:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dr Reddys Laboratories Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amid Mixed Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dr-reddys-laboratories-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-mixed-performance-3774536</link><description>Dr Reddys Laboratories Ltd, a stalwart in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector and a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to face a challenging market environment. Despite its large-cap status and steady institutional interest, the stock’s recent performance has lagged behind the broader market benchmarks, prompting a reassessment of its investment appeal.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>ddf3ed8490630fb8199465e4cc560dad</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:59:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Grasim Industries Ltd Strengthens Position as Nifty 50 Constituent Amid Robust Market Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/grasim-industries-ltd-strengthens-position-as-nifty-50-constituent-amid-robust-market-performance-3774539</link><description>Grasim Industries Ltd, a key player in the Cement &amp; Cement Products sector, continues to solidify its stature within the Nifty 50 index, reflecting strong institutional confidence and outperforming benchmark indices. Recent upgrades in its investment grade and sustained market momentum underscore its growing appeal among investors.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>5a08e7bbe237750f81d0d05577683baa</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:59:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oil &amp; Natural Gas Corporation Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amid Mixed Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/oil-natural-gas-corporation-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-mixed-performance-3774537</link><description>Oil &amp; Natural Gas Corporation Ltd. (ONGC), a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to command significant attention from investors and institutions alike. Despite a recent downgrade in its mojo grade and a subdued price performance relative to the broader market, ONGC’s role within India’s benchmark index underscores its strategic importance in the oil sector and the wider economy.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>0bdc1a668a7b5c62fdf8233bbaaa3354</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:59:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 03:59:15 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>