<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 06:44:41 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Neuland Laboratories Gains 0.06%: Mixed Technical Signals and Earnings Impact Weekly</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/neuland-laboratories-gains-006-mixed-technical-signals-and-earnings-impact-weekly-3841054</link><description>Neuland Laboratories Ltd closed the week marginally higher by 0.06% at Rs.13,043.80, outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The stock exhibited significant volatility, surging 6.86% on Monday before retreating in the following days amid mixed technical signals and market concerns. Despite a strong intraday high early in the week, the stock faced pressure from profit warnings and technical downgrades, resulting in a cautious trading environment by Friday.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>fed9b5db54205c1944e08b37aede41f4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 06:44:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vaghani Techno-Build Ltd Gains 8.26%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vaghani-techno-build-ltd-gains-826-5-key-factors-driving-the-rally-3841053</link><description>Vaghani Techno-Build Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance from 09 to 13 February 2026, gaining 8.26% to close at Rs.285.00, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The stock set multiple new 52-week and all-time highs during the week, reflecting sustained momentum amid mixed broader market conditions. This review analyses the key events and price movements that shaped the stock’s trajectory over the week.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>f209cae84f6c0bd4fc6c333c2f840728</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 06:44:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Saven Technologies Gains 7.15%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/saven-technologies-gains-715-2-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-rally-3841051</link><description>Saven Technologies Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 7.15% from ₹44.59 to ₹47.78 between 9 and 13 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. This rally was driven by a positive financial turnaround reported on 9 February and an improved valuation outlook announced on 10 February, both contributing to renewed investor interest despite lingering liquidity concerns.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>c5027eb74178422cb194157a5074877a</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 06:44:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Atlantaa Ltd Falls 8.35%: Financial Struggles and Rising Costs Weigh on Stock</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/atlantaa-ltd-falls-835-financial-struggles-and-rising-costs-weigh-on-stock-3841052</link><description>Atlantaa Ltd’s shares declined sharply by 8.35% over the week ending 13 February 2026, underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.54%. The stock opened at Rs.46.09 and closed at Rs.42.24, pressured by deepening operating losses and mixed quarterly results that highlighted ongoing financial challenges. Despite some stabilisation in financial trends, rising interest costs and negative returns on capital weighed heavily on investor sentiment throughout the week.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>5164cd36d4c7f30d2dfa02ea097521ad</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 06:44:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Madhusudan Industries Declines 1.54%: Operational Challenges and Flat Q3 Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/madhusudan-industries-declines-154-operational-challenges-and-flat-q3-performance-3841050</link><description>Madhusudan Industries Ltd experienced a volatile week ending 13 February 2026, with its share price declining 1.54% from Rs.32.49 to Rs.31.99, underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s fluctuations were driven by mixed quarterly results and ongoing margin pressures, reflecting operational challenges in the edible oil sector amid a broadly cautious market environment.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>b12ca60ba4e7cd2e30efe79887586861</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 06:44:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>B A G Films &amp; Media Ltd Gains 3.44%: Margin Pressures and Profit Surge Shape Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/b-a-g-films-media-ltd-gains-344-margin-pressures-and-profit-surge-shape-week-3841043</link><description>B A G Films &amp; Media Ltd recorded a 3.44% gain over the week ending 13 Feb 2026, closing at Rs.5.71 compared to Rs.5.52 the previous Friday. This outperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s 0.54% decline, reflecting mixed investor sentiment amid a backdrop of margin pressures and a notable profit surge reported in the quarter ended December 2025.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>f3e59eae1c7b05277da47807823eaba7</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 06:44:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rodium Realty Gains 19.62%: Earnings and Valuation Shifts Drive Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rodium-realty-gains-1962-earnings-and-valuation-shifts-drive-volatility-3841047</link><description>Rodium Realty Ltd delivered a remarkable weekly performance, surging 19.62% from Rs.157.50 to Rs.188.40 between 9 and 13 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s sharp gains were driven by a strong Q3 FY26 revenue report and a notable upgrade in valuation attractiveness amid a volatile market backdrop.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>9370d904905e1ba869a58b305085275d</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 06:44:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Welspun Living Ltd Gains 0.61%: Technical Momentum and Earnings Pressure Shape Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/welspun-living-ltd-gains-061-technical-momentum-and-earnings-pressure-shape-week-3841049</link><description>Welspun Living Ltd closed the week with a modest gain of 0.61%, rising from Rs.140.35 on 6 February to Rs.141.20 on 13 February 2026. This performance notably outpaced the Sensex, which declined by 0.54% over the same period, reflecting resilience amid mixed financial results and improving technical momentum. The week was marked by sharp intraday volatility, a significant earnings announcement, and a technical upgrade that collectively shaped investor sentiment.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>8d31d7b150fa91af87b46514c840f3fa</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 06:44:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Risa International Ltd Gains 3.92%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Move</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/risa-international-ltd-gains-392-2-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-move-3841042</link><description>Risa International Ltd’s stock closed the week at Rs.0.53, marking a 3.92% gain from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.0.51, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. Despite a challenging midweek marked by a 52-week low and disappointing quarterly results, the stock rebounded in the final two sessions, reflecting mixed investor sentiment amid ongoing fundamental concerns.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>e2c0839003e30891bee38548215b3353</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 06:44:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Persistent Systems Declines 6.31%: 5 Key Factors Behind the Weekly Slide</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/persistent-systems-declines-631-5-key-factors-behind-the-weekly-slide-3841048</link><description>Persistent Systems Ltd experienced a challenging week, closing at Rs.5,476.50 on 13 Feb 2026, down 6.31% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.5,845.55. This decline notably outpaced the Sensex’s modest 0.54% drop over the same period, reflecting sectoral headwinds and technical weakness amid heightened derivatives activity and bearish market sentiment.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>4395c9dca4e0316d025bac51b7b33234</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 06:44:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Emerald Finance Ltd Falls 3.61%: Valuation Shift Amid Market Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/emerald-finance-ltd-falls-361-valuation-shift-amid-market-pressure-3841046</link><description>Emerald Finance Ltd’s stock declined by 3.61% over the week ending 13 February 2026, underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.54%. The share price oscillated between a 52-week low and modest intraday recoveries, reflecting mixed investor sentiment amid positive earnings but persistent sectoral challenges. Despite the weekly loss, valuation metrics improved, signalling renewed price attractiveness in a cautious market environment.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>35252fb86078a642465040656aba87cd</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 06:44:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shraddha Prime Projects Ltd Declines 0.60%: Mixed Technical and Valuation Signals Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shraddha-prime-projects-ltd-declines-060-mixed-technical-and-valuation-signals-shape-the-week-3841045</link><description>Shraddha Prime Projects Ltd experienced a volatile week from 9 to 13 February 2026, closing marginally lower by 0.60% at Rs.181.55 compared to the previous Friday’s close of Rs.182.65. This performance slightly underperformed the Sensex, which declined 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a sharp initial drop, followed by a partial recovery amid mixed technical signals and a downgrade to a Hold rating by MarketsMOJO, reflecting a cautious market stance despite attractive valuation metrics and robust long-term fundamentals.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>e563e2ada4926527c85fe805a4c34a40</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 06:44:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Speciality Restaurants Declines 4.87%: Key Events Behind the Weekly Slide</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/speciality-restaurants-declines-487-key-events-behind-the-weekly-slide-3841044</link><description>Speciality Restaurants Ltd experienced a challenging week from 9 to 13 February 2026, with its stock price declining by 4.87% to close at Rs.104.50, underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a strong Q3 profit report on 11 February followed by a sharp drop to a 52-week low on 13 February, reflecting mixed investor sentiment amid margin pressures and technical weakness.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>3cd10d6312b1bb02f7e5c5c358e75a98</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 06:44:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Step Two Corporation Gains 0.69%: Valuation Shift and Profit Return Drive Market Interest</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/step-two-corporation-gains-069-valuation-shift-and-profit-return-drive-market-interest-3841041</link><description>Step Two Corporation Ltd closed the week ending 13 Feb 2026 with a modest gain of 0.69%, rising from Rs.28.80 to Rs.29.00, while the Sensex declined by 0.54% over the same period. The stock’s stability amid a weakening broader market was supported by the company’s return to profitability in Q3 FY26 and a notable upgrade in its valuation metrics, signalling a shift in market sentiment despite lingering operational challenges.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>084847d77b6c7e2af09997d46ff7b348</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 06:44:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MT Educare Ltd Gains 7.64%: 4 Key Events Driving Volatility This Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mt-educare-ltd-gains-764-4-key-events-driving-volatility-this-week-3841040</link><description>MT Educare Ltd delivered a volatile yet positive week, gaining 7.64% from ₹1.44 to ₹1.55, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The stock experienced sharp intraday swings, hitting both upper and lower circuit limits amid fluctuating investor sentiment and subdued liquidity. Despite the strong price gains, the company’s fundamental outlook remains weak with a Strong Sell rating, underscoring the complex dynamics behind this micro-cap’s recent performance.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>9623e3c3881a86d63d342d09df43989d</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 06:44:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dec-2025 Quarterly Earnings Review: Mixed Results Across Market Caps with Select Standouts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/dec-2025-quarterly-earnings-review-mixed-results-across-market-caps-with-select-standouts-3841028</link><description>As the Dec-2025 quarter earnings season draws to a close with 3,956 companies reporting, the aggregate results paint a nuanced picture of India’s corporate health. While the proportion of companies delivering positive results has inched up to 46.0%, sectoral and market-capitalisation distinctions reveal divergent trajectories, underscoring the uneven pace of recovery and growth across industries.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>83dba5628b4f3454eea617af44175526</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 06:44:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ashapura Minechem Ltd Falls 11.16%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ashapura-minechem-ltd-falls-1116-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3841039</link><description>Ashapura Minechem Ltd experienced a volatile week from 9 to 13 February 2026, opening at Rs.647.80 and closing sharply lower at Rs.540.90, marking an 11.16% decline. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s modest 0.54% drop over the same period, reflecting significant price pressure on the stock amid mixed market conditions and sector-specific challenges.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>88b96b7d15d75f33e86d02b8e0b48c1d</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 06:44:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A.K.Capital Services Ltd Gains 3.99%: Valuation Shift and Mixed Fundamentals Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/akcapital-services-ltd-gains-399-valuation-shift-and-mixed-fundamentals-shape-the-week-3841038</link><description>A.K.Capital Services Ltd recorded a 3.99% gain over the week ending 13 February 2026, closing at Rs.1,580.35 compared to Rs.1,519.75 the previous Friday. This performance notably outpaced the Sensex, which declined by 0.54% during the same period, reflecting a week of mixed signals where strong price momentum contrasted with a downgrade in valuation and fundamental assessments.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>3e78d288b3beacd53ee7c6900513748d</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 06:44:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pennar Industries Gains 0.42%: 2 Key Factors Driving This Week’s Mixed Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pennar-industries-gains-042-2-key-factors-driving-this-weeks-mixed-momentum-3841037</link><description>Pennar Industries Ltd closed the week with a modest gain of 0.42%, ending at Rs.177.60 on 13 February 2026, marginally outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a strong start with a 5.54% surge on Monday, followed by mixed price movements amid shifting technical momentum and improved valuation metrics. These developments reflect a nuanced market sentiment balancing short-term volatility against longer-term fundamental appeal.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>24843920ba6f52ca7f077377adf9efae</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 06:44:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nava Ltd Declines 1.40% This Week: Mixed Signals Amid Valuation Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nava-ltd-declines-140-this-week-mixed-signals-amid-valuation-pressure-3841036</link><description>Nava Ltd’s stock closed the week ending 13 Feb 2026 at ₹554.50, down 1.40% from ₹562.40 the previous Friday, underperforming the Sensex which declined 0.54% over the same period. The week was marked by a cautious tone amid mixed financial results, a technical momentum shift, and a valuation downgrade, all contributing to subdued investor sentiment despite the company’s strong long-term returns.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>cb135dfb906503e93e1baadc655d5777</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 06:44:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 06:44:41 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>