<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:20:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Are Concord Enviro Systems Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-concord-enviro-systems-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3840636</link><description>Concord Enviro Systems Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, showing a net loss of ₹8.18 crores compared to a profit in the previous quarter, alongside declining revenue and increased costs, indicating operational challenges and reduced investor confidence.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>146ee1fa28e127c7b63e09048d3ff21e</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Stanley Lifestyles Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-stanley-lifestyles-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3840635</link><description>Stanley Lifestyles Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, showing a net loss of -₹0.60 crores, a decline in net sales, and significant margin erosion, indicating operational challenges and waning investor confidence.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>917962e7418408db95b44f04a4c472af</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Akums Drugs &amp; Pharmaceuticals Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-akums-drugs-pharmaceuticals-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3840634</link><description>Akums Drugs &amp; Pharmaceuticals Ltd's latest results show strong operational improvements, with net sales up 14.76% year-on-year and a net profit increase of 62.63% sequentially. However, concerns remain about its low return on equity and underperformance relative to the market, indicating mixed overall performance.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>35152f2e252347395527c7899882409a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Ola Electric Mobility Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-ola-electric-mobility-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3840633</link><description>Ola Electric Mobility Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, showing a net loss of ₹487 crores and a 31.88% revenue decline from the previous quarter, indicating significant operational challenges and a lack of investor confidence. The company faces critical financial difficulties with deteriorating margins and increasing cash burn, raising doubts about its path to profitability.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>67b83076ed1db72f576666add6309269</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Z-Tech (India) Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-z-tech-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3840632</link><description>Z-Tech (India) Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show strong revenue growth of 58.04% year-on-year and improved operating margins, but a low return on equity of 14.91% and signs of slowing growth raise concerns about profitability and valuation sustainability for investors.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>ba590ba72b0861355fc70ee4d7ec81f7</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Platinum Industries Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-platinum-industries-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3840631</link><description>Platinum Industries Ltd's Q3 FY26 results show a gradual recovery with net sales increasing by 6.39% quarter-on-quarter and net profit rising by 8.46%. However, ongoing margin pressures and skepticism about sustainability suggest investors should watch for consistent performance in future quarters.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>628efe1d6903fed5019b32288f0b6485</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Mukka Proteins Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-mukka-proteins-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3840630</link><description>Mukka Proteins Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show strong revenue growth of 167.19% sequentially and 115.57% year-on-year, but profitability is a concern with declining operating margins and a net profit decrease of 9.56% compared to last year. The company faces challenges in maintaining profitability amid high debt levels and interest costs.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>9a7d0aaeaa19c797279b8b94654d41da</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Vraj Iron &amp; Steel Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-vraj-iron-steel-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3840629</link><description>Vraj Iron &amp; Steel Ltd's latest results are concerning, showing an 85.81% decline in net profit to ₹1.10 crore despite a 22.15% revenue growth, indicating significant operational challenges and margin erosion. Investors should watch for improvements in profitability and operational efficiency in upcoming quarters.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>5fe07fd013204decd9eb84640dc87b60</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Vishnu Prakash R Punglia Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-vishnu-prakash-r-punglia-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3840628</link><description>Vishnu Prakash R Punglia Ltd's latest results are concerning, with a net profit decline of 84.62% year-on-year and ongoing revenue struggles, indicating significant operational challenges and a need for strategic improvements.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>1009786c6982ac2d694da5447285b49c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are RBZ Jewellers Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-rbz-jewellers-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3840627</link><description>RBZ Jewellers Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show strong revenue growth with net sales up 56% quarter-on-quarter, but profitability is under pressure with a 6.09% decline in net profit and a significant drop in profit margins. Investors should be cautious due to rising interest costs and negative operational cash flow, alongside concerns from the exit of foreign institutional investors.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>95c1015eaa84128d2863f5eaa9963c60</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Viviana Power Tech Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-viviana-power-tech-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3840626</link><description>Viviana Power Tech Ltd's latest results show impressive revenue growth with net sales up 99.98% sequentially and 226.33% year-on-year, but profitability is a concern as operating and PAT margins have significantly declined, indicating challenges in maintaining sustainable profits. Overall, the results present a mixed outlook with strong market expansion but questions about operational efficiency.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>2505fadfd7d8503986654e6d01736491</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Exicom Tele-Systems Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-exicom-tele-systems-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3840625</link><description>Exicom Tele-Systems Ltd's latest results are concerning, showing a net loss of ₹67.87 crores and a negative operating margin of -11.68%, despite a year-on-year revenue growth of 40.74%. The company faces significant profitability challenges and rising costs, indicating a critical need for strategic intervention.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>133baf552f58329221a933928b90be69</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Plaza Wires Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-plaza-wires-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3840624</link><description>Plaza Wires Ltd's latest results show strong profit growth with a net profit of ₹1.80 crores, up 246.15% quarter-on-quarter, but revenue declined 11.04% from the previous quarter, indicating volatility. While profitability has improved, concerns about low return on equity and high valuation relative to peers suggest caution moving forward.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>9653261fbc080b8562be8a9c687350b2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Blue Jet Healthcare Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-blue-jet-healthcare-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3840623</link><description>Blue Jet Healthcare Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, showing a 39.57% year-on-year decline in net sales and a 59.42% drop in net profit, despite a slight sequential improvement. The company faces significant operational challenges, raising questions about its growth sustainability, although it maintains a strong balance sheet.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>33810eb768599302afc27f8c55ff97bf</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Markolines Pavement Technologies Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-markolines-pavement-technologies-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3840622</link><description>Markolines Pavement Technologies Ltd reported strong Q2 FY26 results with a 54.23% revenue growth and a 135.84% increase in net profit, indicating effective operations despite some margin compression. However, the stock has declined recently, reflecting market challenges that may present investment opportunities.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>5ff39f794ea6e3aabad4bda97a1b0dea</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Khazanchi Jewellers Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-khazanchi-jewellers-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3840621</link><description>Khazanchi Jewellers Ltd's latest results show moderate growth, with net sales increasing by 7.37% to ₹589.02 crores and net profit rising by 6.71% to ₹25.13 crores, indicating a slowdown compared to previous quarters driven by festive demand. While the company continues to grow, the pace has diminished, reflecting market adjustments and the need for operational efficiency.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>ceb670c42ce43ffee27150593b686e14</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Rategain Travel Technologies Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-rategain-travel-technologies-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3840620</link><description>RateGain Travel Technologies Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth with net sales up 83% quarter-on-quarter, but profitability has declined sharply, with net profit down 48% from the previous quarter, raising concerns about sustainability and cost management. While the balance sheet is solid, the significant drop in profit margins indicates challenges ahead.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>12dc2514509f8c0dfcf63d92127af70f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Dollex Agrotech Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-dollex-agrotech-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3840619</link><description>Dollex Agrotech Ltd's latest results are mixed; while net profit increased significantly quarter-on-quarter, it declined year-on-year, and net sales dropped sharply, raising concerns about revenue sustainability and high financial risk due to leverage and governance issues.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>a66e2334d770d28374ae2b86bbbf8e62</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Prevest Denpro Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-prevest-denpro-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3840618</link><description>Prevest Denpro Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results are strong, with net sales of ₹18.64 crores and a net profit of ₹5.54 crores, reflecting significant quarter-on-quarter growth of 18.20% and 25.62%, respectively. The company shows improved operational efficiency and a solid balance sheet, although ongoing monitoring of financial metrics is advised.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>f37efd1a774e21f91943dd6ace22a4f9</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Trejhara Solutions Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-trejhara-solutions-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3840617</link><description>Trejhara Solutions Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show strong year-on-year sales growth of 426.64% but a concerning sequential decline in net profit by 66.11%, raising questions about operational stability and profitability sustainability. Overall, while revenue growth is impressive, the significant drop in profit and low return metrics indicate challenges ahead.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>19807a50ad38e08d5addfd843630f0a7</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>