<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:29:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Standard Enginnering Technology Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-standard-enginnering-technology-ltd-fallingrising-3838787</link><description>On 13-Feb, Standard Engineering Technology Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.81% to close at ₹129.50. This drop comes amid a series of negative trends including underperformance relative to its sector, declining investor participation, and technical indicators signalling pressure on the stock.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>974ec1c88003595524f88b78ba369cfb</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:29:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sahasra Electronic Solutions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sahasra-electronic-solutions-ltd-fallingrising-3838786</link><description>As of 13-Feb, Sahasra Electronic Solutions Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.98% to ₹267.30. This drop reflects a broader pattern of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and diminishing investor participation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c13a2a918eec26c82710f5fc2bd32b8d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:29:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Rajputana Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-rajputana-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3838785</link><description>On 13-Feb, Rajputana Industries Ltd witnessed a notable uptick in its share price, rising by 3.49% to close at ₹80.00. This gain stands out against a backdrop of mixed performance over recent periods and fluctuating investor participation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2303d66f638956f1b5f442bac78e1515</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:29:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-awfis-space-solutions-ltd-fallingrising-3838784</link><description>On 13-Feb, AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, falling 10.07% to ₹324.00, marking a new 52-week and all-time low of ₹321.2. This drop reflects a continuation of a downward trend that has seen the stock lose over 18% in the past four days amid broader concerns about its financial health and market performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a74e00281da195fcfe5cca3b722666f1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:29:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Enser Communications Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-enser-communications-ltd-fallingrising-3838783</link><description>On 13-Feb, Enser Communications Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, falling by 11.72% to close at ₹11.30, marking a continuation of a prolonged downward trend that has significantly underperformed the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>042b0e52f18e4f4b129c2af2e6446596</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:29:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Epack Durable Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-epack-durable-ltd-fallingrising-3838782</link><description>On 13-Feb, Epack Durable Ltd’s stock price fell by 2.48% to close at ₹249.95, continuing a recent downward trend driven by disappointing financial results, deteriorating profitability, and waning promoter confidence.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1cbbb43a7301ad4f41a6a49f25aeef70</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:29:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Medi Assist Healthcare Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-medi-assist-healthcare-services-ltd-fallingrising-3838781</link><description>On 13-Feb, Medi Assist Healthcare Services Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.95% to close at ₹404.25. This drop reflects a continuation of recent negative trends driven by disappointing quarterly financial results and valuation pressures, despite the company’s strong long-term fundamentals.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d55efde3b981f9dd990d43f83aa84740</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:29:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vedant Fashions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vedant-fashions-ltd-fallingrising-3838780</link><description>On 13-Feb, Vedant Fashions Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, closing at ₹455.00, down ₹24.8 or 5.17% for the day. This drop marks a continuation of a downward trend that has persisted over recent weeks, reflecting broader concerns about the company’s financial performance and valuation metrics relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>dc9b10041168e4f817c38fd6a4de1a4a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:29:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Divgi Torqtransfer Systems Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-divgi-torqtransfer-systems-ltd-fallingrising-3838779</link><description>On 13-Feb, Divgi Torqtransfer Systems Ltd witnessed a significant surge in its share price, rising by 14.3% to ₹745.55, reflecting robust quarterly performance and sustained market outperformance against benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>bb70a3484aa46b6c1eb64571b796aea8</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:29:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Tega Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-tega-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3838778</link><description>On 13-Feb, Tega Industries Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, falling by 6.03% to close at ₹1,656.60. This drop reflects mounting investor concerns following disappointing quarterly results and valuation pressures despite the company’s strong long-term performance metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6901ae9e4552a5eb9db68f73c3c86407</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:29:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Euro Panel Products Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-euro-panel-products-ltd-fallingrising-3838777</link><description>On 13-Feb, Euro Panel Products Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 1.57% to ₹187.90 despite opening the day with a gap down. This upward movement contrasts with the broader sector's decline and reflects the stock's resilience and recent positive momentum.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c5ed74c4f7b749fd61a7b245c7e57c99</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:29:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ksolves India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ksolves-india-ltd-fallingrising-3838776</link><description>On 13-Feb, Ksolves India Ltd witnessed a significant drop in its share price, falling by 5.58% to close at ₹284.45. This decline follows a two-day losing streak, reflecting a notable shift in investor sentiment despite the stock's recent outperformance against broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ea1bac36bd0e039d3eb7053b39c6501a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:29:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Nila Spaces Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-nila-spaces-ltd-fallingrising-3838775</link><description>On 13-Feb, Nila Spaces Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, falling by 1.79% to close at ₹14.25. This drop comes amid a broader short-term downtrend despite the company’s robust long-term financial performance and positive quarterly results.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f9fba51b9136bc8b529ffffabc6e9a4f</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:29:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Cohance Lifesciences Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-cohance-lifesciences-ltd-fallingrising-3838774</link><description>On 13-Feb, Cohance Lifesciences Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, falling nearly 10% to close at ₹315.60, marking a new 52-week low. This steep drop reflects a combination of disappointing financial results, sustained underperformance relative to benchmarks, and heightened market concerns over promoter share pledging.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b805b4a39a841e1ac220a8772ce6393f</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:29:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vikas Lifecare Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vikas-lifecare-ltd-fallingrising-3838773</link><description>On 13-Feb, Vikas Lifecare Ltd’s stock price continued its downward trajectory, closing at ₹1.61, down 0.62% from the previous session. The stock’s persistent decline reflects a combination of weak price momentum, falling investor participation, and sustained underperformance relative to key market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>dde46db1817fbe1da8369ac45ba3aeae</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:29:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Marine Electricals (India) Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-marine-electricals-india-ltd-fallingrising-3838772</link><description>As of 13-Feb, Marine Electricals (India) Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.92% to ₹182.71. This drop reflects a broader underperformance relative to market benchmarks and sector peers, despite the company’s strong operational metrics and long-term growth trajectory.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6dc1250deed64e505a0ba21b60b6ebc6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:29:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Omfurn India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-omfurn-india-ltd-fallingrising-3838771</link><description>On 13-Feb, Omfurn India Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 6.49% to close at ₹63.40. This sharp drop comes despite the stock's strong one-week performance, highlighting a complex interplay of market dynamics and investor sentiment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>65aff24a2572e82f8d7748f7fff0d6f3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:29:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is GCM Securities Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gcm-securities-ltd-fallingrising-3838770</link><description>On 13-Feb, GCM Securities Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 5.41% to close at ₹0.70. This drop reflects a continuation of a broader downtrend that has persisted over multiple timeframes, significantly underperforming the benchmark Sensex and its sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f74c69a1b69c8464ec20ef0796645d67</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:29:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Magadh Sugar &amp; Energy Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-magadh-sugar-energy-ltd-fallingrising-3838769</link><description>As of 13-Feb, Magadh Sugar &amp; Energy Ltd’s stock price has fallen sharply, reflecting a combination of disappointing recent financial results, sustained underperformance relative to benchmarks, and subdued investor confidence.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8321ff3110123500f7abeeab1e0825c0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:29:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ahimsa Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ahimsa-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3838768</link><description>On 13-Feb, Ahimsa Industries Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, closing at ₹24.85 with a gain of ₹1.15 or 4.85%. This upward movement stands out against the broader market trends, reflecting a combination of strong technical indicators and increased investor interest.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7ffff22952c286d4385a3b71f84b6dea</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:29:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:29:57 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>