<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:23:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>When is the next results date for Viji Finance Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-viji-finance-ltd-3776730</link><description>The next results date for Viji Finance Ltd is January 6, 2026.
Time: 37 minutes ago</description><guid>eb1ee1da946c273ca3641f468820b5c8</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:23:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When is the next results date for Anand Rathi Wealth Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-anand-rathi-wealth-ltd-3776729</link><description>The next results date for Anand Rathi Wealth Ltd is January 12, 2026.
Time: 37 minutes ago</description><guid>9cafc03dcdac794406b60b6f95817eb5</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:23:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When is the next results date for Globus Spirits Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-globus-spirits-ltd-3776728</link><description>The next results date for Globus Spirits Ltd is January 9, 2026.
Time: 37 minutes ago</description><guid>97cfdb3244b9d564c4a75590b2d9970b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:23:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When is the next results date for Mangalore Refinery &amp; Petrochemicals Ltd.?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-mangalore-refinery-petrochemicals-ltd-3776727</link><description>The next results date for Mangalore Refinery &amp; Petrochemicals Ltd. is 15 January 2026.
Time: 37 minutes ago</description><guid>07aba8af79d783d12e0f3b74288d54ef</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:23:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>What is the bonus history of Pro Fin Capital?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/what-is-the-bonus-history-of-pro-fin-capital-3776725</link><description>Pro Fin Capital's most recent bonus was a 1:1 issue announced for January 2, 2026, following a 2:1 bonus issued on April 29, 2022. The company has a history of rewarding shareholders through bonus issues.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>d251e7f3a169487f8b49c0e434204bb7</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:23:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lupin Added to Mojo Stocks: A Strategic Inclusion Backed by Robust Financials</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/mojo-premium/lupin-added-to-mojo-stocks-a-strategic-inclusion-backed-by-robust-financials-3776724</link><description>Lupin, a leading large-cap pharmaceutical company, has been added to the prestigious Mojo Stocks list as of 31 December 2025, reflecting its robust financial performance and strategic fit within the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector. This inclusion underscores Lupin’s strong fundamentals, impressive quarterly growth, and attractive valuation metrics, making it a compelling choice for investors seeking exposure to quality pharma stocks with sustainable growth prospects.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>be57be0e17e8037e8555676e03b43d87</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:23:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DDev Plastiks Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ddev-plastiks-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3776697</link><description>DDev Plastiks Industries Ltd, a small-cap player in the Specialty Chemicals sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, raising concerns about the stock’s near-term momentum and long-term strength.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>2ef7462661e8295af689cf05cd8c3a6a</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:23:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manorama Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/manorama-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3776695</link><description>Manorama Industries Ltd, a prominent player in the FMCG sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential shift towards a bearish trend, raising concerns about the stock's near-term momentum and long-term strength despite its strong historical performance.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>4ddcf1919be3011cb29c63bd2147eb34</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:23:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elitecon International Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/elitecon-international-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3776696</link><description>Elitecon International Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term momentum and investor sentiment.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>a4a765c12239b1d909992d24741a97be</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:23:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Advanced Enzyme Technologies Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/advanced-enzyme-technologies-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3776693</link><description>Advanced Enzyme Technologies Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a prolonged bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>b08a5e17ddd14d73f337c1eeb4520295</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:23:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Olectra Greentech Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/olectra-greentech-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3776692</link><description>Olectra Greentech Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>9d49e4038b0f863cc90c363a35b98f2d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:23:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sikozy Realtors Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sikozy-realtors-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3776689</link><description>Sikozy Realtors Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Realty sector, has recently formed a Death Cross as its 50-day moving average (DMA) crossed below the 200-DMA, signalling a significant bearish trend and potential long-term weakness for the stock. This technical development, coupled with deteriorating fundamentals and weak price performance, underscores growing investor caution.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>82e8c14ae9481b2d88478eabae08eaec</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:23:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>B2B Software Technologies Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/b2b-software-technologies-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3776690</link><description>B2B Software Technologies Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a sustained bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>bf3f4859c0dbc6bb272c8e114e5e5c45</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:23:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nalwa Sons Investments Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nalwa-sons-investments-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3776686</link><description>Nalwa Sons Investments Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development highlights a deterioration in the stock’s short- to medium-term momentum, raising concerns about sustained weakness in the coming months.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>c05021c90c884f583252d3722e414365</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:23:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>One Point One Solutions Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/one-point-one-solutions-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3776691</link><description>One Point One Solutions Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout, suggesting a shift in long-term momentum and a possible trend reversal for the stock within the Commercial Services &amp; Supplies sector.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>51c2b9e6a151c38fe5aaee8abeecea24</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:23:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ludlow Jute &amp; Specialities Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ludlow-jute-specialities-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3776685</link><description>Ludlow Jute &amp; Specialities Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s short- to medium-term momentum and raising concerns about its near-term outlook.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>706ff1d3560550101083390c5a249cb7</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:23:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Road Network Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Indicating Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-road-network-ltd-forms-golden-cross-indicating-potential-bullish-breakout-3776694</link><description>Bharat Road Network Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, suggesting that the stock could be poised for an upward trend reversal despite its challenging recent performance.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>87e88e7077a081b4ca8d232e72818324</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:23:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:23:25 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>