<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 04:00:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Sensex Edges Higher Amid Mixed Sectoral Trends; Telecom Leads Gains</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-edges-higher-amid-mixed-sectoral-trends-telecom-leads-gains-3786561</link><description>The Indian equity market witnessed a cautious session on 9 Jan 2026, with the Sensex eking out a marginal gain of 0.02% to close at 84,198.56, recovering from an early dip. While large caps showed resilience, mid and small caps struggled, reflecting a mixed market breadth amid subdued global cues and sectoral divergence.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>1240f436d3607f6106cbe75741bdbf2c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 04:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Max Healthcare Institute Ltd Faces Downgrade Amidst Nifty 50 Membership and Market Challenges</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/max-healthcare-institute-ltd-faces-downgrade-amidst-nifty-50-membership-and-market-challenges-3786560</link><description>Max Healthcare Institute Ltd, a prominent hospital sector large-cap stock and a constituent of the Nifty 50 index, has recently undergone a notable downgrade in its Mojo Grade from Hold to Sell as of 31 Oct 2025. This shift comes amid a challenging performance trajectory and evolving institutional holding patterns, raising questions about its benchmark status and future prospects within India’s premier equity index.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>55b5c14a4865fb6628bfb7395f4f15d7</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 04:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HDFC Life Insurance: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hdfc-life-insurance-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-mixed-market-signals-3786559</link><description>HDFC Life Insurance Company Ltd continues to assert its position as a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, reflecting its stature within India’s insurance sector. Despite recent short-term price pressures, the company’s large-cap status, institutional holding patterns, and benchmark implications underscore its significance for investors and market participants alike.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>6cf880f4d8f7c9ce3bd52e5637119c89</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 04:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sbi-life-insurance-company-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-3786557</link><description>SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd continues to assert its prominence within the Nifty 50 index, reflecting robust institutional interest and outperforming key benchmarks. Despite a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade to Hold, the stock’s sustained gains and strategic positioning in the insurance sector underscore its significance for investors tracking India’s blue-chip equities.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>4abd93fcaeb400b3ed0fb7ddf7e079b4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 04:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Auto Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-auto-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-3786558</link><description>Bajaj Auto Ltd, a stalwart in the Indian automobile sector and a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to demonstrate resilience and strategic significance amid evolving market conditions. Recent upgrades in its Mojo Grade and sustained outperformance against the Sensex underscore its growing appeal among institutional investors and benchmark trackers alike.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>3692860d11848edee300a767e4efb8eb</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 04:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maruti Suzuki India Ltd Strengthens Position as Nifty 50 Constituent Amid Institutional Interest</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/maruti-suzuki-india-ltd-strengthens-position-as-nifty-50-constituent-amid-institutional-interest-3786556</link><description>Maruti Suzuki India Ltd, a stalwart in the Indian automobile sector and a key Nifty 50 constituent, continues to demonstrate robust market performance and growing institutional confidence. With a recent upgrade in its Mojo Grade to 'Buy' and a market capitalisation exceeding ₹5.22 lakh crores, the company is poised to maintain its benchmark status while delivering superior returns relative to the broader market.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>b079baaf75f139bcd84a1d69bbf11728</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 04:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Finance Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-finance-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-3786555</link><description>Bajaj Finance Ltd continues to assert its prominence within the Nifty 50 index, reflecting robust institutional interest and a nuanced performance trajectory. Despite recent market headwinds, the company’s sustained large-cap status and strategic positioning in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector underscore its critical role in benchmark indices and investor portfolios alike.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>1ece9ed883641672c4d93de26b8f92eb</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 04:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd Faces Headwinds Despite Nifty 50 Inclusion</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-motors-passenger-vehicles-ltd-faces-headwinds-despite-nifty-50-inclusion-3786553</link><description>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd, a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to face headwinds as it grapples with underperformance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices. Despite its large-cap status and significant market presence, recent trends reveal a deteriorating outlook, reflected in its downgraded mojo grade and subdued price action, raising questions about its near-term trajectory and institutional investor sentiment.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>599a21ee3d6505d265b5d4e3126bd60b</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 04:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Market Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sun-pharmaceutical-industries-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-market-dynamics-3786551</link><description>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd, a stalwart in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, continues to assert its significance as a Nifty 50 constituent. Despite recent modest declines, the company’s robust institutional holdings and benchmark status underpin its strategic importance in India’s equity markets.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>80f1a3d8a783176f8950b6af81a1bca2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 04:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Ltd Strengthens Position as Nifty 50 Constituent Amid Institutional Interest</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mahindra-mahindra-ltd-strengthens-position-as-nifty-50-constituent-amid-institutional-interest-3786554</link><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Ltd (M&amp;M), a stalwart in the Indian automobile sector, continues to consolidate its stature as a key Nifty 50 constituent. Recent developments highlight a notable upgrade in its investment appeal, driven by robust fundamentals, institutional holding dynamics, and its critical role within the benchmark index.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>0ae2bedee60598fd20be54ea70be0938</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 04:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Finserv Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-finserv-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-3786552</link><description>Bajaj Finserv Ltd, a prominent holding company within India’s financial sector, continues to command significant attention as a Nifty 50 constituent. Despite recent market fluctuations and a downgrade in its Mojo Grade from Buy to Hold, the company’s robust long-term performance and strategic positioning within the benchmark index underscore its importance for investors and institutional stakeholders alike.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>ed93320e03d97e5c116e0b9f86291cdd</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 04:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Enterprises Ltd Faces Continued Pressure Amid Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-enterprises-ltd-faces-continued-pressure-amid-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-shifts-3786549</link><description>Adani Enterprises Ltd, a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to grapple with downward momentum as institutional investors recalibrate their holdings. Despite its large-cap status and diversified business model, the stock’s recent performance and valuation metrics highlight growing concerns among market participants, underscoring the challenges of maintaining benchmark relevance amid evolving market dynamics.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>e13a0727463e2e27181ab9b7d206b197</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 04:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Mahindra Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amid Mixed Performance and Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tech-mahindra-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-mixed-performance-and-institutional-shifts-3786550</link><description>Tech Mahindra Ltd., a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to command attention amid evolving institutional holdings and benchmark implications. Despite recent volatility, the company’s large-cap stature and sectoral positioning in Computers - Software &amp; Consulting underscore its strategic importance in India’s equity landscape.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>2534140749dd5b8d1fafb5061825f6db</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 04:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Unilever Ltd Faces Sell Downgrade Amid Mixed Performance and Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-unilever-ltd-faces-sell-downgrade-amid-mixed-performance-and-institutional-shifts-3786547</link><description>Hindustan Unilever Ltd (HUL), a stalwart of India’s FMCG sector and a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, has experienced a nuanced performance trajectory amid shifting market dynamics and institutional investor behaviour. Despite its large-cap stature and benchmark status, recent downgrades and subdued returns highlight challenges in maintaining its growth momentum in a competitive environment.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>b776396d5c19dad53d2d1a8f54445c8e</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 04:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Ports &amp; Special Economic Zone Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-ports-special-economic-zone-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-shifts-3786539</link><description>Adani Ports &amp; Special Economic Zone Ltd (APSEZ), a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to demonstrate resilience amid recent market fluctuations. Despite a modest decline in the short term, the stock’s long-term performance and strategic positioning within the transport infrastructure sector underscore its significance for institutional investors and benchmark indices alike.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>36285f99b1384e74a0647202a54f3eb6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 04:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Grasim Industries Ltd Strengthens Position as Key Nifty 50 Constituent Amid Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/grasim-industries-ltd-strengthens-position-as-key-nifty-50-constituent-amid-institutional-shifts-3786544</link><description>Grasim Industries Ltd, a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, has recently seen its Mojo Grade upgraded from Hold to Buy, reflecting improved investor sentiment and robust fundamentals. This upgrade, coupled with its significant market capitalisation and steady institutional interest, underscores the company’s growing influence within the Cement &amp; Cement Products sector and its impact on benchmark indices.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>5da72df1834ba6c8248286dce0cb0b11</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 04:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oil &amp; Natural Gas Corporation Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amid Mixed Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/oil-natural-gas-corporation-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-mixed-performance-3786541</link><description>Oil &amp; Natural Gas Corporation Ltd. (ONGC), a stalwart in India’s oil sector and a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, has recently experienced notable shifts in institutional holdings and market performance. Despite a challenging year marked by a 10.57% decline against the Sensex’s 8.68% gain, ONGC’s large-cap status and high dividend yield continue to attract investor attention amid evolving benchmark dynamics.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>ca3322961abb37df51cf8748e0edc83c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 04:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reliance Industries Ltd: Navigating Market Pressures Amidst Nifty 50 Benchmark Status</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/reliance-industries-ltd-navigating-market-pressures-amidst-nifty-50-benchmark-status-3786542</link><description>Reliance Industries Ltd, a cornerstone of the Indian equity market and a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, has experienced a turbulent trading phase recently. Despite a strong long-term track record outperforming the Sensex, the stock has faced short-term headwinds, reflected in a five-day consecutive decline. This article analyses the implications of its index membership, recent institutional holding trends, and the broader impact on benchmark performance.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>72f6fe1067496abc3dd8c5df5c0c13c8</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 04:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cipla Ltd: Navigating Challenges Amidst Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cipla-ltd-navigating-challenges-amidst-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-shifts-3786545</link><description>Cipla Ltd., a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index and a stalwart in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, has recently undergone a notable downgrade by MarketsMOJO, shifting from a Hold to a Sell rating. This development comes amid subdued price performance relative to the broader market and evolving institutional holding patterns, raising questions about the stock’s near-term outlook and its role within the benchmark index.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>7b6320069c08ef7cb772962a519fb82e</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 04:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Steel Ltd Strengthens Position as Nifty 50 Constituent Amid Robust Institutional Interest</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-steel-ltd-strengthens-position-as-nifty-50-constituent-amid-robust-institutional-interest-3786546</link><description>Tata Steel Ltd continues to assert its prominence within the Nifty 50 index, buoyed by strong financial metrics, a recent upgrade to a 'Strong Buy' rating, and sustained outperformance relative to the benchmark Sensex. As a key player in the ferrous metals sector, the company’s evolving institutional holdings and market cap dynamics underscore its critical role in shaping index movements and investor sentiment.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>af33769abfc9c128bc36525e96740f02</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 04:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 04:00:29 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>