<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:55:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Deepak Builders &amp; Engineers India Faces Challenging Market Conditions Amid Revised Evaluation</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/deepak-builders-engineers-india-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-weak-financials-and-bearish-technicals-3763458</link><description>Deepak Builders &amp; Engineers India is currently navigating a difficult phase as recent assessment changes reflect a more cautious market outlook. The construction sector stock has experienced notable shifts across key evaluation parameters including quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators, signalling a complex investment environment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>569f872e89a81b725c8dfdea1daf4d1b</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kross Ltd: Analytical Perspective Shifts Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/kross-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-deteriorating-technicals-and-financial-trends-3763457</link><description>Kross Ltd, a key player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has experienced a revision in its market assessment following recent changes across multiple evaluation parameters. The company’s financial performance, valuation metrics, technical indicators, and quality factors have all contributed to a nuanced shift in analytical perspective, reflecting both challenges and opportunities in the current market environment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f9f35b44cb265e66d9073c356930c5c0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sai Silks (Kalamandir) Faces Mixed Signals Amidst Market and Financial Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sai-silks-kalamandir-downgraded-to-sell-amid-technical-weakness-and-growth-concerns-3763454</link><description>Sai Silks (Kalamandir), a notable player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, is currently navigating a complex market environment marked by contrasting technical indicators and financial metrics. Recent shifts in market assessment reflect a nuanced picture shaped by valuation, financial trends, quality of earnings, and technical signals, all of which are influencing investor sentiment and positioning.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>91fad8a864b6ce80a5e7c294453fabdc</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tatva Chintan Pharma Chem: Analytical Perspective Shift Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/tatva-chintan-pharma-chem-downgraded-to-hold-amid-mixed-technical-and-valuation-signals-3763456</link><description>Tatva Chintan Pharma Chem, a key player in the Specialty Chemicals sector, has experienced a revision in its market assessment following a detailed evaluation of its quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. This article examines the factors influencing the recent changes in the company’s analytical perspective, highlighting the interplay between its robust quarterly performance and evolving technical signals.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>844d4c5e5ed0c4ed965e29c38ce69100</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Antony Waste Handling Cell Sees Shift in Market Assessment Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/antony-waste-handling-cell-upgraded-to-sell-on-technical-improvements-despite-financial-challenges-3763452</link><description>Antony Waste Handling Cell has experienced a notable shift in market assessment following recent changes in its technical indicators and financial performance. While the stock has shown some positive price movement in the short term, underlying financial metrics and longer-term returns present a complex picture for investors navigating the Other Utilities sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>abc0b9ca07d479247200f4a18123c00a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Orissa Bengal Carrier’s Market Assessment Reflects Mixed Signals Amid Financial and Technical Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/orissa-bengal-carrier-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-weak-financials-and-technical-setbacks-3763449</link><description>Orissa Bengal Carrier, a key player in the transport services sector, has experienced a revision in its market evaluation following a detailed analysis of its financial performance, valuation metrics, technical indicators, and overall quality parameters. This article explores the factors influencing the recent shift in market assessment and what they imply for investors and stakeholders.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7de7dfcff90313332ffa6a18aa6edbce</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Galactico Corporate Services Faces Challenging Market Dynamics Amid Revised Evaluation</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/galactico-corporate-services-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-weak-fundamentals-and-bearish-technicals-3763453</link><description>Galactico Corporate Services, a player in the diversified sector, is currently navigating a complex market environment as recent assessment changes reflect shifts across multiple evaluation parameters. The company’s financial trends, valuation metrics, technical indicators, and overall quality have all contributed to a nuanced market assessment, underscoring the challenges and opportunities ahead for investors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9f60cbdee7ecd473138759001814e68a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kwality Pharmaceuticals Sees Shift in Market Assessment Amid Strong Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/kwality-pharmaceuticals-upgraded-to-buy-on-strong-financials-and-technical-momentum-3763451</link><description>Kwality Pharmaceuticals has experienced a notable revision in its market evaluation, driven by a combination of robust financial results, attractive valuation metrics, and evolving technical indicators. The company’s recent performance across key parameters highlights a nuanced outlook for investors in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f94f8a9e386cdc18943a4f442f1ce4ab</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Inani Marbles &amp; Industries: Analytical Review Highlights Key Evaluation Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/inani-marbles-industries-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-weak-fundamentals-and-bearish-technicals-3763450</link><description>Inani Marbles &amp; Industries has undergone a revision in its market assessment, reflecting notable shifts across quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. This comprehensive analysis explores the factors influencing the company’s current standing within the miscellaneous sector, providing investors with a detailed understanding of its recent performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c6468477655e6a61b9348cf10248d414</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shukra Bullions Sees Shift in Market Assessment Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/shukra-bullions-stock-rating-upgraded-to-sell-amid-mixed-technical-and-fundamental-signals-3763448</link><description>Shukra Bullions, a key player in the diversified commercial services sector, has experienced a notable shift in market assessment driven by evolving technical trends and a complex financial backdrop. While the company’s recent quarter reflected flat financial performance, changes in technical indicators and valuation metrics have influenced the overall evaluation of the stock.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a01124400d1f6cab06b133184b6c8a6c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pasupati Acrylon's Market Assessment Reflects Balanced Outlook Amid Mixed Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/pasupati-acrylon-downgraded-to-buy-amid-mixed-technical-and-valuation-signals-3763455</link><description>Pasupati Acrylon, a key player in the petrochemicals sector, has recently undergone a revision in its market evaluation, reflecting nuanced shifts across quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. This article analyses the factors influencing the company's current standing and what they imply for investors navigating the evolving market landscape.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>befdc8877a5ef774282bb2cc56ba96cb</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shrydus Industries: Analytical Reassessment Reflects Market and Financial Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/shrydus-industries-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-weak-financials-and-bearish-technicals-3763447</link><description>Shrydus Industries, a player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has undergone a revision in its evaluation reflecting shifts in technical indicators, valuation metrics, financial trends, and market sentiment. This reassessment highlights the complexities facing the company amid challenging market conditions and evolving investor perspectives.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5615b48829a637c1fba773a5fa3c3b41</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Steel Authority Of India: Analytical Perspective Shifts Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/steel-authority-of-india-downgraded-to-sell-amid-technical-and-financial-concerns-3763445</link><description>Steel Authority Of India has experienced a revision in its market assessment following a detailed review of its quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. This article explores the factors influencing the recent changes in analytical perspective, providing investors with a comprehensive understanding of the company’s current standing within the ferrous metals sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ccd02f371fc8c56cd2e904d51b5bea33</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AVI Products India: Analytical Perspective Shift Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/avi-products-india-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-weak-financials-and-mixed-technical-signals-3763443</link><description>AVI Products India, a player in the Trading &amp; Distributors sector, has experienced a revision in its market assessment following a detailed analysis of its quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. This article explores the factors influencing the recent changes in the company’s evaluation metrics, providing investors with a comprehensive understanding of its current standing.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>72680be16618d2b82aae631b69568582</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Greenlam Industries Faces Mixed Signals Amidst Market and Financial Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/greenlam-industries-downgraded-to-sell-amid-weak-financials-and-technical-signals-3763442</link><description>Greenlam Industries, a key player in the plywood boards and laminates sector, has experienced a notable shift in its market evaluation following recent developments across technical indicators, financial performance, valuation metrics, and investor participation. This article analyses the factors influencing the company’s current standing and what they imply for investors navigating the evolving landscape.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>31d4e5120a8bdbe12e17984d59a9ea7c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adarsh Plant Protect Sees Shift in Market Assessment Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/adarsh-plant-protect-stock-rating-upgraded-to-sell-on-technical-improvements-3763441</link><description>Adarsh Plant Protect, a player in the Pesticides &amp; Agrochemicals sector, has experienced a notable shift in its market evaluation, reflecting a complex interplay of technical indicators and financial fundamentals. While technical trends suggest a more optimistic outlook, the company’s financial performance continues to present challenges, prompting a nuanced reassessment of its investment profile.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ed1eb7106dd7bd801ec109ef38930e73</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ingersoll-Rand (India) Faces Shift in Market Assessment Amidst Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ingersoll-rand-india-downgraded-to-sell-amid-technical-weakness-and-valuation-concerns-3763440</link><description>Ingersoll-Rand (India), a key player in the Compressors, Pumps &amp; Diesel Engines sector, has experienced a notable shift in its market evaluation, reflecting a complex interplay of technical indicators, valuation metrics, financial trends, and overall quality considerations. This article analyses the factors influencing the recent revision in the company’s assessment, providing investors with a comprehensive understanding of the current market stance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7ee61b2bc3f8d67f378960c03cd70001</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Welspun Specialty Solutions Sees Shift in Market Assessment Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/welspun-specialty-solutions-upgraded-to-hold-on-technical-improvement-and-financial-performance-3763444</link><description>Welspun Specialty Solutions, a key player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, has experienced a notable revision in its market evaluation following recent developments across technical indicators, financial performance, valuation metrics, and long-term trends. This article analyses the factors influencing the shift in market assessment and what they imply for investors navigating the current landscape.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>83f7d6a8981f200365bc3ad7c1d3a57f</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Garuda Construction and Engineering: Technical Momentum Shifts Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/garuda-construction-and-engineering-sees-mixed-technical-signals-amid-price-momentum-shift-3763439</link><description>Garuda Construction and Engineering has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, reflecting a complex interplay of market forces and indicator signals. While the stock’s year-to-date return stands at a robust 47.5%, technical parameters suggest a transition from a mildly bullish trend to a more sideways movement, prompting a closer examination of key indicators such as MACD, RSI, and moving averages.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>eff740a564b23b7ae860f8ee38809929</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deepak Builders &amp; Engineers India Faces Bearish Momentum Amid Technical Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/deepak-builders-engineers-india-faces-intensified-bearish-momentum-amid-technical-deterioration-3763437</link><description>Deepak Builders &amp; Engineers India, a key player in the construction sector, is currently exhibiting a shift in technical momentum with several indicators signalling a bearish trend. The stock’s recent price movements and technical parameters suggest a cautious outlook as it navigates a challenging market environment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f0699f8cf8dc5241338f1d45ef2ba329</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 03:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>