<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 12:36:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Mixed Earnings Momentum as Nearly Half of 925 Stocks Report Dec-2025 Quarterly Results</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/mixed-earnings-momentum-as-nearly-half-of-925-stocks-report-dec-2025-quarterly-results-3813234</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has unfolded with a mixed bag of results as 925 companies declared their financials, reflecting a cautious yet improving corporate performance environment. While the overall proportion of companies reporting positive results has risen to 49.0%, sectoral and market capitalisation segments reveal divergent trends that investors should carefully analyse.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>46ec19142861a0909238e8e90295bda6</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 12:36:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AXISCADES Technologies Gains 6.66%: 2 Key Factors Driving This Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/axiscades-technologies-gains-666-2-key-factors-driving-this-weeks-momentum-3813232</link><description>AXISCADES Technologies Ltd recorded a solid weekly gain of 6.66%, closing at ₹1,229.60 on 30 Jan 2026, outperforming the Sensex which rose 1.62% over the same period. The stock showed a volatile but ultimately bullish trajectory, driven by a sharp rebound after an initial dip and a notable upper circuit hit amid strong buying interest. Despite mixed technical signals and a Hold rating, the week’s price action reflected renewed investor confidence and robust liquidity.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>a64187c344c05c2a1eca9e4026d9fca3</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 12:36:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>State Bank of India Gains 4.68%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/state-bank-of-india-gains-468-6-key-factors-driving-the-rally-3813230</link><description>State Bank of India (SBI) delivered a strong weekly performance from 26 to 30 January 2026, gaining 4.68% to close at Rs.1,077.55, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% rise over the same period. The stock hit multiple new 52-week and all-time highs during the week, reflecting robust momentum amid mixed market conditions and sectoral fluctuations. This review analyses the key events that shaped SBI’s price action and market positioning throughout the week.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>c5a3182b12651b334cb2127673f6b3ea</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 12:36:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Winsome Yarns Ltd Falls 4.47%: 4 Key Events Shaping This Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/winsome-yarns-ltd-falls-447-4-key-events-shaping-this-weeks-volatility-3813231</link><description>Winsome Yarns Ltd experienced a turbulent week from 26 to 30 January 2026, closing down 4.47% at Rs.1.71 despite the Sensex gaining 1.62% over the same period. The stock oscillated between lower and upper circuit limits multiple times amid heavy selling pressure and sporadic buying interest, reflecting persistent volatility and investor uncertainty in this micro-cap garment sector player.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>b574a41cc5e9549a09222ed4ea75128b</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 12:36:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ICRA Ltd Gains 6.75%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Move</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/icra-ltd-gains-675-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-move-3813227</link><description>ICRA Ltd’s stock advanced 6.75% over the week ending 30 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% gain. The week was marked by a mix of strong price rallies, flat quarterly financial results amid margin pressures, and a shift in technical momentum to a mildly bearish stance. Despite challenges in profitability, the stock demonstrated resilience with notable intraday gains and volume-supported accumulation, reflecting a complex but cautiously optimistic market sentiment.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>67580767ff350beeb8abc7cf78f29942</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 12:36:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jindal Drilling &amp; Industries Ltd Falls 5.11% Amid Intensified Bearish Momentum: 4 Key Factors Driving the Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jindal-drilling-industries-ltd-falls-511-amid-intensified-bearish-momentum-4-key-factors-driving-the-decline-3813229</link><description>Jindal Drilling &amp; Industries Ltd experienced a challenging week ending 30 January 2026, with its share price declining 5.11% from Rs.506.45 to Rs.480.55, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.62% over the same period. The stock faced intensified bearish momentum, hitting fresh 52-week lows and enduring significant volatility amid mixed technical signals and disappointing quarterly results.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>86cb038df2ef8a43ceaa732d01ac9c75</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 12:36:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tanla Platforms Gains 6.35%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tanla-platforms-gains-635-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-rally-3813225</link><description>Tanla Platforms Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, rising 6.35% from Rs.481.60 to Rs.512.20 between 26 and 30 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% gain over the same period. The stock’s trajectory was shaped by a volatile start, a strong midweek rally supported by an upgrade to Hold, and a technical momentum shift amid mixed market signals, reflecting cautious optimism among investors.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>e21fa8d31a04b47d5f4d970a283de969</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 12:36:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>National Aluminium Company Ltd Gains 3.85%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/national-aluminium-company-ltd-gains-385-6-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3813226</link><description>National Aluminium Company Ltd (NACL) delivered a mixed yet resilient performance during the week ending 30 January 2026, closing with a 3.85% gain to Rs.384.70 despite a sharp 10.32% drop on the final trading day. The stock outperformed the Sensex’s 1.62% rise over the same period, driven by a series of new 52-week highs, strong fundamentals, and heightened derivatives market activity. However, the week ended on a note of volatility and profit-taking, reflecting cautious investor sentiment amid sectoral pressures.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>e3a7612113cc76917f93f330c0078ea5</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 12:36:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gabriel India Ltd Gains 3.99%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gabriel-india-ltd-gains-399-2-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-rally-3813222</link><description>Gabriel India Ltd recorded a 3.99% gain over the week ending 30 January 2026, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% rise. The stock showed resilience amid mixed market conditions, driven by a valuation shift signalling renewed price attractiveness and a strong intraday surge on the final trading day. These developments underscore a week of notable price action and evolving investor sentiment for the auto components firm.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>69821ea862124b324acf522dd9740e98</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 12:36:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>APL Apollo Tubes Ltd Gains 2.23%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/apl-apollo-tubes-ltd-gains-223-6-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3813224</link><description>APL Apollo Tubes Ltd closed the week ending 30 January 2026 with a 2.23% gain, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% rise over the same period. The stock demonstrated strong resilience and momentum, hitting multiple new 52-week and all-time highs amid robust financial results and heightened market activity. Despite some volatility towards the week’s close, the company’s fundamentals and technical positioning remained solid, underpinning investor confidence in this mid-cap iron and steel products leader.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>b395e7586c515c91bfdaac485abfbd92</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 12:36:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Electronics Ltd Gains 9.54%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-electronics-ltd-gains-954-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3813223</link><description>Bharat Electronics Ltd (BEL) delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 9.54% from Rs.409.90 to Rs.449.00 between 26 and 30 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% gain over the same period. The stock’s rally was marked by a new 52-week high, an all-time intraday peak, robust quarterly results, and sustained institutional interest, underscoring its leadership in the aerospace and defence sector amid mixed market conditions.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>9d150d2e0e29d5d578232bc23f793c0d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 12:36:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Genesys International Gains 1.15% Despite Four-Day Slide: 4 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/genesys-international-gains-115-despite-four-day-slide-4-key-factors-driving-the-week-3813221</link><description>Genesys International Corporation Ltd closed the week with a modest gain of 1.15%, ending at Rs.312.50 on 30 January 2026, despite a challenging start marked by a series of 52-week lows. The stock underperformed the Sensex’s 1.62% rise over the same period, reflecting persistent headwinds from company-specific financial pressures and broader market volatility. However, a strong intraday rally on the final trading day signalled a potential short-term reversal after four consecutive sessions of decline.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>509914672929f5dd16ac25ade63dea45</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 12:36:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Praveg Ltd Gains 10.93%: 3 Key Technical Shifts Shape Weekly Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/praveg-ltd-gains-1093-3-key-technical-shifts-shape-weekly-performance-3813220</link><description>Praveg Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 10.93% from Rs.264.40 to Rs.293.30 between 27 and 30 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% gain over the same period. The stock showed robust intraday rallies early in the week before facing technical headwinds and a mild pullback towards the close. This review analyses the key events and technical signals shaping Praveg’s price action amid a mixed market backdrop.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>16709084301c04d70ba85c4320bc25b9</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 12:36:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vintage Coffee &amp; Beverages Ltd’s Mixed Week: -0.47% Price Change Amid Strong Financials</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vintage-coffee-beverages-ltds-mixed-week--047-price-change-amid-strong-financials-3813228</link><description>Vintage Coffee &amp; Beverages Ltd closed the week ending 30 January 2026 at Rs.147.20, down 0.47% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.147.90. This modest decline contrasted with the broader Sensex’s robust 1.62% gain over the same period, indicating a relative underperformance amid a backdrop of mixed news flow including valuation shifts, quarterly results, and rating upgrades.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>573d079375f380d04f81fdec6ba5fbc7</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 12:36:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Borosil Renewables Ltd Declines 2.15% Despite Strong Quarterly Results: 4 Key Factors Explaining the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/borosil-renewables-ltd-declines-215-despite-strong-quarterly-results-4-key-factors-explaining-the-week-3813219</link><description>Borosil Renewables Ltd closed the week ending 30 January 2026 at Rs.494.70, down 2.15% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.505.55, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.62% over the same period. The stock showed early strength with gains on 27 and 28 January, buoyed by robust quarterly results announced on 29 January, but profit-taking and technical caution weighed on the latter part of the week. This review analyses the key events shaping the stock’s performance and the implications for investors.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>e7a15fd96f0cfed4325418a4056d6c6d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 12:36:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Investment Corporation Gains 2.96%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-investment-corporation-gains-296-2-key-factors-driving-the-week-3813216</link><description>Tata Investment Corporation Ltd recorded a weekly gain of 2.96%, closing at Rs.622.30 on 30 Jan 2026, outperforming the Sensex which rose 1.62% over the same period. The week was marked by a technical downgrade early on, followed by a strong rebound supported by quarterly earnings that revealed profit growth amid underlying volatility.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>54e4e91fa779391fd22e54918dacb102</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 12:36:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PTC India Financial Services Ltd Gains 10.17%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ptc-india-financial-services-ltd-gains-1017-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3813217</link><description>PTC India Financial Services Ltd delivered a strong performance this week, rising 10.17% from Rs.29.78 to Rs.32.81, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% gain over the same period. The stock’s momentum was driven by robust intraday rallies, mixed but improving technical signals, and a cautious market environment that saw a shift towards bearish momentum by week’s end.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>4d99594c334bcadb24049f089746c8bc</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 12:36:31 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>