<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:29:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Forbes Precision Tools &amp; Machine Parts Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/forbes-precision-tools-machine-parts-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amidst-prolonged-downtrend-3789910</link><description>Shares of Forbes Precision Tools &amp; Machine Parts Ltd have declined to an all-time low, reflecting a sustained period of underperformance relative to the broader market and its sector peers. The stock’s recent movements underscore persistent difficulties faced by the company within the industrial manufacturing sector.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>028c397f208c6f52510a0f21e0534126</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:29:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Yasho Industries Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 12 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/yasho-industries-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-12-jan-2026-3789907</link><description>Yasho Industries Ltd witnessed a sharp intraday decline on 12 Jan 2026, touching a low of Rs 1266, down 7.82% from the previous close. The stock underperformed its sector and broader market amid heightened volatility and persistent downward pressure.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>d3346bce25154ba1c47927acda78968f</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:29:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Holdings &amp; Investment Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-holdings-investment-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-3789909</link><description>Bajaj Holdings &amp; Investment Ltd experienced notable intraday weakness on 12 Jan 2026, touching a low of ₹10,745 as the stock faced significant price pressure amid broader market declines and sector underperformance.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>7b7654826381ddf03ad1087ec44d7d8e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:29:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Siemens Ltd. Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 12 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/siemens-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-12-jan-2026-3789906</link><description>Siemens Ltd. experienced a notable decline today, touching an intraday low of Rs 2,955.6, reflecting a 3.07% drop as the stock faced significant price pressure amid broader market weakness and sector underperformance.
Time: 56 minutes ago</description><guid>e0c7293d2af83cc110b18d0895cfb02c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:29:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dolphin Offshore Enterprises (India) Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dolphin-offshore-enterprises-india-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-3789908</link><description>Shares of Dolphin Offshore Enterprises (India) Ltd declined sharply today, touching an intraday low of Rs 420, reflecting a 7.2% drop as the stock underperformed its sector and broader market amid prevailing price pressures and subdued market sentiment.
Time: 56 minutes ago</description><guid>be0134c56498ca8abe2f2a3a4d3d753d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:29:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Astron Paper &amp; Board Mill Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/astron-paper-board-mill-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3789904</link><description>Astron Paper &amp; Board Mill Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Paper, Forest &amp; Jute Products sector, witnessed intense selling pressure on 12 Jan 2026, hitting its lower circuit limit and closing at a fresh 52-week low of ₹5.45. The stock’s maximum daily loss of 2.63% reflects mounting investor concerns amid deteriorating fundamentals and subdued market sentiment.
Time: 59 minutes ago</description><guid>97c572b356025bdec87d645da8ab3ca2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:29:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reliable Data Services Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/reliable-data-services-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3789903</link><description>Shares of Reliable Data Services Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, plunged sharply on 12 Jan 2026, hitting the lower circuit limit as panic selling gripped the stock. The price fell by the maximum permissible daily loss of 5.88%, closing at ₹151.8, reflecting intense selling pressure and a significant drop in investor confidence.
Time: 59 minutes ago</description><guid>c86b1d5a55c27e628ff260855f42065c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:29:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eurotex Industries and Exports Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eurotex-industries-and-exports-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3789905</link><description>Eurotex Industries and Exports Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, witnessed intense selling pressure on 12 Jan 2026, hitting its lower circuit limit with a maximum daily loss of 4.96%. The stock’s sharp decline reflects mounting investor concerns amid deteriorating fundamentals and subdued market participation.
Time: 59 minutes ago</description><guid>f343a8685368933c1d16a0c1910a70fb</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:29:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maan Aluminium Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/maan-aluminium-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3789896</link><description>Maan Aluminium Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non-Ferrous Metals sector, witnessed intense selling pressure on 12 Jan 2026, hitting its lower circuit limit with a sharp decline of 4.99% to close at ₹139.46. The stock’s performance starkly underperformed its sector and the broader market, reflecting mounting investor concerns and a sustained downtrend over recent sessions.
Time: 59 minutes ago</description><guid>f0f3e0774eb1cc65e09a836fc832009d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:29:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Equippp Social Impact Technologies Ltd Plunges to Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/equippp-social-impact-technologies-ltd-plunges-to-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3789895</link><description>Equippp Social Impact Technologies Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, witnessed a sharp decline on 12 Jan 2026, hitting its lower circuit limit as intense selling pressure gripped the stock. The share price plunged by 4.97% to close at ₹20.07, marking the maximum permissible daily loss and signalling heightened investor anxiety amid a sustained downtrend.
Time: 59 minutes ago</description><guid>7673a4447a6b4f2e5850feec60f05b3d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:29:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fischer Medical Ventures Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/fischer-medical-ventures-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3789893</link><description>Fischer Medical Ventures Ltd, a small-cap player in the commodity chemicals sector, witnessed intense selling pressure on 12 Jan 2026, culminating in the stock hitting its lower circuit limit. The share price plunged by 4.35% to close at ₹38.45, marking a new 52-week low of ₹38.19 during intraday trade. This sharp decline reflects mounting investor concerns amid sustained negative momentum and unfilled supply overwhelming demand.
Time: 59 minutes ago</description><guid>4d9af8b3166898379a7e7aef8c9f76dc</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:29:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tejas Networks Ltd Faces Sharp Decline Amid Heavy Trading and Institutional Sell-Off</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tejas-networks-ltd-faces-sharp-decline-amid-heavy-trading-and-institutional-sell-off-3789902</link><description>Tejas Networks Ltd, a key player in the Telecom Equipment &amp; Accessories sector, witnessed a significant sell-off on 12 Jan 2026, marked by one of the highest value turnovers in the market. The stock plunged over 10.8% intraday, hitting a fresh 52-week low, amid heightened volatility and increased institutional participation, signalling growing investor caution.
Time: 59 minutes ago</description><guid>edebd9b1fc026af48fef3cf6d8e22801</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:29:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sadbhav Engineering Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sadbhav-engineering-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3789901</link><description>Sadbhav Engineering Ltd, a micro-cap player in the construction sector, witnessed intense selling pressure on 12 Jan 2026, hitting its lower circuit price limit of ₹8.38. The stock recorded a maximum daily loss of 4.99%, marking a fresh 52-week low and extending its losing streak to seven consecutive sessions, reflecting mounting investor concerns and deteriorating market sentiment.
Time: 59 minutes ago</description><guid>c823ff958409abe9ae7ce1e6f283cfda</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:29:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TV Vision Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure and Panic Selling</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tv-vision-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-and-panic-selling-3789900</link><description>TV Vision Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Media &amp; Entertainment sector, witnessed a sharp decline on 12 Jan 2026, hitting its lower circuit limit as panic selling gripped investors. The stock closed at ₹6.65, marking a maximum daily loss of 2.15%, amid unrelenting supply and subdued investor participation.
Time: 59 minutes ago</description><guid>74c3d83ac76b205811ac24088dbf738f</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:29:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vedanta Ltd. Leads High-Value Trading Amid Strong Institutional Interest</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vedanta-ltd-leads-high-value-trading-amid-strong-institutional-interest-3789899</link><description>Vedanta Ltd., a leading player in the non-ferrous metals sector, has emerged as one of the most actively traded stocks by value on 12 Jan 2026, reflecting heightened investor interest and robust market participation. The stock’s strong performance, coupled with significant institutional buying and large order flows, underscores its growing appeal amid a positive sectoral backdrop.
Time: 59 minutes ago</description><guid>c4f676ab37b8ffa017dfe5a43c9590b3</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:29:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cerebra Integrated Technologies Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cerebra-integrated-technologies-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3789898</link><description>Shares of Cerebra Integrated Technologies Ltd, a micro-cap player in the IT - Hardware sector, plunged sharply on 12 Jan 2026, hitting the lower circuit limit as intense selling pressure gripped the stock. The price decline of 4.9% marked the maximum daily loss allowed, reflecting panic selling and a significant imbalance between supply and demand.
Time: 59 minutes ago</description><guid>19fa6c4ca129eaacb8dc854ed900cd68</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:29:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BSE Ltd Sees Heavy Put Option Activity Amid Bullish Price Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bse-ltd-sees-heavy-put-option-activity-amid-bullish-price-momentum-3789894</link><description>BSE Ltd, a key player in the Capital Markets sector, has witnessed significant put option trading activity ahead of the 27 January 2026 expiry, signalling increased bearish positioning and hedging among investors. Despite the stock’s recent outperformance and strong technicals, the surge in put contracts at the ₹2,700 strike price suggests cautious sentiment as market participants brace for potential volatility in the near term.
Time: 59 minutes ago</description><guid>b5365532d839d55653b43d4f63dca648</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:29:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arvee Laboratories Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/arvee-laboratories-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3789885</link><description>Arvee Laboratories (India) Ltd surged to its upper circuit limit on 12 Jan 2026, registering a maximum daily gain of 5.0% as robust buying interest propelled the stock to ₹199.52. This sharp rally comes despite a challenging sector backdrop and a recent downgrade in the company’s mojo rating, highlighting a complex interplay of market forces and investor sentiment.
Time: 59 minutes ago</description><guid>65e4a9e8e820b8085c3c3bde5f1e7fb7</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:29:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shakti Pumps Surges on Heavy Value Trading Amid Institutional Interest</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shakti-pumps-surges-on-heavy-value-trading-amid-institutional-interest-3789897</link><description>Shakti Pumps (India) Ltd emerged as one of the most actively traded stocks by value on 12 Jan 2026, registering a significant intraday rally that outpaced both its sector and the broader Sensex. The stock’s strong performance was underpinned by heightened investor participation, robust volume, and a notable upgrade in its mojo grade, signalling shifting market sentiment despite lingering caution from institutional analysts.
Time: 59 minutes ago</description><guid>c360c6f02a57210cc4dee4ee9b076059</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:29:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hitachi Energy India Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hitachi-energy-india-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-price-action-3789890</link><description>Hitachi Energy India Ltd has witnessed a significant 18.6% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s recent underperformance. This spike in open interest, coupled with increased volumes and a sustained price decline, suggests evolving market positioning and potential directional bets among traders.
Time: 59 minutes ago</description><guid>1c0a6f8fbd8a15f4ad20e9fc4b679c4a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:29:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:29:49 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>