<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:27:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Entero Healthcare Solutions Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.49% Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/entero-healthcare-solutions-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-749-surge-3783379</link><description>Entero Healthcare Solutions Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 6 Jan 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 1,212.6, marking a 9.21% increase from its previous close. This notable rally outpaced the Retailing sector and the broader market indices, reflecting a significant reversal after two days of decline.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>6686bb176a8a16f01ac2f2192913702a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:27:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>National Peroxide Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/national-peroxide-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amidst-prolonged-downtrend-3783378</link><description>National Peroxide Ltd’s stock has declined to an all-time low, reflecting a sustained period of underperformance relative to the broader market and its sector peers. The commodity chemicals company’s shares have been steadily losing ground, with recent trading marking a significant milestone in its downward trajectory.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>d7e9e6bf3f9f7d0dd2188ab146469788</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:27:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Clean Science &amp; Technology Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/clean-science-technology-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amidst-prolonged-downtrend-3783377</link><description>Clean Science &amp; Technology Ltd, a player in the Specialty Chemicals sector, has recorded a new all-time low of Rs.857 today, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock’s performance continues to trail behind key market benchmarks, reflecting a challenging period for the company amid subdued financial metrics and reduced promoter confidence.
Time: 30 minutes ago</description><guid>00966a0bb404753aa1857d2251c5084b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:27:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anupam Rasayan India Ltd Stock Hits All-Time High, Marking a Significant Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/anupam-rasayan-india-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-marking-a-significant-milestone-3783375</link><description>Anupam Rasayan India Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting its all-time high stock price, reflecting a robust performance trajectory in the specialty chemicals sector. This achievement underscores the company’s sustained growth and strong market positioning amid a competitive industry landscape.
Time: 30 minutes ago</description><guid>6221596de87dd266b8a60e597daa217a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:27:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trade-Wings Ltd Stock Hits All-Time High of Rs.513.8 on 6 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/trade-wings-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-of-rs5138-on-6-jan-2026-3783376</link><description>Trade-Wings Ltd reached a significant milestone on 6 Jan 2026, hitting an all-time high of Rs.513.8. This achievement reflects a remarkable upward trajectory, with the stock demonstrating sustained strength and outperformance relative to key benchmarks over recent periods.
Time: 33 minutes ago</description><guid>cad258639a0d6ff7051cdbceca688991</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:27:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mukka Proteins Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mukka-proteins-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3783374</link><description>Mukka Proteins Ltd has reached a new all-time low of Rs.23.71, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock’s performance continues to lag behind both its sector and broader market indices, reflecting persistent pressures on the company’s financial and operational metrics.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>1f636981b9ffe6d91a5f602bf1e5771f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:27:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hardwyn India Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.19.42</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hardwyn-india-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs1942-3783366</link><description>Hardwyn India Ltd, a player in the Furniture and Home Furnishing sector, reached a significant milestone today by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.19.42, marking a notable surge in its stock price and reflecting strong momentum in the market.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>8ba00957b64078ab542195017879d05e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:27:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Integra Essentia Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.1.48 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/integra-essentia-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs148-amidst-continued-downtrend-3783373</link><description>Integra Essentia Ltd, a player in the FMCG sector, recorded a fresh 52-week low of Rs.1.48 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid ongoing downward momentum and subdued financial performance.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>380d3fc2c7b447abe312fa31bcfee099</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:27:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shankara Building Products Ltd Hits Intraday High with 12.39% Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shankara-building-products-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-1239-surge-3783371</link><description>Shankara Building Products Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 6 Jan 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 123.5, marking a 15.96% increase from its previous close. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting heightened trading activity and volatility.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>4697460936820c0e5a9c0b51e221b1d8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:27:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>National Standard (India) Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/national-standard-india-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3783370</link><description>National Standard (India) Ltd, a player in the Realty sector, has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.1206 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has underperformed both its sector and the broader market, reflecting ongoing concerns about its financial performance and market positioning.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>c17ca6cc98775202ab11980b13b85a2d</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:27:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Metals &amp; Ferro Alloys Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indian-metals-ferro-alloys-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-3783365</link><description>Indian Metals &amp; Ferro Alloys Ltd experienced a significant intraday decline on 6 Jan 2026, touching a low of Rs 1305, down 10.37% from the previous close. The stock underperformed its sector and the broader market, reflecting immediate selling pressure and subdued market sentiment within the ferrous metals space.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>08fd2316b7482479bad19220440affe6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:27:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Divis Laboratories Ltd Hits Intraday High with 3.0% Surge on 6 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/divis-laboratories-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-30-surge-on-6-jan-2026-3783369</link><description>Divis Laboratories Ltd demonstrated robust intraday strength on 6 Jan 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 6,575.45, marking a 3.34% increase from its previous close. This performance notably outpaced the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector and the broader Sensex index, underscoring the stock’s resilience amid a mixed market environment.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>59b5276fbd7c9164f3b02120b851297a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:27:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Suraj Products Ltd. Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.204.75 Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/suraj-products-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs20475-amid-continued-downtrend-3783372</link><description>Suraj Products Ltd., a player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, has recorded a fresh 52-week low of Rs.204.75, marking a significant decline in its share price amid broader market fluctuations and company-specific performance factors.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>3d779425e671cd540baa13ce4b28be44</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:27:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jagsonpal Pharmaceuticals Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs 186</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jagsonpal-pharmaceuticals-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs-186-3783364</link><description>Jagsonpal Pharmaceuticals Ltd has declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.186, marking a significant downturn in its stock performance amid broader market fluctuations and company-specific valuation concerns.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>cc91e8a5d53406911593bfd5e7fb0efc</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:27:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Graphite India Ltd. Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.672.45</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/graphite-india-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs67245-3783367</link><description>Graphite India Ltd. has reached a significant milestone by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.672.45, marking a notable surge in the Electrodes &amp; Refractories sector. This achievement reflects the stock’s robust momentum amid a mixed market environment.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>05f6b96f6882a97961a216ad44d0e0be</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:27:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JHS Svendgaard Laboratories Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.9.04</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jhs-svendgaard-laboratories-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs904-3783368</link><description>JHS Svendgaard Laboratories Ltd has touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.9.04 today, marking a significant decline in its share price amid a sustained downward trend over recent sessions. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing concerns about its financial health and market positioning.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>aaf3c2af7d166de799850d2beb9d74ce</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:27:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GNA Axles Ltd. Hits Intraday High with 7.51% Surge on 6 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gna-axles-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-751-surge-on-6-jan-2026-3783363</link><description>GNA Axles Ltd. demonstrated robust intraday strength on 6 Jan 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 373, marking an 8.38% increase from its previous close. This performance outpaced the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector by 8%, underscoring the stock’s notable momentum amid a broadly subdued market environment.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>dbac3fb0c9a7a034c960d7d231e160a8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:27:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thyrocare Technologies Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.3% Surge on 6 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/thyrocare-technologies-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-73-surge-on-6-jan-2026-3783362</link><description>Thyrocare Technologies Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 6 Jan 2026, surging 7.3% to touch a day’s high of Rs 507.75. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, continuing its upward momentum with notable volatility and sustained gains across multiple moving averages.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>fecc6aed428780b20ef44d0fedfbf249</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:27:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>National Aluminium Company Ltd Hits Intraday High with 5.36% Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/national-aluminium-company-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-536-surge-3783361</link><description>National Aluminium Company Ltd (NACL) demonstrated robust intraday performance on 6 January 2026, surging to a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs. 350.4, marking a 5.88% increase from the previous close. This strong upward movement outpaced the Aluminium &amp; Aluminium Products sector and the broader market indices, underscoring the stock’s current momentum.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>b941f924989d272d737fd9f4d20d590d</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:27:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Goyal Aluminiums Ltd Surges 19.95% to Hit Upper Circuit Amid Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/goyal-aluminiums-ltd-surges-1995-to-hit-upper-circuit-amid-robust-buying-pressure-3783360</link><description>Goyal Aluminiums Ltd witnessed a remarkable surge on 6 Jan 2026, hitting its upper circuit limit with a 19.95% gain to close at ₹10.34. This sharp rally was driven by intense buying interest, substantial volume, and a widening gap from sector and benchmark indices, signalling strong investor confidence despite the company’s recent strong sell rating.
Time: 57 minutes ago</description><guid>5d5245582490a558fe68995600b4972b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:27:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:27:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>