<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:25:43 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Motisons Jewellers Surges 17.53%: Key Technical and Financial Shifts Drive Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/motisons-jewellers-surges-1753-key-technical-and-financial-shifts-drive-volatility-3825556</link><description>Motisons Jewellers Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, surging 17.53% from ₹11.52 to ₹13.54 between 2 and 6 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 1.51% gain over the same period. The week was marked by notable technical momentum shifts, rating upgrades and downgrades, and impressive intraday rallies that underscored the stock’s volatile yet resilient character amid mixed sector and market conditions.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>1fef1389405c21a4706f54156de527a1</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:25:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Happy Forgings Ltd Gains 3.05%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/happy-forgings-ltd-gains-305-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3825555</link><description>Happy Forgings Ltd closed the week ending 6 February 2026 with a modest gain of 3.05%, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise over the same period. The stock exhibited notable volatility, highlighted by a sharp 7.46% surge on 3 February, followed by a series of technical upgrades and mixed market signals that shaped investor sentiment throughout the week.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>e002299075ff0d3d15e8bf100c556b43</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:25:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RBZ Jewellers Gains 4.01%: Technical Shift and Quarterly Strength Drive Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rbz-jewellers-gains-401-technical-shift-and-quarterly-strength-drive-momentum-3825550</link><description>RBZ Jewellers Ltd delivered a solid weekly performance, rising 4.01% from ₹136.00 to ₹141.45 between 2 and 6 February 2026, comfortably outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period. The week was marked by a notable technical upgrade to a 'Hold' rating, driven by improved momentum indicators and robust quarterly financial results, which helped the stock recover from an early-week dip and sustain gains despite mixed market signals.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>d988026354165e4796d69d073504387e</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:25:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jyoti CNC Automation Ltd Gains 1.86%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jyoti-cnc-automation-ltd-gains-186-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3825554</link><description>Jyoti CNC Automation Ltd closed the week ending 6 February 2026 with a modest gain of 1.86%, slightly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise. The stock experienced significant volatility, including a sharp rebound on 3 February following two days of decline, before settling near the week’s close. This review analyses the key events and technical signals shaping the stock’s performance over the past five trading sessions.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>cf0c2061271ce127ce453267de6d6f6a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:25:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Digidrive Distributors Gains 5.97%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/digidrive-distributors-gains-597-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3825552</link><description>Digidrive Distributors Ltd’s shares experienced a volatile week, ultimately rising 5.97% from Rs.21.61 to Rs.22.90, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period. The stock’s trajectory was marked by sharp intraday swings, including a fresh 52-week and all-time low early in the week, followed by a strong rebound midweek and a steep correction on the final trading day. This review analyses the key events and market dynamics shaping the stock’s performance from 2 to 6 February 2026.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>6aa85088fd0c72c70ce852f88742e041</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:25:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Medi Assist Healthcare Services Ltd Gains 1.05%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/medi-assist-healthcare-services-ltd-gains-105-6-key-factors-driving-the-week-3825551</link><description>Medi Assist Healthcare Services Ltd recorded a modest weekly gain of 1.05% to close at Rs.403.05 on 6 February 2026, slightly underperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise over the same period. The week was marked by significant volatility, including fresh 52-week lows, technical momentum shifts, and a sharp profit decline reported in Q3 FY26, all contributing to a cautious market sentiment around the stock.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>ebfd79fcbd7e52224e38c011b9756dfd</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:25:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sayaji Hotels Gains 4.99%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sayaji-hotels-gains-499-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-rally-3825553</link><description>Sayaji Hotels (Pune) Ltd closed the week with a 4.99% gain, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise from ₹762.00 to ₹800.00. The stock showed notable volatility during the week, reacting to valuation concerns, record quarterly results, and a stabilising financial trend. Despite a challenging sector backdrop, the company’s operational strength and improved earnings underpinned the price resilience.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>8864a864d11e127fafc3c182ee5ce2cf</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:25:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Epack Durable Ltd Gains 7.44%: 2 Key Factors Driving This Week’s Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/epack-durable-ltd-gains-744-2-key-factors-driving-this-weeks-rally-3825548</link><description>Epack Durable Ltd closed the week ending 6 February 2026 with a notable gain of 7.44%, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise over the same period. The stock demonstrated strong momentum midweek, driven by a sharp gap up on 3 February and an intraday surge on 4 February, before easing slightly in the final sessions. Despite the positive weekly performance, technical indicators and a recent downgrade to a Strong Sell rating suggest caution amid ongoing volatility.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>e5d6dde4e80204ad4d06cb1f7fed4ee2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:25:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BLS E-Services Gains 2.19%: 4 Key Factors Driving This Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bls-e-services-gains-219-4-key-factors-driving-this-weeks-volatility-3825545</link><description>BLS E-Services Ltd closed the week ending 6 February 2026 with a modest gain of 2.19%, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise over the same period. The stock experienced notable intraday volatility, driven by a downgrade to a Sell rating, a strong gap up early in the week, mixed technical momentum, and quarterly results that revealed revenue growth but margin pressures. This review analyses the key events shaping the stock’s performance and the implications for investors navigating a complex market environment.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>706df1e0f32db2217842cc09810e9d8f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:25:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rashi Peripherals Gains 6.40%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rashi-peripherals-gains-640-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3825547</link><description>Rashi Peripherals Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, rising 6.40% from ₹358.60 to ₹381.55 between 2 and 6 February 2026, comfortably outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period. The stock’s trajectory was marked by a new 52-week high, technical upgrades, strong financial results, and a notable upgrade in quality and rating by MarketsMOJO, reflecting a week of significant positive developments amid mixed market conditions.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>1a451088b64ce34c7388637b41fec177</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:25:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apeejay Surrendra Park Hotels Gains 3.54%: Valuation Shifts and Q3 Results Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/apeejay-surrendra-park-hotels-gains-354-valuation-shifts-and-q3-results-shape-the-week-3825546</link><description>Apeejay Surrendra Park Hotels Ltd recorded a 3.54% gain over the week ending 6 February 2026, closing at Rs.125.80 from Rs.121.50. This outpaced the Sensex’s 1.51% rise, reflecting a mixed but cautiously optimistic market response amid valuation shifts and quarterly earnings announcements. The stock showed notable volatility, with a sharp 5.30% jump on 3 February followed by a correction and modest recovery, as investors digested evolving fundamentals and sector dynamics.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>f9d52fad729579514029b4b92220a1d0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:25:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jana Small Finance Bank Ltd Declines 2.65%: 7 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jana-small-finance-bank-ltd-declines-265-7-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-downtrend-3825549</link><description>Jana Small Finance Bank Ltd’s shares declined by 2.65% over the week ending 6 February 2026, closing at Rs.350.60, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.51%. The stock faced persistent downward pressure, hitting fresh 52-week and all-time lows during the week amid continued financial challenges, subdued credit growth, and cautious market sentiment. Despite an upgrade in its mojo grade from Strong Sell to Sell, valuation improvements and increased institutional interest provided some offset to the negative momentum.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>7969b6b09119edd35ac4083db1a503e7</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:25:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Signpost India Ltd Gains 1.84%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Mixed Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/signpost-india-ltd-gains-184-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-mixed-momentum-3825544</link><description>Signpost India Ltd recorded a modest weekly gain of 1.84%, closing at Rs.207.55 on 6 Feb 2026, slightly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise over the same period. The week was marked by a technical upgrade from 'Strong Sell' to 'Sell', mixed market signals, and persistent fundamental challenges, reflecting a cautious but slightly improved outlook for the stock amid sector headwinds.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>a6231b655e705b9a2afaf6dd372a5bed</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:25:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GPT Healthcare Ltd Falls 0.78%: 6 Key Factors Behind the Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gpt-healthcare-ltd-falls-078-6-key-factors-behind-the-prolonged-downtrend-3825542</link><description>GPT Healthcare Ltd’s shares declined by 0.78% over the week ending 6 February 2026, closing at Rs.127.40 compared to Rs.128.40 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s 1.51% gain during the same period, reflecting ongoing operational challenges and investor caution amid fresh 52-week and all-time lows. The week was marked by a series of negative financial updates, rising interest expenses, and reduced institutional participation, all contributing to sustained downward momentum in the stock price.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>baf61f89faef360eccc616c06585fc34</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:25:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Exicom Tele-Systems Ltd Declines 1.63%: Key Financial Struggles and Market Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/exicom-tele-systems-ltd-declines-163-key-financial-struggles-and-market-underperformance-3825543</link><description>Exicom Tele-Systems Ltd’s stock declined by 1.63% over the week ending 06 Feb 2026, closing at Rs.98.07, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.51%. The week was marked by a fresh 52-week and all-time low on 02 Feb, reflecting ongoing financial challenges and weak investor sentiment despite intermittent rebounds midweek.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>8269411d5dcca69c937a571342fe151a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:25:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Platinum Industries Ltd Falls 2.57%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/platinum-industries-ltd-falls-257-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3825541</link><description>Platinum Industries Ltd closed the week at Rs.229.30, down 2.57% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.235.35, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.51% over the same period. The stock’s price movements were influenced by a series of technical and valuation developments, alongside mixed market sentiment and sector-specific challenges, resulting in a cautious outlook for investors.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>620a4bb859740634cc661f2d58788f7b</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:25:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>J.G.Chemicals Ltd Gains 4.72%: 4 Key Technical Shifts Shape Weekly Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jgchemicals-ltd-gains-472-4-key-technical-shifts-shape-weekly-performance-3825539</link><description>J.G.Chemicals Ltd closed the week with a 4.72% gain, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise from 2 to 6 February 2026. The stock exhibited notable intraday volatility and technical shifts amid mixed market sentiment, with key events including a strong surge on 3 February and subsequent technical setbacks by week’s end. Despite the positive weekly return, the stock’s technical indicators reveal ongoing challenges within the commodity chemicals sector and a cautious outlook.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>5974c77b7b81f6161bce6a5a121ffdbc</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:25:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SRM Contractors Ltd Falls 12.39%: Technical Shifts and Valuation Concerns Drive Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/srm-contractors-ltd-falls-1239-technical-shifts-and-valuation-concerns-drive-weekly-decline-3825538</link><description>SRM Contractors Ltd experienced a challenging week from 2 to 6 February 2026, with its share price declining sharply by 12.39% to close at ₹395.15, significantly underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.51% over the same period. The week was marked by a downgrade to a Sell rating amid deteriorating technical indicators and valuation adjustments, compounded by mixed market signals and heightened volatility. Despite strong underlying financials, the stock faced sustained selling pressure, reflecting investor caution in the face of shifting momentum and sector headwinds.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>dace6d8a3d69975e68dcc78c73c5135f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:25:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharti Hexacom Gains 10.19%: Key Technical Shifts and Earnings Drive Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharti-hexacom-gains-1019-key-technical-shifts-and-earnings-drive-weekly-rally-3825540</link><description>Bharti Hexacom Ltd delivered a strong performance this week, rising 10.19% from Rs.1,544.45 to Rs.1,701.85, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period. The stock’s trajectory was shaped by a mix of technical momentum shifts, robust quarterly results, and a notable intraday surge on the final trading day, reflecting renewed investor interest amid a mixed market backdrop.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>189f3c53242f31b6f7350fda141d4c7c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:25:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd Falls 3.28%: Bearish Momentum and Downgrade Shape Weekly Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aadhar-housing-finance-ltd-falls-328-bearish-momentum-and-downgrade-shape-weekly-trend-3825537</link><description>Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd closed the week down 3.28% at Rs.474.50, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.51% over the same period. The stock faced bearish technical momentum, a downgrade to a Sell rating by MarketsMOJO, and mixed technical signals amid sector uncertainties. Despite strong financial fundamentals, these factors combined to weigh on the stock’s performance during the week ending 6 February 2026.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>e58baf41a92d31fe0742f2101b54ac71</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:25:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:25:43 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>