<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:46:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>ARCL Organics Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/arcl-organics-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3848930</link><description>ARCL Organics Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Commodity Chemicals sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about sustained bearish momentum in the near to medium term.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>ef0888dbee88c41a84f106d051a0244c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ethos Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ethos-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3848931</link><description>Ethos Ltd, a player in the Gems, Jewellery and Watches sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>41329675eeb64b15fb2a5e1544a77908</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Suryoday Small Finance Bank Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/suryoday-small-finance-bank-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3848932</link><description>Suryoday Small Finance Bank Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>16b9a889b04965d4002e61003c6673eb</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CreditAccess Grameen Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/creditaccess-grameen-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3848923</link><description>CreditAccess Grameen Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a potential deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum. Investors should carefully analyse this event in the context of the company’s broader financial and market performance.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>2af08eb89c0ce2eebe1983008a102770</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aurum Proptech Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aurum-proptech-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3848924</link><description>Aurum Proptech Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout, indicating a shift in long-term momentum and a possible trend reversal for the micro-cap software and consulting company.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>20703717301b39f4a8895df81a87bb31</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Banco Products Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/banco-products-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3848927</link><description>Banco Products (India) Ltd, a key player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>534b772425b2088324b63bbd799a4235</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>7Seas Entertainment Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/7seas-entertainment-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3848929</link><description>7Seas Entertainment Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action. Investors should carefully consider this warning amid the company’s ongoing underperformance relative to broader market benchmarks.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>0e7476f14edb8fff530b597ff02fae1f</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sangam Finserv Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sangam-finserv-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3848922</link><description>Sangam Finserv Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross—a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses above the 200-DMA. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout, signalling a possible long-term momentum shift and trend reversal for the stock, despite its recent mixed performance and cautious market sentiment.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>dd2ca479d1416b681b60b990deeafaad</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SecureKloud Technologies Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/securekloud-technologies-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3848928</link><description>SecureKloud Technologies Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about long-term weakness amid already challenging fundamentals and market performance.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>c35a76e05821a1cc7afe4d725bb500df</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deep Diamond India Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/deep-diamond-india-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3848921</link><description>Deep Diamond India Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Gems, Jewellery And Watches sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential prolonged bearish trend and highlights the deteriorating momentum in the stock’s price action.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>38b5fa242935af5dde1ad7696ceaa18b</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Godrej Consumer Products Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/godrej-consumer-products-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3848926</link><description>Godrej Consumer Products Ltd (GCPL), a prominent player in the FMCG sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross—a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-DMA. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout, suggesting a shift in long-term momentum and a possible trend reversal in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>5203619537ee403f86c7095798ec2f3c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vardhman Textiles Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vardhman-textiles-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3848925</link><description>Vardhman Textiles Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a long-term momentum shift for the garment and apparel company, which has outperformed the Sensex across multiple time frames.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>ebd3931d3c6fb3ed650042faed30965d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Mixed Results Across 4,085 Stocks in Dec-2025 Quarter</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-mixed-results-across-4085-stocks-in-dec-2025-quarter-3848920</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has concluded for 4,085 stocks, revealing a nuanced landscape of corporate performance marked by modest improvement in positive results and distinct sectoral trends. While aggregate profit growth remains subdued, mid-cap companies continue to outperform their large- and small-cap counterparts, underscoring a divergence in market dynamics heading into 2026.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>2586b60dc80de12522a05660f97bb8c6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Network People Services Technologies Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.1131.7</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/network-people-services-technologies-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs11317-3848856</link><description>Network People Services Technologies Ltd, a player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, recorded a new 52-week low of Rs.1131.7 on 20 Feb 2026, marking a significant price level for the stock amid a mixed market environment.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b395cebfe0afc92173346aa2adf9146c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uma Exports Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/uma-exports-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3848853</link><description>Uma Exports Ltd has reached a fresh 52-week low, reflecting a sustained decline in its share price amid broader market activity. The stock’s latest fall to this significant price level underscores ongoing challenges in its financial performance and valuation metrics.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>62ea8bcff590c40046a848c10d0c4528</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cybertech Systems &amp; Software Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cybertech-systems-software-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3848854</link><description>Cybertech Systems &amp; Software Ltd has recently touched a 52-week low, closing near Rs 118.45, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid a sustained period of negative returns and underperformance relative to its sector and broader market indices.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>5e8064e480f8bc21109f9711ff8aa871</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arrow Greentech Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/arrow-greentech-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3848852</link><description>Arrow Greentech Ltd, a key player in the packaging sector, has recently touched a 52-week low, closing just 2.84% above its lowest price of Rs 404. The stock’s decline reflects ongoing pressures within the company’s performance metrics and market positioning, marking a significant phase in its trading history.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>fbe80822ee629265dcb8ae05fe671760</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alankit Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/alankit-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3848855</link><description>Shares of Alankit Ltd, a player in the Diversified Commercial Services sector, have declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing near Rs 8.75, marking a significant downturn in the stock’s performance over the past year.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>a0340a1ffa3332170f340b2abf16e39d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mid-Cap Segment Sees Modest Decline Amid Mixed Sectoral Performance on 20 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/mid-cap-segment-sees-modest-decline-amid-mixed-sectoral-performance-on-20-feb-2026-3848849</link><description>The mid-cap segment experienced a modest decline this week, with the BSE Midcap index slipping by 1.52% on 20 Feb 2026 and a marginal 0.08% drop over the last five days. Despite the overall subdued performance, select stocks and sectors demonstrated resilience, supported by recent technical upgrades and upcoming earnings announcements that could influence near-term momentum.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>8b6d7e8f9f3703854e94d68c86d54a43</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>