<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:38:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Eternal Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eternal-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3814986</link><description>Eternal Ltd, a prominent player in the E-Retail and E-Commerce sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term momentum and investor sentiment.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>578e6f49b357f46d9397387e8bc2e5e6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wonder Electricals Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/wonder-electricals-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3814985</link><description>Wonder Electricals Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development highlights a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raises concerns about its long-term strength amid already challenging market conditions.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>9ee8ba38afc841e59f1495cdb95a2e8e</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Datamatics Global Services Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/datamatics-global-services-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3814987</link><description>Datamatics Global Services Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>dc3de557265cb8acc4cb60e07b51b85f</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prestige Estates Projects Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/prestige-estates-projects-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3814977</link><description>Prestige Estates Projects Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock's medium to long-term momentum amid mixed market performance and valuation concerns.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>8688ee571a16f72b14e6ada866436414</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TVS Electronics Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tvs-electronics-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3814982</link><description>TVS Electronics Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend and long-term weakness in the stock’s price momentum.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>41cd400e4c9ed1325fb5b5559961cceb</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zuari Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/zuari-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3814980</link><description>Zuari Industries Ltd, a micro-cap player in the sugar sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s near- to medium-term outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>16bc19cbe5cbdd48b8dee0e76bdbbea9</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gujarat Apollo Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gujarat-apollo-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3814978</link><description>Gujarat Apollo Industries Ltd, a micro-cap player in the industrial manufacturing sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend and highlights a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>1703a049144ee0261c1270d7afd7a205</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Renaissance Global Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/renaissance-global-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3814979</link><description>Renaissance Global Ltd, a small-cap player in the Gems, Jewellery and Watches sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s near- to medium-term outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>c36ed896406e8aec1ad7f5eff6d49592</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lactose (India) Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lactose-india-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3814981</link><description>Lactose (India) Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development reflects a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raises concerns about its medium to long-term outlook amid already challenging market conditions.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>aa5b7bea0fb83b842ae85fa184a13070</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SG Finserve Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sg-finserve-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3814983</link><description>SG Finserve Ltd, a small-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Death Cross—a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average—indicating a potential shift towards a sustained bearish trend and signalling deteriorating momentum in the stock’s price action.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>412c9292864279bbee076a77e70c715b</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MEP Infrastructure Developers Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mep-infrastructure-developers-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3814976</link><description>MEP Infrastructure Developers Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average, signalling a potential prolonged bearish trend and deterioration in the stock’s momentum.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>39f9b7ca05e9973b9f22b003560daaab</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Swarnsarita Jewels India Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/swarnsarita-jewels-india-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3814984</link><description>Swarnsarita Jewels India Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-DMA. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout, indicating a shift in long-term momentum and a possible trend reversal for the micro-cap stock in the Gems, Jewellery And Watches sector.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>fa8ae7865192d6c5af0fc133f433303c</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dec 2025 Quarterly Earnings Reveal Mixed Market Sentiment with Mid Caps Leading Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/dec-2025-quarterly-earnings-reveal-mixed-market-sentiment-with-mid-caps-leading-growth-3814975</link><description>The December 2025 quarterly earnings season has delivered a nuanced picture of corporate performance across market capitalisations, with mid-cap companies outperforming their large-cap counterparts in terms of positive results. While aggregate profit growth remains modest, sectoral leaders and select small caps have demonstrated robust financial metrics, signalling pockets of strength amid broader market caution.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>bd2c180e1718c090071b84bfcd87625d</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>W S Industries Falls 1.31%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/w-s-industries-falls-131-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3814973</link><description>W S Industries (India) Ltd closed the week ending 30 January 2026 at ₹76.62, down 1.31% from the previous Friday’s close of ₹77.64, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.62% over the same period. The stock’s week was marked by a downgrade to a Strong Sell rating, a shift in technical momentum from sideways to bearish, and persistent financial weakness, all contributing to a cautious market sentiment despite intermittent intraday gains.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>72c31268a0d3571667c78d1db3bbac6e</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SKM Egg Products Gains 10.42%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/skm-egg-products-gains-1042-2-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-surge-3814972</link><description>SKM Egg Products Export (India) Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, rising 10.42% from Rs.179.45 to Rs.198.15 between 26 and 30 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% gain over the same period. The stock’s momentum was propelled by a stellar Q3 profit announcement and strong technical signals amid a broader FMCG sector rally, although it faced a minor pullback on the final trading day.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>64522b8e621e1cdd79f3f83d64f3e0da</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prerna Infrabuild Gains 0.08%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/prerna-infrabuild-gains-008-2-key-factors-driving-the-week-3814969</link><description>Prerna Infrabuild Ltd’s stock showed a marginal gain of 0.08% over the week ending 30 January 2026, closing at Rs.25.53 from Rs.25.51. This performance contrasted with the broader Sensex, which advanced 1.62% during the same period, highlighting a relative underperformance amid mixed financial signals and operational challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f7efda7f23661bb491a2b355ce49fe66</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahanagar Telephone Nigam Ltd Surges 17.09%: 4 Key Events Driving Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mahanagar-telephone-nigam-ltd-surges-1709-4-key-events-driving-volatility-3814971</link><description>Mahanagar Telephone Nigam Ltd (MTNL) delivered a remarkable weekly performance, surging 17.09% from Rs.29.02 to Rs.33.98 between 26 and 30 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 1.62% gain. The week was marked by extreme volatility, including a fresh 52-week low, strong intraday rallies, and an upper circuit hit, reflecting a complex interplay of market dynamics and investor sentiment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>54ccae610ee421ccabd2dfa4ef93e5b0</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>eClerx Services Ltd Gains 7.85%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eclerx-services-ltd-gains-785-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-rally-3814970</link><description>eClerx Services Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 7.85% from ₹4,314.50 to ₹4,653.25 between 26 and 30 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% gain over the same period. The stock demonstrated robust intraday strength, hitting near 52-week highs amid positive quarterly results, technical momentum shifts, and valuation upgrades, marking a week of notable investor interest and market confidence.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7168095a3fae22e003a56014fef301bf</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Brigade Enterprises Ltd’s 1.16% Weekly Decline Amidst 52-Week Lows and Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/brigade-enterprises-ltds-116-weekly-decline-amidst-52-week-lows-and-mixed-market-signals-3814968</link><description>Brigade Enterprises Ltd experienced a challenging week ending 30 January 2026, with its share price declining 1.16% from Rs.760.85 to Rs.752.05, underperforming the Sensex which rose 1.62% over the same period. The stock hit multiple 52-week lows during the week, reflecting persistent financial pressures and sectoral headwinds despite some late-week recovery.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>43bb1fbe3cf448a26cd886965a3274f5</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mangalore Refinery &amp; Petrochemicals Ltd Gains 13.61%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mangalore-refinery-petrochemicals-ltd-gains-1361-6-key-factors-driving-the-rally-3814967</link><description>Mangalore Refinery &amp; Petrochemicals Ltd. (MRPL) delivered a strong weekly performance from 26 to 30 January 2026, surging 13.61% to close at Rs.176.50, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% gain. The stock’s rally was fuelled by a series of positive developments including a Mojo Grade upgrade, exceptional volume surges, and robust technical momentum, marking a notable phase of accumulation and investor confidence in the oil refining sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>89d6320c3e7c44de5d7a8a154e505844</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:38:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>