<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:04:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Sensex Dips 0.25% Amid Broad Market Weakness; Realty Sector Leads Losses</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-dips-025-amid-broad-market-weakness-realty-sector-leads-losses-3795606</link><description>The Indian equity market closed lower on 20 Jan 2026, with the Sensex slipping 210.23 points or 0.25% to trade at 83,035.95 amid broad-based sector weakness. Realty stocks led the declines while the metal sector provided some respite, reflecting cautious investor sentiment ahead of key corporate earnings and mixed global cues.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>9f1f7eef1130b38b800258035fd5533c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jio Financial Services Ltd Faces Headwinds Amid Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jio-financial-services-ltd-faces-headwinds-amid-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-shifts-3795605</link><description>Jio Financial Services Ltd, a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, is currently navigating a challenging phase marked by underperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices. Recent downgrades in its mojo grade, coupled with a sustained decline in share price and institutional holding adjustments, underscore the complexities facing this large-cap Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) in the evolving market landscape.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>b042a772eb462ece4a3ca30971419bdd</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eternal Ltd Faces Downgrade Amidst Mixed Market Performance and Nifty 50 Membership Impact</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eternal-ltd-faces-downgrade-amidst-mixed-market-performance-and-nifty-50-membership-impact-3795603</link><description>Eternal Ltd, a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index and a major player in the E-Retail sector, has recently undergone a significant rating downgrade from Hold to Sell, reflecting growing concerns over its valuation and recent performance trends. Despite its large-cap status and historical outperformance relative to the Sensex, the company now faces headwinds from institutional investors and benchmark pressures that could influence its near-term trajectory.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>ae9a679e81a29c793cc6bb2f6dd23fa6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Max Healthcare Institute Ltd Faces Headwinds Amid Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/max-healthcare-institute-ltd-faces-headwinds-amid-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-shifts-3795604</link><description>Max Healthcare Institute Ltd, a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, has recently undergone a notable downgrade in its Mojo Grade from Hold to Sell as of 31 October 2025. This development comes amid a challenging performance trajectory and evolving institutional holding patterns, raising questions about the stock’s future prospects within the benchmark index.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>04e5db4a0dc502baa6237f483d430d58</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HDFC Life Insurance Company Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amid Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hdfc-life-insurance-company-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-institutional-shifts-3795602</link><description>HDFC Life Insurance Company Ltd, a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, has experienced a nuanced performance trajectory as it navigates institutional holding changes and the pressures of benchmark status. Despite a modest 0.33% gain on 20 Jan 2026, the stock’s valuation and technical indicators suggest challenges ahead, prompting a recent downgrade in its investment grade.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>0bf531b2152cc0263e057321c7b947e2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sbi-life-insurance-company-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-3795601</link><description>SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd continues to assert its prominence within the Indian equity landscape, bolstered by its status as a Nifty 50 constituent and a large-cap heavyweight in the insurance sector. Despite a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade to 'Hold', the stock's robust year-on-year performance and institutional interest underscore its strategic importance for investors navigating benchmark-driven portfolios.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>429a911b68a2e2f1cacfcb1e900b89c6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maruti Suzuki India Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amid Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/maruti-suzuki-india-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-institutional-shifts-3795599</link><description>Maruti Suzuki India Ltd continues to assert its prominence within the Nifty 50 index, reflecting its stature as a bellwether in the Indian automobile sector. Despite a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade to Hold from Buy, the stock’s robust market capitalisation and consistent outperformance against the Sensex underscore its enduring appeal among institutional investors and market participants alike.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>549f16fa2e0ef10f029dc872767b5ab8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Finance Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-finance-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-3795598</link><description>Bajaj Finance Ltd, a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to demonstrate its pivotal role within India’s financial markets despite recent volatility. The company’s evolving institutional shareholding patterns and its benchmark status underscore its significance for investors and market participants alike.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>1b4bcdf0516cf4f177eb172fe1d4047c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd Faces Challenges Amid Nifty 50 Membership</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-motors-passenger-vehicles-ltd-faces-challenges-amid-nifty-50-membership-3795600</link><description>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd, a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to grapple with significant headwinds as reflected in its recent financial performance and market metrics. Despite its large-cap status and benchmark inclusion, the stock has underperformed the broader market over the past year, prompting a downgrade in its Mojo Grade to Sell from Hold on 4 November 2024.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>94bfaa0f6421e66ceea08cf1bc2f5236</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Ltd Strengthens Position as Nifty 50 Constituent Amid Institutional Interest</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mahindra-mahindra-ltd-strengthens-position-as-nifty-50-constituent-amid-institutional-interest-3795596</link><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Ltd (M&amp;M), a stalwart in the Indian automobile sector, continues to solidify its standing within the Nifty 50 index, reflecting robust institutional confidence and outperforming key benchmarks. Recent upgrades in its investment grade and sustained market cap dominance underscore its pivotal role in shaping market sentiment and sectoral trends.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>3cbfc4b2b31551f0833c6e8869feb690</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Larsen &amp; Toubro Ltd: Navigating Market Challenges as a Key Nifty 50 Constituent</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/larsen-toubro-ltd-navigating-market-challenges-as-a-key-nifty-50-constituent-3795597</link><description>Larsen &amp; Toubro Ltd. (L&amp;T), a stalwart in India’s construction sector and a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, is currently facing a nuanced phase marked by a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade from Buy to Hold. Despite its large-cap stature and significant market presence, the stock’s recent performance and valuation metrics suggest a cautious outlook amid evolving market dynamics and sectoral pressures.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>982987d3f5b56478ee0249db3bfdf252</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Finserv Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-finserv-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-3795594</link><description>Bajaj Finserv Ltd, a prominent holding company and a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, has witnessed a subtle yet significant shift in its market dynamics as institutional holdings adjust and benchmark pressures mount. Despite recent underperformance relative to the sector and the broader Sensex, the company’s long-term growth trajectory and index membership continue to underscore its strategic importance in India’s financial landscape.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>c5846991d2777acd15ef3eba25505a6e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Enterprises Ltd Faces Continued Pressure Amid Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-enterprises-ltd-faces-continued-pressure-amid-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-shifts-3795591</link><description>Adani Enterprises Ltd, a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to grapple with significant market challenges as institutional investors recalibrate their holdings. Despite its large-cap status and historical outperformance, the diversified conglomerate has seen its mojo grade deteriorate to a strong sell, reflecting mounting concerns over valuation and sectoral pressures.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>0581f686926990198b37fe6ee649bb83</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Mahindra Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tech-mahindra-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-3795593</link><description>Tech Mahindra Ltd, a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to demonstrate resilience amid evolving market conditions. With a recent upgrade in its Mojo Grade to 'Buy' and sustained institutional interest, the stock's performance and benchmark status remain pivotal for investors tracking the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>7c80646426b42a6febc6e8e3832a9ed5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Unilever Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amid Mixed Performance and Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-unilever-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-mixed-performance-and-institutional-shifts-3795592</link><description>Hindustan Unilever Ltd (HUL), a stalwart of the FMCG sector and a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to demonstrate resilience amid evolving market dynamics. Despite a modest upgrade in short-term price momentum, the company faces challenges reflected in its recent downgrade to a Sell rating by MarketsMOJO, underscoring shifting institutional sentiments and the broader implications for its benchmark status.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>10ab33357670164d7a8d98a86d15052d</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Ports &amp; Special Economic Zone Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-ports-special-economic-zone-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-3795588</link><description>Adani Ports &amp; Special Economic Zone Ltd (APSEZ), a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to demonstrate its significance within India’s transport infrastructure sector amid fluctuating market dynamics and evolving institutional holdings. Despite recent short-term price pressures, the stock’s long-term performance and benchmark status underscore its pivotal role in investor portfolios and market indices.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>480f27e89119d9107ee44a9719b33ce0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kotak-mahindra-bank-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-shifts-3795595</link><description>Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd continues to assert its significance within the Nifty 50 index, reflecting its stature as a leading private sector bank in India. Despite a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade from Buy to Hold, the bank’s market cap of ₹4,27,059.47 crore and consistent outperformance against sector benchmarks underscore its enduring appeal to institutional investors and market participants alike.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>39b2b59dffc43dd2c42e518dc908db25</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reliance Industries Ltd: Navigating Market Challenges Amid Nifty 50 Membership</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/reliance-industries-ltd-navigating-market-challenges-amid-nifty-50-membership-3795589</link><description>Reliance Industries Ltd, a cornerstone of the Indian oil sector and a key Nifty 50 constituent, continues to demonstrate resilience despite recent market pressures. With a market capitalisation exceeding ₹19 lakh crores and a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade to Hold, the stock’s performance and institutional interest remain pivotal for investors tracking benchmark indices and sectoral trends.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>f42bbcdd5979fa44145a716c6e544a54</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cipla Ltd: Navigating Challenges as a Nifty 50 Pharmaceutical Giant</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cipla-ltd-navigating-challenges-as-a-nifty-50-pharmaceutical-giant-3795590</link><description>Cipla Ltd, a stalwart in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector and a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, is currently facing a challenging phase marked by subdued price performance and a recent downgrade in its investment grade. Despite its large-cap status and benchmark inclusion, the stock has underperformed the broader market and its sector peers, reflecting shifting institutional sentiments and evolving market dynamics.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>1291a8e612c75529a57d90515201405f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Steel Ltd Strengthens Position as Nifty 50 Constituent with Robust Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-steel-ltd-strengthens-position-as-nifty-50-constituent-with-robust-performance-3795587</link><description>Tata Steel Ltd continues to solidify its stature within the Nifty 50 index, demonstrating impressive performance metrics and institutional backing that underscore its significance in India’s ferrous metals sector. The company’s recent upgrade to a Strong Buy rating reflects growing investor confidence amid a backdrop of sustained outperformance against the benchmark Sensex.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>226939930ffc820967fabb394c2e93dd</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:04:47 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>