<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:26:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Are Epack Durable Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-epack-durable-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3798978</link><description>Epack Durable Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show strong revenue growth of 100.58% to ₹427.75 crores, but profitability has declined significantly, with a net profit of ₹2.59 crores and a PAT margin dropping to 0.61%. While revenue recovery is positive, concerns about operational challenges and reliance on other income raise caution about the company's financial health.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>113fb0aed1c2e0bbecc1f2a3675003ea</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:26:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are CreditAccess Grameen Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-creditaccess-grameen-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3798977</link><description>CreditAccess Grameen Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are positive, showing a net profit of ₹252.09 crore and a year-on-year profit growth of 353.31%, indicating a strong operational turnaround despite slight declines in net interest income. The company's improved operating margin and effective risk management further highlight its recovery in the microfinance sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6e62af2759766f49531a2710aa08a86b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:26:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Dhampur Bio Organics Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-dhampur-bio-organics-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3798976</link><description>Dhampur Bio Organics Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 19.68% year-on-year, but the company reported a net loss of ₹15.99 crores and ongoing operational challenges, raising concerns about its profitability and financial stability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>35476b1b31b9c9709816855e46c3d2fa</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:26:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Asian Warehousing Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-asian-warehousing-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3798975</link><description>Asian Warehousing Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 108.70% year-on-year, but the company reported no net profit and declining operating margins, indicating significant operational inefficiencies and challenges in profitability. Overall, while revenue is up, the financial outlook remains concerning due to these issues.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>45fbb39029b218c7c51fb85b0f214902</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:26:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are K.P. Energy Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-kp-energy-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3798974</link><description>K.P. Energy Ltd's latest results show strong year-on-year revenue growth of 62.84% and a net profit increase of 56.69%, indicating solid performance in the renewable energy sector, though growth rates have moderated compared to previous years. While the company maintains a stable operating profit margin and strong return on equity, it faces challenges due to project-based revenue volatility.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2db9007cdd55186e63a1eaa20dac339b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:26:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are KPI Green Energy Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-kpi-green-energy-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3798973</link><description>KPI Green Energy Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results show strong revenue growth of 76.35% year-on-year, with net sales reaching ₹634.30 crores, and a net profit increase of 56.03% to ₹109.11 crores. However, the company faces margin pressures due to rising interest costs, indicating mixed operational performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3d4c1e6c3c229fbab16ca33127d9a236</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:26:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Prime Securities Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-prime-securities-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3798972</link><description>Prime Securities Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 42.54% to ₹30.19 crores, but a concerning 74.39% decline in net profit to ₹2.10 crores, indicating significant operational challenges and margin pressures. While the company has a solid return on equity and a debt-free balance sheet, investors should be cautious due to the declining profitability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>921150afef9b54316ca59274392c39ee</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:26:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are AU Small Finance Bank Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-au-small-finance-bank-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3798971</link><description>AU Small Finance Bank Ltd's latest results show a net profit growth of 26.34% year-on-year, but with a decline in net interest margin to 5.7% and a drop in CASA ratio to 29.0%, indicating mixed performance and challenges in maintaining profitability. Overall, while the bank is generating profit and managing asset quality well, it faces pressures on margins and deposit mobilization.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>22f6064384d72e453432d14dde327353</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:26:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are BIGBLOC Construction Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-bigbloc-construction-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3798970</link><description>BIGBLOC Construction Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 28.14% to ₹72.81 crores, but a net profit decline of 15.14% to ₹1.85 crores and low profitability margins indicate ongoing challenges, leading to a negative market reaction and a one-year stock return of -34.55%.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a7a436196647c18cdad23401cf4f1cbd</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:26:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Refex Industries Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-refex-industries-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3798969</link><description>Refex Industries Ltd's latest results show strong profit growth and improved margins, with a net profit of ₹37.44 crores, up 76.85% sequentially. However, revenue volatility and operational challenges raise concerns about sustainability, leading to a cautious outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>000fc8f63d1387068baa386a4d66b977</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:26:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Mastek Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-mastek-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3798968</link><description>Mastek Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show mixed performance: while net profit increased by 11.19% quarter-on-quarter, revenue declined by 3.69%, raising concerns about sustainability. The company has strong margins and capital efficiency, but achieving last year's revenue levels will require a strong Q4.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9ec6c7007272d901ba26d5991fc61f89</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:26:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Shoppers Stop Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-shoppers-stop-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3798967</link><description>Shoppers Stop Ltd's latest results show modest sales growth but a significant 69.14% decline in net profit, raising concerns about profitability and high debt levels, indicating substantial challenges ahead for the company.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6ee937f99801e23e13e51c5925b1859a</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:26:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Mallcom (India) Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-mallcom-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3798966</link><description>Mallcom (India) Ltd's latest results show a mixed performance with a net profit increase of 12.40% year-on-year, but a 5.88% decline in revenue quarter-on-quarter. While operating margins improved, concerns about rising costs and revenue volatility suggest careful monitoring of the company's financial health is needed.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2d7739dd478b25cc71ba86395dec8417</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:26:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Umiya Buildcon Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-umiya-buildcon-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3798965</link><description>Umiya Buildcon Ltd's latest results are concerning, showing a 38.31% sequential decline in net sales and an 83.01% drop in net profit, indicating significant operational challenges and a high debt burden that may affect future performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>26f9fc82b82532b94d16f4c383b39a14</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:26:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are DCM Shriram Ltd. latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-dcm-shriram-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3798964</link><description>DCM Shriram Ltd.'s latest results show strong revenue growth of 13.20% year-on-year, but declining profit margins and rising costs raise concerns about profitability. While there is sequential improvement in net profit, the overall mixed performance suggests challenges ahead for margin recovery and cost management.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0e97b06e646e512665de321eb8fb6e09</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:26:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Supreme Petrochem Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-supreme-petrochem-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3798963</link><description>Supreme Petrochem Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show a 14.60% increase in net sales to ₹1,280.93 crores, but a significant 36.69% decline in net profit to ₹30.57 crores, indicating operational challenges and margin compression despite a solid balance sheet. Overall, the results are concerning due to declining profitability and efficiency metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ad94560faad4d21852ae68f970f1d021</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:26:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are R S Software (India) Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-r-s-software-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3798962</link><description>R S Software (India) Ltd's latest results are poor, showing a net loss of ₹5.92 crores and a 64.71% drop in revenue year-on-year, indicating significant operational challenges and a need for urgent restructuring to improve financial health.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>06ac01669d4add267d41f999f85c02c7</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:26:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Roselabs Finance Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-roselabs-finance-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3798961</link><description>Roselabs Finance Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show a slight improvement with net sales of ₹1.21 crores after two quarters of zero sales, but the company still faces significant challenges, including a net loss of ₹0.04 crores and negative financial metrics, indicating ongoing concerns about its viability and sustainability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a505c7b46dc40940e051a7a5464a621b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:26:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are PTC India Financial Services Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-ptc-india-financial-services-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3798960</link><description>PTC India Financial Services Ltd's latest results are concerning, showing a 7.66% decline in net sales and a 44.30% drop in net profit, marking ongoing operational challenges and sustained revenue contraction. The company's profitability and operational efficiency are under pressure, raising concerns about its future growth.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8400f90a13253ffd39f1dfd42d491c01</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:26:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Piccadily Sugar &amp; Allied Inds Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-piccadily-sugar-allied-inds-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3798959</link><description>Piccadily Sugar &amp; Allied Industries Ltd's latest results show revenue growth, but profitability has declined significantly, with a net profit of only ₹0.07 crores and concerning operational metrics, including a low return on equity and high tax burden, indicating ongoing financial challenges. Overall, the outlook remains negative despite some revenue increases.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>da1b50d998d9e837bcc3fb10c53cee7b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:26:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:26:57 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>