<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:21:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Prism Johnson . Hits Intraday High with Strong Trading Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/prism-johnson-surges-to-intraday-high-with-1105-gain-on-23-dec-2025-3767261</link><description>Prism Johnson . demonstrated robust intraday performance on 23 Dec 2025, surging to an intraday high of Rs 144.75, reflecting a gain of 11.47% during the trading session. The stock outpaced its sector peers and the broader market, supported by heightened volatility and sustained buying interest throughout the day.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>7dc20e897c034b225cd0e7e749bab951</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:21:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jindal Drilling &amp; Industries Hits Intraday High with Strong 8.14% Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jindal-drilling-industries-hits-intraday-high-with-814-surge-on-23-dec-2025-3767260</link><description>Jindal Drilling &amp; Industries recorded a robust intraday performance on 23 Dec 2025, surging to an intraday high of Rs 569, reflecting a gain of 9.21% during the trading session. The stock outpaced its sector and broader market indices, marking a notable day of trading activity in the oil sector.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>8df047c5a4914597704452477d7e7f1e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:21:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jain Marmo Industries Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.18.24 Amidst Market Headwinds</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jain-marmo-industries-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs1824-3767258</link><description>Jain Marmo Industries has reached a new 52-week low, closing at Rs.18.24 today, reflecting a continued downward trend over the past year. This decline contrasts with broader market movements, as the Sensex remains near its 52-week high, underscoring the stock’s relative underperformance within the miscellaneous sector.
Time: 38 minutes ago</description><guid>491b2e78a8990e0dfe44ea3e1054e1e1</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:21:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PBM Polytex Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.50.23 Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pbm-polytex-stock-hits-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3767255</link><description>PBM Polytex, a player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.50.23 today, marking a significant milestone in its recent price movement. The stock has been under pressure, reflecting a sustained downward trend over the past year and recent sessions.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>6b83692dee7a0be95eeb669f59512106</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:21:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Forge Reaches New 52-Week High of Rs.1464, Marking Significant Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-forge-reaches-new-52-week-high-of-rs1464-marking-significant-milestone-3767257</link><description>Bharat Forge has attained a new 52-week high of Rs.1464, underscoring a notable phase of momentum in the auto components sector. This milestone reflects the stock’s sustained upward trajectory amid broader market movements and company-specific financial developments.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>8c753d74e5dce698a9c51fb1212d0d3d</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:21:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Galaxy Bearings Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.475.4 Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/galaxy-bearings-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs4754-amid-continued-downtrend-3767256</link><description>Galaxy Bearings has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.475.4, marking a significant decline amid a sustained period of negative returns and underperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>a2faedda1aea4c27f90d570a943e8f27</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:21:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arfin India Hits New 52-Week High of Rs.66.78, Marking Strong Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/arfin-india-hits-new-52-week-high-of-rs6678-marking-strong-momentum-3767259</link><description>Arfin India, a key player in the Non-Ferrous Metals sector, reached a fresh 52-week high of Rs.66.78 today, reflecting notable momentum in its stock performance amid a broadly positive market environment.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>77227c8b3b6677bf2ecd683c97576776</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:21:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KFin Technologies Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amidst Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kfin-technologies-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amidst-bullish-momentum-3767253</link><description>KFin Technologies Ltd has experienced a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, coinciding with a period of sustained price gains and increased trading volumes. This development reflects evolving market positioning and heightened investor interest in the capital markets sector, warranting a closer examination of the underlying factors and potential implications for the stock’s near-term trajectory.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>52890ea4c53e6078754f9b87bbaa4c4b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:21:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kalyan Jewellers India Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Market Activity</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kalyan-jewellers-india-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3767254</link><description>Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd has experienced a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, reflecting a shift in market positioning and investor interest. This development coincides with the stock’s recent outperformance relative to its sector and broader market indices, signalling evolving sentiment in the Gems, Jewellery And Watches industry.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>008b6f2cffc175f66d469e87afc48449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:21:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>360 ONE WAM Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/360-one-wam-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-market-positioning-3767252</link><description>360 ONE WAM Ltd has registered a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, reflecting evolving market positioning and heightened investor activity. The stock’s recent performance, coupled with shifts in volume and liquidity metrics, offers insights into potential directional bets and market sentiment in the capital markets sector.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>a14137a6f55706a8a124e4ff37375304</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:21:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dalmia Bharat Sees Notable Surge in Open Interest Amid Market Activity</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dalmia-bharat-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-market-outperformance-3767248</link><description>Dalmia Bharat Ltd, a key player in the Cement &amp; Cement Products sector, has registered a significant rise in open interest in its derivatives segment, reflecting evolving market positioning and investor interest. This development coincides with a positive price movement and shifting volume patterns, offering insights into potential directional bets in the stock.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>f2c6007d0b90c58837ed7b51ae58cd71</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:21:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Green Energy Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Mixed Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-green-energy-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3767251</link><description>Adani Green Energy Ltd has registered a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, reflecting heightened market activity and evolving positioning among traders. Despite this surge, the stock's price movement has shown modest weakness relative to its sector, suggesting a complex interplay between speculative interest and underlying market sentiment.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>926dd7dbe827fe1f09b2894899bfe746</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:21:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/crompton-greaves-consumer-electricals-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3767249</link><description>Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals has witnessed a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. This development comes amid a backdrop of mixed price movements and evolving volume patterns, offering insights into potential directional bets on the stock.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>316cd116f9f8617f5bdbcd1e1abfd7a0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:21:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alkem Laboratories Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Mixed Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/alkem-laboratories-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3767245</link><description>Alkem Laboratories Ltd has experienced a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, reflecting heightened market activity and evolving investor positioning. Despite this surge, the stock’s price movement has shown a mixed trend, underperforming its sector and reversing gains after two consecutive days of positive returns.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>7589034ebeb34277f912c7a6c6b62bce</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:21:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Energy Solutions Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-energy-solutions-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3767246</link><description>Adani Energy Solutions has experienced a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, signalling a shift in market positioning and investor sentiment. This development comes amid a backdrop of subdued price movement and fluctuating volume patterns, prompting closer scrutiny of potential directional bets in the power sector stock.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>992cc1a33321ae193595a9058dfc78c4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:21:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maruti Suzuki India Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Market Activity</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/maruti-suzuki-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3767247</link><description>Maruti Suzuki India Ltd has experienced a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, reflecting heightened market participation and evolving positioning among traders. This development coincides with the stock reaching a new 52-week high, even as it underperformed its sector on the day, signalling nuanced investor sentiment in the automobile sector.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>6dffeba6ec22cc6821d9e8e272b47949</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:21:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Info Edge (India) Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/info-edge-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-derivatives-activity-3767244</link><description>Info Edge (India) Ltd, a prominent player in the E-Retail and E-Commerce sector, has witnessed a significant surge in open interest within its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and evolving investor positioning. This development coincides with the stock’s recent outperformance relative to its sector and broader indices, reflecting shifting market dynamics and potential directional bets.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>2c2e66d6ac10e1d7a1c2e6cc99996388</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:21:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Larsen &amp; Toubro Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Market Activity</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/larsen-toubro-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amidst-steady-price-momentum-3767250</link><description>Larsen &amp; Toubro Ltd. (LT), a prominent player in the construction sector, has witnessed a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market participation and evolving positioning among traders. This development comes as the stock trades close to its 52-week high, reflecting a complex interplay of volume dynamics and investor sentiment.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>945363eb3f79cf14e3b44601831dca9b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:21:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NMDC Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amidst Strong Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nmdc-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-price-momentum-3767243</link><description>NMDC Ltd has registered a notable rise in open interest in its derivatives segment, coinciding with a fresh 52-week high and sustained price gains. This development reflects evolving market positioning and heightened investor participation in the minerals and mining sector.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>bfb5bf222514f92d8df700a657454e9a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:21:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Glenmark Pharmaceuticals Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Rising Market Activity</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/glenmark-pharmaceuticals-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-market-positioning-3767240</link><description>Glenmark Pharmaceuticals has experienced a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, reflecting heightened market participation and evolving positioning among investors. This development coincides with the stock’s recent outperformance relative to its sector and sustained gains over the past several sessions, signalling increased investor focus on the pharmaceutical and biotechnology company.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>afa290bcf0e285317bf6b881805fe092</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:21:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 09:21:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>