<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:56:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Salzer Electronics Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/salzer-electronics-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3828318</link><description>Salzer Electronics Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 15 Dec 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 09 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and technical outlook.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>f7eb5aa0c4e2294fd724905e9e58d573</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Munjal Auto Industries Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/munjal-auto-industries-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3828317</link><description>Munjal Auto Industries Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 14 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 09 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>fb2d489d9b325e1b0b508de4f2a2db1f</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Total Transport Systems Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/total-transport-systems-ltd-is-rated-sell-3828315</link><description>Total Transport Systems Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 05 February 2026, reflecting a shift from the previous Hold status. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here are based on the company’s current position as of 09 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date view of the stock’s fundamentals, returns, and technical outlook.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>a2772ce71bf9fe9090b43b3800b7dfd4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blue Jet Healthcare Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/blue-jet-healthcare-ltd-is-rated-sell-3828314</link><description>Blue Jet Healthcare Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 06 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 09 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date perspective on the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>4145fde9e9d8b8b28ac57a206458cc8f</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal-Mogul Goetze (India) Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/federal-mogul-goetze-india-ltd-is-rated-hold-3828313</link><description>Federal-Mogul Goetze (India) Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 28 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 09 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>8de9f825f8d0393091a5b4f459f77351</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahindra EPC Irrigation Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/mahindra-epc-irrigation-ltd-is-rated-sell-3828311</link><description>Mahindra EPC Irrigation Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 16 January 2026. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 09 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date analysis of the company’s standing.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>816e3e444f9037d2562f51647a875229</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CG-VAK Software &amp; Exports Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/cg-vak-software-exports-ltd-is-rated-sell-3828309</link><description>CG-VAK Software &amp; Exports Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 11 August 2025, reflecting a change from the previous Hold rating. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here represent the stock’s current position as of 09 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trend, and technical outlook.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>4f23865209ee119da4bbb4268716e52a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anik Industries Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/anik-industries-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3828308</link><description>Anik Industries Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 12 August 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 09 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>2a56e26bbc87246591c2a478fc17df81</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maheshwari Logistics Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/maheshwari-logistics-ltd-is-rated-sell-3828306</link><description>Maheshwari Logistics Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 05 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 09 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date insight into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>61faeeff8cf58fd72591ff56dd1048ea</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lux Industries Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/lux-industries-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3828305</link><description>Lux Industries Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 06 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock’s current position as of 09 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>474d46b0f2556971bf1a6f123c19f36a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Balaxi Pharmaceuticals Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/balaxi-pharmaceuticals-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3828297</link><description>Balaxi Pharmaceuticals Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 12 Nov 2025, reflecting a shift from the previous 'Sell' grade. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here represent the stock's current position as of 09 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of its performance and outlook.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>c56650573e695598f13dc6358cae6826</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Entertainment Network (India) Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/entertainment-network-india-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3828296</link><description>Entertainment Network (India) Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 28 January 2026, reflecting a shift from the previous 'Sell' grade. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here are current as of 09 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the stock's position.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>367b505fbc7d0e4f519d5f0b937b9dc3</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Navkar Urbanstructure Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/navkar-urbanstructure-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3828292</link><description>Navkar Urbanstructure Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 28 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 09 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>547f9af6f72005e3bc2c5bd12a25d14c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tyche Industries Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/tyche-industries-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3828295</link><description>Tyche Industries Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 10 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 09 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>3ae4a77ade3a9a83e7baa179c36d2406</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mega Nirman &amp; Industries Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/mega-nirman-industries-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3828294</link><description>Mega Nirman &amp; Industries Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 21 January 2026, reflecting a reassessment of the stock's outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed below are current as of 09 February 2026, providing investors with the latest perspective on the company’s position.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>22933e67516c4624c33e5cfa746d860c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KIFS Financial Services Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/kifs-financial-services-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3828291</link><description>KIFS Financial Services Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 29 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 09 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>9b3decd2c0dc10737f862455a9626307</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gujarat Toolroom Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/gujarat-toolroom-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3828290</link><description>Gujarat Toolroom Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 08 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 09 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>c0d6d1ab9650ba3072d27188db710fa2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manugraph India Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/manugraph-india-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3828288</link><description>Manugraph India Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 28 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 09 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>65c44279c62a6a19c8a1779257ecc68e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Basant Agro Tech (India) Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/basant-agro-tech-india-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3828287</link><description>Basant Agro Tech (India) Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 06 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 09 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>5c89d3bde01ea576e803420e0e78afa7</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Akash Infraprojects Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/akash-infraprojects-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3828286</link><description>Akash Infraprojects Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 19 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 09 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>29c64ed44c00f757e02343179567a7c6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:56:26 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>