<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 04:02:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Sensex Edges Higher Amid Mixed Sectoral Trends; Metals Lead Gains</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-edges-higher-amid-mixed-sectoral-trends-metals-lead-gains-3801129</link><description>The Indian equity market closed marginally higher on 23 Jan 2026, with the Sensex gaining 67.42 points or 0.08% to settle at 82,374.79. Despite a cautious start and mixed sectoral performance, metals emerged as the top-performing sector, while realty lagged. Market breadth remained weak, reflecting investor caution amid global uncertainties and upcoming corporate earnings.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>b6c09c532aa4c21c5b43f47d9509455a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 04:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jio Financial Services Ltd Faces Challenges Amid Nifty 50 Membership and Sector Headwinds</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jio-financial-services-ltd-faces-challenges-amid-nifty-50-membership-and-sector-headwinds-3801125</link><description>Jio Financial Services Ltd, a recent entrant to the prestigious Nifty 50 index, is navigating a complex market environment marked by subdued price performance, a downgrade in its mojo rating, and shifting institutional holdings. Despite its large-cap status and sector prominence within the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) space, the stock has struggled to keep pace with benchmark indices, raising questions about its near-term outlook and strategic positioning.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>f6b803e4e3f2927c0165e3b1be569145</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 04:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eternal Ltd’s Nifty 50 Membership Highlights Institutional Shifts and Market Challenges</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eternal-ltds-nifty-50-membership-highlights-institutional-shifts-and-market-challenges-3801124</link><description>Eternal Ltd, a prominent player in the E-Retail and E-Commerce sector, has recently undergone a downgrade from Hold to Sell by MarketsMOJO, reflecting growing concerns over its valuation and near-term performance. Despite its significant presence as a Nifty 50 constituent, the stock has struggled to maintain momentum amid broader market volatility and sector-specific challenges.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>e6704923f42a5c272196f598a0649dba</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 04:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Max Healthcare Institute Ltd: Navigating Challenges Amidst Nifty 50 Membership</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/max-healthcare-institute-ltd-navigating-challenges-amidst-nifty-50-membership-3801123</link><description>Max Healthcare Institute Ltd, a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, has recently undergone a notable downgrade in its mojo grade from Hold to Sell, reflecting growing concerns over its market performance and valuation metrics. Despite its large-cap status and significant market capitalisation, the hospital sector heavyweight has struggled to keep pace with benchmark indices, prompting investors and analysts to reassess its outlook.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>26a41474654c4c232718ffcd0a4d0351</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 04:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Auto Ltd. Strengthens Position as Nifty 50 Constituent Amid Institutional Interest</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-auto-ltd-strengthens-position-as-nifty-50-constituent-amid-institutional-interest-3801128</link><description>Bajaj Auto Ltd., a stalwart in the Indian automobile sector and a prominent Nifty 50 constituent, continues to demonstrate resilience amid evolving market conditions. With a recent upgrade in its Mojo Grade from Sell to Hold and steady institutional interest, the company’s performance offers valuable insights into its benchmark significance and investor sentiment.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>ca2ddc7034198a0cdf88011ac59b3e30</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 04:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maruti Suzuki India Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/maruti-suzuki-india-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-3801126</link><description>Maruti Suzuki India Ltd continues to assert its significance within the Nifty 50 index, reflecting robust long-term performance despite recent short-term volatility. Institutional holding patterns and benchmark status remain pivotal factors shaping investor sentiment and market positioning for this automobile sector heavyweight.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>ba2a2caf9f3c17c74ac84bfa366d6dd4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 04:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Finance Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-finance-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-3801127</link><description>Bajaj Finance Ltd, a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to command significant attention from investors amid evolving institutional holdings and benchmark dynamics. Despite recent short-term headwinds, the company’s large-cap stature and robust long-term performance underpin its critical role within India’s financial markets.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>05f9c85ce423121829036a66a8590908</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 04:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd Faces Challenges Amid Nifty 50 Membership</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-motors-passenger-vehicles-ltd-faces-challenges-amid-nifty-50-membership-3801122</link><description>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd, a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, has experienced notable challenges in recent trading sessions, reflecting broader sectoral pressures and shifting institutional holdings. Despite its large-cap status and significant market presence, the stock’s recent downgrade and underperformance relative to benchmarks highlight the complexities investors face in the current automobile sector landscape.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>e7bc7920c7c9b56570e055e81b5da956</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 04:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd: Navigating Challenges Amidst Nifty 50 Membership</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sun-pharmaceutical-industries-ltd-navigating-challenges-amidst-nifty-50-membership-3801120</link><description>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd, a stalwart in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector and a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, is currently facing a complex market environment. Despite its large-cap stature and benchmark status, recent institutional holding changes and a downgrade in its mojo grade have cast a shadow over its near-term outlook. This article analyses the implications of these developments for investors and the broader market context.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>d1a7d873730a73cc578a21aab7b4cad1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 04:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JSW Steel Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amid Institutional Shifts and Market Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jsw-steel-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-institutional-shifts-and-market-dynamics-3801121</link><description>JSW Steel Ltd., a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to demonstrate resilience and strategic positioning within the ferrous metals sector. Despite a slight dip in its daily performance, the stock’s sustained gains over recent months and its robust long-term returns underscore its significance as a bellwether for the steel industry and the broader market.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>280669788a4263637d2c550be424b8d8</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 04:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Ltd Strengthens Position as a Key Nifty 50 Constituent Amid Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mahindra-mahindra-ltd-strengthens-position-as-a-key-nifty-50-constituent-amid-institutional-shifts-3801119</link><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Ltd (M&amp;M), a stalwart in the Indian automobile sector, continues to demonstrate resilience and strategic significance as a constituent of the Nifty 50 index. Despite recent market headwinds, the company’s upgraded mojo grade and sustained institutional interest underscore its pivotal role in India’s large-cap automobile landscape.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>b98c54a1b50429c2beccb48acabd5db0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 04:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Larsen &amp; Toubro Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amid Mixed Market Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/larsen-toubro-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-mixed-market-performance-3801118</link><description>Larsen &amp; Toubro Ltd. (L&amp;T), a stalwart in the Indian construction sector and a prominent Nifty 50 constituent, has recently experienced a recalibration in its market standing. Despite its large-cap status and historical outperformance relative to the Sensex, the company’s latest Mojo Grade downgrade from Buy to Hold signals a cautious outlook amid evolving institutional holdings and sectoral pressures. This article analyses L&amp;T’s current market position, the significance of its benchmark membership, and the implications for investors navigating the capital goods space.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>3f25cac3c29f238031577799000be70c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 04:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Finserv Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-finserv-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-3801117</link><description>Bajaj Finserv Ltd, a prominent holding company and a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to demonstrate resilience amid evolving market conditions. Despite a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade from Buy to Hold, the stock’s long-term performance remains robust, underscoring its significance within India’s benchmark index and the broader financial sector.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>c37db53f994120c69125f2921452c97c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 04:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Enterprises Ltd Faces Downgrade Amidst Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-enterprises-ltd-faces-downgrade-amidst-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-shifts-3801116</link><description>Adani Enterprises Ltd, a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to grapple with significant headwinds as it underperforms both its sector and the broader market. Despite its large-cap status and inclusion in India’s premier benchmark, the stock has seen a marked deterioration in investor sentiment, reflected in its recent downgrade to a Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO and persistent declines across multiple time frames.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>9ea988b9f3e05602e46525b6b5a05da6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 04:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tech Mahindra Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Institutional Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tech-mahindra-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-institutional-dynamics-3801114</link><description>Tech Mahindra Ltd., a prominent player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, continues to consolidate its stature within the Nifty 50 index, buoyed by positive institutional sentiment and a recent upgrade in its investment grade. The stock’s performance relative to benchmarks and sector peers highlights its growing appeal among investors navigating a volatile market environment.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>d00ff91d00cd495f76bb0cd9e6d9860d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 04:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Unilever Ltd Faces Downgrade Amid Mixed Performance and Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-unilever-ltd-faces-downgrade-amid-mixed-performance-and-institutional-shifts-3801115</link><description>Hindustan Unilever Ltd (HUL), a flagship FMCG constituent of the Nifty 50 index, has recently been downgraded from a Hold to a Sell rating, reflecting growing concerns over its subdued performance relative to the benchmark Sensex and evolving institutional investor sentiment. Despite its large-cap stature and critical role in the index, the company’s recent financial metrics and market dynamics suggest a cautious outlook for investors.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>7538ad5119e3dd44fdf609937bdcb70c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 04:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dr Reddys Laboratories Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amid Mixed Performance and Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dr-reddys-laboratories-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-mixed-performance-and-institutional-shifts-3801113</link><description>Dr Reddys Laboratories Ltd, a stalwart in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector and a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, has recently experienced notable shifts in institutional holdings and market sentiment. Despite a recent upgrade in short-term price momentum, the stock faces challenges reflected in its revised Mojo Grade and valuation metrics, underscoring the complex dynamics of maintaining benchmark status in a competitive large-cap environment.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>8b34134795cb02d6c0b56ad1d4cd9c95</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 04:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Ports &amp; Special Economic Zone Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership and Market Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-ports-special-economic-zone-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-and-market-dynamics-3801112</link><description>Adani Ports &amp; Special Economic Zone Ltd, a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to demonstrate its strategic importance within India’s transport infrastructure sector. Despite a modest dip in daily trading, the stock’s long-term performance and evolving institutional holdings underscore its pivotal role in benchmark indices and investor portfolios.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>0313823a9058307093e2c433c9a3995d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 04:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Grasim Industries Ltd: Cement Sector Leader Strengthens Nifty 50 Presence Amid Institutional Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/grasim-industries-ltd-cement-sector-leader-strengthens-nifty-50-presence-amid-institutional-shifts-3801110</link><description>Grasim Industries Ltd, a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index and a heavyweight in the Cement &amp; Cement Products sector, has recently experienced notable shifts in institutional holdings and market positioning. Despite a slight dip in daily performance, the company’s upgraded mojo grade and robust long-term returns underscore its significance within the benchmark index and cement sector landscape.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>cb26fbbf6513b840d5c63637054e1c67</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 04:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oil &amp; Natural Gas Corporation Ltd: Navigating Nifty 50 Membership Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/oil-natural-gas-corporation-ltd-navigating-nifty-50-membership-amid-mixed-market-signals-3801111</link><description>Oil &amp; Natural Gas Corporation Ltd. (ONGC), a stalwart in India’s oil sector and a key constituent of the Nifty 50 index, continues to command significant attention amid evolving market dynamics. Despite a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade from Buy to Hold, the company’s large-cap status, robust dividend yield, and strategic importance within the benchmark index underscore its enduring relevance for investors and institutions alike.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>c34f73547b95c0bade94acbe76c8f007</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 04:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 04:02:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>