<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:25:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>When is the next results date for Borana Weaves Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-borana-weaves-ltd-3794875</link><description>The next results date for Borana Weaves Ltd is 22 January 2026.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>44d38f1b41f74fb82b7754896d876504</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:25:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When is the next results date for Dolphin Medical?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-dolphin-medical-3794874</link><description>The next results date for Dolphin Medical is January 30, 2026.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>3a95bc435ceb91c04f915ccac77135cd</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:25:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When is the next results date for Bluestone Jewellery &amp; Lifestyle Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-bluestone-jewellery-lifestyle-ltd-3794873</link><description>The next results date for Bluestone Jewellery &amp; Lifestyle Ltd is January 22, 2026.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>c25b8ec0d2bcab2b11ea5b9d4248920d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:25:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When is the next results date for Krystal Integrated Services Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-krystal-integrated-services-ltd-3794872</link><description>The next results date for Krystal Integrated Services Ltd is January 22, 2026.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>1d9572940b70c1833abff2aee4b8a656</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:25:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When is the next results date for Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-nuvama-wealth-management-ltd-3794871</link><description>The next results date for Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd is January 23, 2026.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>e47dcaae486abe7ed1e4f8ffb67d3a6c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:25:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When is the next results date for Alkyl Amines Chemicals Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-alkyl-amines-chemicals-ltd-3794870</link><description>The next results date for Alkyl Amines Chemicals Ltd is February 3, 2026.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>fb1ebc75df988207bbe6ee123461d8d0</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:25:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When is the next results date for Lykis Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-lykis-ltd-3794869</link><description>The next results date for Lykis Ltd is 23 January 2026.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>019e27d69472d17897bbf61140119bd3</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:25:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When is the next results date for Achyut Healthcare Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-achyut-healthcare-ltd-3794868</link><description>The next results date for Achyut Healthcare Ltd is January 21, 2026.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>28730156d54f10adc07be1248bfa90b6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:25:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When is the next results date for Rajnish Retail Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-rajnish-retail-ltd-3794867</link><description>The next results date for Rajnish Retail Ltd is January 21, 2026.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>5d39264e6a7cfaeff27f8ba660e2632c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:25:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>When is the next results date for Arcee Industries Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-arcee-industries-ltd-3794866</link><description>The next results date for Arcee Industries Ltd is 24 January 2026.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>2f10c277c78876a94ddbf7a151e5d264</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:25:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aarti Surfactants Q2 FY26: Margin Compression Weighs on Profitability Despite Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/aarti-surfactants-q2-fy26-margin-compression-weighs-on-profitability-despite-revenue-growth-3794854</link><description>Aarti Surfactants Limited, a speciality surfactants manufacturer serving home and personal care, agro, and oil industries, reported a challenging Q2 FY26 performance marked by sharp margin contraction despite top-line growth. The company posted a net profit of ₹1.56 crores for the quarter ended September 2025, representing a steep decline of 46.94% quarter-on-quarter and 13.81% year-on-year. With a market capitalisation of ₹327 crores, the micro-cap speciality chemicals player faces mounting pressure from operating margin compression that has weighed heavily on bottom-line performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>12ad2c9b6330e03d6b9839b2b260ce6b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:25:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>National Standard (India) Q2 FY26: Other Income Masks Operational Struggles in Real Estate Pivot</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/national-standard-india-q2-fy26-other-income-masks-operational-struggles-in-real-estate-pivot-3794853</link><description>National Standard (India) Ltd., a small-cap real estate company with a market capitalisation of ₹3,910 crores, reported net profit of ₹4.26 crores for Q2 FY26, marking a substantial 330.30% jump quarter-on-quarter but an 11.25% decline year-on-year. The company's stock has experienced significant volatility, currently trading at ₹1,851.00, down 5.31% from the previous close and sitting 57.17% below its 52-week high of ₹4,322.00.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d104167ce2aabaa9d3e4916b68dacc6e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:25:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Show Mixed Trends with Mid Caps Leading Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-with-mid-caps-leading-growth-3794840</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has delivered a mixed bag of results across market capitalisations, with an overall improvement in positive outcomes compared to previous quarters. While mid-cap companies led the charge with a robust 66.0% positive result rate, large caps lagged behind at 35.0%, highlighting divergent sectoral and size-based performance trends amid evolving economic conditions.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>905f5c1a9411f171d8465347a7e60168</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:25:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Force Motors Added to Mojo Stocks Amid Strong Financial Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/mojo-premium/force-motors-added-to-mojo-stocks-amid-strong-financial-momentum-3794839</link><description>Force Motors has been added to the prestigious Mojo Stocks list as of 19 January 2026, reflecting its remarkable financial turnaround and bullish momentum. The small-cap automobile manufacturer has demonstrated exceptional quarterly performance, prompting a strategic inclusion that aligns with MarketsMojo’s focus on fundamentally strong and momentum-driven stocks.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>8deef976f84e2d8d99048d9f82b3dd2a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:25:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ind-Swift Labs Joins Hidden Turnarounds List Following Robust Quarterly Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/mojo-premium/ind-swift-labs-joins-hidden-turnarounds-list-following-robust-quarterly-growth-3794838</link><description>Ind-Swift Labs, a micro-cap pharmaceutical company, has been added to the prestigious Hidden Turnarounds list as of 19 January 2026, following a remarkable quarter of financial performance and a shift in market sentiment. This inclusion highlights the company’s emerging potential as a turnaround candidate with robust growth prospects and improving fundamentals.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>77c285890168c081c51cde541cc4828d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:25:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bansal Wire Industries Q3 FY26: Profit Surge Masks Margin Pressures and Technical Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/bansal-wire-industries-q3-fy26-profit-surge-masks-margin-pressures-and-technical-weakness-3794845</link><description>Bansal Wire Industries Ltd., a small-cap player in the iron and steel products sector with a market capitalisation of ₹4,665 crores, reported a consolidated net profit of ₹43.27 crores for Q3 FY26 (Oct-Dec'25), marking a sequential improvement of 12.92% from the previous quarter. However, this profit growth came amidst a marginal revenue decline and persistent margin pressures, whilst the stock continues to languish in bearish technical territory, down 25.95% over the past year.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>cf5c030b86380e8b633c4f6c3de3aac3</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:25:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanathnagar Enterprises Q3 FY26: Losses Deepen as Revenue Remains Dormant</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/sanathnagar-enterprises-q3-fy26-losses-deepen-as-revenue-remains-dormant-3794844</link><description>Sanathnagar Enterprises Limited, a micro-cap realty company with a market capitalisation of ₹13.00 crores, reported a net loss of ₹0.08 crores in Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), marking its third consecutive quarter of losses. The company, which operates with zero revenue generation, continues to struggle with operational viability as employee costs and administrative expenses drain cash reserves. Despite the concerning fundamentals, the stock surged 4.89% on January 19, 2026, trading at ₹42.48, though this appears disconnected from underlying business performance.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>a21ee820ad6c160fbbe76482e4df567d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:25:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ISF Ltd: Micro-Cap NBFC Struggles with Persistent Losses and Elevated Valuation</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/isf-ltd-micro-cap-nbfc-struggles-with-persistent-losses-and-elevated-valuation-3794843</link><description>ISF Ltd., a micro-cap non-banking financial company (NBFC) with a market capitalisation of just ₹10.00 crores, continues to face severe operational challenges as reflected in its historical financial performance. Trading at ₹0.95 per share as of January 19, 2026, the stock has plunged 6.86% in a single session, extending a brutal decline that has seen it lose 39.49% over the past year and a staggering 64.42% over two years. With an average Return on Equity of merely 1.75% and a troubling loss-making track record in recent quarters, the company presents a compelling case study in financial distress within the NBFC sector.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>08b80627a0226dbd9421d9816763517a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:25:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oberoi Realty Q3 FY26: Premium Developer Faces Margin Pressure Amid Volume Slowdown</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/oberoi-realty-q3-fy26-premium-developer-faces-margin-pressure-amid-volume-slowdown-3794842</link><description>Oberoi Realty Ltd., one of Mumbai's most prestigious real estate developers, reported a consolidated net profit of ₹622.64 crores for Q3 FY26, marking a marginal 0.69% year-on-year growth but an 18.10% sequential decline from the previous quarter's ₹760.26 crores. The results reflect a challenging quarter characterised by volume moderation and margin compression, raising concerns about near-term momentum for this ₹60,062-crore market capitalisation company.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>f623df9c394f84cd398b7ee6c4264bfe</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:25:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:25:29 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>