<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:44:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Physicswallah Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amidst Continued Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/physicswallah-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amidst-continued-decline-3863918</link><description>Physicswallah Ltd’s stock price has fallen to a new all-time low of ₹81.39, marking a significant decline amid sustained negative returns and underperformance relative to the broader market and its sector peers.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>07a5331ff83f5975467bb60e76065459</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:44:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indo Farm Equipment Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indo-farm-equipment-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amid-prolonged-downtrend-3863917</link><description>Indo Farm Equipment Ltd’s stock plunged to a fresh all-time low of Rs.114 on 2 Mar 2026, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock’s performance over recent months and years reflects a sustained period of underperformance relative to the broader market and its sector peers.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>a1f107434ae08ef1af45e2799cb87d30</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:44:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Concord Enviro Systems Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/concord-enviro-systems-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amid-prolonged-downtrend-3863916</link><description>Concord Enviro Systems Ltd, a player in the Other Utilities sector, has reached a new all-time low of Rs.289.75, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing downward trajectory. The stock’s recent performance highlights a sustained period of decline, reflecting a challenging environment for the company amid broader sectoral and market pressures.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>052f3b94dc0077902561745ebbcb5d4a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:44:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dam Capital Advisors Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dam-capital-advisors-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3863914</link><description>Dam Capital Advisors Ltd has reached a new all-time low of Rs.143.5, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock’s performance continues to lag behind both its sector and broader market indices, reflecting a challenging period for the capital markets company.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>f0d3498cfa150f2c135adef85f67c294</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:44:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>One Mobikwik Systems Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/one-mobikwik-systems-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3863915</link><description>One Mobikwik Systems Ltd, a player in the Financial Technology sector, has reached a new all-time low of Rs.181.05, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock’s recent performance reflects a sustained period of underperformance relative to both its sector and broader market indices.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>d728fbfb90595dcbd00f291cf09ac119</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:44:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Odigma Consultancy Solutions Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amidst Continued Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/odigma-consultancy-solutions-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amidst-continued-decline-3863913</link><description>Odigma Consultancy Solutions Ltd, a player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has reached a new all-time low of Rs.24, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock’s recent performance reflects a sustained downward trajectory, underperforming both its sector and broader market indices over multiple time frames.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>1df573ffa0bd52b7503f2a629b6d9ee4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:44:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Suraksha Diagnostic Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/suraksha-diagnostic-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3863912</link><description>Suraksha Diagnostic Ltd, a player in the healthcare services sector, has reached a new all-time low price of Rs. 227.95, marking a significant decline amid a period of sustained underperformance relative to the broader market and its sector peers.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>3c6278294fce07ef8ed7f3e9bead24a4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:44:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Swiggy Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/swiggy-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3863910</link><description>Swiggy Ltd’s share price plunged to a new all-time low of Rs. 285.85 on 2 Mar 2026, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing decline. The company’s shares have underperformed both the broader market and its sector peers, reflecting persistent headwinds and subdued financial metrics.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>3e61d10e7e5d23b7c81d820950930996</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:44:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Afcons Infrastructure Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/afcons-infrastructure-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amid-prolonged-downtrend-3863911</link><description>Afcons Infrastructure Ltd’s stock plunged to a new all-time low of Rs. 271.8 on 2 Mar 2026, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock has endured a sustained downtrend, underperforming both its sector and the broader market over multiple time frames, reflecting persistent pressures within the construction industry and company-specific financial strains.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>e78b9416c74dc5d8f57f02fdf34d4529</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:44:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deepak Builders &amp; Engineers India Ltd Hits All-Time Low at Rs 70 Amid Prolonged Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/deepak-builders-engineers-india-ltd-hits-all-time-low-at-rs-70-amid-prolonged-decline-3863909</link><description>Deepak Builders &amp; Engineers India Ltd has reached a new all-time low of Rs.70, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing downward trajectory. The stock’s performance continues to lag behind both its sector and broader market indices, reflecting persistent pressures on the company’s financial health and market valuation.
Time: 29 minutes ago</description><guid>3455d55bce958f996484249d21652338</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:44:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manba Finance Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/manba-finance-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amid-prolonged-underperformance-3863908</link><description>Manba Finance Ltd, a Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC), has recorded a new all-time low of Rs.115.05, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing share price decline. The stock’s recent performance reflects a sustained downward trajectory, underperforming both its sector and broader market indices over multiple time frames.
Time: 29 minutes ago</description><guid>674bc6273ebc1237c5bfe4bbf7483223</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:44:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tolins Tyres Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tolins-tyres-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amid-prolonged-downtrend-3863907</link><description>Tolins Tyres Ltd has recorded a new all-time low of Rs.93.6, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock has endured a sustained period of losses, reflecting broader pressures within the Tyres &amp; Rubber Products sector and the company’s recent performance metrics.
Time: 29 minutes ago</description><guid>be641f587e04c2d08a2cc288d6d982c0</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:44:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Housing Finance Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-housing-finance-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3863906</link><description>Bajaj Housing Finance Ltd’s stock plunged to a new all-time low of Rs.81.4 on 2 Mar 2026, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock has underperformed its sector and benchmark indices over multiple time frames, reflecting persistent pressures on its market valuation despite steady operational metrics.
Time: 29 minutes ago</description><guid>dabc0826377565202e9032bcef15eeeb</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:44:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amidst Mixed Financial Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sanofi-consumer-healthcare-india-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amidst-mixed-financial-signals-3863904</link><description>Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd’s stock plunged to a new all-time low of Rs. 3,950.5 on 2 Mar 2026, marking a significant moment in the company’s market journey. The stock’s recent performance reflects a complex interplay of valuation concerns and market dynamics within the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector.
Time: 29 minutes ago</description><guid>5920341a469ff640d86bf3aa85dd8a63</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:44:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gala Precision Engineering Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amid Market Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gala-precision-engineering-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amid-market-underperformance-3863905</link><description>Gala Precision Engineering Ltd’s stock plunged to a new all-time low of Rs. 648.05 on 2 Mar 2026, marking a significant decline amid broader sector weakness and persistent underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 30 minutes ago</description><guid>a1596991665c6dbb77b21783a2703169</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:44:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ecos (India) Mobility &amp; Hospitality Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amid Market Downturn</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ecos-india-mobility-hospitality-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amid-market-downturn-3863903</link><description>Ecos (India) Mobility &amp; Hospitality Ltd, a player in the transport services sector, has recorded a new all-time low of Rs.141.05, marking a significant decline amid broader market pressures. The stock’s performance continues to lag behind key benchmarks, reflecting ongoing difficulties in maintaining momentum within a challenging environment.
Time: 30 minutes ago</description><guid>0a3e280676539944d2e69448addd15d6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:44:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Saraswati Saree Depot Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/saraswati-saree-depot-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amid-prolonged-downtrend-3863901</link><description>Saraswati Saree Depot Ltd, a player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has reached a new all-time low of Rs. 52.5, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock’s recent performance reflects sustained pressure, with returns sharply lagging behind benchmark indices and sector peers.
Time: 30 minutes ago</description><guid>ab335bd197c9ca45d717d3560168bc9a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:44:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanstar Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sanstar-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3863900</link><description>Sanstar Ltd, a company operating in the Other Agricultural Products sector, has reached a new all-time low of Rs.77, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock’s performance continues to lag behind key market indices and sector benchmarks, reflecting persistent challenges in its financial and operational metrics.
Time: 31 minutes ago</description><guid>47acb9834317e9994c2ed678d6a17887</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:44:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bansal Wire Industries Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bansal-wire-industries-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amid-prolonged-downtrend-3863899</link><description>Bansal Wire Industries Ltd, a player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, has reached a new all-time low of Rs.249.2, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock’s performance continues to lag behind key benchmarks, reflecting persistent pressures across multiple timeframes.
Time: 31 minutes ago</description><guid>6a75eedbef0955b8f70578c2883b33c9</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:44:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stanley Lifestyles Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/stanley-lifestyles-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3863902</link><description>Stanley Lifestyles Ltd, a key player in the Furniture and Home Furnishing sector, has recorded a new all-time low of Rs.156.85, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock’s performance over recent months highlights a sustained downward trajectory, reflecting a combination of financial pressures and sectoral headwinds.
Time: 31 minutes ago</description><guid>8b5e25ef953fb80c7ede428b8b14a761</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:44:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:44:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>