<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:17:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Jyoti Structures Gains 3.20%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Rebound</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jyoti-structures-gains-320-5-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-rebound-3804263</link><description>Jyoti Structures Ltd’s stock rebounded with a 3.20% gain over the week ending 23 January 2026, closing at Rs.9.04 compared to Rs.8.76 the previous Friday. This performance notably outpaced the Sensex, which declined 3.31% during the same period, reflecting a mixed week marked by sharp declines early on followed by a strong intraday rally and a modest finish. The stock’s volatility was driven by a series of 52-week lows, a significant intraday surge, and quarterly results that revealed both profit growth and structural concerns.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>eea24f63198f7847fd1965cd42168cd1</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vimta Labs Declines 5.92%: 5 Key Technical Shifts Shape Weekly Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vimta-labs-declines-592-5-key-technical-shifts-shape-weekly-performance-3804264</link><description>Vimta Labs Ltd closed the week ending 23 January 2026 at Rs.512.35, down 5.92% from Rs.544.60 the previous Friday, underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. The stock experienced significant volatility amid a series of technical momentum shifts and a downgrade to a Sell rating, reflecting growing investor caution despite the company’s strong long-term fundamentals.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>faa46d4da34411603e02bb6f1eafff9b</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DCM Shriram Ltd. Falls 4.96%: Mixed Technical Signals and Q3 Results Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dcm-shriram-ltd-falls-496-mixed-technical-signals-and-q3-results-shape-the-week-3804262</link><description>DCM Shriram Ltd. closed the week ending 23 January 2026 at Rs.1,103.95, down 4.96% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.1,161.60. This decline outpaced the Sensex’s 3.31% fall over the same period, reflecting a week marked by technical momentum shifts, a downgrade in analyst rating, and mixed financial signals. Despite a strong operational rebound reported midweek, the stock faced selling pressure amid broader market weakness and cautious investor sentiment.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>fd89f6f96d5503bee5d54edab874b42d</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bosch Ltd Falls 4.22%: Technical Weakness and Flat Financials Weigh on Stock</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bosch-ltd-falls-422-technical-weakness-and-flat-financials-weigh-on-stock-3804261</link><description>Bosch Ltd. experienced a challenging week on the BSE, closing at Rs.35,279.10 on 23 January 2026, down 4.22% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.36,833.20. This decline outpaced the Sensex’s 3.31% fall over the same period, reflecting a combination of technical weakness and a significant downgrade by MarketsMOJO. Despite some intraday recoveries, the stock struggled to regain momentum amid flat financial results and bearish technical signals.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>ce4e8577ba1f5c986cbbb3ba9ba5e8bb</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanghi Industries Falls 6.92%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sanghi-industries-falls-692-2-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3804260</link><description>Sanghi Industries Ltd experienced a challenging week ending 23 January 2026, with its stock price declining 6.92% from Rs.64.91 to Rs.60.42, underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. The week was marked by a significant downgrade to a Strong Sell rating amid deteriorating financials and bearish technical momentum, alongside mixed market signals that contributed to heightened volatility and investor caution.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>75cf9822643b1d5242f7373d44948fe2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Steel Strips Wheels Ltd Falls 9.04%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/steel-strips-wheels-ltd-falls-904-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3804259</link><description>Steel Strips Wheels Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its stock price declining by 9.04% from Rs.197.35 to Rs.179.50, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 3.31% fall over the same period. The week was marked by a series of bearish technical signals, a downgrade to Strong Sell, stabilised yet pressured quarterly results, and mixed market sentiment amid ongoing margin concerns.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>254e8f9c710eacaf1ee654337a16b50d</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kernex Microsystems Falls 15.79%: 4 Key Factors Behind the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kernex-microsystems-falls-1579-4-key-factors-behind-the-weekly-decline-3804258</link><description>Kernex Microsystems (India) Ltd experienced a challenging week ending 23 January 2026, with its stock price declining by 15.79% from ₹1,349.95 to ₹1,136.75. This underperformance was notably sharper than the Sensex’s 3.31% fall over the same period, reflecting a combination of technical shifts, sector pressures, and market sentiment that weighed heavily on the stock’s performance.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>4eb7322352c09a2aa0668eb053b387fa</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gujarat State Fertilizers &amp; Chemicals Ltd: 0.20% Weekly Dip Amid Valuation Shifts and Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gujarat-state-fertilizers-chemicals-ltd-020-weekly-dip-amid-valuation-shifts-and-market-volatility-3804257</link><description>Gujarat State Fertilizers &amp; Chemicals Ltd (GSFC) ended the week marginally lower by 0.20%, closing at Rs.173.65 on 23 January 2026, despite a notable shift in its valuation grade from fair to attractive. The stock’s performance contrasted sharply with the broader BSE Sensex, which declined 3.31% over the same period, signalling relative resilience amid sector headwinds and a downgrade to a Sell rating by MarketsMOJO. Key events during the week included the downgrade announcement on 20 January and a valuation upgrade on 22 January, both influencing investor sentiment and price movements.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>13fe5bef4e50011e7e8a3657ea00a53a</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Excel Realty N Infra Ltd Falls 9.56%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/excel-realty-n-infra-ltd-falls-956-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3804256</link><description>Excel Realty N Infra Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its share price declining 9.56% from ₹1.36 to ₹1.23, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 3.31% fall over the same period. The stock faced intense selling pressure early in the week, hitting lower circuit limits on consecutive days before a brief rebound on 21 Jan 2026. Despite this recovery, the stock closed the week near its lows amid persistent volatility and cautious investor sentiment.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>a505dfa1d2237ae74815ba9352f9683f</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coforge Ltd Falls 5.55%: 7 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Market Moves</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/coforge-ltd-falls-555-7-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-market-moves-3804255</link><description>Coforge Ltd’s stock price declined by 5.55% over the week ending 23 January 2026, underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31%. The week was marked by a shift in technical momentum, a downgrade in investment rating, heavy options market activity signalling mixed investor sentiment, and a quarterly financial report showing strong revenue growth but margin pressures. These developments collectively shaped a cautious market outlook for the mid-cap IT software and consulting firm.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>f94a7bf8d9f37fbb74171c4ea329d9fb</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coromandel International Ltd Falls 3.26%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Move</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/coromandel-international-ltd-falls-326-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-move-3804254</link><description>Coromandel International Ltd closed the week down 3.26% at Rs.2,246.50, slightly outperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31%. The week was marked by a significant technical development with the formation of a Golden Cross, an upgrade in the company’s investment rating to Buy, and a shift in technical momentum to mildly bullish. Despite short-term volatility and some daily declines, these factors collectively shaped the stock’s performance and outlook during the week ending 23 January 2026.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>96d1c92753ddcaef69f4187c3ba05881</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PNB Gilts Ltd Falls 4.32%: 4 Key Factors Shaping This Week’s Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pnb-gilts-ltd-falls-432-4-key-factors-shaping-this-weeks-decline-3804253</link><description>PNB Gilts Ltd closed the week down 4.32% at Rs.77.22, underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. The stock experienced volatile trading amid mixed technical signals and a cautious upgrade in rating, reflecting ongoing challenges in profitability and market sentiment. Despite a strong intraday surge early in the week, the stock faced mounting selling pressure towards the close, highlighting a complex market environment for this NBFC.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>fa0f18a54445c829ff49c47787a3b738</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Everest Kanto Cylinder Ltd Gains 5.72%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/everest-kanto-cylinder-ltd-gains-572-4-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3804252</link><description>Everest Kanto Cylinder Ltd’s stock delivered a volatile week, closing with a 5.72% gain to Rs.114.65 despite a challenging market backdrop. This performance notably outpaced the Sensex, which declined 3.31% over the same period, reflecting a complex interplay of valuation shifts, technical rebounds, and exceptional trading volumes amid a prevailing bearish sentiment.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>272fae29df8ff0635966d1c919a76ab4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Murudeshwar Ceramics Declines 6.43%: Downgrade and Valuation Shifts Shape Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/murudeshwar-ceramics-declines-643-downgrade-and-valuation-shifts-shape-week-3804251</link><description>Murudeshwar Ceramics Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its share price declining by 6.43% from Rs.34.51 on 19 January to Rs.32.00 on 23 January 2026. This underperformance contrasted with the broader Sensex, which fell 3.31% over the same period. The week was marked by a significant downgrade to a Strong Sell rating and a nuanced shift in valuation metrics, both influencing investor sentiment and price action.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>0bb10bdb67dd6d3624d0f1079c01aa4d</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tribhovandas Bhimji Zaveri Ltd Gains 0.49%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tribhovandas-bhimji-zaveri-ltd-gains-049-4-key-factors-driving-the-week-3804250</link><description>Tribhovandas Bhimji Zaveri Ltd (TBZ) closed the week ending 23 January 2026 with a modest gain of 0.49%, closing at Rs.164.40, outperforming the Sensex which declined 3.31% over the same period. The stock showed resilience amid a volatile market, buoyed by a strong quarterly profit surge, a significant gap-up opening midweek, and mixed but improving technical momentum. Despite some late-week bearish signals, TBZ’s relative strength versus the benchmark index highlights cautious optimism among investors.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>885ffe7ef0063d7cee167ce09a702fe1</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Syngene International Ltd Falls 13.49%: 5 Key Factors Behind the Steep Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/syngene-international-ltd-falls-1349-5-key-factors-behind-the-steep-decline-3804249</link><description>Syngene International Ltd experienced a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its stock price plunging 13.49% to close at Rs.542.55, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 3.31% decline over the same period. The stock faced sustained selling pressure amid deteriorating financial results, bearish technical indicators, and heightened derivatives activity, culminating in a downgrade to a Strong Sell rating by MarketsMOJO.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>78ecb98bb9bbcb51562db7c16924a4a9</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dalmia Bharat Sugar &amp; Industries Ltd Drops 1.79% Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dalmia-bharat-sugar-industries-ltd-drops-179-amid-mixed-market-signals-3804238</link><description>Dalmia Bharat Sugar &amp; Industries Ltd experienced a turbulent week from 19 to 23 January 2026, closing with a 1.79% decline to Rs.273.60, despite the broader Sensex falling 3.31%. The stock hit multiple 52-week lows early in the week before staging a sharp rebound on 22 January, only to retreat again on the final trading day. This review analyses the key events and price movements that defined the stock’s performance amid challenging market conditions.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a937186d3599e4784db10c5aee06c571</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Palred Technologies Falls 16.71%: 5 Key Factors Behind the Steep Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/palred-technologies-falls-1671-5-key-factors-behind-the-steep-weekly-decline-3804237</link><description>Palred Technologies Ltd endured a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its share price plunging 16.71% to close at Rs.36.98, significantly underperforming the Sensex which declined 3.31% over the same period. The stock faced relentless selling pressure, hitting multiple lower circuit limits and a new 52-week low, before a late-week speculative surge pushed it briefly to an upper circuit. This review analyses the key events and market dynamics shaping Palred’s turbulent week.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5cd43b5a5e6e05da361f94a6334754be</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ITI Ltd Falls 7.35%: Downgrade and Bearish Momentum Define the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/iti-ltd-falls-735-downgrade-and-bearish-momentum-define-the-week-3804236</link><description>ITI Ltd’s stock price declined sharply by 7.35% over the week ending 23 January 2026, closing at Rs.279.90 from Rs.302.10 the previous Friday. This underperformance was more pronounced than the Sensex’s 3.31% fall during the same period, reflecting mounting concerns over the company’s deteriorating fundamentals, technical momentum shifts, and weak market sentiment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>33b3fae803f556e80ae634327874e8d6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nectar Lifescience Declines 3.87%: Circuit Limits and Operational Woes Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nectar-lifescience-declines-387-circuit-limits-and-operational-woes-shape-the-week-3804235</link><description>Nectar Lifescience Ltd experienced a turbulent week on the BSE, closing at Rs.14.66 on 23 Jan 2026, down 3.87% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.15.25. This decline slightly underperformed the Sensex, which fell 3.31% over the same period. The stock’s week was marked by sharp swings, including hitting both lower and upper circuit limits, reflecting intense volatility amid mixed investor sentiment and operational challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7d6dcd9024d50178ee7ce2123ff21942</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:17:23 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>