<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:25:16 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Home First Finance Gains 2.76%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Move</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/home-first-finance-gains-276-2-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-move-3803206</link><description>Home First Finance Company India Ltd recorded a modest weekly gain of 2.76%, closing at Rs.1,112.40 on 23 January 2026, outperforming the Sensex which declined 3.31% over the same period. The week was marked by a valuation recalibration and a strong Q3 profit announcement, which influenced the stock’s price trajectory amid volatile market conditions.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>f4a070c46241f7f8b35165fe8ed7dc4f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:25:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nureca Ltd Falls 9.26%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nureca-ltd-falls-926-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3803208</link><description>Nureca Ltd’s shares declined by 9.26% over the week ending 23 January 2026, closing at ₹282.15 from ₹310.95 the previous Friday. This underperformance, while sharper than the Sensex’s 3.31% fall, followed a volatile week marked by an initial surge to upper circuit limits, a subsequent sharp reversal hitting the lower circuit, and a steady decline into the week’s close. The stock’s technical upgrade to ‘Hold’ and positive quarterly results contrasted with the week’s price weakness, reflecting a complex interplay of momentum, profit-taking, and market sentiment.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>ab86b53ac05508ede306bf84e945c997</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:25:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Heranba Industries Ltd Falls 3.37% Amidst All-Time Low and Financial Struggles</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/heranba-industries-ltd-falls-337-amidst-all-time-low-and-financial-struggles-3803207</link><description>Heranba Industries Ltd’s stock declined by 3.37% over the week ending 23 January 2026, marginally underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31%. The week was marked by the stock hitting a fresh 52-week and all-time low on 21 January, reflecting ongoing financial and operational challenges. Despite a brief rebound midweek, the overall trend remained negative amid weak profitability and rising interest expenses.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>c5118a33ad79b360d0a09440b3a34f9d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:25:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Easy Trip Planners Ltd Drops 9.42%: 6 Key Factors Behind the Steep Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/easy-trip-planners-ltd-drops-942-6-key-factors-behind-the-steep-weekly-decline-3803205</link><description>Easy Trip Planners Ltd endured a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its share price declining by 9.42% to close at ₹6.35, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 3.31% fall over the same period. The stock hit multiple 52-week lows amid persistent financial setbacks, elevated promoter share pledging, and mixed technical signals that reflect ongoing bearish momentum despite some short-term stabilisation attempts.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>b17319c452eae3ad2bfe77054c3bc8b8</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:25:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anupam Rasayan India Ltd Falls 7.23%: Technical Shift and Hold Rating Mark Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/anupam-rasayan-india-ltd-falls-723-technical-shift-and-hold-rating-mark-week-3803204</link><description>Anupam Rasayan India Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its stock price declining by 7.23% from Rs.1,316.65 to Rs.1,221.40, underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. The week was marked by a significant downgrade in the company’s Mojo Grade from Buy to Hold, reflecting mixed technical signals and valuation concerns amid strong underlying financials. Despite a midweek bounce, the stock closed the week lower, signalling a cautious market stance.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>f7069c7bce0bebc32128c5bee1fb392e</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:25:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Laxmi Organic Industries Ltd Falls 4.96%: Five Key Factors Behind the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/laxmi-organic-industries-ltd-falls-496-five-key-factors-behind-the-weekly-decline-3803203</link><description>Laxmi Organic Industries Ltd’s shares declined by 4.96% over the week ending 23 January 2026, closing at Rs.138.95 from Rs.146.20. This underperformance was sharper than the Sensex’s 3.31% fall, reflecting persistent financial and operational challenges amid broader market volatility. The stock hit multiple 52-week and all-time lows during the week, underscoring sustained downward momentum despite occasional intraday recoveries.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>27620b8e1a7316a6f31ddd2301001f6f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:25:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kalyan Jewellers Falls 21.40%: 7 Key Factors Driving the Sharp Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kalyan-jewellers-falls-2140-7-key-factors-driving-the-sharp-decline-3803201</link><description>Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd experienced a steep decline of 21.40% over the week ending 23 January 2026, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31%. The stock’s persistent downtrend was marked by multiple 52-week lows, a downgrade to a Sell rating by MarketsMOJO, and heightened bearish technical signals amid heavy trading volumes and rising derivatives open interest.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>f8c8f920d1134d138681593957710246</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:25:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Suryoday Small Finance Bank Falls 6.33%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/suryoday-small-finance-bank-falls-633-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3803202</link><description>Suryoday Small Finance Bank Ltd’s shares declined by 6.33% over the week ending 23 January 2026, underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31%. The stock opened at Rs.140.35 on 19 January and closed at Rs.132.55 on 23 January, reflecting a challenging week marked by valuation concerns, technical momentum shifts, mixed quarterly results, and subdued market sentiment. Despite some intraday recoveries, the overall trend was negative amid heightened volatility and cautious investor outlook.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>5b5c932f5e40fbc1be4969d7550502fb</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:25:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Suvidhaa Infoserve Ltd Falls 6.19%: 5 Key Factors Behind the Steep Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/suvidhaa-infoserve-ltd-falls-619-5-key-factors-behind-the-steep-decline-3803209</link><description>Suvidhaa Infoserve Ltd’s stock declined by 6.19% over the week ending 23 January 2026, closing at Rs.3.18 compared to Rs.3.39 the previous Friday. This underperformance was sharper than the Sensex’s 3.31% fall, reflecting persistent financial and operational challenges amid a prolonged downtrend. The stock hit multiple 52-week and all-time lows during the week, underscoring ongoing investor caution despite occasional short-term rebounds.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>d750425270304e1faec35f71c16b3f44</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:25:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lodha Developers Falls 15.94%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Sharp Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lodha-developers-falls-1594-5-key-factors-driving-the-sharp-decline-3803200</link><description>Lodha Developers Ltd endured a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its share price plunging 15.94% to close at Rs.899.85, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 3.31% decline over the same period. The stock repeatedly hit fresh 52-week lows amid sustained selling pressure, sectoral headwinds, and cautious market sentiment, despite the company’s robust financial performance and strong institutional backing.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>01c91007581ef58b5081097116866adc</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:25:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sona BLW Precision Forgings Ltd Dips 0.49% Despite 5.75% Intraday Surge: 7 Key Developments This Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sona-blw-precision-forgings-ltd-dips-049-despite-575-intraday-surge-7-key-developments-this-week-3803198</link><description>Sona BLW Precision Forgings Ltd closed the week ending 23 January 2026 with a slight decline of 0.49%, settling at ₹457.85 from ₹460.10 the previous Friday. This modest drop contrasted sharply with the broader Sensex’s 3.31% fall over the same period, signalling relative resilience amid a volatile market backdrop. The week was marked by a series of technical shifts, rating upgrades, and a notable intraday surge, reflecting a complex interplay of investor sentiment and sectoral dynamics.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>28dbe9d681e008f6ed228d355b454eb2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:25:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>India Pesticides Ltd Falls 8.97%: 3 Key Technical and Financial Factors Driving the Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/india-pesticides-ltd-falls-897-3-key-technical-and-financial-factors-driving-the-decline-3803197</link><description>India Pesticides Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its stock price declining by 8.97% from ₹162.85 to ₹148.25, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 3.31% fall over the same period. Despite an upgrade to a Hold rating reflecting improved technical indicators and positive quarterly financial results, the stock faced persistent bearish momentum and mixed signals across multiple technical timeframes, culminating in a volatile trading week marked by sharp daily declines and intermittent recoveries.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>eef8022c847cacfbc9ff38d2ba1298e4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:25:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>G R Infraprojects Ltd Declines 0.58% Amidst Persistent Downtrend and Sector Challenges</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/g-r-infraprojects-ltd-declines-058-amidst-persistent-downtrend-and-sector-challenges-3803199</link><description>G R Infraprojects Ltd’s stock closed the week at Rs.920.05, down 0.58% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.925.40, marginally outperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. The week was marked by the stock hitting fresh 52-week and all-time lows amid persistent downward momentum, despite intermittent small rebounds. Key events including multiple new lows and notable put options activity influenced the price trajectory, reflecting ongoing challenges in the company’s financial performance and market sentiment.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>dca60755db5db88e40f090bea67db002</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:25:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eternal Ltd Falls 10.05%: 5 Key Factors Behind the Sharp Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eternal-ltd-falls-1005-5-key-factors-behind-the-sharp-weekly-decline-3803195</link><description>Eternal Ltd’s shares declined sharply over the week ending 23 January 2026, closing at Rs.258.65, down 10.05% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.287.55. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s 3.31% fall, signalling a notably weaker trend for the stock amid mixed market signals, technical pressures, and sector headwinds.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>5f9a81fd45b41dba80e62d19cd675dc2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:25:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alivus Life Sciences Ltd Gains 0.20%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/alivus-life-sciences-ltd-gains-020-4-key-factors-driving-the-week-3803196</link><description>Alivus Life Sciences Ltd closed the week marginally higher by 0.20% at Rs.882.10, outperforming the Sensex which declined 3.31% over the same period. The stock experienced a predominantly bearish trend early in the week amid technical downgrades and sector headwinds, before rebounding strongly on the final trading day following robust quarterly results. This mixed week was shaped by shifting technical momentum, improving financial performance, and cautious investor sentiment.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>a79ebeec0dcd623c0b57649f4bee954c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:25:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tatva Chintan Pharma Chem Ltd Falls 16.14%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tatva-chintan-pharma-chem-ltd-falls-1614-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3803192</link><description>Tatva Chintan Pharma Chem Ltd experienced a turbulent week ending 23 January 2026, with its share price declining sharply by 16.14%, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. Despite an outstanding quarterly financial performance reported midweek, the stock faced intense selling pressure and volatility, culminating in steep losses on the final two trading days. This review analyses the key events and market dynamics that shaped the stock’s challenging week.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>b0a77c439412ddbd088d63cec4fb0a35</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:25:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Network People Services Technologies Ltd Falls 7.32%: Technical Shifts Amid Financial Struggles</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/network-people-services-technologies-ltd-falls-732-technical-shifts-amid-financial-struggles-3803194</link><description>Network People Services Technologies Ltd experienced a challenging week, closing at Rs.1,295.70 on 23 January 2026, down 7.32% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.1,398.05. This decline notably outpaced the Sensex’s 3.31% fall over the same period, reflecting a combination of technical shifts, financial headwinds, and market volatility that shaped the stock’s performance throughout the week.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>6bc9c0b8d2a56352239f0b52e52df78c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:25:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meghmani Organics Ltd Falls 7.74%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/meghmani-organics-ltd-falls-774-5-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3803191</link><description>Meghmani Organics Ltd experienced a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its share price declining by 7.74% to close at Rs.55.80, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. The stock hit multiple 52-week and all-time lows amid persistent bearish momentum, despite some positive financial results reported recently. This review analyses the key events and market dynamics that shaped the stock’s performance during the week.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>f5f3a2229e071369587eed54fcdca302</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:25:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paras Defence Falls 5.84% Amid Bearish Momentum and Margin Pressure: Key Weekly Insights</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/paras-defence-falls-584-amid-bearish-momentum-and-margin-pressure-key-weekly-insights-3803193</link><description>Paras Defence and Space Technologies Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its share price declining 5.84% from ₹662.35 to ₹623.70, underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. The stock faced bearish technical momentum and margin pressures amid volatile market conditions, reflecting a cautious investor sentiment despite the company’s sustained growth momentum in Q3 FY26.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>8f118d96ba950914f647db9a6531febd</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:25:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aditya Birla Sun Life AMC Declines 6.24%: Mixed Signals Amid Financial and Technical Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aditya-birla-sun-life-amc-declines-624-mixed-signals-amid-financial-and-technical-shifts-3803190</link><description>Aditya Birla Sun Life AMC Ltd experienced a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its stock price declining by 6.24% to close at Rs.780.00, underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. Despite a strong start and an upgrade in rating early in the week, the stock faced mounting pressure amid mixed technical signals and a flat quarterly financial trend, culminating in a cautious market sentiment by week’s end.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>5e4d4ef991356557cf4372021382b258</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:25:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:25:16 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>