<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:26:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>LTI Mindtree Ltd Hits Intraday High with Strong 3.13% Surge on 1 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lti-mindtree-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-strong-313-surge-on-1-feb-2026-3814766</link><description>LTI Mindtree Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 1 Feb 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 6,158, marking a 3.15% increase from the previous close. This upward movement outpaced its sector and broader market indices, reflecting a notable rebound after two days of declines.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>428e8602d3eb2efb93a6152ef9d61e5b</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:26:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Advanced Enzyme Technologies Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/advanced-enzyme-technologies-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-3814768</link><description>Advanced Enzyme Technologies Ltd experienced a notable decline today, touching an intraday low of Rs 277, reflecting sustained price pressure amid broader market weakness and sector underperformance.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>131f209a76b25c549b1a01ee3ffc033a</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:26:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Media Matrix Worldwide Ltd Hits Intraday High with 8.71% Surge on 1 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/media-matrix-worldwide-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-871-surge-on-1-feb-2026-3814767</link><description>Media Matrix Worldwide Ltd demonstrated robust intraday strength on 1 Feb 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 9.88, marking a significant 16.24% rise from its previous close. The stock outperformed its sector and the broader market, reflecting notable trading momentum amid a volatile session.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>1bc66b5846752bdc96b9ab40e291e80b</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:26:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Softtech Engineers Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/softtech-engineers-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3814762</link><description>Softtech Engineers Ltd has recently touched a 52-week low, closing just 1.34% above its lowest price of Rs 276.25. This marks a significant downturn for the company within the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, reflecting ongoing challenges in its financial and market performance.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>0cf5e20d065a093ad54e0064ddd3eb83</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:26:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I G Petrochemicals Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.348.05 Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/i-g-petrochemicals-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs34805-amidst-continued-underperformance-3814763</link><description>I G Petrochemicals Ltd’s stock declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.348.05 on 1 Feb 2026, marking a significant downturn amid ongoing challenges reflected in its financial performance and market positioning. The stock has underperformed its sector and benchmark indices, continuing a downward trend that has persisted over recent sessions.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>1eff7150fb8e7b328d813b948e8e7e67</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:26:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Comfort Intech Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.5.66</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/comfort-intech-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs566-3814764</link><description>Comfort Intech Ltd, a player in the beverages sector, has touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.5.66 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid subdued financial performance and valuation concerns.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>31b7ee33cbc1f487b2bdaeab5493ecf0</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:26:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ajmera Realty &amp; Infra India Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.134.8</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ajmera-realty-infra-india-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs1348-3814765</link><description>Ajmera Realty &amp; Infra India Ltd’s shares declined sharply to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.134.8 on 1 Feb 2026, reflecting ongoing headwinds in the realty sector and company-specific performance pressures. The stock underperformed its sector and broader market indices, marking a significant milestone in its recent price trajectory.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>aba810710641196bb683fa47671e69d5</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:26:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Bank Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 1 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indian-bank-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-1-feb-2026-3814761</link><description>Indian Bank experienced a notable intraday decline on 1 Feb 2026, touching a low of Rs 840, down 7.83% from its previous close. The stock underperformed both its sector and the broader market, reflecting immediate selling pressure amid a sharply reversing Sensex and weakening sentiment in public sector banks.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>c6c1da4db24e17ec13718a830b8a3bc8</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:26:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Financial Services Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mahindra-mahindra-financial-services-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-3814760</link><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Financial Services Ltd (stock code 605836) experienced a notable intraday decline on 1 Feb 2026, touching a low of Rs 356.35, down 5.14% from the previous close. The stock underperformed both its sector and the broader market, reflecting immediate selling pressure amid a sharply reversing Sensex.
Time: 38 minutes ago</description><guid>3367e421dfc069d0b664c0886bdd15d7</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:26:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IIFL Finance Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amidst Price Pressure on 1 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/iifl-finance-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amidst-price-pressure-on-1-feb-2026-3814756</link><description>IIFL Finance Ltd experienced a notable decline on 1 Feb 2026, touching an intraday low of Rs 485.65, reflecting a sharp price correction amid broader market weakness and sectoral pressures. The stock underperformed both its sector and the benchmark Sensex, continuing a recent trend of subdued performance.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>e4ec55783634b9913647e82aff022938</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:26:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ajmera Realty &amp; Infra India Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ajmera-realty-infra-india-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-3814757</link><description>Ajmera Realty &amp; Infra India Ltd experienced significant intraday weakness on 1 Feb 2026, with its share price plunging to a fresh 52-week low of Rs 134.8, reflecting intense selling pressure and underperformance relative to the broader market and sector peers.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>8af059bf9340a0f248ac878a90d689c6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:26:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uniphos Enterprises Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Weak Fundamentals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/uniphos-enterprises-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-weak-fundamentals-3814759</link><description>Shares of Uniphos Enterprises Ltd have declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing near Rs 112.65, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory. This new low reflects persistent challenges faced by the company, as it continues to underperform relative to its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>77c3f80a1fa95feec354cfa6fc50545c</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:26:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Relaxo Footwears Ltd Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/relaxo-footwears-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3814758</link><description>Relaxo Footwears Ltd commenced trading today with a pronounced gap down, opening at Rs 372.05, reflecting a 5.37% decline from its previous close. This weak start underscores prevailing market apprehensions surrounding the stock, which has underperformed both its sector and the broader Sensex index in recent sessions.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>e8b0cf93b0bb5a139fe507af81f6040a</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:26:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cohance Lifesciences Ltd Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cohance-lifesciences-ltd-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3814750</link><description>Cohance Lifesciences Ltd, a key player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, recorded a new 52-week low of Rs.367.35 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid broader market volatility and sector underperformance.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>8dd6551d04c9f8a0a3d139e02b5af9d8</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:26:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vishal Bearings Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vishal-bearings-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3814752</link><description>Vishal Bearings Ltd’s shares declined sharply to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.60.02 on 1 Feb 2026, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory. The stock underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting persistent pressures on its valuation and financial metrics.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>7d58ea820ce141660d5bc069cf6cbe31</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:26:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Srestha Finvest Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Weak Financial Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/srestha-finvest-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-weak-financial-performance-3814754</link><description>Srestha Finvest Ltd, a Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC), has touched a new 52-week and all-time low of Rs.0.25 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid broader sectoral and market pressures.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>5f9e1622e5efcf556ca8f72b16983ace</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:26:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MKVentures Capital Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mkventures-capital-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3814753</link><description>MKVentures Capital Ltd, a Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC), recorded a fresh 52-week low of Rs.944.05 today, marking a significant decline in its share price amid broader market volatility and sectoral pressures.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>c23a99eb3ec4a913e80d6c3adb8eba08</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:26:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gujarat Hotels Ltd. Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gujarat-hotels-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3814751</link><description>Gujarat Hotels Ltd. has declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.191.7, marking a significant downturn in the stock’s performance amid broader market volatility and sectoral pressures. The stock’s recent slide reflects ongoing challenges in maintaining momentum within the Hotels &amp; Resorts sector.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>488b6e6a059eb050a7a26178bd5f3e3e</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:26:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ITL Industries Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.243.75</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/itl-industries-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs24375-3814749</link><description>ITL Industries Ltd touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.243.75 today, marking a significant decline in its share price amid ongoing subdued performance and market volatility. The stock’s fall to this level reflects persistent challenges in sustaining growth and investor confidence within the industrial manufacturing sector.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>1dcb9dd643dfe0517db067abd9ca837a</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:26:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jio Financial Services Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jio-financial-services-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-3814746</link><description>Jio Financial Services Ltd experienced significant intraday weakness on 1 Feb 2026, with its share price touching a low of Rs 238.7, marking a 6.19% decline from previous levels. The stock underperformed both its sector and the broader market, reflecting immediate selling pressure and subdued market sentiment.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>8db59ef7972f6d77adce55624e062fbe</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:26:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:26:13 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>