<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:37:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Show Mixed Trends with Mid Caps Leading Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-with-mid-caps-leading-growth-3821132</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has revealed a nuanced picture across Indian equities, with 1,224 companies reporting results. While aggregate profit growth remains robust in pockets, the proportion of companies delivering positive results has shown only modest improvement compared to previous quarters. Market cap segments continue to diverge, with mid-cap firms outperforming their large-cap counterparts in terms of earnings beats.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>1ca8500d54f319aa0b118b30fe81d00d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:37:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are TruAlt Bioenergy Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-trualt-bioenergy-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3821089</link><description>TruAlt Bioenergy Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show impressive revenue growth of 520.96% quarter-on-quarter and 71.82% year-on-year, but profitability has declined, with net profit down 7.79% year-on-year and operating margins under pressure. Overall, while revenue performance is strong, concerns about margin compression and financial metrics suggest caution moving forward.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>17133b11b1351d8b82c4b0422335032a</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:37:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Indo Farm Equipment Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-indo-farm-equipment-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3821088</link><description>Indo Farm Equipment Ltd's latest results show a 39.7% increase in net profit and a 10.09% rise in revenue, indicating growth. However, declining operating margins and low return on equity, coupled with a significant drop in stock price and institutional investor confidence, suggest underlying operational challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e5dc1cab027c5a3e99557416e358309f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:37:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are IRM Energy Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-irm-energy-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3821087</link><description>IRM Energy Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show a net profit of ₹12.66 crores, reflecting a 9.05% sequential decline but a 5.41% year-on-year growth. While net sales grew 12.06% year-on-year, the company faces challenges in maintaining profitability and operational efficiency, as indicated by declining margins and returns on equity and capital employed.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2af94d7104d5d89165dcd1b477487735</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:37:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Dam Capital Advisors Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-dam-capital-advisors-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3821086</link><description>Dam Capital Advisors Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, showing a 34.67% decline in net sales and a 61.53% drop in net profit compared to the previous quarter, indicating significant operational challenges in a volatile market. Despite a strong return on equity, the results reflect the risks and fluctuations typical in the investment banking sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c5f39dc5c5bdc6eee7b54b970af94c22</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:37:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Pelatro Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-pelatro-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3821085</link><description>Pelatro Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show strong revenue growth of 90.76% year-on-year, but a concerning net profit decline of 18.49%, indicating operational challenges and margin sustainability issues. Investors should watch for improvements in profitability and margin stability in future quarters.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a1103fe81f452d21026380be9157319f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:37:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Rashi Peripherals Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-rashi-peripherals-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3821084</link><description>Rashi Peripherals Ltd's Q3 FY26 results show strong year-on-year growth, with net profit up 131% to ₹73.55 crores and revenue increasing 42.60% to ₹4,030.41 crores, despite a slight sequential decline in revenue and modest operating margins. Overall, the results indicate robust growth but highlight ongoing challenges in the competitive IT hardware distribution sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>afaa72410b07088656790f666f5fc5ba</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:37:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Apeejay Surrendra Park Hotels Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-apeejay-surrendra-park-hotels-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3821083</link><description>Apeejay Surrendra Park Hotels Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 16.83% year-on-year, but a significant net profit decline of 39.44% due to rising costs and high tax rates, indicating operational challenges despite positive sales trends. Investors should monitor future margin recovery and operational efficiency.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7378e9034ad1f19178fe575cf813a9e7</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:37:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Mankind Pharma Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-mankind-pharma-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3821082</link><description>Mankind Pharma Ltd's latest results show an 11.52% year-on-year increase in net sales to ₹3,567.20 crores, but a concerning 20.09% sequential drop in net profit to ₹408.75 crores, alongside declining margins, indicating operational challenges despite some growth. The company faces pressures from rising costs and must focus on improving profitability and efficiency.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>533e805b629eadde6c8bc21c1e71e10e</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:37:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Avalon Technologies Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-avalon-technologies-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3821081</link><description>Avalon Technologies Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results are positive, showing an 18.30% quarter-on-quarter revenue growth and a 75.79% increase in net profit, although ongoing margin volatility poses challenges for sustained profitability. Investors should monitor the company's ability to stabilize margins and maintain growth moving forward.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8618dceedff3d866fe043e1c45216f87</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:37:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Global Health Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-global-health-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3821080</link><description>Global Health Ltd's latest results show mixed performance: while net profit slightly declined by 0.36% from the previous quarter, revenue grew by 6.63%, marking the seventh consecutive quarter of growth. However, operating margins contracted due to rising costs, and the company's high valuation has raised some investor concerns.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2c3da8e70f732ef38af0f1ce6ead52a7</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:37:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are SignatureGlobal India Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-signatureglobal-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3821079</link><description>SignatureGlobal India Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results are poor, showing a net loss of ₹46.86 crores and a 54.83% decline in revenue year-on-year, indicating significant operational challenges and inefficiencies. The company's performance lags behind peers in the real estate sector, raising concerns about its market navigation and execution capabilities.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>087fe80ad5080d9eda2a68c0eb344df2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:37:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Global Surfaces Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-global-surfaces-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3821078</link><description>Global Surfaces Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results are concerning, showing a net loss of ₹4.67 crores and a 27.41% decline in net sales, alongside negative operating margins and significant reliance on non-operating income. The company's financial health is under pressure, indicating serious operational challenges that need to be addressed.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>add71edaf964910d949640b9c2d42703</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:37:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are NMDC Steel Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-nmdc-steel-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3821077</link><description>NMDC Steel Ltd's latest results for Q3 FY26 show strong revenue growth of 41.90% year-on-year, but the company reported a net loss of ₹243.97 crores due to operational challenges and increased costs, indicating ongoing profitability issues despite market share gains.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5fee4a9a8e0ae71ece039c432f90a5d7</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:37:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Eureka Forbes Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-eureka-forbes-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3821076</link><description>Eureka Forbes Ltd's latest results are concerning, showing a 71.41% decline in net profit year-on-year and compressed margins, despite a 7.97% revenue growth. The significant drop in profitability and low return on equity indicate ongoing operational challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>059a989232900f21d415ac872ac0485c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:37:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Aeroflex Neu Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-aeroflex-neu-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3821075</link><description>Aeroflex Neu Ltd's latest results show a significant net profit increase of 292.31% year-on-year, but this is largely due to non-operating income, with modest revenue growth and declining operating margins indicating underlying operational challenges. Overall, the company's financial health appears weak, with low return metrics and stock underperformance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4d52bb4cbcb191dad081aa15e250ac67</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:37:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Devyani International Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-devyani-international-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3821074</link><description>Devyani International Ltd's latest results show a net loss of ₹10.39 crores, widening from the previous year, despite a revenue growth of 11.32% to ₹1,440.90 crores. The company faces challenges with declining operating margins and high financial leverage, raising concerns about its profitability and operational efficiency.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f10944e7a9c1fb3dd319c3309e8bbbe0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:37:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Restaurant Brands Asia Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-restaurant-brands-asia-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3821073</link><description>Restaurant Brands Asia Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show strong revenue growth and improved operational efficiency, but the company still reported a net loss of ₹43.54 crores, indicating ongoing challenges in achieving profitability. While there are positive signs, the sustainability of its business model remains uncertain.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>45bf5de6a3788f0a4fc0300eeaeffe3b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:37:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-tamilnad-mercantile-bank-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3821072</link><description>Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd's latest results are positive, with a net profit of ₹341.50 crores, a 13.74% year-on-year increase, and improved asset quality, reflected in a gross NPA ratio of 0.91%. The bank shows strong operational performance and growth potential, making it an encouraging option for investors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>87f2895f5b360289a75302bfb0365241</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:37:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Nazara Technologies Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-nazara-technologies-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3821071</link><description>Nazara Technologies Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 65.07% year-on-year, but the company reported a net loss of ₹29.35 crores, raising concerns about profitability and operational efficiency despite the revenue increase. Investors should monitor the company's ability to achieve sustainable profits moving forward.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5dc2660192ecf18205cca4427d62a6b4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:37:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:37:39 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>