<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Pace E-Commerce Ventures Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-pace-e-commerce-ventures-ltd-fallingrising-3783809</link><description>On 06-Jan, Pace E-Commerce Ventures Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.13% to close at ₹18.80. This drop comes after a brief two-day rally and reflects broader challenges faced by the stock over recent periods.
Time: 25 seconds ago</description><guid>2936b3d94b4f4f4d01ba85967d3e1deb</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Home First Finance Company India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-home-first-finance-company-india-ltd-fallingrising-3783808</link><description>On 06-Jan, Home First Finance Company India Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.02% to close at ₹1,071.50. This drop reflects a short-term underperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market, despite the company’s robust long-term financial performance and positive quarterly results.
Time: 32 seconds ago</description><guid>1858a8c47cb94c2e17fe41c65f1629d9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Euro Panel Products Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-euro-panel-products-ltd-fallingrising-3783807</link><description>On 06-Jan, Euro Panel Products Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 3.81% to close at ₹169.30. This downturn reflects a broader pattern of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and sector peers, compounded by subdued investor participation and technical weaknesses.
Time: 32 seconds ago</description><guid>7aa0d07a3b2de397706aadbc7fdd38a3</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Debock Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-debock-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3783806</link><description>On 06-Jan, Debock Industries Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, closing at ₹1.66, down 2.92% from the previous session. This drop reflects ongoing challenges faced by the company, including sustained operating losses and significant underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 33 seconds ago</description><guid>c27f3a12c793a2f3c47a41cb3b60a443</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Hardwyn India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-hardwyn-india-ltd-fallingrising-3783805</link><description>On 06-Jan, Hardwyn India Ltd witnessed a significant price rise of 10.65%, closing at ₹19.22, driven by robust short-term performance and a fresh 52-week high, outpacing both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 46 seconds ago</description><guid>f37c5e2be49a01f9c3691a42b573f5a8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-orissa-bengal-carrier-ltd-fallingrising-3783804</link><description>On 06-Jan, Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 9.15% to close at ₹48.15. This sharp drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s underperformance relative to broader market benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 59 seconds ago</description><guid>d6ac7f3c65f855127ae625118fcc42c4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Gautam Gems Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gautam-gems-ltd-fallingrising-3783803</link><description>As of 06-Jan, Gautam Gems Ltd’s stock price has continued its downward trajectory, reflecting persistent fundamental weaknesses and consistent underperformance against market benchmarks.
Time: 1 minute ago</description><guid>6c2b4d2803144a3f1639aae281cdae2b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Omfurn India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-omfurn-india-ltd-fallingrising-3783802</link><description>On 06-Jan, Omfurn India Ltd witnessed a significant drop in its share price, closing at ₹77.00, down ₹6.50 or 7.78% from the previous close. This decline marks a fresh 52-week low for the stock and reflects a broader trend of underperformance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 1 minute ago</description><guid>2a32c36ac4d65f8562df9ee19e52a266</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sikko Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sikko-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3783801</link><description>On 06-Jan, Sikko Industries Ltd witnessed a modest decline in its share price, falling by 1.4% to close at ₹4.92. This movement comes despite the company’s impressive long-term performance and robust financial metrics, indicating short-term market pressures rather than fundamental weaknesses.
Time: 1 minute ago</description><guid>dbe7b6c8fab299a4a90e38718a78bef2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Manomay Tex India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-manomay-tex-india-ltd-fallingrising-3783800</link><description>On 06-Jan, Manomay Tex India Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 4.19% to close at ₹189.90. This drop reflects a continuation of recent downward momentum, with the stock underperforming both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 minute ago</description><guid>b21b28b317e15dd47a586d211df30288</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Beta Drugs Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-beta-drugs-ltd-fallingrising-3783799</link><description>On 06-Jan, Beta Drugs Ltd witnessed a notable uptick in its share price, rising by 1.2% to close at ₹1,664.20. This movement reflects a continuation of recent positive momentum despite some contrasting longer-term performance trends.
Time: 1 minute ago</description><guid>b6df162a3ce192712fcbda60a7f24b8a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Prime Fresh Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-prime-fresh-ltd-fallingrising-3783798</link><description>On 06-Jan, Prime Fresh Ltd's stock price rose sharply by 5.0% to close at ₹269.05, reflecting sustained investor confidence driven by impressive recent returns and solid fundamental indicators.
Time: 1 minute ago</description><guid>cffc922a8e47ec3f26ca3e9083391e92</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shankara Building Products Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shankara-building-products-ltd-fallingrising-3783797</link><description>On 06-Jan, Shankara Building Products Ltd witnessed a sharp rise in its share price, climbing 20.0% to close at Rs 127.80. This significant uptick comes despite the company’s recent challenges and mixed financial performance, reflecting a complex interplay of valuation appeal, institutional interest, and short-term market dynamics.
Time: 1 minute ago</description><guid>3a8e167c329361771ee24c2f087badb5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Indian Energy Exchange Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-indian-energy-exchange-ltd-fallingrising-3783796</link><description>On 06-Jan, Indian Energy Exchange Ltd witnessed a significant price rise of 10.28%, closing at ₹148.10, driven by robust quarterly performance and strong institutional backing despite some concerns over long-term growth and valuation.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>c2f82e3ade8b09bf3f8e88a7f5ac9139</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shanti Overseas (India) Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shanti-overseas-india-ltd-fallingrising-3783795</link><description>As of 06-Jan, Shanti Overseas (India) Ltd’s stock price has continued its downward trajectory, reflecting persistent operational challenges and diminishing investor confidence.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>200944911ede63486b569da447e9d066</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Constronics Infra Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-constronics-infra-ltd-fallingrising-3783794</link><description>On 06-Jan, Constronics Infra Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, falling by 8.51% to close at ₹55.80. This significant drop reflects a continuation of the stock's underperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>5a1f7544f7b0fb1f619061cc88fda617</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Radhagobind Commercial Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-radhagobind-commercial-ltd-fallingrising-3783793</link><description>As of 06-Jan, Radhagobind Commercial Ltd’s stock price has fallen sharply, reflecting persistent fundamental weaknesses and sustained underperformance relative to key market benchmarks.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>75653382d447f433cd9e59c36af1ff34</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ascom Leasing &amp; Investments Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ascom-leasing-investments-ltd-fallingrising-3783792</link><description>On 06-Jan, Ascom Leasing &amp; Investments Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, closing at ₹134.50, up ₹4.50 or 3.46%, reaching a fresh 52-week high of ₹134.8. This upward momentum reflects robust investor interest and significant outperformance relative to key benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>911bcfb700b0751871b3bfef0f2a62a9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Amit Securities Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-amit-securities-ltd-fallingrising-3783791</link><description>On 06-Jan, Amit Securities Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, falling by 9.94% to close at ₹32.98. This significant drop reflects a combination of weak long-term fundamentals, poor recent performance relative to benchmarks, and a reversal after a brief rally.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>7075d7f98ac8192b6a25469b4f72d614</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Deep Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-deep-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3783790</link><description>On 06-Jan, Deep Industries Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.85% to close at ₹421.00. This drop continues a four-day losing streak, reflecting investor caution despite the company’s robust operational performance and improving fundamentals.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>e65f32929a2c13399e702c9d78c4733c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>