<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:56:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/awfis-space-solutions-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amidst-prolonged-downtrend-3845886</link><description>Shares of AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd have declined to an all-time low, reflecting a sustained period of underperformance relative to the broader market and sector peers. The stock’s recent fall underscores significant pressures faced by the company within the diversified commercial services sector, as evidenced by its deteriorating price trends and financial metrics.
Time: 3 minutes ago</description><guid>a5f3a0f94f11e22ba2f56c0328a3c72d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:56:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NIBE Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.18% Surge on 18 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nibe-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-718-surge-on-18-feb-2026-3845884</link><description>NIBE Ltd, a key player in the Aerospace &amp; Defense sector, recorded a robust intraday performance on 18 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 1,129.4, marking a 7.32% increase. This strong uptick outpaced the broader market and sector indices, reflecting notable trading momentum despite a subdued Sensex session.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>a885628ea17bf83c87285ebc0eb0b99c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:56:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Steel Ltd Hits Intraday High with 3.0% Surge on 18 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-steel-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-30-surge-on-18-feb-2026-3845885</link><description>Tata Steel Ltd demonstrated a strong intraday performance on 18 Feb 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 209.5, marking a 3.15% increase from its previous close. This notable rise outpaced the broader Sensex, which ended marginally lower, underscoring Tata Steel’s resilience amid mixed market conditions.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>08d02fc8130b2d3b011b3c1ba078b092</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:56:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ecos (India) Mobility &amp; Hospitality Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.163.05</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ecos-india-mobility-hospitality-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs16305-3845883</link><description>Ecos (India) Mobility &amp; Hospitality Ltd’s stock declined sharply to a new 52-week low of Rs.163.05 on 18 Feb 2026, marking a significant downturn amid a six-day losing streak that has seen the share price fall by 22.59%. This decline comes despite a broadly stable market environment, with the Sensex trading marginally lower and close to its own 52-week high.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>f92002e21bd26903b38243ef0cb944fc</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:56:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uma Exports Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.30 Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/uma-exports-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs30-amid-continued-downtrend-3845877</link><description>Uma Exports Ltd, a player in the Trading &amp; Distributors sector, has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.30, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has underperformed both its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing pressures on its financial and market performance.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>c8ec2a40d8c0339a36e3f6aaf86aa88e</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:56:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AGS Transact Technologies Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ags-transact-technologies-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-weakness-3845874</link><description>AGS Transact Technologies Ltd has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.3.6 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing concerns about the company’s financial health and recent performance metrics.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>6be5dafb657a4bfe2824d0471366d095</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:56:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Allcargo Logistics Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.8.85 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/allcargo-logistics-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs885-amidst-continued-downtrend-3845878</link><description>Allcargo Logistics Ltd’s shares declined to a fresh 52-week and all-time low of Rs.8.85 on 18 Feb 2026, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory. This new low reflects persistent headwinds faced by the company amid a challenging market environment and subdued financial performance.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>9a6caf8d2bc8648b75d8cfe066b06656</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:56:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Danlaw Technologies India Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.620.5</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/danlaw-technologies-india-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs6205-3845882</link><description>Danlaw Technologies India Ltd’s stock touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.620.5 today, marking a significant decline amid a challenging market environment and company-specific performance factors. This new low reflects a continued downward trend over the past year, with the stock underperforming both its sector and broader market indices.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>601417213082de3d69f849f29e6271a0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:56:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coral India Finance &amp; Housing Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.33.86</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/coral-india-finance-housing-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs3386-3845875</link><description>Shares of Coral India Finance &amp; Housing Ltd have declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.33.86, marking a significant drop amid broader market fluctuations and company-specific performance concerns. The stock has underperformed its sector and key benchmarks, reflecting ongoing pressures on its financial metrics and valuation.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>506d9d2e34756bd6e3892d6efeda190b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:56:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Magnus Steel &amp; Infra Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at ₹53.94</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/magnus-steel-infra-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-5394-3845876</link><description>Magnus Steel &amp; Infra Ltd has surged to a fresh 52-week and all-time high of Rs.53.94, marking a significant milestone in its market performance. This achievement reflects sustained momentum, with the stock demonstrating robust gains over the past fortnight and outperforming its sector peers.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>f045d14cb9d39f40359506bc8c762c30</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:56:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Daikaffil Chemicals India Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/daikaffil-chemicals-india-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-weakness-3845880</link><description>Daikaffil Chemicals India Ltd’s stock declined sharply to a fresh 52-week low of Rs 46.26 on 18 Feb 2026, marking a significant drop amid ongoing pressures in the specialty chemicals sector. The stock underperformed its sector peers and broader market indices, reflecting persistent challenges in its financial and operational metrics.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>6a64636a41d7e3ce62e98d90d058fa9b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:56:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Covidh Technologies Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.33.06</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/covidh-technologies-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs3306-3845879</link><description>Covidh Technologies Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.33.06 today, marking a continuation of its strong upward momentum with a 1.97% gain on the day and a remarkable 51.03% return over the past 21 trading sessions.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>aca1dfbdd4ed15ff6f98f57bb874148b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:56:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dhunseri Ventures Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.243</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dhunseri-ventures-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs243-3845881</link><description>Dhunseri Ventures Ltd’s shares touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.243 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has now recorded losses for six consecutive sessions, accumulating a fall of 8.84% over this period, reflecting ongoing pressures within the company’s financial performance and market positioning.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>ff9361dce1a5a47d6d46fc85d3fd2b07</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:56:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AGS Transact Technologies Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amid Steep Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ags-transact-technologies-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amid-steep-decline-3845873</link><description>AGS Transact Technologies Ltd has plunged to a new all-time low of Rs.3.65, marking a significant downturn in its market performance. The stock’s persistent decline over recent months reflects mounting pressures within the financial technology sector and highlights the company’s ongoing difficulties in maintaining profitability and investor confidence.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>f35274da4000c3c186feec025c8bf639</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:56:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ecos (India) Mobility &amp; Hospitality Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ecos-india-mobility-hospitality-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amidst-prolonged-downtrend-3845867</link><description>Ecos (India) Mobility &amp; Hospitality Ltd has reached a new all-time low of Rs.165.25, marking a significant downturn as the stock continues its downward trajectory with a six-day losing streak and a cumulative decline exceeding 21% in that period.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>b7f6079f2f2c4a613bcbf9ddd37374b3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:56:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cummins India Ltd Hits Intraday High with Strong 3.01% Surge on 18 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cummins-india-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-strong-301-surge-on-18-feb-2026-3845868</link><description>Cummins India Ltd. surged to an intraday high of Rs 4750 on 18 Feb 2026, marking a robust 3.32% increase during the trading session. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, continuing its upward trajectory with a third consecutive day of gains.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>41acdc15695f3ad5c79fffb98f34bbf3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:56:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>E2E Networks Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit on Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/e2e-networks-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-on-robust-buying-pressure-3845869</link><description>E2E Networks Ltd, a small-cap player in the IT - Hardware sector, witnessed a remarkable surge on 18 Feb 2026, hitting its upper circuit limit with a 20.0% gain. The stock closed at ₹3,068.20, marking a maximum daily price band increase of ₹511.30. This sharp rally was driven by robust buying interest, significant turnover, and a regulatory freeze on further trading, reflecting intense demand that remained unfilled throughout the session.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>5f6787ab318af29c72c71e217fedfb0f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:56:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Waaree Energies Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/waaree-energies-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-price-action-3845870</link><description>Waaree Energies Ltd (WAAREEENER) has witnessed a significant 18.7% rise in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this surge, the stock underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting a complex interplay between bullish bets and profit-taking pressures.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>3d35440b7a1a67b02be7db28868f4322</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:56:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ICICI Lombard Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Positive Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/icici-lombard-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-positive-market-momentum-3845864</link><description>ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Ltd has witnessed a notable surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market participation and potential directional bets. The stock’s recent performance, coupled with rising volumes and improved investor sentiment, suggests a shift in market positioning that merits close attention from traders and investors alike.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>a790d3510a12ae612efc07ad1cf09105</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:56:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BLB Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit on Strong Buying Momentum Amid Elevated Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/blb-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-on-strong-buying-momentum-amid-elevated-volatility-3845866</link><description>BLB Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, witnessed a remarkable surge on 18 Feb 2026, hitting its upper circuit limit with an 18.44% gain. The stock’s strong buying momentum, coupled with heightened investor participation and significant unfilled demand, propelled it to close near its daily price band ceiling, signalling robust market interest despite a cautious sector backdrop.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>a18473004c673cec3d933eb876d579ee</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:56:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:56:17 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>