<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 12:30:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>GRP Stock Evaluation Revised Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/grp-stock-upgraded-from-strong-sell-to-sell-by-marketsmojo-on-27-may-2025-3764758</link><description>GRP, a small-cap player in the Industrial Products sector, has undergone a revision in its market evaluation, reflecting nuanced shifts across key financial and technical parameters. This update highlights the company's current position amid challenging market conditions and evolving investor sentiment.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>18f5ee2c0d5e81527fdf18722e128603</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 12:30:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fredun Pharma Sees Revised Market Evaluation Amid Strong Financial Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/fredun-pharma-upgraded-to-buy-by-marketsmojo-on-strong-financial-and-valuation-metrics-3764756</link><description>Fredun Pharma, a microcap player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, has experienced a revision in its market evaluation reflecting recent developments in its financial and technical outlook. This shift highlights evolving investor perceptions amid robust growth indicators and valuation metrics.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>91f9a3046f39aba6a00a3c187f806709</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 12:30:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kellton Tech Sees Revision in Market Evaluation Amid Mixed Financial Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/kellton-tech-downgraded-to-sell-by-marketsmojo-amid-weak-performance-and-bearish-technicals-3764757</link><description>Kellton Tech, a microcap player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has experienced a revision in its market evaluation reflecting a nuanced shift in its financial and technical outlook. This adjustment follows a detailed reassessment of the company’s quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators, highlighting both strengths and challenges in its recent performance.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>21487d9f829509281035294b4f539801</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 12:30:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Agarwal Indl. Sees Revision in Market Assessment Amidst Challenging Financial Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/agarwal-indl-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-weak-financials-and-bearish-technicals-3764753</link><description>Agarwal Indl., a small-cap player in the petrochemicals sector, has experienced a revision in its market evaluation reflecting recent financial and technical developments. The company’s assessment metrics have shifted following a series of operational challenges and market performance indicators that have influenced investor sentiment.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>d4ea29364ab2100e34490590ac9d58e4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 12:30:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Confidence Petro’s Evaluation Revised Amidst Challenging Market Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/confidence-petro-downgraded-to-sell-as-mojo-score-declines-to-46-3764755</link><description>Confidence Petro has experienced a revision in its market evaluation, reflecting shifts across key analytical parameters amid a backdrop of sustained underperformance and sector-specific challenges.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>506a9d409e491fb36693f301b6350490</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 12:30:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Australian Prem Sees Revision in Market Evaluation Amid Mixed Financial Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/australian-prem-downgraded-to-sell-by-marketsmojo-amid-declining-mojo-score-3764754</link><description>Australian Prem, a microcap player in the Other Electrical Equipment sector, has experienced a revision in its market evaluation reflecting a nuanced shift in its financial and technical outlook. This adjustment comes amid a backdrop of mixed performance indicators and evolving market conditions.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>f3a698b6f239c7bd5ae9b61eca4c5320</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 12:30:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indo Amines Sees Revision in Market Evaluation Amid Mixed Financial Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/indo-amines-downgraded-to-sell-by-marketsmojo-amid-declining-mojo-score-3764752</link><description>Indo Amines, a microcap player in the specialty chemicals sector, has experienced a revision in its market evaluation metrics, reflecting a nuanced shift in its financial and technical outlook. This adjustment comes amid a backdrop of subdued stock performance and contrasting fundamental indicators.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>bebacb916df88858dc41e7cc69579860</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 12:30:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I G Petrochems Sees Revision in Market Evaluation Amid Challenging Financials</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/i-g-petrochems-upgraded-from-strong-sell-to-sell-by-marketsmojo-on-16-dec-2025-3764751</link><description>I G Petrochems has experienced a revision in its market evaluation, reflecting changes in its fundamental and technical outlook. This adjustment comes amid a backdrop of subdued financial performance and sector-specific challenges within the commodity chemicals industry.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>f280316b053e4ba01cb21ffbde4f1645</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 12:30:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dhunseri Vent. Sees Revision in Market Assessment Amidst Challenging Financials</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/dhunseri-vent-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-worsening-financials-and-bearish-technicals-3764750</link><description>Dhunseri Vent., a microcap player in the diversified sector, has experienced a revision in its market assessment reflecting recent financial and technical developments. The company’s evaluation metrics have shifted in response to ongoing operational challenges and market performance trends.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>a1b9c2d6a186666cb84d5d42635ec319</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 12:30:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 12:30:29 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>