<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:00:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Q3 FY2026 Earnings Review: Mixed Results Across Market Caps with Mid Caps Leading Profit Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/q3-fy2026-earnings-review-mixed-results-across-market-caps-with-mid-caps-leading-profit-growth-3784037</link><description>The September 2025 quarter earnings season has unfolded with a mixed bag of results across market capitalisation segments, revealing nuanced sectoral performances and a modest improvement in aggregate profitability. While mid-cap companies have demonstrated robust earnings growth, large caps continue to face headwinds, underscoring the divergent trajectories within the Indian equity landscape.
Time: 30 minutes ago</description><guid>33974c834ad6de32a1f7bd159b1adb3d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Emcure Pharmaceuticals Downgraded to Hold Amid Mixed Technical and Valuation Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/emcure-pharmaceuticals-downgraded-to-hold-amid-mixed-technical-and-valuation-signals-3784035</link><description>Emcure Pharmaceuticals Ltd has seen its investment rating downgraded from Buy to Hold as of 6 January 2026, reflecting a nuanced reassessment across quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. Despite robust quarterly financials and strong management efficiency, evolving technical signals and valuation concerns have tempered enthusiasm among analysts, prompting a more cautious stance on the stock.
Time: 59 minutes ago</description><guid>82a0ad3fa1312a8c2d8e2d21b5b587a4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Borosil Scientific Ltd Upgraded to 'Sell' as Valuation and Technicals Improve</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/borosil-scientific-ltd-upgraded-to-sell-as-valuation-and-technicals-improve-3784034</link><description>Borosil Scientific Ltd has seen its investment rating upgraded from Strong Sell to Sell as of 6 January 2026, reflecting a nuanced shift in its technical outlook and valuation metrics despite ongoing challenges in financial performance and long-term growth prospects.
Time: 59 minutes ago</description><guid>96fb90882be198a3444db527b643ff2c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Capital Small Finance Bank Ltd Upgraded to Hold on Improved Technicals and Valuation</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/capital-small-finance-bank-ltd-upgraded-to-hold-on-improved-technicals-and-valuation-3784036</link><description>Capital Small Finance Bank Ltd has seen its investment rating upgraded from Sell to Hold, reflecting a nuanced improvement across technical indicators, valuation metrics, financial trends, and overall quality. This recalibration comes amid a backdrop of mixed market performance and solid quarterly financial results, signalling cautious optimism for investors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>68272b7772e8a32f9bbdf8360880b96c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gandhar Oil Refinery Upgraded to Hold on Improved Technicals and Valuation</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/gandhar-oil-refinery-upgraded-to-hold-on-improved-technicals-and-valuation-3784033</link><description>Gandhar Oil Refinery (India) Ltd has seen its investment rating upgraded from Sell to Hold, reflecting a notable improvement in its technical outlook and valuation metrics. Despite recent challenges in long-term growth and market underperformance, the company’s financial trends and technical indicators have shown signs of stabilisation, prompting analysts to revise their stance cautiously optimistic.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ab996316a1e9234f891089affe81bc00</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blue Jet Healthcare Downgraded to Sell Amid Technical Weakness and Flat Financials</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/blue-jet-healthcare-downgraded-to-sell-amid-technical-weakness-and-flat-financials-3784032</link><description>Blue Jet Healthcare Ltd has been downgraded from a Hold to a Sell rating by MarketsMOJO as of 6 January 2026, reflecting a combination of deteriorating technical indicators, flat financial performance, and valuation concerns despite strong long-term fundamentals. The downgrade highlights growing investor caution amid mixed signals across quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical parameters.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>abcf4f8f63d2d5566eb687e7ad8324f5</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IRM Energy Ltd Downgraded to Sell Amid Weak Technicals and Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/irm-energy-ltd-downgraded-to-sell-amid-weak-technicals-and-valuation-concerns-3784031</link><description>IRM Energy Ltd has been downgraded from a Hold to a Sell rating as of 6 January 2026, reflecting deteriorating technical indicators, expensive valuation metrics, and disappointing long-term financial trends. Despite some positive quarterly results, the company’s overall outlook has weakened, prompting a reassessment of its investment appeal within the gas sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2693a38ad9747e0adcff42c689af444d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Plaza Wires Ltd Downgraded to Strong Sell Amid Weak Fundamentals and Bearish Technicals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/plaza-wires-ltd-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-weak-fundamentals-and-bearish-technicals-3784030</link><description>Plaza Wires Ltd, a player in the Cables - Electricals sector, has seen its investment rating downgraded from Sell to Strong Sell as of 6 January 2026. This shift reflects deteriorating technical indicators, weak long-term financial trends, and subpar valuation metrics, signalling caution for investors amid a challenging market environment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>773269f862f8a9cb09d21c07b9ecdf89</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Emcure Pharmaceuticals Ltd Sees Shift to Mildly Bullish Momentum Amid Technical Indicator Changes</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/emcure-pharmaceuticals-ltd-sees-shift-to-mildly-bullish-momentum-amid-technical-indicator-changes-3784029</link><description>Emcure Pharmaceuticals Ltd has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, moving from a bullish to a mildly bullish stance as of early January 2026. This change is underscored by mixed signals from key technical indicators such as MACD, RSI, moving averages, and volume-based metrics, reflecting a nuanced outlook for the pharmaceutical and biotechnology sector stock.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3c6540922a2e145875074ac0f63c6bbb</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Go Digit General Insurance Ltd Technical Momentum Shifts Amid Sideways Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/go-digit-general-insurance-ltd-technical-momentum-shifts-amid-sideways-trend-3784024</link><description>Go Digit General Insurance Ltd has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, moving from a mildly bullish stance to a sideways trend as of early January 2026. This transition is underscored by mixed signals from key technical indicators such as MACD, RSI, Bollinger Bands, and moving averages, reflecting a period of consolidation and uncertainty for investors in the insurance sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5ddd70bfc9508931c10df527a0f6f9e0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>R K Swamy Ltd Faces Bearish Technical Shift Amidst Weak Price Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/r-k-swamy-ltd-faces-bearish-technical-shift-amidst-weak-price-momentum-3784027</link><description>R K Swamy Ltd, a key player in the Media &amp; Entertainment sector, has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, moving from a mildly bearish stance to a more pronounced bearish trend. This transition is underscored by mixed signals from key technical indicators such as MACD, RSI, Bollinger Bands, and moving averages, reflecting growing investor caution amid a challenging market backdrop.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>858fa24beb8f225f81029be52cfd5738</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sula Vineyards Ltd Rating Upgraded to Sell Amid Mixed Technical and Financial Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sula-vineyards-ltd-rating-upgraded-to-sell-amid-mixed-technical-and-financial-signals-3784028</link><description>Sula Vineyards Ltd has seen its investment rating upgraded from Strong Sell to Sell as of 6 January 2026, reflecting a nuanced shift in its technical outlook despite ongoing financial challenges. The company’s technical indicators have improved from a bearish to a mildly bearish stance, while valuation metrics remain attractive. However, the firm continues to grapple with deteriorating profitability and subdued long-term growth prospects, underscoring a complex investment case for market participants.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4f59e686fd2f4328d0eaf3a4ac820616</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GPT Healthcare Ltd Sees Mixed Technical Signals Amid Price Momentum Shift</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gpt-healthcare-ltd-sees-mixed-technical-signals-amid-price-momentum-shift-3784026</link><description>GPT Healthcare Ltd has experienced a subtle shift in its technical momentum, moving from a bearish to a mildly bearish trend, as reflected in recent market data and technical indicators. Despite a modest day gain of 2.71%, the stock’s overall technical outlook remains cautious, with mixed signals from key momentum and trend-following tools.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9da15903e7daaa7b2bdeb95fdcef3fca</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Juniper Hotels Ltd Faces Bearish Momentum Amid Technical Downturn</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/juniper-hotels-ltd-faces-bearish-momentum-amid-technical-downturn-3784023</link><description>Juniper Hotels Ltd has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, with key indicators signalling a bearish trend. The stock’s recent price action and technical parameters suggest increasing downside risks, contrasting with broader market resilience as reflected by the Sensex.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>70a69f0c4ed5ef7dc44bc99bf50156b2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Capital Small Finance Bank Ltd Sees Mixed Technical Signals Amid Price Momentum Shift</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/capital-small-finance-bank-ltd-sees-mixed-technical-signals-amid-price-momentum-shift-3784022</link><description>Capital Small Finance Bank Ltd has experienced a subtle shift in its technical momentum, moving from a bearish stance to a mildly bearish outlook, reflecting a complex interplay of technical indicators. Despite a modest decline in its share price, the stock’s recent performance relative to the Sensex and evolving technical signals suggest cautious optimism for investors navigating the Other Bank sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6965cc34b1445fcf52123540ba4c3407</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Muthoot Microfin Ltd Technical Momentum Shifts Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/muthoot-microfin-ltd-technical-momentum-shifts-amid-mixed-market-signals-3784021</link><description>Muthoot Microfin Ltd has experienced a nuanced shift in its technical momentum, moving from a bullish to a mildly bullish trend as of early January 2026. Despite a modest day decline of 1.20%, the stock’s technical indicators present a complex picture, with some signals pointing to strength while others suggest caution. This analysis delves into the recent technical developments, comparing them with broader market trends and historical performance to provide a comprehensive view for investors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6e729b42fc5254b674c513795c2b5a06</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Inox India Ltd Technical Momentum Shifts Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/inox-india-ltd-technical-momentum-shifts-amid-mixed-market-signals-3784020</link><description>Inox India Ltd has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, moving from a mildly bearish stance to a more sideways trend as of early January 2026. Despite a modest day gain of 1.29%, the stock’s technical indicators present a complex picture, with mixed signals from MACD, RSI, moving averages, and other momentum oscillators, reflecting cautious investor sentiment amid broader market dynamics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0724f24b4b11f81aba3b6295fd2f0bb7</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gandhar Oil Refinery (India) Ltd Shows Technical Momentum Shift Amid Mixed Indicators</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gandhar-oil-refinery-india-ltd-shows-technical-momentum-shift-amid-mixed-indicators-3784018</link><description>Gandhar Oil Refinery (India) Ltd has exhibited a notable shift in its technical momentum, moving from a mildly bearish stance to a mildly bullish outlook as of early January 2026. This change is underscored by a blend of technical indicator signals, including MACD, RSI, moving averages, and volume-based metrics, reflecting a complex but cautiously optimistic scenario for investors in the oil sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>150d7f9ffb86f19611fb0fa6f01ac728</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd Upgraded to Buy on Strong Financial and Technical Metrics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/tamilnad-mercantile-bank-ltd-upgraded-to-buy-on-strong-financial-and-technical-metrics-3784025</link><description>Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd has been upgraded from a Hold to a Buy rating, reflecting significant improvements across technical indicators, valuation metrics, financial trends, and overall quality. The upgrade, effective from 06 Jan 2026, is underpinned by robust quarterly financial results, a bullish technical outlook, and attractive valuation compared to peers, signalling renewed investor confidence in this private sector bank.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1935da6b0cd60d397104105b288b984d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Protean eGov Technologies Ltd Faces Bearish Momentum Amid Technical Deterioration</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/protean-egov-technologies-ltd-faces-bearish-momentum-amid-technical-deterioration-3784019</link><description>Protean eGov Technologies Ltd has experienced a notable shift in its technical momentum, with key indicators signalling a transition from a mildly bearish to a more pronounced bearish trend. This change comes amid a significant decline in the stock’s price performance over the past year, contrasting sharply with broader market gains.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>eb56c9791cd9443c3f2d8526165ac087</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>