<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:35:22 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec 2025 Results Reveal Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-reveal-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3862797</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has unfolded with a nuanced picture across market capitalisations, reflecting a cautious yet improving corporate performance landscape. With 4,094 companies reporting results, the proportion of positive earnings has edged up modestly to 46.0%, signalling a gradual recovery from the subdued trends seen earlier in the year.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>f2e84d82a73132a46188d704fa33990c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wardwizard Foods Declines 3.74%: Earnings and Valuation Challenges Shape Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/wardwizard-foods-declines-374-earnings-and-valuation-challenges-shape-week-3862796</link><description>Wardwizard Foods &amp; Beverages Ltd experienced a challenging week on the BSE, with its stock price declining 3.74% from ₹9.10 on 13 Feb 2026 to ₹8.76 on 20 Feb 2026, underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The week was marked by mixed trading sessions influenced by the company’s Q3 FY26 results revealing revenue growth but persistent profitability struggles, alongside a detailed valuation analysis highlighting elevated risk metrics and subdued market sentiment.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>632cacec9f94e66d74a39bb401af566d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rallis India Gains 7.80%: Four Key Factors Driving This Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rallis-india-gains-780-four-key-factors-driving-this-weeks-momentum-3862795</link><description>Rallis India Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 7.80% from Rs.264.60 to Rs.285.25 between 16 and 20 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain over the same period. The stock’s trajectory was shaped by a series of technical momentum shifts, an upgrade in investment rating, and robust financial results, all contributing to renewed investor interest amid a mixed sector backdrop.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>c3cd0e66403bd4b8d103d1ce288fe3b0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sangal Papers Gains 1.35%: Stabilisation and Valuation Shift Drive Weekly Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sangal-papers-gains-135-stabilisation-and-valuation-shift-drive-weekly-performance-3862791</link><description>Sangal Papers Ltd closed the week at Rs.199.00, marking a 1.35% gain from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.196.35, outperforming the Sensex which rose 0.39% over the same period. The week was characterised by a stabilisation in the company’s quarterly financial performance, an upgrade in its investment rating from Strong Sell to Sell, and a notable improvement in valuation metrics amidst ongoing sector challenges. Despite sideways price movement midweek, the stock demonstrated resilience relative to the broader market, reflecting cautious investor sentiment amid mixed fundamental signals.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>72906a5f680bd7f3f2345bc41ae5bc62</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Last Mile Enterprises Gains 2.06%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/last-mile-enterprises-gains-206-2-key-factors-driving-the-week-3862794</link><description>Last Mile Enterprises Ltd recorded a modest weekly gain of 2.06%, closing at Rs.6.44 on 20 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex which rose 0.39% over the same period. The week was marked by sharp intraday volatility driven by a significant financial downturn announcement and a contrasting surge in revenue masking profit collapse. These developments influenced trading volumes and price swings, reflecting investor caution amid deteriorating fundamentals.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>c4aa33a4f64b56257da643dd701bfb6a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vishvprabha Ventures Declines 4.95%: Financial Struggles and Valuation Risks Weigh</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vishvprabha-ventures-declines-495-financial-struggles-and-valuation-risks-weigh-3862793</link><description>Vishvprabha Ventures Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its stock price falling 4.95% from Rs.59.80 to Rs.56.84, underperforming the BSE Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The week was marked by a steep quarterly loss announcement, a downgrade to a Strong Sell rating, heightened valuation risks, and a fall to a 52-week low, all contributing to bearish sentiment and volatile trading.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>53f0e2512a579aa5ec00d95eaf1a4929</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ahluwalia Contracts Falls 10.95%: Technical Downgrade and Valuation Shift Shape Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ahluwalia-contracts-falls-1095-technical-downgrade-and-valuation-shift-shape-week-3862790</link><description>Ahluwalia Contracts (India) Ltd experienced a challenging week from 16 to 20 February 2026, with its stock price declining sharply by 10.95% to close at Rs.804.60, significantly underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The week was marked by intense selling pressure, a technical downgrade, and a shift in valuation perception, all contributing to the stock’s downward trajectory amid a volatile market backdrop.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>b238333ae12642532df3771313103cb4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HCL Technologies Declines 1.23% Amid Mixed Signals and Options Activity</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hcl-technologies-declines-123-amid-mixed-signals-and-options-activity-3862792</link><description>HCL Technologies Ltd closed the week ending 20 February 2026 at Rs.1,437.05, down 1.23% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.1,454.95, underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The week was marked by a shift from short-term technical optimism to increased bearish sentiment reflected in heavy put option activity, followed by a surge in call options and open interest, signalling a complex and volatile market environment for the stock.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>f46f8c78053920142fb1a7570666b426</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pro Fin Capital Services Ltd Falls 6.57%: Valuation Shifts and Downgrade Shape Weekly Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pro-fin-capital-services-ltd-falls-657-valuation-shifts-and-downgrade-shape-weekly-trend-3862789</link><description>Pro Fin Capital Services Ltd experienced a challenging week, closing at Rs.3.70 on 20 Feb 2026, down 6.57% from the opening price of Rs.3.96 on 16 Feb 2026. This decline contrasted with the Sensex’s modest gain of 0.39% over the same period, highlighting the stock’s underperformance amid mixed fundamental and technical signals. Key events included a downgrade to a Sell rating and a subsequent valuation upgrade signalling renewed price attractiveness despite short-term weakness.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>8cf1acc1de20328d3f50f4fe7f6f11ae</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gujarat Natural Resources Gains 1.10%: Valuation and Technical Shifts Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gujarat-natural-resources-gains-110-valuation-and-technical-shifts-shape-the-week-3862788</link><description>Gujarat Natural Resources Ltd recorded a modest weekly gain of 1.10%, closing at Rs.105.85 on 20 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex which rose 0.39% over the same period. The week was marked by a downgrade to a Sell rating amid stretched valuation concerns and a subtle shift in technical momentum, reflecting a complex interplay between strong recent financial performance and cautionary signals from market indicators.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>330ec49fd5b223a726515338592b7547</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CIAN Agro Gains 4.14%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cian-agro-gains-414-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3862787</link><description>CIAN Agro Industries &amp; Infrastructure Ltd delivered a solid weekly performance, rising 4.14% from Rs.1,302.90 to Rs.1,356.80 between 16 and 20 February 2026, comfortably outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain. The week was marked by two consecutive 5.0% gap-up openings, reflecting strong market sentiment and improved valuation perceptions, despite some volatility midweek. This review analyses the key events shaping the stock’s trajectory and their impact on price movements.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>3a766d3ad23b49b9a0e70e07859ef2f0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Axis Bank Gains 1.14%: Mixed Signals Amid Robust Trading and Option Activity</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/axis-bank-gains-114-mixed-signals-amid-robust-trading-and-option-activity-3862786</link><description>Axis Bank Ltd delivered a modest weekly gain of 1.14% from Rs.1,368.25 to Rs.1,383.85 between 23 and 27 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.96% over the same period. The week was characterised by strong trading volumes, mixed option market signals, and fluctuating investor participation, reflecting a nuanced market sentiment amid broader sectoral and macroeconomic factors.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>5936cdcb5bed0e4143966c0f2e2e514d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Moschip Technologies Gains 1.59%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/moschip-technologies-gains-159-3-key-factors-driving-the-week-3862785</link><description>Moschip Technologies Ltd closed the week with a modest gain of 1.59%, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.96% over the same period. The stock exhibited notable volatility, surging sharply on 23 February before facing technical headwinds later in the week. This review analyses the key events and technical developments that shaped Moschip’s price action from 23 to 27 February 2026.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>dda382e8e4ceb06981bc6977457b8098</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tarmat Ltd Surges 29.78% in a Week: 3 Key Drivers Behind the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tarmat-ltd-surges-2978-in-a-week-3-key-drivers-behind-the-rally-3862784</link><description>Tarmat Ltd delivered a remarkable weekly performance, surging 29.78% from Rs.54.71 on 23 February to Rs.71.00 on 27 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.96% over the same period. The stock’s rally was marked by two consecutive days of hitting new 52-week highs and a dramatic upper circuit surge, reflecting strong buying momentum amid mixed market conditions.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>98fc151ad791c0759d13cedb4555a8bb</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Karur Vysya Bank Gains 0.91%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/karur-vysya-bank-gains-091-4-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3862783</link><description>Karur Vysya Bank Ltd. closed the week ending 27 Feb 2026 with a modest gain of 0.91%, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.96% over the same period. The stock demonstrated resilience amid mixed market conditions, hitting new 52-week and all-time highs midweek before retreating slightly on the final trading day. Strong fundamentals, institutional confidence, and sustained earnings growth underpinned the stock’s performance despite broader market volatility.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>865d498ad0d16d3bf47275466479082a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GMR Airports Gains 0.97%: Derivatives Surge and Technical Momentum Drive Weekly Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gmr-airports-gains-097-derivatives-surge-and-technical-momentum-drive-weekly-performance-3862779</link><description>GMR Airports Ltd closed the week with a modest gain of 0.97%, rising from Rs.99.68 to Rs.100.65, while the Sensex declined by 0.96% over the same period. The stock demonstrated resilience amid mixed market conditions, supported by a significant surge in derivatives open interest and a marked shift in technical momentum. These developments highlight evolving investor sentiment and technical strength in the transport infrastructure sector.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>4c779c4ade093185f4b4ed3bf51d1557</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GHV Infra Projects Ltd Gains 2.45%: 4 Key Technical Shifts Shape Weekly Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ghv-infra-projects-ltd-gains-245-4-key-technical-shifts-shape-weekly-performance-3862781</link><description>GHV Infra Projects Ltd closed the week with a 2.45% gain, outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.96% over the same period. Despite a challenging start marked by a significant gap down on 23 February 2026, the stock demonstrated resilience through a series of technical momentum shifts and sector tailwinds, closing at Rs.344.30 on 27 February 2026. This review analyses the key events and technical developments that shaped the stock’s performance during the week.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>329455a007c7ddefca29f013aa6f1e7a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Megasoft Ltd Falls 10.60%: Circuit Hits and Volatility Define the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/megasoft-ltd-falls-1060-circuit-hits-and-volatility-define-the-week-3862780</link><description>Megasoft Ltd experienced a turbulent week from 23 to 27 February 2026, closing at Rs.159.75, down 10.60% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.178.70. This decline significantly outpaced the Sensex’s modest 0.96% fall over the same period. The stock’s week was marked by extreme volatility, including hitting both upper and lower circuit limits amid strong buying and selling pressures, reflecting heightened investor uncertainty and speculative activity.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>497d74a4fb069d21f5cf4e75b3059432</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chennai Petroleum Gains 9.12%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/chennai-petroleum-gains-912-4-key-factors-driving-the-rally-3862782</link><description>Chennai Petroleum Corporation Ltd (CPCL) delivered a robust weekly gain of 9.12%, closing at Rs.963.00 on 27 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 0.96% over the same period. The stock’s strong performance was supported by a series of positive fundamental updates, technical momentum shifts, and institutional confidence, culminating in an upgrade to a Strong Buy rating by MarketsMOJO.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>b0c6f61adcfae48efba577480f4f71e9</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Asian Star Company Ltd Falls 5.61%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/asian-star-company-ltd-falls-561-3-key-factors-driving-the-decline-3862775</link><description>Asian Star Company Ltd’s stock declined by 5.61% over the week ending 27 February 2026, closing at Rs.606.00 compared to Rs.642.00 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s modest 0.96% fall, reflecting a combination of deteriorating technical momentum, weak financial trends, and valuation shifts that shaped investor sentiment throughout the week.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>2acd2dc68732c4fc458bee3c4780bfc2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:35:22 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>