<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:33:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>AWFIS Space Solutions Q3 FY26: Profitability Rebounds Sharply Amid Persistent Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/awfis-space-solutions-q3-fy26-profitability-rebounds-sharply-amid-persistent-valuation-concerns-3816866</link><description>AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd., a small-cap player in India's co-working space sector, delivered a strong sequential profit recovery in Q3 FY26, with net profit surging 60.02% quarter-on-quarter to ₹15.97 crores. However, the year-on-year comparison tells a starkly different story, with profits plunging 58.70% from the exceptional ₹38.67 crores reported in Q3 FY25. Despite robust revenue momentum and margin expansion, the stock continues to trade under severe pressure, down 41.62% over the past year and hovering near its 52-week low of ₹377.60.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>64349a5d58bca178f72b0be68a076b52</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:33:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PB Fintech Q3 FY26: Profitability Surge Masks Valuation Concerns as Stock Tumbles</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/pb-fintech-q3-fy26-profitability-surge-masks-valuation-concerns-as-stock-tumbles-3816865</link><description>PB Fintech Ltd., the parent company of Policybazaar and Paisabazaar, delivered a stellar operational performance in Q3 FY26, with consolidated net profit surging 166.15% year-on-year to ₹134.86 crores, yet investors responded with sharp selling, pushing the stock down 3.44% to ₹1,562.35 on February 02, 2026. The fintech major, commanding a market capitalisation of ₹73,600 crores, demonstrated robust revenue momentum with net sales climbing 38.24% YoY to ₹1,613.55 crores in the September quarter, marking the highest quarterly revenue in company history.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f02d9dcbb89d7978085ec919d383490c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:33:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindcon Chemicals Q2 FY26: Profit Plunges 46% Despite Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/hindcon-chemicals-q2-fy26-profit-plunges-46-despite-revenue-growth-3816864</link><description>Hindcon Chemicals Ltd., a micro-cap speciality chemicals manufacturer focused on the construction industry, reported a sharp 45.93% quarter-on-quarter decline in consolidated net profit for Q2 FY26, despite posting modest revenue growth. The company's net profit dropped to ₹0.73 crores from ₹1.35 crores in Q1 FY26, whilst net sales rose marginally by 2.96% to ₹15.32 crores. The disappointing results, coupled with a sustained bearish technical trend, have pushed the stock down 48.44% over the past year, significantly underperforming both the Sensex and its sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>89c871170d5c17ad49bcce1b2aaeddbd</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:33:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rajkamal Synthetics Q2 FY26: Profit Surge Masks Deteriorating Margins and Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/rajkamal-synthetics-q2-fy26-profit-surge-masks-deteriorating-margins-and-valuation-concerns-3816863</link><description>Rajkamal Synthetics Ltd., a micro-cap player in India's garments and apparels sector, posted a consolidated net profit of ₹0.99 crores for Q2 FY26 (July-September 2025), marking a robust sequential improvement of 20.73% from Q1 FY26's ₹0.82 crores. However, the year-on-year comparison reveals a troubling narrative: profits declined 36.54% from ₹1.56 crores in Q2 FY25, even as revenue surged 223.30% to ₹17.62 crores. The stock, trading at ₹41.99 with a market capitalisation of just ₹28.00 crores, has struggled significantly, posting a one-year return of negative 28.77% against the Sensex's positive 5.37% gain.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0ae50bb78c55cc6f3e1c47217dedb46b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:33:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Urja Global Q2 FY26: Profitability Plunges as Revenue Contracts Sharply</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/urja-global-q2-fy26-profitability-plunges-as-revenue-contracts-sharply-3816862</link><description>Urja Global Ltd., a micro-cap player in the heavy electrical equipment sector, reported disappointing results for Q2 FY26, with consolidated net profit declining 16.00% sequentially to ₹0.42 crores from ₹0.50 crores in Q1 FY26. The company's market capitalisation stands at ₹550.00 crores, with shares trading at ₹10.07 as of February 02, 2026, down 4.55% on the day following persistent pressure from weak operational performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>60e64c07ac6311d1481bf40c55869799</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:33:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indiabulls Limited Q2 FY26: Spectacular Turnaround Masks Persistent Structural Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/indiabulls-limited-q2-fy26-spectacular-turnaround-masks-persistent-structural-concerns-3816861</link><description>Indiabulls Limited (NSE: IBULLSLTD), a micro-cap diversified commercial services company with a market capitalisation of ₹2,545 crores, reported a dramatic turnaround in Q2 FY26 with consolidated net profit of ₹74.60 crores compared to a loss of ₹11.72 crores in the same quarter last year. However, the stock has declined sharply by 48.54% over the past three months, currently trading at ₹10.76—just 1.51% above its 52-week low of ₹10.60—as investors remain sceptical about the sustainability of this recovery amidst a history of volatile performance and negative equity.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8c3fbc8ae4dfb0497233cb541f718149</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:33:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Ventive Hospitality Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-ventive-hospitality-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3816859</link><description>Ventive Hospitality Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results show a strong net profit increase to ₹52.57 crores, up 95.21% from the previous quarter, despite a slight decline in net sales. However, concerns remain regarding declining operating margins, low return on equity, and reliance on non-operating income.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ce0598d6918290f4b1b7f07011a53440</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:33:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Campus Activewear Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-campus-activewear-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3816858</link><description>Campus Activewear Ltd's Q3 FY26 results are strong, with record net sales and profit, but the company faces long-term growth challenges and high valuation concerns, leading to mixed signals about its financial health.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>418c044a1cd638a85498bd316ec6e999</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:33:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Latent View Analytics Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-latent-view-analytics-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3816857</link><description>Latent View Analytics Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 23.25% year-on-year, reaching ₹257.54 crores, but profitability has declined, with net profit down 12.69% from the previous quarter and operating margins contracting, indicating operational challenges despite solid revenue performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a54616053411405e65613228584f643c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:33:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Chemicals Q3 FY26: Profit Plunge Deepens as Margin Pressures Mount</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/tata-chemicals-q3-fy26-profit-plunge-deepens-as-margin-pressures-mount-3816860</link><description>Tata Chemicals Limited has reported a consolidated net loss of ₹39.00 crores for Q3 FY26, marking a dramatic reversal from the ₹77.00 crore profit recorded in Q2 FY26. The commodity chemicals major, with a market capitalisation of ₹18,430 crores, witnessed its stock decline 2.27% to ₹726.15 following the results announcement, extending a troubling pattern of underperformance that has seen the stock shed 24.71% over the past year. The quarter's results underscore mounting operational challenges, with operating margins contracting sharply despite modest revenue growth, raising serious questions about the sustainability of earnings in the current demand environment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>888b21fc901b333d493a1a8eac1fd1b9</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:33:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Hyundai Motor India Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-hyundai-motor-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3816856</link><description>Hyundai Motor India Ltd's Q3 FY26 results show record revenue of ₹17,973.49 crores, up 7.96% year-on-year, but net profit declined 21.49% quarter-on-quarter to ₹1,234.40 crores, indicating profitability challenges despite strong demand for SUVs. Overall, the performance reflects mixed results with significant margin compression that investors should monitor closely.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>482046ac606341f108ffbbe28796ed59</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:33:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Sundaram Finance Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-sundaram-finance-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3816855</link><description>Sundaram Finance Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are strong, with a net profit of ₹541.36 crores, an 18.86% year-on-year increase, and a solid rise in interest income. The company shows good operational efficiency and profitability, although there is room for improvement in capital efficiency and net interest margins.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>53da190491d3df764c85a4b00be627ca</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:33:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Utkarsh Small Finance Bank Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-utkarsh-small-finance-bank-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3816854</link><description>Utkarsh Small Finance Bank Ltd's latest results are concerning, reporting a net loss of ₹348.46 crores and a significant decline in income and asset quality, with a gross NPA ratio of 12.42%. The bank faces ongoing operational challenges, reflected in its negative profitability and deteriorating financial metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>976d7310c7e69c778f5b7cc9024e7afb</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:33:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Iris Clothings Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-iris-clothings-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3816853</link><description>Iris Clothings Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth with net sales increasing by 18.50% sequentially, but declining profit margins and net profit indicate challenges in maintaining profitability. Overall, while sales are up, concerns about operational efficiency persist.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>27495800788f348c9f32827be53008de</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:33:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Geekay Wires Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-geekay-wires-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3816852</link><description>Geekay Wires Ltd's latest results show improved operating margins but stagnant revenue growth and declining profit margins, raising concerns about sustainability and financial health. While the company is in expansion mode, its reliance on non-operating income and underperformance in stock price suggest caution for investors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d2217ca9abf35f82196d36ac8e8a9359</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:33:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Bharat Wire Ropes Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-bharat-wire-ropes-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3816851</link><description>Bharat Wire Ropes Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results show a mixed performance, with a net profit decline of 17.72% sequentially but a year-on-year increase of 36.01%. However, revenue decreased both sequentially and year-on-year, indicating operational challenges and a slowdown in growth momentum.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ebb7c83bb527743bf3db3b12f5ad3dda</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:33:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Sinclairs Hotels Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-sinclairs-hotels-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3816850</link><description>Sinclairs Hotels Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results are poor, showing a net loss of -₹2.04 crore and a 42.77% drop in revenue, primarily due to seasonal challenges in the hospitality sector. Despite a year-on-year revenue growth of 11.14%, the company faces ongoing structural issues and a negative operating margin.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d2ddd4fddf74302e18a61689fbdf88a2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:33:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Jet Freight Logistics Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-jet-freight-logistics-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3816849</link><description>Jet Freight Logistics Ltd's latest results show mixed performance, with a 30% sequential decline in net sales and a 51% drop in net profit compared to the previous quarter, although there was a year-on-year profit increase. The company faces operational challenges and capital efficiency issues, despite some improvements in operating margins.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>da287d99bd390038afe894a1422a043c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:33:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Silver Touch Technologies Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-silver-touch-technologies-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3816848</link><description>Silver Touch Technologies Ltd's latest results are positive, showing a net profit increase of 109.32% year-on-year and a revenue growth of 29.52%, despite facing challenges like rising interest costs. Overall, the company demonstrates strong operational performance and expanding margins.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>49b591714de8e332b2fb323aa4ee7d24</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:33:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:33:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>