<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:41:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Indostar Capital Finance Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indostar-capital-finance-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3811515</link><description>Indostar Capital Finance Ltd has declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.202.3, marking a significant downturn in its stock price amid broader market fluctuations and company-specific performance factors.
Time: 3 minutes ago</description><guid>c181e5a0964a5989bec35216af87c8fb</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:41:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ganges Securities Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.117.1 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ganges-securities-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs1171-amidst-continued-downtrend-3811514</link><description>Ganges Securities Ltd, a player in the FMCG sector, recorded a new 52-week low of Rs.117.1 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amidst a volatile trading session and ongoing underperformance relative to its sector and broader market indices.
Time: 3 minutes ago</description><guid>e82cf6dc7d800671fbb6697792a8adf9</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:41:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Super Sales India Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.543 Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/super-sales-india-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs543-amid-continued-downtrend-3811516</link><description>Super Sales India Ltd, a player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.543 today, marking a significant decline amid ongoing market pressures and sector underperformance. The stock’s recent trajectory highlights a challenging period for the company, with notable volatility and sustained downward momentum.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>d47e43151c55e84838356c1be361db04</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:41:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>State Bank of India Stock Hits All-Time High, Marking a Significant Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/state-bank-of-india-stock-hits-all-time-high-marking-a-significant-milestone-3811512</link><description>State Bank of India (SBI) has reached a new all-time high, underscoring its robust performance and sustained growth trajectory. The stock's recent surge reflects a remarkable journey marked by consistent gains and strong market positioning within the public sector banking industry.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>8f46b931ceb18a2a60197e36dba7142b</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:41:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bal Pharma Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.65.01</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bal-pharma-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs6501-3811513</link><description>Bal Pharma Ltd’s shares declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.65.01 on 30 Jan 2026, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory. The pharmaceutical company’s stock has underperformed both its sector and the broader market, reflecting persistent pressures on its financial and operational metrics.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>52ce644a08fca6bb4b897518de8a63da</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:41:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Next Mediaworks Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/next-mediaworks-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-underperformance-3811511</link><description>Next Mediaworks Ltd has declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing at ₹4.02 on 30 Jan 2026, marking a significant downturn in the stock’s performance over the past year amid persistent financial headwinds and sector underperformance.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>89fc7983f1c6438c019b8b904ecdda23</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:41:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JNK India Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.31% Surge on 30 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jnk-india-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-731-surge-on-30-jan-2026-3811509</link><description>JNK India Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 30 Jan 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 227.85, marking a 7.45% increase from its previous close. This notable uptick outpaced the broader industrial manufacturing sector and occurred despite a subdued market environment.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>89bdff9149bdb439abb16e538473b839</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:41:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Supreme Petrochem Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.0% Surge on 30 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/supreme-petrochem-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-70-surge-on-30-jan-2026-3811508</link><description>Supreme Petrochem Ltd demonstrated robust intraday strength on 30 Jan 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 565.2, marking a 7.38% increase from its previous close. This performance notably outpaced the broader Sensex, which traded lower amid a cautious market mood.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>a05ceb6bb44eebea28127613dde115c2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:41:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KSB Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.14% Surge on 30 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ksb-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-714-surge-on-30-jan-2026-3811507</link><description>KSB Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 30 Jan 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 736.3, marking an 8.08% increase from its previous close. The stock outpaced its sector and the broader market, reflecting notable buying momentum during the trading session.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>422c6d38559d6cde84acfe570a5f18e3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:41:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Steel Strips Wheels Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.0% Surge on 30 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/steel-strips-wheels-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-70-surge-on-30-jan-2026-3811506</link><description>Steel Strips Wheels Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 30 Jan 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 203.95, marking a 7.31% increase from the previous close. This rally outpaced the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector and the broader Sensex index, reflecting a notable reversal after two days of decline.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>d42479a53863748a5633da09709f4b25</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:41:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Bijlee Ltd Hits Intraday High with 8.33% Surge on 30 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-bijlee-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-833-surge-on-30-jan-2026-3811505</link><description>Bharat Bijlee Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 30 Jan 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 2,696.25, marking an 8.33% increase from its previous close. This notable uptick outpaced the broader sector and market indices, reflecting strong trading momentum despite a subdued Sensex opening.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>220ea0632b633be86789a2e5845e7043</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:41:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>One 97 Communications Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Price Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/one-97-communications-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-price-weakness-3811503</link><description>One 97 Communications Ltd, the parent company of Paytm, has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite recent price declines, the spike in open interest and volume suggests increased speculative interest and potential directional bets in the near term.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>a34629b0b3265d9a19f06e255ed88c34</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:41:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shekhawati Industries Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shekhawati-industries-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-robust-buying-pressure-3811504</link><description>Shekhawati Industries Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, witnessed a remarkable surge on 30 Jan 2026, hitting its upper circuit price limit with a strong 9.42% gain. This sharp rally was driven by intense buying interest, resulting in the stock touching an intraday high of ₹15.93, marking a near 20% jump from its previous close. Despite the surge, the stock experienced significant volatility and a regulatory freeze was imposed due to the upper circuit hit, leaving a substantial portion of demand unfilled.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>fff4ba71ccfdcd76d33c6b407f9d55e9</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:41:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mazagon Dock Shipbuilders Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mazagon-dock-shipbuilders-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-momentum-3811502</link><description>Mazagon Dock Shipbuilders Ltd (MAZDOCK) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. The stock has outperformed its sector peers and demonstrated robust volume and price action, prompting a closer examination of the underlying market dynamics and potential directional bets.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>8762d13dc74d9f3999ff7c37620d3479</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:41:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dalmia Bharat Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dalmia-bharat-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3811499</link><description>Dalmia Bharat Ltd has witnessed a notable 10.6% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a marginal price gain of 0.12% on 30 Jan 2026, the stock remains under pressure from technical indicators and a recent downgrade by MarketsMOJO to a Sell rating, reflecting a complex interplay of bullish and bearish forces.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>75991b451f95475047b70f23ed6d5b63</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:41:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>