<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:20:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Are Krishana Phoschem Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-krishana-phoschem-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3790239</link><description>Krishana Phoschem Ltd's latest results are strong, with a 116.79% increase in revenue and a 62.30% rise in net profit year-on-year. However, profit margins have contracted, indicating some operational challenges that need monitoring.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>61070d07e63675237380513193dff85c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:20:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Krishana Phoschem Q3 FY26: Stellar Growth Momentum Continues with 62% Profit Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/krishana-phoschem-q3-fy26-stellar-growth-momentum-continues-with-62-profit-surge-3790127</link><description>Krishana Phoschem Limited, a Rajasthan-based fertiliser and specialty chemicals manufacturer, has delivered an exceptional third quarter performance for FY2026, reporting a net profit of ₹33.32 crores—a remarkable 62.29% year-on-year surge from ₹20.53 crores in Q3 FY25. The company's stock, currently trading at ₹494.85 with a market capitalisation of ₹2,979 crores, has demonstrated extraordinary momentum over the past year with returns of 160.42%, significantly outperforming the Sensex's 8.21% gain by a staggering 152 percentage points.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>9ba49461fd171a0a012cc7fcf08a5286</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:20:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Raj Rayon Industries Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/raj-rayon-industries-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3790200</link><description>Raj Rayon Industries Ltd, a small-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, witnessed a sharp decline on 12 Jan 2026 as it hit its lower circuit price limit, closing at ₹21.41. The stock faced intense selling pressure, resulting in a maximum daily loss of 1.97%, reflecting growing investor concerns amid deteriorating technical and fundamental indicators.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>4d3f0bac48ebcd3ef89e0d1f8960d6f9</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:20:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blue Coast Hotels Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/blue-coast-hotels-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3790198</link><description>Blue Coast Hotels Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Hotels &amp; Resorts sector, witnessed intense selling pressure on 12 Jan 2026, hitting its lower circuit limit with a sharp 4.97% decline to close at ₹30.78. The stock’s performance starkly underperformed its sector and broader market benchmarks, reflecting mounting investor concerns and panic selling in a highly volatile trading session.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>12cbc9ec9000bed0eae3311fc8649819</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:20:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:20:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>