<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:35:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Silver Touch Technologies Hits New 52-Week High of Rs.884.85</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/silver-touch-technologies-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs88485-3760243</link><description>Silver Touch Technologies, a key player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, reached a significant milestone today by touching a new 52-week high of Rs.884.85. This achievement marks a notable phase of momentum for the stock amid a mixed market environment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a4ada0e3f4085d11e39a5c1e24e88d44</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:35:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>InfoBeans Technologies Hits New 52-Week High of Rs.788.6 Marking Strong Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/infobeans-technologies-hits-new-52-week-high-of-rs7886-on-16-dec-2025-3760244</link><description>InfoBeans Technologies has reached a significant milestone by touching a new 52-week high of Rs.788.6, reflecting sustained momentum in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector. This achievement underscores the stock’s robust performance amid a mixed market environment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>71ff08617d67ec6136d1dbeee78168d9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:35:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sensex and Nifty Slip Amid Broad Market Weakness; Vedanta and Kirloskar Oil Among Top Movers</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-and-nifty-slip-amid-broad-market-weakness-realty-sector-leads-declines-3760242</link><description>Indian equity benchmarks Sensex and Nifty concluded the trading session on 16 Dec 2025 with declines, reflecting broad-based selling pressure across sectors. While the Nifty closed at 25,860.10, down 167.2 points or 0.64%, the Sensex settled at 84,679.86, lower by 533.50 points or 0.63%. Market breadth remained weak with a significant number of stocks declining, led by losses in Realty and financial services sectors.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>c201097e5d0071120db9062b8bdc1862</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:35:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chemfab Alkalis Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.450 Amidst Weak Financial Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/chemfab-alkalis-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3760240</link><description>Chemfab Alkalis has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.450, marking a significant decline in its stock price as it underperforms both its sector and the broader market amid subdued financial results and valuation concerns.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>c14458adbef2b3570d213823464965a7</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:35:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>LKP Securities Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.15.52 Amid Market Downturn</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lkp-securities-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs1552-amidst-continued-downtrend-3760239</link><description>LKP Securities touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.15.52 today, marking a significant decline amid broader market weakness and sector underperformance. The stock’s current price level reflects ongoing pressures within the capital markets sector and a challenging financial performance over the past year.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ad5dbd6c39526ef516a8465fa7f635b8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:35:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Allcargo Logistics Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.10.99 Amid Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/allcargo-logistics-stock-hits-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3760236</link><description>Shares of Allcargo Logistics have reached a new 52-week low of Rs.10.99, marking a significant decline amid a sustained period of negative returns and underperformance relative to the broader market and sector peers.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>23b6e427661c3d1cb6dc5d0d1fa03355</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:35:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pee Cee Cosma Sope Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.361.6 Amid Market Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pee-cee-cosma-sope-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3760232</link><description>Pee Cee Cosma Sope, a player in the FMCG sector, touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.361.6 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid broader market fluctuations and sector underperformance.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>49eb96839479f436855e5223add7b7b4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:35:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Zinc Hits New 52-Week High of Rs.572.85, Marking Strong Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-zinc-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs57285-3760229</link><description>Hindustan Zinc has reached a significant milestone by touching a new 52-week high of Rs.572.85, reflecting sustained momentum in the non-ferrous metals sector despite broader market pressures. This achievement highlights the stock’s resilience and upward trajectory over the past year.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>62cdc6d87e332908fc80abb72b5d5a6e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:35:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zenlabs Ethica Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.21.5 Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/zenlabs-ethica-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs215-amid-continued-underperformance-3760230</link><description>Zenlabs Ethica has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.21.5, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing price decline. The stock’s recent performance reflects a continuation of a downward trend that has persisted over the past year, with the share price now trading well below all major moving averages.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>2ff5fbd31adf39fa139b3d6cb7639828</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:35:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>COSCO (India) Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.210.3 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cosco-india-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3760238</link><description>COSCO (India) has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.210.3, marking a significant decline in its share price as the stock continues to trade below all major moving averages amid subdued financial performance and sector underperformance.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>c4de38d7ef352f11e1ad78650bcbf696</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:35:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sundaram Brake Linings Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.665.05</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sundaram-brake-linings-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-decline-3760235</link><description>Sundaram Brake Linings has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.665.05, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid a broader market downturn. The stock has been trading below all key moving averages and has underperformed its sector and the broader market over the past year.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>03a53355be0b9a1a59d10e1c53a836b2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:35:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Investment Trust of India Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.112.05</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/the-investment-trust-of-india-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3760234</link><description>The Investment Trust of India stock reached a new 52-week low of Rs.112.05 today, marking a significant decline amid broader market fluctuations and company-specific performance factors.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>41d5666120e8ec873214ae8420e7a7f9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:35:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SMT Engineering Hits New 52-Week High of Rs.167.3 Marking Significant Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/smt-engineering-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs1673-mark-3760237</link><description>SMT Engineering has reached a new 52-week high of Rs.167.3, reflecting a remarkable rally that has propelled the stock to its highest price level in over a year. This milestone underscores the sustained momentum the company has experienced amid a challenging broader market environment.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>a19418090e69e34cf9a2d027f76dfb4b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:35:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cupid Stock Hits New 52-Week High of Rs.424.85, Marking Significant Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cupid-stock-hits-new-52-week-high-of-rs42485-on-16-dec-2025-3760233</link><description>Cupid, a leading player in the FMCG sector, reached a new 52-week high of Rs.424.85 today, reflecting a strong rally and sustained momentum in its share price. This milestone underscores the stock's robust performance over the past year and highlights key financial metrics that have supported this upward trajectory.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>0d7f9d148beea8dd77e0937e16f01d4b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:35:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mangalam Industrial Finance Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.0.81 Amid Market Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mangalam-industrial-finance-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3760231</link><description>Mangalam Industrial Finance has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.0.81, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid broader market fluctuations and sectoral underperformance. The stock’s recent trajectory reflects ongoing challenges within the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector and specific company-level factors.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>562de4889b90fecceb073058e300907e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:35:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nova Agritech Stock Hits All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nova-agritech-stock-hits-all-time-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3760226</link><description>Shares of Nova Agritech have reached a new all-time low of ₹39.11, marking a significant point in the company’s market performance as it continues to trade below all key moving averages and underperform its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>1fb9488d648a2454addcfe274fb184d9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:35:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cupid Stock Surges Over 350% in Six Months, Outperforming Market Benchmarks</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/small-and-micro-cap-stocks-deliver-exceptional-half-year-returns-amidst-market-volatility-3760224</link><description>Cupid has delivered an extraordinary return of 350.89% over the past six months, significantly outpacing broader market indices and peers within the FMCG sector. This remarkable performance highlights the stock’s strong momentum amid a challenging market environment, driven by a combination of bullish technical indicators and robust financial fundamentals.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ca9c36825c0a8ca534edf872fc331304</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:35:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Osiajee Texfab Leads Market Rally with Exceptional 632% Return in One Year</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/osiajee-texfab-leads-market-rally-with-exceptional-632-return-in-one-year-3760225</link><description>Osiajee Texfab has delivered an extraordinary return of 632.19% over the past year, significantly outpacing benchmark indices and peers across various sectors. This remarkable performance places the micro-cap garment and apparel company at the forefront of market gainers, driven by a combination of bullish technical signals and solid financial fundamentals despite its premium valuation.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>f76c15c76ea04a7da46ae9e468e2aee3</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:35:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vedanta Hits Intraday High of Rs 571.5 with Strong Intraday Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vedanta-hits-intraday-high-with-329-surge-on-16-dec-2025-3760227</link><description>Vedanta recorded a robust intraday surge on 16 Dec 2025, touching a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs 571.5, reflecting a 3.91% rise during the trading session. This performance stands out amid a broader market decline, with the stock outperforming its sector and the Sensex index.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>db2f9fe6080f29f3c2f412e137d22ebd</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:35:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cupid Stock Hits All-Time High Amidst Remarkable Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cupid-stock-hits-all-time-high-marking-a-milestone-in-fmcg-sector-3760221</link><description>Cupid, a leading player in the FMCG sector, has reached an all-time high in its stock price, marking a significant milestone in its market journey. The stock’s recent performance reflects a sustained period of growth and resilience, positioning it prominently within its industry.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>bc971644384d9e82046f6f7dc9fa86bf</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:35:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:35:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>