<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:29:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Standard Enginnering Technology Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-standard-enginnering-technology-ltd-fallingrising-3819405</link><description>On 03-Feb, Standard Engineering Technology Ltd witnessed a significant intraday rally, with its share price rising by 7.22% to close at ₹121.80, outperforming both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c765e6b71a6ac7924fe8959a73280a80</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Mamata Machinery Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-mamata-machinery-ltd-fallingrising-3819404</link><description>On 03-Feb, Mamata Machinery Ltd witnessed a significant price rise of 11.46%, closing at ₹418.20, marking a notable rebound after two days of decline and outperforming its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7b227dfb56d76fd709aa46bce4c18208</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is EMA Partners India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ema-partners-india-ltd-fallingrising-3819403</link><description>On 03-Feb, EMA Partners India Ltd witnessed a significant price increase of 10.64%, closing at ₹91.00, driven by heightened investor participation and strong short-term momentum despite longer-term challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>206adaf0e0ca5d88574d6336cd12777c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sahasra Electronic Solutions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sahasra-electronic-solutions-ltd-fallingrising-3819401</link><description>On 03-Feb, Sahasra Electronic Solutions Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 6.37% to ₹274.05 by 09:20 PM. This upward movement reflects a significant shift in investor sentiment, supported by increased trading volumes and outperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6604220a7b6d9aa5b67660a16b3d13d9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Suraksha Diagnostic Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-suraksha-diagnostic-ltd-fallingrising-3819402</link><description>On 03-Feb, Suraksha Diagnostic Ltd’s stock surged by 5.89% to close at ₹286.00, significantly outperforming both its sector and the broader market benchmarks. This rise reflects a combination of robust trading volumes, favourable technical indicators, and underlying company fundamentals that have attracted increased investor participation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1962a22500b61e9bb90503a772bebb83</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Arkade Developers Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-arkade-developers-ltd-fallingrising-3819400</link><description>On 03-Feb, Arkade Developers Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 4.12% to close at ₹122.70. This upward movement comes despite the company’s challenging long-term performance and valuation concerns, reflecting a short-term rebound within a broader context of underperformance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>24c3a295636e55815aef904fd2f86225</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Rajputana Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-rajputana-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3819399</link><description>As of 03-Feb, Rajputana Industries Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 5.96% to ₹80.00. This upward movement reflects a combination of increased investor participation and robust underlying financial metrics, despite some challenges in recent quarterly results.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b8124b9f3ddd270134e27244a3bc908f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Gajanand International Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gajanand-international-ltd-fallingrising-3819398</link><description>On 03-Feb, Gajanand International Ltd's stock price rose by 6.04% to ₹9.65, marking a notable intraday gain despite a challenging longer-term performance and underwhelming technical indicators.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6bb01bbe99ad4e91fd8193fe45077dcd</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Kronox Lab Sciences Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-kronox-lab-sciences-ltd-fallingrising-3819397</link><description>On 03-Feb, Kronox Lab Sciences Ltd witnessed a notable intraday price increase of 4.61%, closing at ₹128.10, reflecting a positive shift in investor sentiment despite the stock’s longer-term underperformance relative to the benchmark Sensex.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ba6ff8366762ac698ebbf80b3e2897fd</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Italian Edibles Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-italian-edibles-ltd-fallingrising-3819396</link><description>On 03-Feb, Italian Edibles Ltd witnessed a significant price increase of 8.0%, closing at ₹28.35, reflecting a strong rebound driven by heightened investor participation and outperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>27cd656476e336edff45aa7df1593ca7</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Megatherm Induction Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-megatherm-induction-ltd-fallingrising-3819395</link><description>On 03-Feb, Megatherm Induction Ltd witnessed a significant price increase of 13.29%, closing at ₹225.05, reflecting a strong intraday rally despite its subdued longer-term returns.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f26207ac81c2a9f954f6369d194fad90</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Azad Engineering Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-azad-engineering-ltd-fallingrising-3819394</link><description>On 03-Feb, Azad Engineering Ltd witnessed a significant intraday surge of 5.91%, closing at ₹1,536.70, reflecting a notable recovery after two days of decline and outperforming its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b6a55266ec4cbf302a01f18e30b6c78b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vinyas Innovative Technologies Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vinyas-innovative-technologies-ltd-fallingrising-3819393</link><description>On 03-Feb, Vinyas Innovative Technologies Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing by 6.75% to close at ₹1,056.05. This surge stands out against a backdrop of mixed performance metrics and fluctuating investor participation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c2115645feacb9dd56353a254dcebe54</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-nuvama-wealth-management-ltd-fallingrising-3819392</link><description>On 03-Feb, Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd witnessed a significant rise in its share price, climbing 6.06% to close at ₹1,360.80. This upward movement reflects a combination of strong recent performance, sectoral momentum, and investor interest despite some underlying valuation concerns.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e312bbd4a4b2b1f32b7ade8c73a0d02c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Jio Financial Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-jio-financial-services-ltd-fallingrising-3819391</link><description>On 03-Feb, Jio Financial Services Ltd witnessed a significant price increase of 8.07%, closing at ₹263.95, reflecting a strong intraday performance despite some underlying financial challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5e365048e71101e6088fa87731f61fc3</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Mega Flex Plastics Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-mega-flex-plastics-ltd-fallingrising-3819390</link><description>On 03-Feb, Mega Flex Plastics Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 4.59% to ₹114.00 by 09:13 PM. This upward movement reflects a combination of strong technical positioning and increased investor participation, setting the stock apart from broader market trends.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>32e8e0353bb68c7eb54a14c179748e8c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Harsha Engineers International Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-harsha-engineers-international-ltd-fallingrising-3819388</link><description>On 03-Feb, Harsha Engineers International Ltd witnessed a significant price rise of 9.04%, closing at ₹401.65, driven by short-term market momentum despite underlying concerns over its long-term financial performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3a98e7da5f5b0808a53c88b8891d55a7</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is eMudhra Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-emudhra-ltd-fallingrising-3819389</link><description>As of 03-Feb, eMudhra Ltd's stock price rose sharply by 7.58% to ₹563.70, reflecting a notable outperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices. This upward movement follows a series of positive quarterly results and sustained long-term growth, despite some valuation concerns and recent underperformance against the broader market.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f33c2aca5b8401a900cd21f4cf0f40c2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Venus Pipes &amp; Tubes Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-venus-pipes-tubes-ltd-fallingrising-3819387</link><description>On 03-Feb, Venus Pipes &amp; Tubes Ltd witnessed a significant price rise of 9.23%, closing at ₹1,103.35, reflecting a notable rebound after two days of decline and outperforming its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2a876ae3d109339a6f28e24621ef4bb9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Acutaas Chemicals Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-acutaas-chemicals-ltd-fallingrising-3819386</link><description>On 03-Feb, Acutaas Chemicals Ltd's stock price rose by 1.26% to ₹1,960.05, continuing its impressive upward trajectory driven by robust financial performance and sustained market outperformance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f45f83d19774b8d9143ed3c40c6fc98c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 21:29:39 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>