<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 04:00:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is EMA Partners India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ema-partners-india-ltd-fallingrising-3790517</link><description>On 12-Jan, EMA Partners India Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.93% to close at ₹84.45. This drop reflects a broader trend of underperformance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices, compounded by technical indicators signalling bearish momentum.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>ab1b8ad3f437bf6022d08174707176e8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 04:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Unimech Aerospace and Manufacturing Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-unimech-aerospace-and-manufacturing-ltd-fallingrising-3790516</link><description>On 12-Jan, Unimech Aerospace and Manufacturing Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹860.25, down ₹29.00 or 3.26% from the previous session. This drop continues a sustained downward trajectory that has seen the stock underperform both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>b8c5911ddd6d82112991ab2e3bba75a9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 04:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Afcons Infrastructure Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-afcons-infrastructure-ltd-fallingrising-3790515</link><description>On 12-Jan, Afcons Infrastructure Ltd’s stock price fell sharply to ₹355.65, marking a 2.11% decline and hitting a new 52-week and all-time low of ₹354.35. This drop reflects a continuation of a downward trend driven by weak financial performance, poor debt servicing ability, and significant promoter share pledging, which have collectively weighed on investor sentiment.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>05cddcd76cc1bb599dea284ff61bdb8e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 04:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Arkade Developers Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-arkade-developers-ltd-fallingrising-3790514</link><description>On 12-Jan, Arkade Developers Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹127.75, down ₹2.25 or 1.73%. This drop reflects a continuation of a downward trend amid underwhelming returns and valuation pressures despite some operational strengths.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>a1802f277f3160cd2560fc390fcb71cd</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 04:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sahasra Electronic Solutions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sahasra-electronic-solutions-ltd-fallingrising-3790513</link><description>On 12-Jan, Sahasra Electronic Solutions Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.97% to close at ₹268.15. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock's underperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>526a5b10b710435c3d39e71f4816826e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 04:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sanofi-consumer-healthcare-india-ltd-fallingrising-3790512</link><description>On 12-Jan, Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 1.82% to ₹4,300.00. This drop reflects a continuation of a downward trend influenced by valuation pressures and sustained underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>febd11cf0b98433246be803140305d70</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 04:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sati Poly Plast Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sati-poly-plast-ltd-fallingrising-3790511</link><description>On 12-Jan, Sati Poly Plast Ltd’s stock price fell to a new 52-week and all-time low of ₹55.00, marking a decline of 3.17% for the day and continuing a significant downward trend that has persisted over the past year.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>2d9cd3cdee0a6cedfc64f39eeea2a1dc</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 04:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is GP Eco Solutions India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gp-eco-solutions-india-ltd-fallingrising-3790510</link><description>On 12-Jan, GP Eco Solutions India Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.6% to close at ₹393.15. This drop reflects a broader trend of underperformance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices, signalling investor caution despite the stock's strong longer-term gains.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>a2d768c7581b86e7e34d8dc4ae863070</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 04:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Kronox Lab Sciences Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-kronox-lab-sciences-ltd-fallingrising-3790509</link><description>As of 12-Jan, Kronox Lab Sciences Ltd’s stock price has continued its downward trajectory, reflecting a combination of disappointing returns, valuation pressures, and subdued growth prospects that have weighed heavily on investor sentiment.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>bd65e34363f8ff548fa0bad698edd158</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 04:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Harshdeep Hortico Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-harshdeep-hortico-ltd-fallingrising-3790508</link><description>On 12-Jan, Harshdeep Hortico Ltd’s stock price fell sharply by 4.8%, closing at ₹94.25, reflecting a notable short-term weakness despite its strong longer-term performance.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>90c0d8ee1648091ed52fa3dd90f0b2f0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 04:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Go Digit General Insurance Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-go-digit-general-insurance-ltd-fallingrising-3790507</link><description>As of 12-Jan, Go Digit General Insurance Ltd’s stock price has experienced a notable decline, falling 0.7% to ₹332.55 by 9:16 PM, continuing a downward trend over the past week despite the company’s robust long-term financial performance.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>14a9f6ad94c5d4fbee9b0b74f1a85554</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 04:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Megatherm Induction Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-megatherm-induction-ltd-fallingrising-3790506</link><description>On 12-Jan, Megatherm Induction Ltd's stock price fell by 1.6% to ₹205.60, marking a continuation of a prolonged downtrend that has seen the share price hit a new 52-week low of ₹197.55. The stock's underperformance relative to the broader market and its sector, combined with technical indicators and recent trading volumes, provide a clear explanation for the ongoing decline.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>f99e0960370813bf49e524182afec5f6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 04:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Nova Agritech Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-nova-agritech-ltd-fallingrising-3790505</link><description>On 12-Jan, Nova Agritech Ltd’s stock price fell sharply, closing at ₹36.41, down ₹1.61 or 4.23%, marking a new 52-week and all-time low of ₹36.3 during intraday trading. This decline reflects ongoing challenges in the company’s financial performance and investor sentiment.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>e49c5a8878d27fc986cb26471583c967</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 04:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Electro Force (India) Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-electro-force-india-ltd-fallingrising-3790504</link><description>On 12-Jan, Electro Force (India) Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, closing at ₹30.85, down ₹1.85 or 5.66% from the previous close. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock's underperformance relative to broader market benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>9a3e46043ca470275ab6ba30ac9f3a43</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 04:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Azad Engineering Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-azad-engineering-ltd-fallingrising-3790503</link><description>As of 12-Jan, Azad Engineering Ltd’s stock price has been on a downward trajectory, reflecting a combination of valuation pressures and sustained underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>dab40cce0518578cea742d1fd4608895</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 04:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Gayatri Rubbers and Chemicals Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gayatri-rubbers-and-chemicals-ltd-fallingrising-3790502</link><description>On 12-Jan, shares of Gayatri Rubbers and Chemicals Ltd fell by 1.1% to close at ₹358.00, continuing a downward trend that has persisted over recent weeks and months, reflecting broader challenges faced by the stock relative to market benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>bcb38f57b0259f84df710d4fff1c148e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 04:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is AGS Transact Technologies Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ags-transact-technologies-ltd-fallingrising-3790501</link><description>As of 12-Jan, AGS Transact Technologies Ltd has experienced a notable decline in its share price, continuing a sustained downtrend that starkly contrasts with broader market gains and sector performance.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>8cfde6caef8374e65f981caf40691a79</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 04:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is DDev Plastiks Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ddev-plastiks-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3790500</link><description>On 12-Jan, shares of DDev Plastiks Industries Ltd fell sharply by 3.93% to close at ₹285.95, continuing a three-day losing streak amid subdued investor participation and underperformance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>5ec28ce296486b7216db0d600e2ac84f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 04:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Venus Pipes &amp; Tubes Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-venus-pipes-tubes-ltd-fallingrising-3790499</link><description>On 12-Jan, Venus Pipes &amp; Tubes Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 3.38% to close at ₹1,109.90. This drop reflects a continuation of recent negative momentum, with the stock underperforming both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>37ae2154c788fafc5473e19c7cb54865</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 04:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Suvidhaa Infoserve Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-suvidhaa-infoserve-ltd-fallingrising-3790498</link><description>As of 12-Jan, Suvidhaa Infoserve Ltd’s stock price has continued its downward trajectory, reflecting persistent challenges in both its financial health and market performance. The share price closed at ₹3.45, down by 2.27%, underscoring investor concerns amid weak fundamentals and sustained underperformance relative to benchmarks.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>b64c3443990303464f374fffb444a70c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 04:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 04:00:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>