<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:29:35 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Virtual Galaxy Infotech Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-virtual-galaxy-infotech-ltd-fallingrising-3810443</link><description>On 29-Jan, Virtual Galaxy Infotech Ltd's stock price rose by 1.86% to ₹142.15, outperforming both its sector and the broader market despite recent downward trends over longer periods.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>9b50d227eb0f9e6158563b34c8596b6d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:29:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Chamunda Electrical Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-chamunda-electrical-ltd-fallingrising-3810442</link><description>On 29-Jan, Chamunda Electrical Ltd's stock price surged by 4.67% to ₹48.15, outperforming both its sector and the broader market despite recent underperformance over longer periods.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>e69bf272aff7cb668c5c83af5fabdd36</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:29:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ken Enterprises Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ken-enterprises-ltd-fallingrising-3810441</link><description>On 29-Jan, Ken Enterprises Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹39.05, down ₹0.95 or 2.38% from the previous session. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s underperformance relative to key market benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>868d205fee55296f7f22677f6984310a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:29:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Rajputana Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-rajputana-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3810440</link><description>On 29-Jan, Rajputana Industries Ltd witnessed a significant price increase of 11.41%, closing at ₹82.50, driven by heightened investor participation and solid underlying financial metrics.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>8b1266b7ba13843b19c4144426d31421</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:29:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is ITC Hotels Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-itc-hotels-ltd-fallingrising-3810439</link><description>On 29-Jan, ITC Hotels Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹177.85, down ₹3.20 or 1.77% from the previous close, reflecting a continuation of underperformance relative to the broader market and its sector peers.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>bf5243ddeadfd7ab1cd64493a03a3dbe</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:29:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Entero Healthcare Solutions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-entero-healthcare-solutions-ltd-fallingrising-3810438</link><description>On 29-Jan, Entero Healthcare Solutions Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, falling by 1.79% to close at ₹1,102.55. This drop comes despite the company’s strong underlying fundamentals and positive long-term growth indicators, reflecting a complex interplay of market dynamics and investor sentiment.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>900879cc47cdb93347aff512b93e5fac</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:29:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Italian Edibles Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-italian-edibles-ltd-fallingrising-3810437</link><description>On 29-Jan, Italian Edibles Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling 5.12% to close at ₹24.10, marking a fresh 52-week and all-time low of ₹24.05 during the trading session. This downturn reflects a broader pattern of underperformance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>b780c1dabbab1d8ef7d4d7846725d807</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:29:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Nova Agritech Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-nova-agritech-ltd-fallingrising-3810436</link><description>On 29-Jan, Nova Agritech Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹32.25, down ₹1.05 or 3.15% from the previous session. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock's underperformance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>ee92ad6a427fc1a10b0d1ffc6611d7a3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:29:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Epack Durable Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-epack-durable-ltd-fallingrising-3810435</link><description>On 29-Jan, Epack Durable Ltd’s stock price fell by 2.08% to ₹221.20, continuing a prolonged downtrend driven by weak financial performance, deteriorating fundamentals, and declining investor confidence.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>4c9ee3e219532b332400b6a9d4073504</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:29:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Gayatri Rubbers and Chemicals Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gayatri-rubbers-and-chemicals-ltd-fallingrising-3810434</link><description>On 29-Jan, Gayatri Rubbers and Chemicals Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 4.87% to ₹355.20 by 9:11 PM, outperforming its sector and the broader market indices despite a challenging longer-term performance record.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>826b666fe56090e31d36783a01344cdf</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:29:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Medplus Health Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-medplus-health-services-ltd-fallingrising-3810433</link><description>On 29-Jan, Medplus Health Services Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 1.97% to close at ₹772.20. This drop reflects a combination of short-term market pressures and underlying fundamental concerns despite the company’s recent operational strengths.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>ce9c092ee4cb1ec50f55263fa868dd6e</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:29:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Suvidhaa Infoserve Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-suvidhaa-infoserve-ltd-fallingrising-3810432</link><description>On 29-Jan, Suvidhaa Infoserve Ltd’s stock price fell sharply by 12.73% to ₹2.81, hitting a new 52-week and all-time low of ₹2.7. This decline reflects a continuation of the company’s prolonged underperformance relative to market benchmarks and persistent fundamental weaknesses.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>60a1ca6765ed2d45783656cfc2e992ea</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:29:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vijaya Diagnostic Centre Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vijaya-diagnostic-centre-ltd-fallingrising-3810431</link><description>As of 29-Jan, Vijaya Diagnostic Centre Ltd’s share price has declined to ₹940, reflecting a 1.61% drop on the day and continuing a downward trend over recent weeks. This fall is underpinned by a combination of valuation pressures, underwhelming recent financial performance, and relative underperformance against market benchmarks.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>22266994e76b89ad62332f1e11060776</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:29:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shyam Metalics &amp; Energy Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shyam-metalics-energy-ltd-fallingrising-3810430</link><description>On 29-Jan, Shyam Metalics &amp; Energy Ltd's stock surged by 4.26% to close at ₹871.00, continuing a three-day rally that has seen an 11.87% gain. This rise comes despite some concerning financial indicators, reflecting a complex interplay of strong market performance and underlying operational challenges.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>eef891738d053656562abc1f2886e769</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:29:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Apt Packaging Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-apt-packaging-ltd-fallingrising-3810429</link><description>Apt Packaging Ltd’s stock price has fallen by 2.04% to ₹96.00, reflecting a notable short-term decline despite the company’s impressive long-term performance relative to the broader market.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>f609d4ce2a9f94b651949e2dd330ac82</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:29:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vinny Overseas Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vinny-overseas-ltd-fallingrising-3810428</link><description>As of 29-Jan, Vinny Overseas Ltd’s stock price has fallen sharply, hitting a new 52-week and all-time low of ₹1.01. The share price declined by 5.13% on the day, reflecting ongoing challenges in the company’s financial health and persistent underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>f2f59bf72979f34481008480ee8fb5fb</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:29:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Solex Energy Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-solex-energy-ltd-fallingrising-3810427</link><description>On 29-Jan, Solex Energy Ltd witnessed a significant drop in its share price, falling by 4.07% to close at ₹963.80. This decline reflects a broader pattern of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and diminished investor participation.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>04490aa15930ce12a03103718fcfef05</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:29:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shanti Educational Initiatives Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shanti-educational-initiatives-ltd-fallingrising-3810426</link><description>On 29-Jan, Shanti Educational Initiatives Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 6.71% to close at ₹137.00. This drop reflects a continuation of recent downward momentum amid broader sector weakness and heightened intraday volatility.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>b2d959416b475d5161f0cd3282924ce5</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:29:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shree Tirupati Balajee FIBC Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shree-tirupati-balajee-fibc-ltd-fallingrising-3810425</link><description>On 29-Jan, Shree Tirupati Balajee FIBC Ltd experienced a notable decline in its share price, falling by 5.0% to close at ₹613.70. This drop reflects a broader pattern of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and diminished investor participation.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>d6b28f6ecb7bc2a176b3a61a468eed70</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:29:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Lexus Granito (India) Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-lexus-granito-india-ltd-fallingrising-3810424</link><description>On 29-Jan, Lexus Granito (India) Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹24.77, down ₹0.59 or 2.33% from the previous session. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s underperformance relative to broader market indices and sector peers, driven by persistent fundamental weaknesses and subdued investor sentiment.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>03fc989ecb10da20928cde2442f13b9c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:29:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:29:35 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>