<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:30:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Jana Small Finance Bank Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jana-small-finance-bank-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3807902</link><description>Jana Small Finance Bank Ltd has recorded a new all-time low, closing just 0.15% above its 52-week low of ₹363.5 on 28 Jan 2026, reflecting sustained pressure on the stock amid a challenging market environment and subdued financial performance.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>689da90ea14853e81be196d04f0d1e9b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adtech Systems Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adtech-systems-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3807898</link><description>Adtech Systems Ltd, a player in the Industrial Manufacturing sector, has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.52.7 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid ongoing market pressures and company-specific factors.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>92dc7f465706b1f095569bf708e229db</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TruCap Finance Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.6.61 Amid Continued Financial Struggles</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/trucap-finance-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs661-amid-continued-financial-struggles-3807901</link><description>TruCap Finance Ltd, a Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC), touched a new 52-week and all-time low of Rs.6.61 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid ongoing financial pressures and subdued market performance.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>6ffa01ec4ccebe31f29cf386463e427f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Patanjali Foods Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.492.65</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/patanjali-foods-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs49265-3807899</link><description>Patanjali Foods Ltd, a key player in the edible oil sector, recorded a new 52-week low of Rs.492.65 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid broader market movements. The stock has underperformed its sector and major indices, reflecting ongoing pressures and valuation concerns.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>00c592ba792d0b3e26474e693b158919</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mishra Dhatu Nigam Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.12% Surge on 28 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mishra-dhatu-nigam-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-712-surge-on-28-jan-2026-3807900</link><description>Mishra Dhatu Nigam Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 28 Jan 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 362.3, marking a 7.09% increase. The stock outpaced its sector and broader market indices, reflecting strong trading momentum throughout the session.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>dfa5ac90cce2b4b1360d8a2079582b24</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Orient Green Power Company Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.41% Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/orient-green-power-company-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-741-surge-3807896</link><description>Orient Green Power Company Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 28 Jan 2026, surging 7.41% to hit its day high, significantly outperforming the broader Sensex and its sector peers in the power industry.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>ae36c73fe3971e08217223c16a47561d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DCW Ltd Hits Intraday High with Strong 7.1% Surge on 28 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dcw-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-strong-71-surge-on-28-jan-2026-3807891</link><description>DCW Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 28 Jan 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 47.41, marking an 8.91% increase from its previous close. The stock outperformed the broader Sensex and its sector peers, reflecting notable trading momentum within the petrochemicals industry.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>71f86f2b73231d84b7d76a2d013b9999</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Radico Khaitan Ltd. Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 28 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/radico-khaitan-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-28-jan-2026-3807893</link><description>Radico Khaitan Ltd. experienced a notable decline today, touching an intraday low of Rs 2,761.65, reflecting a sharp price pressure of -5.49% during the trading session. This downturn comes amid broader market dynamics and sector-specific challenges, with the stock underperforming its beverages sector peers and the benchmark Sensex.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>d4ea34afec31787601d13bbbf557bc12</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vimta Labs Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 28 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vimta-labs-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-28-jan-2026-3807894</link><description>Shares of Vimta Labs Ltd declined sharply on 28 Jan 2026, hitting their intraday low as the stock faced significant price pressure despite a broadly positive market backdrop. The healthcare services company’s stock fell by 7.75%, underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.23% on the day.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>90d075edaf1c4f308b3a99be9577a201</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indo Tech Transformers Ltd Hits Intraday High with 8.06% Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indo-tech-transformers-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-806-surge-3807897</link><description>Indo Tech Transformers Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 28 Jan 2026, surging 8.06% to touch a day’s high of ₹1,225, significantly outperforming the Sensex and its sector peers in Heavy Electrical Equipment.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>84ec9d503468307a041d1aad145583e7</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dolat Algotech Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.0% Surge on 28 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dolat-algotech-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-70-surge-on-28-jan-2026-3807895</link><description>Dolat Algotech Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 28 Jan 2026, surging 7.0% to touch a day’s high of Rs 85.1. This marked a significant rebound following two consecutive days of decline, with the stock outperforming its sector and the broader market indices.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>59442a90d324bfc2466bd85bb1e43b62</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shree Karthik Papers Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shree-karthik-papers-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3807890</link><description>Shree Karthik Papers Ltd has touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.6.35 today, marking a significant decline in its share price amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing pressures on the company’s financial and operational metrics.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>99930af7269f4f14fe1460aadb93c959</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KNR Constructions Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.29% Surge on 28 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/knr-constructions-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-729-surge-on-28-jan-2026-3807892</link><description>KNR Constructions Ltd demonstrated robust intraday momentum on 28 Jan 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 143.6, marking a 6.77% rise from its previous close. The stock outperformed its sector and the broader market, reflecting significant trading activity and renewed focus within the construction industry.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>153035c73b60c6f7d0c8fd51621e513d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kush Industries Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.6.21</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kush-industries-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs621-3807888</link><description>Kush Industries Ltd, a player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.6.21 today, marking a significant decline amid ongoing downward momentum. The stock’s recent performance highlights persistent challenges reflected in its valuation and financial metrics.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>78f092e93bf8f1b3f33f125227c72985</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Electronics Ltd Hits New 52-Week High of Rs.454.5 on 28 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-electronics-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-of-rs4545-on-28-jan-2026-3807889</link><description>Bharat Electronics Ltd (BEL) surged to a fresh 52-week and all-time high of Rs.454.5 on 28 Jan 2026, marking a significant milestone in its stock performance. The aerospace and defence company demonstrated robust momentum, outperforming its sector and continuing a strong upward trajectory over recent sessions.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>80c9d10c6ca947144b98ebc68cf58e30</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hitachi Energy India Ltd Surges to Intraday High with 5.05% Gain</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hitachi-energy-india-ltd-surges-to-intraday-high-with-505-gain-3807884</link><description>Hitachi Energy India Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 28 Jan 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 17,527.95, marking a 4.92% increase. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting strong trading momentum within the Heavy Electrical Equipment industry.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>52541c235dc448b677a89fb68f92d1ea</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd Hits Intraday High with 5.03% Surge on 28 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rail-vikas-nigam-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-503-surge-on-28-jan-2026-3807883</link><description>Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 28 Jan 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 340.8, marking a 5.22% increase. This strong uptick outpaced the broader construction sector and reflected a notable rebound after two consecutive days of decline.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>689b45bd12967ed2b3e08a6b27b85f50</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Dynamics Ltd Hits Intraday High with 5.28% Surge on 28 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-dynamics-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-528-surge-on-28-jan-2026-3807885</link><description>Bharat Dynamics Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 28 Jan 2026, surging 5.28% to touch a day’s high of Rs 1,546.4, outperforming its sector and broader market indices amid positive trading momentum.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>1fba27879b49619b74e061550b3f5638</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Metals &amp; Ferro Alloys Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.09% Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indian-metals-ferro-alloys-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-709-surge-3807886</link><description>Indian Metals &amp; Ferro Alloys Ltd demonstrated robust intraday strength on 28 Jan 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 1,225, marking a 7.97% increase from its previous close. This performance outpaced the broader Sensex, which recorded a modest gain of 0.14% during the session.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>34fcaa38778a37dedf5bb0a15e9fa89d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bansal Wire Industries Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.09% Surge on 28 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bansal-wire-industries-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-709-surge-on-28-jan-2026-3807881</link><description>Bansal Wire Industries Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 28 Jan 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 275, marking a 7.4% increase. This notable uptick outpaced the broader Iron &amp; Steel Products sector and reversed a six-day downward trend for the stock.
Time: 42 minutes ago</description><guid>a627ad91c08490b0910e2c79210ce693</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:30:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>