<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:46:50 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is GP Eco Solutions India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gp-eco-solutions-india-ltd-fallingrising-3817006</link><description>On 02-Feb, GP Eco Solutions India Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, falling by 1.67% to close at ₹315.40. This drop reflects ongoing short-term underperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>9d8848abd7c6f37942c1ad6708b7f8e8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is GHCL Textiles Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ghcl-textiles-ltd-fallingrising-3817005</link><description>As of 02-Feb, GHCL Textiles Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.41% to close at ₹72.80. This drop reflects a continuation of recent negative trends driven by subdued investor participation, underwhelming returns, and concerns over management efficiency despite some positive operational metrics.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>c590215ad3e44b0f4a832a572a8e4b85</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Maks Energy Solutions India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-maks-energy-solutions-india-ltd-fallingrising-3817004</link><description>On 02-Feb, Maks Energy Solutions India Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 4.92% to close at ₹28.05. This drop reflects a broader trend of underperformance relative to key market benchmarks and sector peers, highlighting challenges faced by the stock in recent trading sessions.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>d726d70be14024411caf17db9cbc877c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Campus Activewear Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-campus-activewear-ltd-fallingrising-3817003</link><description>On 02-Feb, Campus Activewear Ltd witnessed a significant price increase of 5.81%, closing at ₹269.60, driven by robust quarterly performance and sustained positive momentum despite longer-term challenges.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>d900b6f89546d0c266617e8e20ae6b54</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vinny Overseas Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vinny-overseas-ltd-fallingrising-3817002</link><description>On 02-Feb, Vinny Overseas Ltd's stock price continued its downward trajectory, closing at ₹1.02, down 1.92% from the previous session. This decline reflects a sustained period of underperformance relative to both its sector and broader market benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>3cd3c7e9223da4a0b29a313d0887d774</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Goldkart Jewels Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-goldkart-jewels-ltd-fallingrising-3817001</link><description>On 02-Feb, Goldkart Jewels Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 8.36% to close at ₹252.00. This drop comes amid a backdrop of exceptional long-term performance, highlighting a complex market dynamic for the stock.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>e5d7aa3a3b123288d9349daf1a700ec0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Marine Electricals (India) Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-marine-electricals-india-ltd-fallingrising-3817000</link><description>As of 02-Feb, Marine Electricals (India) Ltd's stock price rose by 1.29% to ₹186.37, reflecting a short-term rebound despite longer-term underperformance relative to the broader market and sector benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>43fa95f1da0242a6ebdb818db34de445</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-orissa-bengal-carrier-ltd-fallingrising-3816999</link><description>On 02-Feb, Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd witnessed a significant price increase of 9.14%, closing at ₹59.00. This rise comes despite several indicators suggesting caution, reflecting a complex market dynamic for the stock.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>2911cd6c26b07c720e0d563325d97e5e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is M K Proteins Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-m-k-proteins-ltd-fallingrising-3816998</link><description>On 02-Feb, M K Proteins Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, closing at ₹5.03, down 4.91% from the previous session. This drop reflects a continuation of a broader downward trend driven by disappointing financial results and subdued investor sentiment.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>144ab0bc77ebfebce6f804e0c80e470d</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shree Tirupati Balajee FIBC Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shree-tirupati-balajee-fibc-ltd-fallingrising-3816997</link><description>On 02-Feb, Shree Tirupati Balajee FIBC Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 4.13% to close at ₹531.00. This drop reflects a broader trend of underperformance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices, compounded by weakening investor participation and technical indicators signalling bearish momentum.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>df97b6c318c0ccf18fac04ce821e1cd4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Archidply Decor Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-archidply-decor-ltd-fallingrising-3816996</link><description>On 02-Feb, Archidply Decor Ltd’s stock price fell sharply by 6.41% to ₹70.05, reflecting a continuation of its recent underperformance relative to market benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>c1d4f07c49e8f9a384f10b0782929a18</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Rander Corporation Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-rander-corporation-ltd-fallingrising-3816995</link><description>On 02-Feb, Rander Corporation Ltd’s stock price rose by 1.84% to ₹11.61, outperforming both its sector and the broader market benchmarks despite some signs of weakening investor participation.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>29a79e0b1a739177af20215d40c4075f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Housing Development &amp; Infrastructure Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-housing-development-infrastructure-ltd-fallingrising-3816994</link><description>On 02-Feb, Housing Development &amp; Infrastructure Ltd recorded a notable intraday price increase of 4.81%, closing at ₹2.18. This rise comes despite the company’s prolonged underperformance against market benchmarks and ongoing fundamental weaknesses.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>fe7c2eddab90024da033067323a1af65</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Apar Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-apar-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3816993</link><description>On 02-Feb, Apar Industries Ltd saw its share price rise by 1.16% to ₹8,156.45, continuing a notable upward trend driven by robust long-term fundamentals and consistent quarterly performance.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>871e1158630870c20823833915ed206e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is CSB Bank Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-csb-bank-ltd-fallingrising-3816992</link><description>On 02-Feb, CSB Bank Ltd's shares fell by 1.72% to close at ₹411.00, continuing a recent downward trend despite the bank's robust financial performance and strong capital position.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>3f80a1e39afa747df290704b77589ae9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Anand Rayons Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-anand-rayons-ltd-fallingrising-3816991</link><description>On 02-Feb, Anand Rayons Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, closing at ₹298.05, down by ₹15.65 or 4.99% from the previous close. This drop continues a recent pattern of underperformance against both its sector and broader market benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>779a9af7b87ec3d8832bce10e7b01442</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Parin Enterprises Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-parin-enterprises-ltd-fallingrising-3816990</link><description>On 02-Feb, Parin Enterprises Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, closing at ₹659.00, up ₹21.00 or 3.29% from the previous session. This upward movement reflects a continuation of the stock’s robust performance relative to broader market benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>9e18a73cbb906ff54f31e640b15bf1ba</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Dhruv Consultancy Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-dhruv-consultancy-services-ltd-fallingrising-3816989</link><description>As of 02-Feb, Dhruv Consultancy Services Ltd’s stock price has fallen sharply, reflecting a combination of weak financial performance, declining investor confidence, and sustained underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>c9e22c87615b406a4d4453c6cfbb2015</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Manorama Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-manorama-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3816988</link><description>On 02-Feb, Manorama Industries Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 4.72% to close at ₹1,301.65. This drop comes amid a mixed backdrop of strong long-term performance and short-term sector weakness.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>5e429f7952b4651ed4f3af08eb8e8738</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is IRIS Regtech Solutions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-iris-regtech-solutions-ltd-fallingrising-3816987</link><description>As of 02-Feb, IRIS Regtech Solutions Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling 5.18% to close at ₹283.00. This drop reflects a broader trend of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and growing investor caution despite the company’s strong operational metrics.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>6a0eef3543496bf2db466adae2ff82f7</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:46:50 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>