<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:38:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>KPIT Technologies Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kpit-technologies-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-price-action-3837747</link><description>KPIT Technologies Ltd has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, coinciding with a pronounced decline in its share price. This unusual combination of rising open interest and falling prices suggests a shift in market positioning, with investors possibly taking fresh bearish bets or hedging existing exposures amid heightened volatility.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>421b18a35665285a202f213a63f0effe</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:38:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alkem Laboratories Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Volatile Trading</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/alkem-laboratories-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-volatile-trading-3837749</link><description>Alkem Laboratories Ltd witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment on 13 Feb 2026, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite the stock’s underperformance and elevated volatility, the sharp increase in open interest suggests that traders are actively recalibrating their directional bets amid a challenging market backdrop.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>9ade2a89782e6d8a69699475bb40197d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:38:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blue Jet Healthcare Ltd Plunges to Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/blue-jet-healthcare-ltd-plunges-to-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3837744</link><description>Blue Jet Healthcare Ltd, a small-cap player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, witnessed intense selling pressure on 13 Feb 2026, hitting its lower circuit limit and closing near its 52-week low. The stock plunged by nearly 10%, underperforming both its sector and the broader market, as panic selling and unfilled supply overwhelmed investor sentiment.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>83df52df57f046fa8c046da5e0c6b4ea</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:38:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Info Edge Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amidst Weak Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/info-edge-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amidst-weak-price-action-3837742</link><description>Info Edge (India) Ltd, a key player in the E-Retail and E-Commerce sector, has witnessed a notable 12.65% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock hitting a fresh 52-week low of ₹1,104.2. This development comes amid a three-day consecutive decline in the stock price, raising questions about market positioning and potential directional bets by investors.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>0a4e4c405d01db37471494f89a0587f9</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:38:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prestige Estates Projects Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/prestige-estates-projects-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-market-signals-3837748</link><description>Prestige Estates Projects Ltd (PRESTIGE) has witnessed a significant 15.3% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this spike, the stock has underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting cautious sentiment amid recent price declines and increased volatility.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>205988ccfb646cd6c233eebd8406426f</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:38:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eicher Motors Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eicher-motors-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-market-momentum-3837743</link><description>Eicher Motors Ltd (EICHERMOT) has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, coinciding with robust price gains and heightened investor participation. The stock hit a fresh 52-week high of ₹8,119 on 13 Feb 2026, reflecting strong bullish sentiment and a potential directional shift in market positioning.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>f09d80cbd3adb75cb5a5f4d931baaa6f</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:38:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dec-2025 Quarterly Earnings Reveal Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/dec-2025-quarterly-earnings-reveal-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3837731</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has revealed a nuanced picture across Indian equities, with 3,057 companies reporting results. While the overall proportion of positive earnings surprises has improved modestly to 47.0%, sectoral and market-capitalisation-based disparities remain evident, reflecting varied economic dynamics and company-specific factors.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>464a4d04bf335b3f1173d8f2e5ca9c50</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:38:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Surge in Open Interest Signals Renewed Optimism in Torrent Pharmaceuticals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/surge-in-open-interest-signals-renewed-optimism-in-torrent-pharmaceuticals-3837746</link><description>Torrent Pharmaceuticals Ltd. has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, reflecting heightened market participation and a potential shift in investor sentiment. The stock recently hit a new 52-week and all-time high of ₹4,130, supported by robust volume and positive price action, signalling renewed confidence in the large-cap pharmaceutical player.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>094ade19fb2a4880855d4950a52e5750</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:38:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Silver Touch Technologies Ltd Plunges to Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/silver-touch-technologies-ltd-plunges-to-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3837745</link><description>Silver Touch Technologies Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, witnessed a sharp decline on 13 Feb 2026, hitting its lower circuit limit amid intense selling pressure. The stock closed at ₹1,270.4, down 5.0% from the previous close, marking its maximum daily loss and signalling panic selling among investors.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>9bdad75cc26194f544d758fa1a8346e9</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:38:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Best Agrolife Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/best-agrolife-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-robust-buying-pressure-3837739</link><description>Shares of Best Agrolife Ltd surged to hit the upper circuit price limit on 13 Feb 2026, reflecting robust buying interest despite a broader market downturn. The stock's maximum daily gain was capped by regulatory limits, underscoring intense demand and a supply squeeze in this micro-cap player within the Pesticides &amp; Agrochemicals sector.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>e2eecc583c7ead151274b6d684314aff</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:38:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Persistent Systems Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/persistent-systems-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-price-action-3837737</link><description>Persistent Systems Ltd (PERSISTENT) witnessed a notable 10.05% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment on 13 Feb 2026, signalling heightened market activity and shifting positioning among traders. Despite opening sharply lower and trading below key moving averages, the stock outperformed its sector, reflecting a complex interplay of investor sentiment and strategic bets in the software and consulting space.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>64e10ca0bf1205c721edaa181bc1bc05</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:38:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sensex Drops Over 900 Points as Market Breadth Weakens; Metals and Financials Lead Declines</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-drops-over-900-points-as-market-breadth-weakens-metals-and-financials-lead-declines-3837733</link><description>Indian equity markets witnessed a broad-based sell-off on 13 Feb 2026, with the Sensex closing 908.10 points lower at 82,766.82, down 1.09%. The Nifty50 mirrored this weakness, dragged down by losses in metals, finance, and power stocks, while market breadth remained severely negative amid subdued investor sentiment and cautious global cues.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>4bb038d6efb222e91ac57c9df17f88b9</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:38:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reliance Industries Ltd Sees High-Value Trading Amid Sector Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/reliance-industries-ltd-sees-high-value-trading-amid-sector-weakness-3837741</link><description>Reliance Industries Ltd (RELIANCE), a dominant player in the Indian oil sector, witnessed significant trading activity on 13 Feb 2026, with a total traded value exceeding ₹1028 crores. Despite this high liquidity and investor interest, the stock experienced a modest decline, reflecting broader sectoral pressures and cautious market sentiment.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>356cefc17205ad150225a696e05b361c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:38:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Palred Technologies Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/palred-technologies-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3837740</link><description>Palred Technologies Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, surged to hit its upper circuit price limit on 13 Feb 2026, propelled by robust buying interest and sustained investor enthusiasm. The stock closed at ₹43.76, marking a maximum daily gain of 4.46%, underscoring a notable outperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>2c76d853c98bf23c4503b4ddad9f4c48</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:38:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coforge Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amidst Weak Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/coforge-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amidst-weak-price-action-3837738</link><description>Coforge Ltd, a mid-cap player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has witnessed a significant 17.35% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, even as the stock price continues to decline. This divergence between rising open interest and falling prices signals heightened market activity and evolving positioning among traders, raising questions about potential directional bets and future price movements.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>a3ccc2b13f852f69bcfc1351335cb686</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:38:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Centenial Surgical Suture Ltd Reports Positive Financial Turnaround in Q4 2025</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/centenial-surgical-suture-ltd-reports-positive-financial-turnaround-in-q4-2025-3837736</link><description>Centenial Surgical Suture Ltd has demonstrated a notable turnaround in its financial performance for the quarter ended December 2025, shifting from a flat to a positive growth trajectory. Despite lingering challenges in return metrics, the company’s latest quarterly results reveal encouraging signs of revenue expansion and profitability improvements, positioning it cautiously ahead in the competitive healthcare services sector.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>cb3c9624916514e4e2e8d90199e01493</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:38:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mid-Cap Segment Sees Broad Weakness as BSE Midcap Index Declines 0.61%</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/mid-cap-segment-sees-broad-weakness-as-bse-midcap-index-declines-061-3837730</link><description>The BSE Midcap index declined by 0.61% on 13 Feb 2026, reflecting a cautious market mood as sectoral disparities and stock-specific movements shaped the segment’s overall performance. While select stocks like Linde India delivered robust returns, others such as Muthoot Finance faced significant headwinds, underscoring the varied fortunes within the mid-cap universe.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>f0462c1ffe4af56eeff656417a67ad49</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:38:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Large-Cap Segment Faces Broad Sell-Off as Defensive Stocks Outperform</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/large-cap-segment-faces-broad-sell-off-as-defensive-stocks-outperform-3837729</link><description>The large-cap segment, represented by the BSE 100 index, has experienced a notable downturn, declining by 1.11% on the day and 1.32% over the past five sessions. This broad-based weakness was marked by a stark advance-decline ratio of 12 advancing stocks against 88 decliners, underscoring the prevailing bearish sentiment. While Bajaj Finance emerged as the best performer with a 2.01% gain, Adani Power lagged significantly, falling 6.24%, highlighting the divergent fortunes within the segment.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>e5527941bc9c6f0664b90f3981975dce</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:38:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Small-Cap Segment Sees Broad Weakness Amid Select Bright Spots on 13 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/small-cap-segment-sees-broad-weakness-amid-select-bright-spots-on-13-feb-2026-3837732</link><description>The BSE Smallcap index experienced a modest decline of 0.63% on 13 Feb 2026, reflecting a challenging trading session marked by sectoral disparities and weak market breadth. While select stocks such as GE Power delivered robust returns nearing 20%, the broader small-cap universe struggled with a significant number of decliners, underscoring the cautious investor sentiment prevailing in this segment.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>1e0ae2540156c2c4455e81d07d120c23</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:38:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Asian Hotels (North) Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.258 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/asian-hotels-north-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs258-amidst-continued-downtrend-3837723</link><description>Asian Hotels (North) Ltd has touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.258 on 13 Feb 2026, marking a significant decline amid persistent downward momentum. The stock’s recent performance reflects ongoing pressures within the Hotels &amp; Resorts sector, with the share price falling sharply over the past two sessions.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>3ec31da83a3d2c765078f6ed6e9e5425</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:38:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:38:56 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>