<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 12:31:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Maruti Suzuki India Ltd is Rated Buy</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/maruti-suzuki-india-ltd-is-rated-buy-3772231</link><description>Maruti Suzuki India Ltd is rated Buy by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 22 December 2025. While the rating was revised on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 28 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market standing.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>6766284f331af37a1b27917af3bbd158</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 12:31:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Medplus Health Services Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/medplus-health-services-ltd-is-rated-hold-3772230</link><description>Medplus Health Services Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 22 December 2025. While the rating change occurred on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 28 December 2025, providing investors with the most up-to-date view of the stock’s fundamentals, returns, and technical outlook.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>e4de7a984e673ab7f98eb48d0e4ea901</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 12:31:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sbi-life-insurance-company-ltd-is-rated-hold-3772229</link><description>SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 30 July 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 28 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>c4e7babb27874a32b945b30122e321ba</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 12:31:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Overseas Bank is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/indian-overseas-bank-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3772227</link><description>Indian Overseas Bank is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 04 Aug 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 28 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the bank's performance and outlook.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>db13e21155b09ce02c2a060b1a6a8ed3</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 12:31:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 12:31:25 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>