<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 04:50:42 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Carysil Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/carysil-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3840807</link><description>Carysil Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 04 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock's current position as of 15 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>4fd6b56c36c70d9e2b205de540045220</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 04:50:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ginni Filaments Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ginni-filaments-ltd-is-rated-sell-3840803</link><description>Ginni Filaments Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 03 February 2026. While the rating was revised on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 15 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>56b8a0d206d3c941ad00dc9f97208f1e</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 04:50:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Commercial Syn Bags Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/commercial-syn-bags-ltd-is-rated-hold-3840804</link><description>Commercial Syn Bags Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, a rating that was last updated on 07 April 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 15 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of its fundamentals, returns, and market standing.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>d28a34e04dea246e1dab7f13d33dd094</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 04:50:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Investment Trust of India Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/the-investment-trust-of-india-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3840802</link><description>The Investment Trust of India Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 31 July 2025, reflecting a reassessment of the stock’s outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed below are current as of 15 February 2026, providing an up-to-date view of the company’s position in the market.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>ddcead33349121764e17de8537736507</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 04:50:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DIC India Ltd is Rated Sell by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/dic-india-ltd-is-rated-sell-by-marketsmojo-3840801</link><description>DIC India Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 27 May 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 15 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>426b25669102134236de1c416f59d2d3</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 04:50:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Abbott India Ltd. is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/abbott-india-ltd-is-rated-sell-3840798</link><description>Abbott India Ltd. is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 12 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 15 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>a7cb2879164b0b6b9cf69849e4023eb7</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 04:50:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summit Securities Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/summit-securities-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3840800</link><description>Summit Securities Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 13 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 15 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>00021b4e396c1cd58b3bc6c3fde7fcea</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 04:50:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Euro India Fresh Foods Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/euro-india-fresh-foods-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3840799</link><description>Euro India Fresh Foods Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 01 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed below reflect the stock’s current position as of 15 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>9c8ebddf3bab7be704100424eb337dcf</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 04:50:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Easy Trip Planners Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/easy-trip-planners-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3840797</link><description>Easy Trip Planners Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 13 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed below reflect the stock’s current position as of 15 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>cfeccca95afddd66c3440706b12a7105</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 04:50:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PVR Inox Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/pvr-inox-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3840796</link><description>PVR Inox Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 03 February 2026. While the rating change occurred on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 15 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the stock’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>a5be0f7c514fba9d4c2d5c336649cc74</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 04:50:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Geecee Ventures Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/geecee-ventures-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3840795</link><description>Geecee Ventures Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 23 May 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the company’s current position as of 15 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the stock’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trend, and technical outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>460400e2a0d3e299483e72c4fce06743</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 04:50:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Primo Chemicals Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/primo-chemicals-ltd-is-rated-sell-3840794</link><description>Primo Chemicals Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 07 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 15 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date insight into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>735d144a561de178fd2a26b7ab6bc8fc</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 04:50:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ujaas Energy Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ujaas-energy-ltd-is-rated-sell-3840792</link><description>Ujaas Energy Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 03 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 15 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the stock’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>2d0b7f54eab1b54a4a98ff9736b2d342</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 04:50:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Himatsingka Seide Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/himatsingka-seide-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3840793</link><description>Himatsingka Seide Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 11 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock’s current position as of 15 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trend, and technical outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>d7ed2db51c63bdd66c33f4dd808a44f4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 04:50:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bodal Chemicals Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/bodal-chemicals-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3840791</link><description>Bodal Chemicals Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 13 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 15 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and technical outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>b50580a17dd0dba2cdbeaf4fb2de5d0e</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 04:50:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Colgate-Palmolive (India) Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/colgate-palmolive-india-ltd-is-rated-sell-3840790</link><description>Colgate-Palmolive (India) Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 03 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 15 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market performance.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>3766c261e0652eb07d2177e0d3480f52</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 04:50:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>eMudhra Ltd is Rated Sell by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/emudhra-ltd-is-rated-sell-by-marketsmojo-3840789</link><description>eMudhra Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 12 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 15 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date perspective on the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>a579134a197fba211e1df414cffa5f9b</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 04:50:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Entero Healthcare Solutions Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/entero-healthcare-solutions-ltd-is-rated-sell-3840787</link><description>Entero Healthcare Solutions Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 13 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 15 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>b0c598c34bcb88faabd0b691ad0cc728</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 04:50:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ingersoll-Rand (India) Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ingersoll-rand-india-ltd-is-rated-hold-3840788</link><description>Ingersoll-Rand (India) Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 03 February 2026. While the rating change occurred on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 15 February 2026.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>553eafcc474245fbc5353db035e0d45d</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 04:50:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Donear Industries Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/donear-industries-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3840785</link><description>Donear Industries Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 10 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 15 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>b394ddad644c0b03879b17d652dad636</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 04:50:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 04:50:42 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>