<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:33:27 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Worth Peripherals Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Mixed Financial Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/worth-peripherals-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-mixed-financial-signals-3776618</link><description>Worth Peripherals Ltd has declined to its 52-week low, reflecting a significant downturn in its stock price despite positive quarterly earnings and a stable debt profile. The stock’s current price marks a notable contrast to its previous highs and broader market trends.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>d5e0fbe053d9842174f987ea615a2cfc</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:33:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vedant Fashions Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vedant-fashions-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3776619</link><description>Vedant Fashions Ltd has declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing near Rs 574.6, marking a significant downturn in the garment and apparel sector. This new low comes amid a year of sustained underperformance relative to market benchmarks and peers, reflecting a challenging period for the company’s stock.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ba8c8c945f1cb7eb53ecba01259fb693</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:33:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shankara Building Products Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shankara-building-products-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3776621</link><description>Shankara Building Products Ltd has recently touched a 52-week low, closing near ₹100.3, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid a backdrop of subdued financial performance and persistent underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>a672997cc47bdb472d0c736e292da7c9</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:33:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tijaria Polypipes Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tijaria-polypipes-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3776620</link><description>Tijaria Polypipes Ltd has reached a new 52-week low, reflecting ongoing pressures within the plastic products industrial sector. The stock's latest low price marks a significant decline over the past year, underscoring persistent challenges faced by the company amid broader market dynamics.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>c8280db78788d712e0899f4d0fb88c94</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:33:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sensex and Nifty Rally as Oil &amp; Gas Sector Leads; Small Caps Outperform</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-and-nifty-rally-as-oil-gas-sector-leads-small-caps-outperform-3776617</link><description>Indian equity markets closed higher on 31 Dec 2025, with the Nifty gaining 0.74% to settle at 26,129.60 and the Sensex advancing 0.64% to 85,220.60. Broad-based sectoral strength, led by the Oil &amp; Gas segment, and robust market breadth underpinned the rally as investors positioned ahead of key corporate earnings and global cues.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>f5f5854dbe5e48ae4931187574c40c83</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:33:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Murae Organisor Ltd Hits Day Low Amidst Price Pressure on 31 Dec 2025</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/murae-organisor-ltd-hits-day-low-amidst-price-pressure-on-31-dec-2025-3776613</link><description>Murae Organisor Ltd experienced a significant intraday decline, hitting its day low as the stock fell by 7.14% today, underperforming its sector and broader market indices amid persistent selling pressure and subdued market sentiment.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>d1f0d347e033e6470527faf0119210f4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:33:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thomas Cook (India) Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.02% Surge on 31 Dec 2025</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/thomas-cook-india-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-702-surge-on-31-dec-2025-3776614</link><description>Thomas Cook (India) Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 31 Dec 2025, surging 7.02% to touch a day’s high of Rs 149.7, significantly outperforming the broader Sensex and its sector peers.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>fe4b51820f25022c33d3bb6e14297c90</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:33:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vishnu Prakash R Punglia Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vishnu-prakash-r-punglia-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3776612</link><description>Shares of Vishnu Prakash R Punglia Ltd, a company operating in the construction sector, have declined sharply to a new 52-week low of Rs.52.1 on 31 Dec 2025, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing downward trajectory. This fresh low reflects persistent challenges faced by the company amid a broader market environment that remains buoyant.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>0284f521e45fac815bc6bc99c059560a</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:33:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>S. V. J. Enterprises Ltd Hits New 52-Week High of Rs.536</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/s-v-j-enterprises-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-of-rs536-3776611</link><description>S. V. J. Enterprises Ltd, a key player in the Paper, Forest &amp; Jute Products sector, reached a significant milestone today by hitting a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs.536, marking a notable surge in its stock price and reflecting strong momentum in the market.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>0f3594dd5a0866f0821039f26477f3c2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:33:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mrs Bectors Food Specialities Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.225.5</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mrs-bectors-food-specialities-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs2255-3776608</link><description>Mrs Bectors Food Specialities Ltd has declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.225.5, marking a significant downturn in the stock’s performance amid a rising broader market. The stock has underperformed its sector and the benchmark indices, reflecting ongoing concerns about its valuation and recent financial results.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>19e3e9715a4883ae84dd5a66900b607a</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:33:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Le Lavoir Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.165 Amidst Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/le-lavoir-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs165-amidst-market-volatility-3776604</link><description>Le Lavoir Ltd, a company operating in the Trading &amp; Distributors sector, has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.165 today, marking a significant decline in its share price amid a sustained downward trend over recent sessions.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>c7ff19f1a05054c92290e07341a4a9dd</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:33:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Allcargo Logistics Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/allcargo-logistics-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-underperformance-3776609</link><description>Allcargo Logistics Ltd’s shares declined to a fresh 52-week and all-time low of Rs.10.1 today, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory. This new low reflects persistent pressures on the company’s financial performance and market valuation amid broader sector dynamics.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>fb7a0f550156ac16f2d10c3ba95e5223</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:33:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Geecee Ventures Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/geecee-ventures-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3776605</link><description>Geecee Ventures Ltd, a player in the realty sector, touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.311.95 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing pressures on its financial performance and valuation metrics.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>1138ba50f0f33f86e35aa2efa107d8a0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:33:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SMT Engineering Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.195.75</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/smt-engineering-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs19575-3776606</link><description>SMT Engineering Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs.195.75, marking a remarkable surge in its stock price amid sustained positive momentum in the Trading &amp; Distributors sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>6b1ad767ea3bec3f01a9a86032e4243d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:33:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shivalik Rasayan Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.352</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shivalik-rasayan-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs352-3776607</link><description>Shivalik Rasayan Ltd, a player in the Pesticides &amp; Agrochemicals sector, has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.352 today, marking a significant decline amid ongoing underperformance relative to market benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>504394d47649c2d4ccd05e2b14d620b7</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:33:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Innovative Tech Pack Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Weak Financial Metrics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/innovative-tech-pack-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-weak-financial-metrics-3776610</link><description>Innovative Tech Pack Ltd, a player in the packaging sector, has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.18.01 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid ongoing financial headwinds and underperformance relative to the broader market and sector peers.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>abaab7beae0d8c9658554296c34a0d24</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:33:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stratmont Industries Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.55.35</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/stratmont-industries-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs5535-3776603</link><description>Stratmont Industries Ltd, a player in the Trading &amp; Distributors sector, touched a new 52-week low of Rs.55.35 today, marking a significant decline amid a volatile trading session. This fresh low comes after a series of declines over the past four days, reflecting ongoing pressures on the stock despite a broadly positive market environment.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>cf83a58e6c7d753bbcf6f7215d11a68a</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:33:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tanfac Industries Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.39% Surge on 31 Dec 2025</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tanfac-industries-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-739-surge-on-31-dec-2025-3776599</link><description>Tanfac Industries Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 31 Dec 2025, surging 7.39% to touch a day’s high of Rs 4,248, outperforming its sector and broader market indices amid positive market momentum.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>316ea602aa979356065cfd1af00ee0a3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:33:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Small and Micro Cap Stocks Deliver Exceptional Half-Year Returns Amid Bullish Market Sentiment</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/small-and-micro-cap-stocks-deliver-exceptional-half-year-returns-amid-bullish-market-sentiment-3776598</link><description>In a remarkable display of resilience and growth, select small and micro cap stocks have outperformed the broader market indices over the past six months, delivering extraordinary returns that have caught the attention of investors and analysts alike. These stocks, spanning sectors from FMCG to healthcare and metals, have not only surpassed benchmark returns but have also demonstrated strong technical and financial fundamentals underpinning their rally.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>6d8fafc1180538af9a6fa8ed4b5ae6fe</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:33:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Small Cap Stocks Deliver Exceptional Returns Amid Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/small-cap-stocks-deliver-exceptional-returns-amid-market-volatility-3776597</link><description>In a remarkable display of market outperformance, several small-cap stocks have delivered extraordinary returns over the past year, with Cupid from the FMCG sector emerging as the standout performer, surging an impressive 584.08%. This exceptional growth dwarfs benchmark indices and highlights the potential rewards of focused small-cap investing amid evolving sector dynamics.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>0a71095377b2571ba0999c4a45f7e359</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:33:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 12:33:27 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>