<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:20:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Machhar Industries Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.221.6</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/machhar-industries-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs2216-3777712</link><description>Machhar Industries Ltd, a player in the Specialty Chemicals sector, has recorded a new 52-week low of Rs.221.6 today, marking a significant decline amid a broader market that remains relatively stable. The stock’s recent performance reflects ongoing pressures that have weighed on its valuation over the past year.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>dcc51e16188c1e66155970b32780c737</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:20:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UPL Ltd. Hits New 52-Week High of Rs.801.5 Marking Strong Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/upl-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-of-rs8015-marking-strong-market-momentum-3777713</link><description>UPL Ltd., a leading player in the Pesticides &amp; Agrochemicals sector, reached a fresh 52-week high of Rs.801.5 today, underscoring a sustained rally driven by robust financial performance and positive market sentiment.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>9d766b7a605373757acf468a68e0d746</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:20:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Veranda Learning Solutions Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.34% Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/veranda-learning-solutions-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-734-surge-3777709</link><description>Veranda Learning Solutions Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 1 Jan 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 201.8, marking a 7.34% increase from the previous close. This strong uptick outpaced the broader market and sector indices, reflecting notable trading momentum throughout the session.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>79f049777354806175111589042536ea</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:20:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Universal Cables Ltd. Hits Intraday High with 7.02% Surge on 1 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/universal-cables-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-702-surge-on-1-jan-2026-3777711</link><description>Universal Cables Ltd. demonstrated robust intraday performance on 1 Jan 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 957.4, marking a 7.85% increase from its previous close. This notable uptick outpaced the broader market and sector indices, reflecting strong trading momentum throughout the session.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>a4a81e9da7dbc4acff951a96df6c73e5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:20:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Unitech Ltd Hits Day High with Strong Intraday Surge on 1 January 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/unitech-ltd-hits-day-high-with-strong-intraday-surge-on-1-january-2026-3777710</link><description>Unitech Ltd demonstrated a robust intraday performance on 1 Jan 2026, surging to its day high with a notable 7.11% gain, significantly outpacing the broader market and its sector peers.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>6833f540c4b647a63d1ee328b513cb7a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:20:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Datiware Maritime Infra Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.21.58</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/datiware-maritime-infra-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs2158-3777706</link><description>Datiware Maritime Infra, a key player in the Transport Services sector, reached a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs.21.58 on 1 Jan 2026, marking a significant milestone in its stock performance. The stock outperformed its sector and demonstrated strong momentum amid a broadly positive market backdrop.
Time: 38 minutes ago</description><guid>45e96d649800ea9bdb86e14299e50d40</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:20:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Auto Ltd. Hits New 52-Week High of Rs.9480 on 1 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-auto-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-of-rs9480-on-1-jan-2026-3777703</link><description>Bajaj Auto Ltd., a prominent player in the Indian automobile sector, reached a significant milestone today by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.9480. This achievement underscores the stock’s robust momentum, supported by sustained gains and favourable market conditions.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>84ab14c24abe02b8e9ae9eaa718a3e83</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:20:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lords Ishwar Hotels Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lords-ishwar-hotels-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3777705</link><description>Lords Ishwar Hotels Ltd has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.14.01 today, marking a significant decline in its share price amid persistent downward momentum. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing concerns about its financial health and valuation metrics.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>fa1252baf9a5d3272edc1334e0b07f71</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:20:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Somany Ceramics Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/somany-ceramics-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3777704</link><description>Somany Ceramics Ltd has touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.394.2 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting a challenging period for the company within the diversified consumer products sector.
Time: 39 minutes ago</description><guid>a1fb3bd72804212eeb1e92e7042b34cd</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:20:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Swiggy Ltd Sees Sharp Surge in Open Interest Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/swiggy-ltd-sees-sharp-surge-in-open-interest-amid-mixed-market-signals-3777701</link><description>Swiggy Ltd has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, with a 78.5% increase signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a modest 1.44% day gain and outperforming its sector, the stock remains under pressure with a Strong Sell mojo grade, reflecting cautious sentiment amid evolving market dynamics.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>5133befb28ad3b767d657ed8aa92fb57</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:20:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Waaree Energies Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/waaree-energies-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-price-action-3777702</link><description>Waaree Energies Ltd has witnessed a notable 13.3% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s recent downward price trend. This surge in open interest, coupled with rising delivery volumes and a complex interplay of futures and options values, suggests evolving market positioning and potential directional bets by investors.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>5801e33ae382237a6c21dc9d7ca55373</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:20:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Premier Energies Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/premier-energies-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-technical-signals-3777698</link><description>Premier Energies Ltd (NSE: PREMIERENE) witnessed a notable 16.44% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment on 31 Dec 2025, signalling a shift in market positioning and heightened investor interest. This surge, coupled with rising volumes and a positive price movement, suggests evolving directional bets in the Other Electrical Equipment sector amid a broader market backdrop.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>c157ce86bdf57b2ed47dceaf20dc3e40</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:20:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Energy Solutions Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-energy-solutions-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-momentum-3777699</link><description>Adani Energy Solutions Ltd has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market participation and potential directional bets. The stock has simultaneously hit a new 52-week high, supported by robust volume and sustained gains, reflecting growing investor confidence despite a cautious overall market backdrop.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>a75138df3f0e7bc90ca7b2a8ca532eff</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:20:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sameera Agro and Infra Ltd Plunges to Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sameera-agro-and-infra-ltd-plunges-to-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3777700</link><description>Sameera Agro and Infra Ltd, a micro-cap player in the miscellaneous sector, faced intense selling pressure on 1 Jan 2026, hitting its lower circuit price limit. The stock closed at ₹13.30, marking a maximum daily loss of 2.31%, as panic selling and unfilled supply overwhelmed investor sentiment despite a modest volume of 24,000 shares traded.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>48979fb730a90f428f5dff3eb94cc69a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:20:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jainam Ferro Alloys (I) Ltd Plunges to Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jainam-ferro-alloys-i-ltd-plunges-to-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3777697</link><description>Shares of Jainam Ferro Alloys (I) Ltd, a micro-cap player in the ferrous metals sector, plunged to their lower circuit limit on 1 Jan 2026, registering a maximum daily loss of 5.0%. The stock closed at ₹234.7, down ₹12.35 from the previous close, as intense selling pressure and panic selling gripped investors, leaving supply largely unfilled and trading volumes evaporating.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>695f450c3e70ebbf4c085abc3ca81532</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:20:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ashok Leyland Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Price Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ashok-leyland-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-price-momentum-3777693</link><description>Ashok Leyland Ltd. (ASHOKLEY) has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, coinciding with a robust price rally that has propelled the stock to a fresh 52-week high. This increase in open interest, coupled with rising volumes and sustained gains, signals a shift in market positioning and potential directional bets among investors in the automobile sector.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>a7b6af1292c41c7b6ad15295f81c905b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:20:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ashok Leyland Ltd. Sees Robust Trading Activity Amid Sector Gains</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ashok-leyland-ltd-sees-robust-trading-activity-amid-sector-gains-3777692</link><description>Ashok Leyland Ltd., a prominent player in the Indian automobile sector, witnessed significant trading activity on 1 Jan 2026, marked by a strong value turnover and sustained price gains. The stock outperformed its sector peers and broader market indices, reflecting renewed investor interest and institutional participation despite a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>17f077994c0c87aca72720b612b364d7</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:20:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ashok Leyland Ltd. Sees Exceptional Volume Surge Amidst Sustained Price Gains</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ashok-leyland-ltd-sees-exceptional-volume-surge-amidst-sustained-price-gains-3777695</link><description>Ashok Leyland Ltd., a prominent player in the Indian automobile sector, witnessed an extraordinary surge in trading volume on 1 Jan 2026, accompanied by a robust price rally that outpaced both its sector and the broader market. The stock’s sustained accumulation over the past four days signals growing investor confidence despite a recent downgrade in its mojo grade.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>aa7618f1692efd81c16f31dc14954dc7</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:20:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Holdings &amp; Investment Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-holdings-investment-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3777694</link><description>Bajaj Holdings &amp; Investment Ltd (BAJAJHLDNG) has witnessed a significant 19.4% increase in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this surge, the stock underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting a complex interplay of bullish and bearish sentiments among traders.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>6c4de32050e6bde133a0a22eedbfd9f9</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:20:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Finance Ltd Sees High-Value Trading Amidst Five-Day Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-finance-ltd-sees-high-value-trading-amidst-five-day-decline-3777689</link><description>Bajaj Finance Ltd, a leading player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, witnessed significant trading activity on 1 January 2026, with a total traded value exceeding ₹324 crore. Despite this high liquidity and institutional interest, the stock underperformed its sector and has been on a five-day losing streak, reflecting a complex market sentiment around this large-cap financial stock.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>20854183e7b802db8808bc5e1709bf62</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:20:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:20:25 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>