<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:31 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Kamdhenu Ventures Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kamdhenu-ventures-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3847094</link><description>Kamdhenu Ventures Ltd, a player in the paints sector, has touched a new 52-week and all-time low of Rs.4.49 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing challenges in its financial performance and market positioning.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>0d659c064bbfbe34d98ccf7b6de1f739</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Route Mobile Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/route-mobile-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-underperformance-3847092</link><description>Route Mobile Ltd, a player in the Telecom - Services sector, has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.526.4, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid ongoing challenges and market headwinds. This fresh low reflects a continuation of the stock’s downward trajectory over recent sessions.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>19c91e643351c84357413117e5e47e70</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Radiant Cash Management Services Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/radiant-cash-management-services-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amid-prolonged-downtrend-3847091</link><description>Radiant Cash Management Services Ltd has reached an all-time low, closing just 0.13% above its 52-week low of ₹38.4, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock’s recent performance reflects sustained underperformance relative to both its sector and broader market benchmarks, underscoring a challenging period for the company within the diversified commercial services sector.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>12cbcb87455749b11e54bf5a687db199</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sharika Enterprises Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.10.55</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sharika-enterprises-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs1055-3847088</link><description>Sharika Enterprises Ltd, a player in the Trading &amp; Distributors sector, has declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.10.55 today, marking a significant downturn in its stock performance amid deteriorating financial metrics and market pressures.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>232954f08a2378c1977e42a6a74891e0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lodha Developers Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 19 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lodha-developers-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-19-feb-2026-3847087</link><description>Lodha Developers Ltd experienced notable intraday weakness on 19 Feb 2026, with its stock price touching a low of Rs 1,074.15, reflecting a decline of 2.98% from the previous close. The stock underperformed its Realty sector peers and broader market indices amid a sharply reversing Sensex and prevailing market pressures.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>14d46aa99ed62fb053cb78df5f974fd0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Citadel Realty &amp; Developers Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.34</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/citadel-realty-developers-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs34-3847090</link><description>Citadel Realty &amp; Developers Ltd touched a new 52-week low of Rs.34 on 19 Feb 2026, marking a significant decline in its share price amid broader market fluctuations and sector underperformance. The stock’s fall reflects ongoing concerns about its financial metrics and valuation relative to peers.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>1b2689192e56f9e89219ed87c8a70e58</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Intrasoft Technologies Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs 81</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/intrasoft-technologies-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs-81-3847084</link><description>Intrasoft Technologies Ltd, a player in the E-Retail/ E-Commerce sector, has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.81 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid ongoing challenges and market headwinds. The stock’s performance continues to lag behind sector peers and benchmark indices, reflecting persistent concerns over its financial metrics and market positioning.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>41dcf379c17f97a9668254e3a2c72c44</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ugro Capital Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low at Rs.125 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ugro-capital-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-at-rs125-amidst-continued-downtrend-3847093</link><description>Ugro Capital Ltd, a Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC), has touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.125 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid broader market volatility and company-specific performance pressures. The stock has underperformed its sector and key benchmarks, reflecting ongoing challenges in profitability and market sentiment.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>bd01400cb743bca13ac37d760e023632</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AGI Greenpac Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/agi-greenpac-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3847089</link><description>AGI Greenpac Ltd’s stock declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.583.95 today, marking a significant downturn amid broader market volatility and sector-specific pressures. The stock has now recorded a consecutive seven-day decline, shedding 11.35% over this period and underperforming its packaging sector peers.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>49dc9ef409be7f95bb2d2151da8113c7</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jindal Poly Investment &amp; Finance Company Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs 1354.95</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jindal-poly-investment-finance-company-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs-135495-3847085</link><description>Jindal Poly Investment &amp; Finance Company Ltd, a prominent player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, reached a significant milestone today by hitting a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs 1354.95. This achievement underscores the stock’s robust momentum and reflects the company’s strong financial performance over the past year.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>6d09cf964270763a721b392069ff5fff</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sonal Adhesives Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sonal-adhesives-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3847086</link><description>Sonal Adhesives Ltd, a player in the commodity chemicals sector, has touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.36.1 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has underperformed both its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing pressures on its valuation and performance metrics.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>f5b9634ddf46eec684cf1d8e5bd51bb4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Polycab India Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Signalling Increased Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/polycab-india-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-signalling-increased-market-positioning-3847080</link><description>Polycab India Ltd has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, reflecting a marked shift in market positioning and investor sentiment. The 11.9% increase in open interest, coupled with rising volumes and strong price performance near its 52-week high, suggests growing bullish bets on the electrical cables giant amid steady fundamentals and sector outperformance.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>5d7aa6d90cc8138c0973c9055d9696ab</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tube Investments of India Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tube-investments-of-india-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3847077</link><description>Tube Investments of India Ltd (TIINDIA), a key player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has witnessed a notable surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a modest price gain, the stock’s recent trading patterns and underlying metrics suggest a complex interplay of bullish and cautious sentiments among market participants.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>c050e8476d0e3c5703aa9037614f2bcf</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AU Small Finance Bank Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Signalling Bullish Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/au-small-finance-bank-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-signalling-bullish-market-positioning-3847078</link><description>AU Small Finance Bank Ltd (AUBANK) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, reflecting heightened market activity and a potential shift in investor sentiment. The stock hit a new 52-week high of Rs. 1,039.2 on 19 Feb 2026, supported by robust volume and rising investor participation, signalling renewed bullish momentum in this mid-cap banking stock.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>9e1e20128caef4aee0ced5e6401b46fd</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RBL Bank Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Price Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rbl-bank-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-price-momentum-3847076</link><description>RBL Bank Ltd has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. The stock’s recent price strength, coupled with rising volumes and improving technical indicators, suggests a growing bullish sentiment among traders and investors alike.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>ea05c337ae3a551d1bc43dfc82f476ef</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bandhan Bank Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Positive Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bandhan-bank-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-positive-market-positioning-3847073</link><description>Bandhan Bank Ltd. has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market participation and potential directional bets. The stock outperformed its sector and broader indices, supported by strong volume and favourable moving average trends, despite a slight dip in delivery volumes.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>e7e123d93fa70a8e56a3b1919667b040</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JSW Energy Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jsw-energy-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3847079</link><description>JSW Energy Ltd (JSWENERGY) has witnessed a notable 12.33% increase in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a modest 0.42% gain in the stock price, the surge in OI alongside rising volumes suggests evolving directional bets amid a complex technical backdrop and sector dynamics.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>5d7ac4f376dd87319456be2c2f684563</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Energy Solutions Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-energy-solutions-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3847071</link><description>Adani Energy Solutions Ltd has witnessed a notable 10.06% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s recent underperformance. This surge, coupled with volume patterns and shifting investor positioning, offers a complex picture of market sentiment in the power sector as the stock faces downward pressure after a brief rally.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>0b48e6ad58278800e0de7bf2cda11b6f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Finance Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-finance-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3847075</link><description>Bajaj Finance Ltd, a leading player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has witnessed a notable 10.9% increase in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and evolving investor positioning. Despite a marginal decline in the stock price, the surge in OI alongside volume patterns suggests a complex interplay of directional bets and market sentiment.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>c64fd76354a82cb9afeb50fe077c8f18</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Max Financial Services Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/max-financial-services-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-market-signals-3847074</link><description>Max Financial Services Ltd (MFSL) has witnessed a notable 12.25% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. This surge, coupled with robust volume and price momentum, suggests a growing bullish sentiment among traders, positioning the stock close to its 52-week high amid outperformance in the insurance sector.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>3e8436d27656abf5f4e9e12e53f810b1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:54:31 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>