<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:32:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Pavna Industries Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.23.16 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pavna-industries-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs2316-amidst-continued-downtrend-3771340</link><description>Pavna Industries, a player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, touched a new 52-week low of Rs.23.16 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid a broader market environment that saw the Nifty index close marginally lower. This fresh low underscores ongoing pressures on the company’s share performance over the past year.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e85a52256209dba0fd246340278aceb8</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Network People Services Technologies Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.1347.5</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/network-people-services-technologies-stock-hits-52-week-low-at-rs13475-3771339</link><description>Network People Services Technologies has reached a new 52-week low, with its stock price touching Rs.1347.5 today. This marks a significant price level for the company within the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, reflecting ongoing pressures in its market performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f70ea66ef2f8b21253fd232b61f58cd3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sensex and Nifty Slip Amid Mixed Sector Performance; Rail Vikas and Titan Lead Gains</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-and-nifty-slip-amid-sector-weakness-metal-sector-shines-3771323</link><description>The Indian equity markets concluded the session on 26 December 2025 with the Sensex and Nifty indices registering modest declines, reflecting a cautious investor sentiment amid mixed sectoral trends and subdued breadth. While large caps showed some resilience, mid and small caps faced pressure, with notable divergences among sector performances and individual stock movements.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>c877ee5f0892be64987221f152f85c90</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oxford Industries Hits New 52-Week High of Rs.4.54 Marking Significant Market Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/oxford-industries-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs454-on-26-dec-2025-3771220</link><description>Oxford Industries has reached a new 52-week high of Rs.4.54, reflecting a notable moment in its trading history as the stock demonstrates strong momentum amid a mixed market environment.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>e27e4f9e57a91f159733440f02040047</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wim Plast . Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.444 Amid Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/wim-plast-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs444-amidst-prolonged-downtrend-3771217</link><description>Wim Plast . has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.444, marking a significant decline as the stock continues a nine-day losing streak. This latest price point reflects ongoing pressures within the diversified consumer products sector, with the stock trading below all major moving averages and underperforming key market indices over the past year.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>a805d4668763329fb1681320a1677ee7</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Last Mile Enterprises Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.9.4 Amid Market Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/last-mile-enterprises-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs94-amidst-continued-downtrend-3771214</link><description>Shares of Last Mile Enterprises have declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.9.4, marking a significant price level for the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) amid broader market fluctuations and sectoral underperformance.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>1dc5adc479bdf85296ffc1cdaea06ceb</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Filatex Fashions Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.0.34 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/filatex-fashions-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3771216</link><description>Filatex Fashions has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.0.34, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid ongoing challenges in the garments and apparels sector. The stock's performance over the past year reflects a notable divergence from broader market trends, with the company’s shares underperforming both its sector and the Sensex benchmark.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>a3de1f868acd357f99d3997a55cd763c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SMT Engineering Hits New 52-Week High of Rs.184.55 Marking Significant Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/smt-engineering-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs18455-3771141</link><description>SMT Engineering, a key player in the Trading &amp; Distributors sector, has reached a new 52-week high of Rs.184.55, reflecting a remarkable rally and sustained momentum in recent trading sessions. This milestone underscores the stock’s strong performance relative to its sector and broader market indices.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>bd8c9503d93899407da40165be820add</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Foods &amp; Inns Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.68.57 Amidst Sector Challenges</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/foods-inns-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs6857-amidst-continued-underperformance-3771142</link><description>Foods &amp; Inns, a player in the FMCG sector, has reached a new 52-week low price of Rs.68.57 today, reflecting a significant decline over the past year amid broader market fluctuations and company-specific financial indicators.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>002cdcb53076533cda2d5bcee137fe94</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Saptak Chem &amp; Business Hits New 52-Week High of Rs.29.29</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/saptak-chem-business-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs2929-3771140</link><description>Saptak Chem &amp; Business, a key player in the Trading &amp; Distributors sector, has reached a significant milestone by touching a new 52-week high of Rs.29.29. This achievement marks a notable moment in the stock’s recent performance, reflecting sustained momentum and positive market dynamics.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>1012c60428531f599fececf87e660bd8</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cupid Stock Surges 361.5% in Six Months, Outperforming Market Benchmarks</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/small-and-micro-cap-stocks-deliver-exceptional-half-year-returns-amidst-market-volatility-3770984</link><description>Cupid has delivered an exceptional return of 361.5% over the past six months, significantly outpacing broader market indices and its sector peers. This remarkable performance highlights the stock’s strong momentum amid a challenging market environment, driven by a combination of bullish technical indicators and robust financial fundamentals.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>bbddc19febc260ea931635474b443b57</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Osiajee Texfab Delivers Exceptional 694.61% Return in One Year, Outshining Market Benchmarks</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/osiajee-texfab-leads-market-rally-with-exceptional-6946-return-in-one-year-3770983</link><description>Osiajee Texfab has emerged as a standout performer over the past year, delivering a remarkable return of 694.61%, significantly surpassing broader market indices and sector peers. This extraordinary performance highlights the stock’s strong momentum amid a challenging market environment, driven by a combination of technical strength, positive financial indicators, and sector-specific catalysts.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>38d315907887ab3ae33161aef961309c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>G K P Printing &amp; Packaging Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/g-k-p-printing-packaging-ltd-is-rated-sell-3770949</link><description>G K P Printing &amp; Packaging Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 06 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company's fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>0b7e90d3db7df0f452d0889e18297449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Polylink Polymers (India) Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/polylink-polymers-india-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3770953</link><description>Polylink Polymers (India) Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 23 May 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>9bffd8a0c87dbc42e2409735927f2f32</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Saffron Industries Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/saffron-industries-ltd-is-rated-sell-3770951</link><description>Saffron Industries Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 09 June 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b12d295a569a101c92cb20dc3e0482d7</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shivamshree Businesses Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/shivamshree-businesses-ltd-is-rated-sell-3770950</link><description>Shivamshree Businesses Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 09 Dec 2025. While the rating was revised on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>28976f037ee5f6481fd91faa87e1a93f</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KJMC Corporate Advisors (India) Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/kjmc-corporate-advisors-india-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3770948</link><description>KJMC Corporate Advisors (India) Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 28 April 2025, reflecting a shift from the previous 'Sell' grade. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here represent the stock's current position as of 26 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of its performance and outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>eebf2760d75d93592c5d82b2537b3c07</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DMR Engineering Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/dmr-engineering-ltd-is-rated-sell-3770947</link><description>DMR Engineering Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 20 August 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>36351f1486b1faed66ae4521778906db</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cubical Financial Services Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/cubical-financial-services-ltd-is-rated-sell-3770946</link><description>Cubical Financial Services Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 27 October 2025. However, the analysis below reflects the stock's current position as of 26 December 2025, incorporating the latest fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics to provide investors with an up-to-date perspective.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>24d9fc0b406295813ad4e53c83da4af6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:32:52 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>