<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:42:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Go Digit General Insurance Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/go-digit-general-insurance-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3811796</link><description>Go Digit General Insurance Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>33edc282591ac7f3b54a8a9ea05b1d67</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:42:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Doms Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/doms-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3811797</link><description>Doms Industries Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend and long-term weakness in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>f5c7a5b0a89f5237a333928d507f8e84</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:42:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Synergy Green Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/synergy-green-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3811795</link><description>Synergy Green Industries Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Castings &amp; Forgings sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>8331595b72935a9f63c5d5529b869600</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:42:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NESCO Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nesco-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3811792</link><description>NESCO Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium-term momentum and raising concerns about long-term weakness.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>5b9901201dff66a0ee610c860ff0e114</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:42:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NRB Bearings Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nrb-bearings-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3811794</link><description>NRB Bearings Ltd, a key player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>aba0d307fe9150aea5a2b1c80ecc65cf</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:42:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HLE Glascoat Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hle-glascoat-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3811791</link><description>HLE Glascoat Ltd, a player in the industrial manufacturing sector, has recently formed a Death Cross—a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average—indicating a potential shift towards a bearish trend and signalling long-term weakness in the stock’s price momentum.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>7932161f6020c2bdad9df3ddd37afda5</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:42:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arihant Capital Markets Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/arihant-capital-markets-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3811793</link><description>Arihant Capital Markets Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>c37467c76c45c67eefdb1941d1acd621</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:42:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arunjyoti Bio Ventures Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/arunjyoti-bio-ventures-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3811784</link><description>Arunjyoti Bio Ventures Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about sustained bearish momentum in the near to medium term.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>f0d57786ce8cc59ca612df330c343543</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:42:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IFB Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ifb-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3811787</link><description>IFB Industries Ltd, a player in the Electronics &amp; Appliances sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>59c14baf795840f8a35afd17992c5211</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:42:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vivanza Biosciences Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vivanza-biosciences-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3811786</link><description>Vivanza Biosciences Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>e7cc8d8c6107daddbb8966a9c38ce0be</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:42:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Divis Laboratories Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/divis-laboratories-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3811790</link><description>Divis Laboratories Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum. Investors and market watchers should carefully analyse the implications of this event amid the company’s current financial and market performance.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>3fd72584199ae046c1ec70177d2c689e</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:42:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Birla Precision Technologies Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/birla-precision-technologies-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3811782</link><description>Birla Precision Technologies Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s near to medium-term outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>d5d54a273f33852e168ad545f1254e8d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:42:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Punjab Chemicals &amp; Crop Protection Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/punjab-chemicals-crop-protection-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3811788</link><description>Punjab Chemicals &amp; Crop Protection Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum, raising concerns among investors about potential weakness ahead.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>3365b20ff4624103fdb478f673511f4c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:42:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Swan Corp Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/swan-corp-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3811785</link><description>Swan Corp Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>3b3cff0df32bed9a57fd505104bb2fcb</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:42:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Epuja Spiritech Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/epuja-spiritech-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3811789</link><description>Epuja Spiritech Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about sustained bearish momentum in the near to medium term.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>b9aba112119ea5d0f0d929739adb2ef5</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:42:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DCM Shriram Ltd. Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dcm-shriram-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3811783</link><description>Shares of DCM Shriram Ltd., a diversified sector player, have recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend, indicating potential long-term weakness and trend deterioration for the stock.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>6e8bb444d21a6a964105c8086747ff7f</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:42:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mixed Earnings Landscape as 802 Companies Report Dec-2025 Quarterly Results</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/mixed-earnings-landscape-as-802-companies-report-dec-2025-quarterly-results-3811781</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has delivered a mixed bag of results with 802 companies declaring their numbers. While the overall proportion of positive results has improved to 50.0%, this marks a modest recovery from the subdued performance seen in the previous three quarters. Sectoral and market capitalisation-wise disparities continue to shape the earnings landscape, reflecting varied growth trajectories across industries and company sizes.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>85539ba2c096d1a14b96a5c8c8ca2f68</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:42:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Brigade Enterprises Q3 FY26: Growth Momentum Masks Valuation Concerns Amid Bearish Technicals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/brigade-enterprises-q3-fy26-growth-momentum-masks-valuation-concerns-amid-bearish-technicals-3811798</link><description>Brigade Enterprises Ltd., one of South India's leading real estate developers, reported a consolidated net profit of ₹186.52 crores for Q3 FY26, marking a sequential improvement of 14.78% from Q2 FY26's ₹162.50 crores. However, the year-on-year comparison reveals a concerning 21.05% decline from ₹236.24 crores in Q3 FY25, raising questions about the sustainability of the company's growth trajectory despite strong operational metrics.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>8a3336fef534f448b5df5f0e2bb8fb07</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:42:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Softtech Engineers Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/softtech-engineers-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3811757</link><description>Softtech Engineers Ltd has declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing near Rs 276.25, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing downward trajectory. The stock’s recent performance reflects a series of challenges impacting its valuation and market standing within the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>93d9399716579e31340e358c80b8bc27</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:42:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Medi Assist Healthcare Services Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/medi-assist-healthcare-services-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3811752</link><description>Medi Assist Healthcare Services Ltd has touched a fresh 52-week low, closing just 0.86% above its lowest price of Rs 394, marking a significant phase of decline for the insurance sector stock amid broader market pressures and company-specific factors.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>e8d1b3f0c299c8501c17121aae6b14f8</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:42:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:42:44 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>