<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:57:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Small-Cap Segment Sees Mixed Performance Amid Broader Market Weakness on 16 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/small-cap-segment-sees-mixed-performance-amid-broader-market-weakness-on-16-feb-2026-3841516</link><description>The BSE Smallcap index declined by 0.63% on 16 Feb 2026, reflecting a challenging environment for small-cap stocks amid broader market volatility. Despite the overall downturn, select stocks such as RACL Geartech delivered robust returns, while others like Pennar Industrie lagged significantly. Market breadth indicators reveal a cautious sentiment, with a pronounced skew towards declining stocks in the segment.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>8b8f2eb605ae47e6e1b7c241f1fd7d34</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:57:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mid-Cap Segment Sees Mild Decline Amid Mixed Sectoral Performance on 16 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/mid-cap-segment-sees-mild-decline-amid-mixed-sectoral-performance-on-16-feb-2026-3841515</link><description>The BSE Midcap index experienced a modest decline of 0.61% on 16 Feb 2026, reflecting a cautious market mood amid mixed sectoral performances and uneven breadth. While select stocks delivered notable gains, the overall mid-cap segment struggled to maintain upward momentum, with 79 stocks declining against 64 advancing, resulting in an advance-decline ratio of 0.81x.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>7302f22bdf17c64f18282aa85042fece</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:57:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Large-Cap Segment Edges Higher Led by Power Grid; Hero MotoCorp Lags</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/large-cap-segment-edges-higher-led-by-power-grid-hero-motocorp-lags-3841514</link><description>The large-cap segment edged higher by 0.17% on 16 Feb 2026, with a notable divergence between defensive and cyclical stocks. While Power Grid Corporation led gains with a 3.81% return, Hero MotoCorp lagged, declining 2.01%. Market breadth remained positive with 56 advancing stocks against 43 decliners, reflecting cautious optimism among investors.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>e2f5ed5077722efafbe76996be06dd4b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:57:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Large-Cap Segment Edges Higher Amid Mixed Sectoral Trends on 16 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/large-cap-segment-edges-higher-amid-mixed-sectoral-trends-on-16-feb-2026-3841513</link><description>The large-cap segment, represented by the BSE 100 index, recorded a modest gain of 0.16% on 16 Feb 2026, reflecting a cautious market mood amid mixed sectoral trends. While heavyweight stocks such as Power Grid Corporation delivered robust returns, others like Infosys faced headwinds, underscoring the divergence between defensive and cyclical plays within the segment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6d77b863b13071fdd360213d6a54f0ce</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:57:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Small-Cap Segment Sees Mixed Performance Amid Broader Market Pressure on 16 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/small-cap-segment-sees-mixed-performance-amid-broader-market-pressure-on-16-feb-2026-3841512</link><description>The BSE Smallcap index slipped by 0.63% on 16 Feb 2026, reflecting a cautious mood among investors despite pockets of strong outperformance. While select stocks like Prec. Wires (I) surged over 15%, the broader small-cap universe struggled with a negative advance-decline ratio and sectoral divergences, signalling underlying market fragility.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>527b944c401c4a7b46b9664e600d681b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:57:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mid-Cap Segment Sees Mild Correction Amid Mixed Sectoral Performance on 16 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/mid-cap-segment-sees-mild-correction-amid-mixed-sectoral-performance-on-16-feb-2026-3841511</link><description>The BSE Midcap index experienced a modest decline of 0.61% on 16 Feb 2026, reflecting a mixed performance across the mid-cap segment. While certain stocks like GMR Airports delivered robust returns, others such as Brainbees Solutions faced significant setbacks. The segment’s breadth remained weak with more decliners than advancers, signalling cautious investor sentiment amid upcoming quarterly results.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f2afb99d658b76c94106434c7f0bf2d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:57:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Large-Cap Segment Edges Higher Amid Mixed Stock Performance on 16 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/large-cap-segment-edges-higher-amid-mixed-stock-performance-on-16-feb-2026-3841510</link><description>The large-cap segment, represented by the BSE 100 index, exhibited a marginal gain of 0.02% on 16 Feb 2026, reflecting a cautious market mood amid mixed sectoral trends. While heavyweight stocks like Power Grid Corporation delivered robust returns, cyclical names such as Hindalco Industries lagged, underscoring the ongoing divergence between defensive and cyclical equities.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>3f74e1a80b77cb74667828c45752f97f</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:57:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Small-Cap Segment Faces Pressure Amid Broad Market Weakness on 16 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/small-cap-segment-faces-pressure-amid-broad-market-weakness-on-16-feb-2026-3841508</link><description>The BSE Smallcap index slipped by 0.63% on 16 Feb 2026, reflecting a challenging session for the small-cap segment amid broader market volatility. Despite the overall decline, select stocks such as SRM Contractors bucked the trend with robust gains, while others like Pennar Industrie experienced notable losses. Market breadth indicators reveal a cautious investor sentiment, with declining stocks outnumbering advancers by more than two to one.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>5bc3d6652f9baf35fba2a380a008744d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:57:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mid-Cap Segment Sees Modest Decline Amid Mixed Sectoral Performance on 16 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/mid-cap-segment-sees-modest-decline-amid-mixed-sectoral-performance-on-16-feb-2026-3841509</link><description>The BSE Midcap index experienced a modest decline of 0.61% on 16 Feb 2026, reflecting a cautious mood among investors in the mid-cap segment. While select stocks such as GMR Airports delivered robust returns, the broader market breadth remained weak with more decliners than advancers, signalling a mixed performance across sectors.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>c788d10003fb34c939277f965823ea55</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:57:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mid-Cap Segment Sees Modest Decline Amid Mixed Sectoral Performance on 16 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/mid-cap-segment-sees-modest-decline-amid-mixed-sectoral-performance-on-16-feb-2026-3841505</link><description>The BSE Midcap index experienced a modest decline of 0.61% on 16 Feb 2026, reflecting a cautious market mood as sectoral disparities and stock-specific movements shaped the trading session. While select mid-cap stocks delivered notable gains, broader market breadth remained subdued, signalling investor selectivity in this segment.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>bfbd219a16752aad83d7e3080b4a26a1</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:57:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Large-Cap Segment Edges Higher Amid Mixed Stock Performance on 16 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/large-cap-segment-edges-higher-amid-mixed-stock-performance-on-16-feb-2026-3841507</link><description>The large-cap segment of the Indian equity market exhibited a subdued performance on 16 Feb 2026, with the BSE 100 index inching up by a marginal 0.05%. While select heavyweight stocks delivered modest gains, the overall advance-decline ratio reflected a cautious investor sentiment, underscoring the ongoing tussle between defensive and cyclical sectors.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>b7786ae4314c6e9b5aa3d4ab90f14b36</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:57:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Small-Cap Segment Sees Mixed Performance Amid Sectoral Divergence on 16 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/small-cap-segment-sees-mixed-performance-amid-sectoral-divergence-on-16-feb-2026-3841506</link><description>The BSE Smallcap index declined by 0.63% on 16 Feb 2026, reflecting a challenging trading session for the small-cap segment. Despite pockets of strong sectoral performance, overall market breadth remained weak with more than twice as many stocks declining as advancing. This article analyses the recent trends, sectoral winners and laggards, and breadth indicators to provide a comprehensive view of the small-cap landscape.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>35e127c62f5ae875f60fe52ca77e3948</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:57:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jio Financial Services Ltd Faces Downgrade Amidst Volatile Market Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jio-financial-services-ltd-faces-downgrade-amidst-volatile-market-performance-3841504</link><description>Jio Financial Services Ltd, a prominent constituent of the Nifty 50 index, has recently experienced a downgrade in its Mojo Grade from Hold to Sell, reflecting growing concerns over its valuation and recent price performance. Despite its large-cap status and significant market presence within the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, the stock has underperformed key benchmarks, raising questions about its near-term outlook and institutional investor sentiment.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>f0341e634061df66af4b734f6624bbea</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:57:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eternal Ltd’s Nifty 50 Inclusion Highlights Institutional Shifts and Market Dynamics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eternal-ltds-nifty-50-inclusion-highlights-institutional-shifts-and-market-dynamics-3841503</link><description>Eternal Ltd’s recent inclusion in the Nifty 50 index marks a significant milestone for the e-retail giant, reflecting its growing stature in India’s equity markets. This development not only underscores the company’s market capitalisation and liquidity credentials but also triggers notable shifts in institutional holdings and benchmark-driven portfolio adjustments. As investors recalibrate their strategies, the stock’s performance and valuation metrics warrant close scrutiny amid evolving sector dynamics.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>6eb3597157df65034fabb1b0acd1ddcd</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:57:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:57:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>