<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:51:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Honasa Consumer Ltd Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/honasa-consumer-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3864360</link><description>Honasa Consumer Ltd witnessed a significant gap down at the opening bell today, reflecting heightened market concerns and a weak start. The stock opened sharply lower by 12.36%, underperforming its FMCG sector peers and the broader market indices amid a backdrop of cautious sentiment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3df9187c40bd683acffd6e27e184be7f</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CreditAccess Grameen Ltd Opens with Weak Start, Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/creditaccess-grameen-ltd-opens-with-weak-start-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3864359</link><description>CreditAccess Grameen Ltd witnessed a sharp gap down at the opening bell today, declining by 7.2% to an intraday low of Rs 1,173.65, reflecting heightened market apprehension following overnight developments. The stock’s weak start contributed to its underperformance relative to the broader sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>89b756895a8e7a6d905d0ad16c57e936</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apollo Micro Systems Ltd Opens with Weak Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/apollo-micro-systems-ltd-opens-with-weak-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3864358</link><description>Apollo Micro Systems Ltd, a key player in the Aerospace &amp; Defense sector, opened the trading session on 2 Mar 2026 with a pronounced gap down, reflecting heightened market apprehension. The stock declined sharply by 6.89% at the opening bell, continuing a recent downward trend amid broader sector underperformance and technical pressures.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d4176921c79d5a1d7a3cd1791c8f90ea</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Maruti Suzuki India Ltd Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/maruti-suzuki-india-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3864357</link><description>Maruti Suzuki India Ltd commenced trading on 2 Mar 2026 with a pronounced gap down, opening at a price 6.05% lower than its previous close. This weak start reflects ongoing market apprehensions, with the stock underperforming its sector and broader indices amid a two-day losing streak.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>17104b784c35c30a1625b123178fb264</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NBCC (India) Ltd Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nbcc-india-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3864354</link><description>NBCC (India) Ltd commenced trading today with a pronounced gap down, opening at Rs 83.65, reflecting a sharp decline of 9.79% from the previous close. This weak start underscores prevailing market apprehensions surrounding the construction sector and the stock’s recent performance trajectory.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5c313a285057e094f3e57641fe8373e6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sandur Manganese &amp; Iron Ores Ltd Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sandur-manganese-iron-ores-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3864352</link><description>Sandur Manganese &amp; Iron Ores Ltd experienced a sharp decline at market open on 2 Mar 2026, opening with a gap down of 6.02% amid broader sector weakness and a cautious market mood. The stock’s weak start reflects ongoing pressures despite some technical support, with investors reacting to recent developments and market dynamics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ca416616993e070473c2858c307cd50c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Canara Bank Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/canara-bank-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3864350</link><description>Shares of Canara Bank opened sharply lower on 2 Mar 2026, registering a gap down of 6.13% at the start of trading, reflecting heightened market apprehension despite the stock’s recent positive momentum and upgrade in rating earlier this year.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a20e6d610b35f19efd0e2714431e9008</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd Opens with Weak Start, Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/samvardhana-motherson-international-ltd-opens-with-weak-start-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3864348</link><description>Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd (SMIL) commenced trading today with a pronounced gap down, opening nearly 10% lower than its previous close, reflecting heightened market apprehension following overnight developments. The stock’s weak start has intensified selling pressure, although some technical indicators suggest potential stabilisation in the near term.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c6fa71a8ff10903f1dbf85530d43ac44</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Container Corporation Of India Ltd Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/container-corporation-of-india-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3864356</link><description>Container Corporation Of India Ltd (Stock ID: 336884) opened the trading session on 2 Mar 2026 with a pronounced gap down, reflecting heightened market concerns. The stock declined sharply by 6.82% at the open, hitting a new 52-week low of Rs.461.85, signalling a weak start amid ongoing downward momentum.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d4bcf03e61b37eb7777a84d38cafabf3</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eveready Industries India Ltd Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eveready-industries-india-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3864349</link><description>Eveready Industries India Ltd witnessed a sharp gap down at the opening bell on 2 Mar 2026, reflecting heightened market concerns and a notable shift in investor sentiment. The stock opened at an intraday low of Rs 309.35, marking a decline of 6.79% from its previous close, underperforming both its sector and the broader market indices.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3a30cef8cf2c97a00f76bbb9f77cb125</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Camlin Fine Sciences Ltd Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/camlin-fine-sciences-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3864355</link><description>Camlin Fine Sciences Ltd, a key player in the Specialty Chemicals sector, opened the trading session on 2 March 2026 with a pronounced gap down, reflecting heightened market apprehension. The stock declined sharply by 6.63% at the open, signalling a weak start amid broader sector pressures and company-specific factors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ba4c6f747a51067a51557143397cb702</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>L T Foods Ltd Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/l-t-foods-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3864351</link><description>L T Foods Ltd commenced trading on 2 Mar 2026 with a significant gap down, opening at an intraday low of Rs 361.45, reflecting a 10.15% decline from its previous close. This sharp drop marks a continuation of the stock’s recent downward trend amid broader sector pressures and market concerns.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>05e51a97653dfad4666ac0f772467982</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coromandel International Ltd Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/coromandel-international-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3864353</link><description>Shares of Coromandel International Ltd opened sharply lower on 2 Mar 2026, registering a gap down of 4.28% at the start of trading. This weak opening reflects ongoing market concerns and a continuation of recent downward momentum, with the stock underperforming its sector and broader indices amid subdued investor sentiment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>24d52b414842dfd01a24d6466bab69ae</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Magnus Steel &amp; Infra Ltd Hits All-Time High at Rs.63.16 Mark</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/magnus-steel-infra-ltd-hits-all-time-high-at-rs6316-mark-3864344</link><description>Magnus Steel &amp; Infra Ltd, a key player in the Other Electrical Equipment sector, reached a new all-time high of Rs.63.16 on 2 Mar 2026, underscoring a sustained period of robust performance and significant market momentum.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>73f1230df3f8e94a5f39f97a48e3c4e6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Godrej Consumer Products Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/godrej-consumer-products-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-3864346</link><description>Godrej Consumer Products Ltd (GCPL) experienced notable intraday weakness on 2 Mar 2026, touching a low of Rs 1,150.05, marking a 5.55% decline from its previous close. The stock underperformed its FMCG sector peers and broader market indices, reflecting immediate selling pressure and subdued market sentiment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>22f0dcf166c6160cd4c115918371d9fa</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Solar Industries India Ltd Hits Intraday High with Strong 3.78% Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/solar-industries-india-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-strong-378-surge-3864347</link><description>Solar Industries India Ltd demonstrated robust intraday strength on 2 Mar 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 13,997.75, marking a 3.69% increase from its previous close. This performance stands out amid a volatile market backdrop where the broader Sensex index remained under pressure.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0b9a8a0a9f89f885239ab5edce3e30c2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GHV Infra Projects Ltd Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ghv-infra-projects-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3864345</link><description>Shares of GHV Infra Projects Ltd opened sharply lower on 2 March 2026, registering a gap down of 5.0% at the start of trading. This weak opening reflects market apprehensions following recent developments, with the stock underperforming its sector and broader indices amid heightened volatility.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>94b4f569d5ddfca81a842434824c9179</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank Of India Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bank-of-india-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3864251</link><description>Bank Of India commenced trading on 2 Mar 2026 with a pronounced gap down, opening at an intraday low of Rs 161.85, marking an 8.14% decline from its previous close. This weak start reflects heightened market apprehensions despite the stock’s recent strong performance relative to the broader Sensex.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>15dfe45763d0cc0a31ff33adf597c0a7</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SMS Pharmaceuticals Ltd Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sms-pharmaceuticals-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3864253</link><description>SMS Pharmaceuticals Ltd witnessed a significant gap down at market open on 2 Mar 2026, dropping 16.02% to an intraday low of Rs 322.65. This sharp decline reflects heightened market concerns following overnight developments, resulting in a weak start and notable underperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>375605c596b9a5d5f71a666e886294fd</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rallis India Ltd Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rallis-india-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3864248</link><description>Rallis India Ltd, a key player in the Pesticides &amp; Agrochemicals sector, opened the trading session on 2 Mar 2026 with a pronounced gap down, reflecting heightened market apprehensions. The stock declined sharply by 5.51% at the open, underperforming both its sector and the broader market indices, signalling a weak start to the day.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>219f3eea168ecd85d750d9ba3417812a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>