<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 06:25:19 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Summit Securities Ltd Falls 5.60%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/summit-securities-ltd-falls-560-3-key-factors-driving-the-downtrend-3788959</link><description>Summit Securities Ltd experienced a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, with its stock price declining by 5.60% to close at Rs.1,825.65, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The week was marked by a bearish technical shift, a downgrade to a strong sell rating, and sustained negative momentum amid sectoral headwinds and weak fundamentals.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>307762706e6a8c3709b755abad3698c1</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 06:25:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TCI Finance Ltd Gains 15.40%: 9 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tci-finance-ltd-gains-1540-9-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-rally-3788958</link><description>TCI Finance Ltd delivered a remarkable weekly gain of 15.40%, closing at Rs.34.47 on 9 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined by 2.62% over the same period. The stock’s rally was marked by a series of new 52-week highs, multiple upper circuit hits, and sustained buying pressure amid a mixed broader market environment.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>e944aae534af641aad106c68e9af2f75</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 06:25:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Escorts Kubota Ltd Declines 0.69% Despite Outperforming Sensex by 1.93% This Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/escorts-kubota-ltd-declines-069-despite-outperforming-sensex-by-193-this-week-3788957</link><description>Escorts Kubota Ltd ended the week marginally lower by 0.69% at Rs.3,819.50, underperforming the Sensex which declined 2.62% over the same period. The stock’s price action was shaped by a strong technical upgrade early in the week, a shift to a very expensive valuation rating, and mixed daily price movements amid broader market weakness. Despite the weekly decline, Escorts Kubota demonstrated resilience relative to the benchmark index, supported by robust fundamentals and positive momentum signals.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>9f7df3a247b3ac51448577749ea49039</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 06:25:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bhagyanagar India Ltd Gains 0.92%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bhagyanagar-india-ltd-gains-092-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3788956</link><description>Bhagyanagar India Ltd closed the week with a modest gain of 0.92%, ending at Rs.164.50 on 9 January 2026, despite a turbulent trading week marked by sharp rallies and steep declines. The stock outperformed the Sensex, which fell 2.62% over the same period, reflecting strong but volatile investor interest amid sectoral and company-specific developments.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>03071fc609a98e88d1bc5d83b69390db</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 06:25:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jubilant Foodworks Declines 5.47%: 6 Key Factors Behind the 52-Week Lows</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jubilant-foodworks-declines-547-6-key-factors-behind-the-52-week-lows-3788955</link><description>Jubilant Foodworks Ltd experienced a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, with its stock price declining by 5.47% to close at Rs.521.90, underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The stock hit multiple 52-week lows amid bearish market sentiment, increased derivatives activity, and valuation concerns, despite the company’s solid financial fundamentals and sectoral significance.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>09b406990f5aca66bb30879c63572436</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 06:25:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vodafone Idea Ltd Falls 4.41%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vodafone-idea-ltd-falls-441-5-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3788953</link><description>Vodafone Idea Ltd experienced a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, with its stock price declining 4.41% to close at Rs.11.27, underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62%. Despite this, the stock demonstrated notable trading volumes and technical resilience, including a significant gap up on 9 January. This review analyses the key events and market dynamics shaping Vodafone Idea’s performance over the week.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>68563bae0f1eaa74189bfc38af9fcce6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 06:25:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rajoo Engineers Gains 4.93%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rajoo-engineers-gains-493-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3788952</link><description>Rajoo Engineers Ltd delivered a volatile week with a 4.93% gain from Rs.64.94 to Rs.68.14, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 2.62% over the same period. The stock’s sharp intraday rallies on 5 and 6 January, driven by strong volume and technical momentum, contrasted with subsequent profit-taking and broader market weakness, resulting in a mixed but resilient weekly performance.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>3bae20352567d75e9bf8a208aefb246b</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 06:25:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Viji Finance Ltd Gains 24.00%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/viji-finance-ltd-gains-2400-4-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3788951</link><description>Viji Finance Ltd delivered a remarkable 24.00% gain over the week ending 9 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex, which declined 2.62% during the same period. The stock’s journey was marked by a series of upper circuit hits driven by robust buying momentum, culminating in a sharp reversal on the final trading day amid heavy selling pressure. This review analyses the key events shaping the stock’s volatile week and their impact on price and investor sentiment.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>9cfbeb6657355cfdf4b112d6fc430567</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 06:25:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Solid Stone Company Ltd Gains 0.63%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Mixed Moves</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/solid-stone-company-ltd-gains-063-2-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-mixed-moves-3788950</link><description>Solid Stone Company Ltd recorded a modest weekly gain of 0.63%, closing at Rs.28.89 on 09 Jan 2026, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 2.62% over the same period. The stock showed resilience amid a challenging market backdrop, buoyed by improved valuation metrics midweek and despite ending near a 52-week low. This review analyses the key events shaping the stock’s performance during the week of 5 to 9 January 2026.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>79ab47b913587819ae208ac685995414</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 06:25:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arunis Abode Ltd Gains 7.43%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/arunis-abode-ltd-gains-743-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-rally-3788949</link><description>Arunis Abode Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, gaining 7.43% from Rs.158.15 to Rs.169.90 between 5 and 9 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined by 2.62% over the same period. The stock’s trajectory was marked by multiple new 52-week and all-time highs, reflecting strong investor confidence amid a mixed broader market environment.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>70d5dbdb4676b454fb34a368c3a69668</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 06:25:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Himatsingka Seide Ltd Falls 8.00%: Key Technical and Fundamental Challenges Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/himatsingka-seide-ltd-falls-800-key-technical-and-fundamental-challenges-shape-the-week-3788954</link><description>Himatsingka Seide Ltd’s stock endured a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, declining 8.00% to close at Rs.105.75, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 2.62% fall over the same period. The stock’s downward momentum was marked by a technical downgrade to Strong Sell and a fresh 52-week low, reflecting persistent bearish sentiment amid weak fundamentals and sector headwinds.
Time: 55 minutes ago</description><guid>5262a79fb2b0fc66052af8f2c33f0963</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 06:25:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Easy Trip Planners Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/easy-trip-planners-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3788755</link><description>Easy Trip Planners Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 18 Nov 2025, reflecting a reassessment of the stock’s outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed below are current as of 11 January 2026, providing investors with the latest view of the company’s position.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c6c7c15ec1cc75deb1783085c4dbe3fb</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 06:25:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rishabh Instruments Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/rishabh-instruments-ltd-is-rated-hold-3788752</link><description>Rishabh Instruments Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 13 Oct 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 11 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4a730119066eca4b383a5f306ddb8b2e</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 06:25:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gujarat Industries Power Co Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/gujarat-industries-power-co-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3788753</link><description>Gujarat Industries Power Co Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 13 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 11 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3ba9c4f98a54b516cf05fd83de0e7d92</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 06:25:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>India Pesticides Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/india-pesticides-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3788748</link><description>India Pesticides Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 29 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 11 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>dc21e69e4674a0d5295061cc1a4bfe92</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 06:25:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indokem Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/indokem-ltd-is-rated-sell-3788749</link><description>Indokem Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 16 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 11 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>90040e447bc434ea84eb1d0ca5c2a510</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 06:25:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mac Charles (India) Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/mac-charles-india-ltd-is-rated-sell-3788747</link><description>Mac Charles (India) Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 27 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 11 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>61b61ad012f7ec4bdf9b330bf17318ae</guid><pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 06:25:19 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>