<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:36:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Adani Green Energy Ltd Gains 14.05%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-green-energy-ltd-gains-1405-6-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3826027</link><description>Adani Green Energy Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 14.05% from Rs.851.85 to Rs.971.55 between 2 and 6 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period. The stock exhibited notable intraday volatility and a series of sharp rebounds following earlier declines, reflecting a complex interplay of technical shifts, market sentiment, and sector dynamics.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>ca28d657c988147047dde94327ebc46c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:36:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fine Organic Industries Gains 4.28%: Mixed Technical Signals Shape Weekly Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/fine-organic-industries-gains-428-mixed-technical-signals-shape-weekly-momentum-3826026</link><description>Fine Organic Industries Ltd recorded a solid weekly gain of 4.28%, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise during the week ending 6 February 2026. The stock showed strong momentum early in the week, driven by a notable intraday surge on 3 February, before experiencing a mild correction in the latter sessions amid mixed technical signals. This review analyses the key events and price movements shaping the stock’s performance over the past five trading days.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>c86aa0103b38d58746d651aa4882d698</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:36:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Solara Active Pharma Falls 6.67%: Margin Pressures and Volatility Weigh on Shares</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/solara-active-pharma-falls-667-margin-pressures-and-volatility-weigh-on-shares-3826023</link><description>Solara Active Pharma Sciences Ltd experienced a turbulent week ending 6 February 2026, with its share price declining 6.67% to close at Rs.471.20, sharply underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.51% over the same period. Despite early gains in the week, the stock faced mounting selling pressure amid disappointing quarterly results and heightened intraday volatility, culminating in a steep drop on the final trading day.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>727efb6900cfc6cb6e856ec4f1509406</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:36:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Parvati Sweetners Declines 6.36% Amid Mixed Technicals and Weak Financials</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/parvati-sweetners-declines-636-amid-mixed-technicals-and-weak-financials-3826025</link><description>Parvati Sweetners and Power Ltd experienced a turbulent week, closing at Rs.8.83 on 6 February 2026, down 6.36% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.9.43. This decline contrasted with the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period, highlighting the stock’s underperformance amid mixed technical signals and weak financial fundamentals. The week was marked by a notable Golden Cross formation on 3 February, signalling potential bullish momentum, followed by a downgrade in the company’s rating to Sell, reflecting persistent operational challenges.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>b7f4bc88aefd27a6d9e579e12acda3fa</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:36:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gayatri Highways Gains 11.62%: 4 Key Events Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gayatri-highways-gains-1162-4-key-events-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3826022</link><description>Gayatri Highways Ltd delivered a volatile yet strong performance during the week ending 6 February 2026, surging 11.62% from Rs.1.98 to Rs.2.21, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% gain. The stock experienced sharp swings hitting both upper and lower circuit limits amid intense buying and selling pressures, reflecting a week marked by heightened investor activity and regulatory trading halts.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>bff2cf6a7a574476b536f601c9f51c4b</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:36:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HDFC Asset Management Gains 8.01%: 5 Key Factors Driving This Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hdfc-asset-management-gains-801-5-key-factors-driving-this-weeks-momentum-3826024</link><description>HDFC Asset Management Company Ltd (HDFC AMC) delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 8.01% from ₹2,517.85 to ₹2,719.55 between 2 and 6 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period. The stock’s rally was supported by robust intraday gains, a notable surge in derivatives open interest, and mixed but improving technical signals, reflecting a complex but generally positive market sentiment.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>7b01a7179fa745fa931ae2178f9f0524</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:36:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tembo Global Industries Gains 5.19%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tembo-global-industries-gains-519-5-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-rally-3826021</link><description>Tembo Global Industries Ltd closed the week at Rs.572.30, marking a 5.19% gain from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.544.05, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise over the same period. The stock’s volatile week featured a sharp rebound from early bearish momentum, an upper circuit hit, and a strong quarterly earnings report, reflecting a complex interplay of technical shifts and fundamental strength.
Time: 3 minutes ago</description><guid>1a880fc4ac598d05d1af86237867782c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:36:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aaron Industries Gains 6.84%: Valuation and Earnings Drive Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aaron-industries-gains-684-valuation-and-earnings-drive-volatility-3826019</link><description>Aaron Industries Ltd recorded a robust weekly gain of 6.84%, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise during the week ending 6 February 2026. The stock’s upward momentum was supported by strong profit growth reported in Q3 FY26, despite ongoing concerns over stretched valuation metrics that have led to a Sell mojo grade. This review analyses the key events and price movements shaping the stock’s performance over the week.
Time: 3 minutes ago</description><guid>4242da56ade5eeed08cddacf6421644b</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:36:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Synergy Green Industries Gains 6.80%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/synergy-green-industries-gains-680-3-key-factors-driving-the-week-3826020</link><description>Synergy Green Industries Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, gaining 6.80% from ₹519.00 to ₹554.30 between 2 and 6 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise over the same period. The stock’s trajectory was shaped by a series of technical shifts and rating changes amid ongoing financial challenges, culminating in a cautious upgrade from Strong Sell to Sell. This review analyses the key events and price movements that defined the week for Synergy Green.
Time: 3 minutes ago</description><guid>b2b498fd5225fc40f53555819c91270f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:36:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rajshree Polypack Gains 14.76%: Valuation Shift and Q3 Profit Decline Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rajshree-polypack-gains-1476-valuation-shift-and-q3-profit-decline-shape-the-week-3826018</link><description>Rajshree Polypack Ltd delivered a strong weekly price performance, rising 14.76% from Rs.15.85 to Rs.18.19, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 1.51% gain over the same period. The week was marked by a notable shift in valuation metrics signalling improved price attractiveness, followed by a sharp 52% plunge in Q3 FY26 profit amid contracting revenue, which tempered gains on the final trading day.
Time: 3 minutes ago</description><guid>4580b6656557c2574049475bbdcc524d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:36:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sky Gold &amp; Diamonds Gains 4.79%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Mixed Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sky-gold-diamonds-gains-479-4-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-mixed-momentum-3826017</link><description>Sky Gold &amp; Diamonds Ltd closed the week with a 4.79% gain, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise between 2 and 6 February 2026. The stock exhibited notable intraday volatility, driven by a mix of technical shifts, a rating downgrade, and sector-specific dynamics. Despite a strong midweek surge, the stock ended the week in a consolidation phase, reflecting a complex interplay of bullish and bearish signals.
Time: 3 minutes ago</description><guid>c449beef58db36c8cab4f9e14c817b27</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:36:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aavas Financiers Drops 10.57% Amid Valuation Concerns and Operational Headwinds</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aavas-financiers-drops-1057-amid-valuation-concerns-and-operational-headwinds-3826015</link><description>Aavas Financiers Ltd experienced a challenging week from 2 to 6 February 2026, with its stock price declining sharply by 10.57% to close at Rs.1,301.70, significantly underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.51% over the same period. The week was marked by a series of valuation concerns, operational headwinds, and technical weakness culminating in a fresh 52-week low, despite the company reporting record quarterly earnings. This review analyses the key events and market reactions that shaped the stock’s performance during the week.
Time: 3 minutes ago</description><guid>79ed3733f44fde4b31aaf13b93bdb106</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:36:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manorama Industries Gains 4.04%: 3 Key Technical Shifts Shape Weekly Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/manorama-industries-gains-404-3-key-technical-shifts-shape-weekly-performance-3826016</link><description>Manorama Industries Ltd recorded a 4.04% gain over the week ending 6 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise. The stock exhibited notable volatility, opening sharply lower on 2 February before rallying strongly midweek amid mixed technical signals and market sentiment. Despite a late-week pullback, Manorama Industries demonstrated resilience relative to the broader market, supported by shifts in technical momentum and sector dynamics.
Time: 3 minutes ago</description><guid>5b15a072c0bf27e6cdaa180d90206e21</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:36:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A-1 Ltd Falls 10.18%: Downgrade and Mixed Technicals Shape Volatile Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/a-1-ltd-falls-1018-downgrade-and-mixed-technicals-shape-volatile-week-3826014</link><description>A-1 Ltd experienced a turbulent week ending 6 February 2026, with its share price declining 10.18% from Rs.33.30 to Rs.29.91, sharply underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.51% over the same period. The week was marked by a significant downgrade to a Sell rating amid weakening financials and mixed technical signals, contributing to heightened volatility and investor caution.
Time: 3 minutes ago</description><guid>ebd98ee03a0baf4af923303a2cbf11a6</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:36:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Marine Electricals Gains 4.28%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Mixed Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/marine-electricals-gains-428-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-mixed-momentum-3826012</link><description>Marine Electricals (India) Ltd closed the week at Rs.188.14, marking a 4.28% gain from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.180.41, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise over the same period. Despite this positive price movement, the week was characterised by mixed technical signals and valuation concerns, culminating in a downgrade to a Sell rating. Key developments included the formation of a bearish Death Cross, elevated valuation metrics signalling price risk, and a shift to bearish technical momentum amid mixed momentum indicators.
Time: 3 minutes ago</description><guid>9b17e86401f9d9c1bc1bd732a50931a7</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:36:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vinny Overseas Ltd Gains 15.74%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Volatile Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vinny-overseas-ltd-gains-1574-2-key-factors-driving-the-volatile-week-3826013</link><description>Vinny Overseas Ltd experienced a highly volatile week from 2 to 6 February 2026, ultimately gaining 15.74% to close at Rs.1.25, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 1.51% rise. The week was marked by a dramatic rebound from a 52-week low on 2 February to an upper circuit surge of 19.8% on 3 February, reflecting a sharp shift in market sentiment amid persistent fundamental challenges.
Time: 3 minutes ago</description><guid>618c250f252f8cd1984c79ae48d17ca1</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:36:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vivid Mercantile Ltd Surges 3.81%: Key Financial Turnarounds and Valuation Shifts Drive Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vivid-mercantile-ltd-surges-381-key-financial-turnarounds-and-valuation-shifts-drive-momentum-3826009</link><description>Vivid Mercantile Ltd recorded a mixed but ultimately positive week, closing at Rs.7.08 on 6 February 2026, up 3.81% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.6.82. This outpaced the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period, reflecting a volatile trading week marked by significant price swings, strong quarterly results, and multiple rating upgrades. Despite a sharp 17% drop on the final trading day, the stock’s overall weekly performance was buoyed by robust financial disclosures and improved valuation metrics.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>db29d112fb795060fe77c04c84628a3d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:36:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Iris Clothings Gains 5.12%: Valuation Shifts and Profit Growth Shape Weekly Moves</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/iris-clothings-gains-512-valuation-shifts-and-profit-growth-shape-weekly-moves-3826006</link><description>Iris Clothings Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, rising 5.12% from Rs.32.25 to Rs.33.90 between 2 and 6 February 2026, comfortably outpacing the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period. The week was marked by strong profit growth reported in Q2 FY26 and a notable shift in valuation metrics that sparked investor interest despite concerns over stretched multiples. Daily price movements reflected a mix of optimism and cautious profit-taking amid evolving market sentiment.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>69838dfe8531fe364dd7ca0214bdb505</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:36:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Total Gas Ltd Gains 3.12%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Move</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-total-gas-ltd-gains-312-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-move-3826011</link><description>Adani Total Gas Ltd closed the week ending 6 February 2026 with a 3.12% gain, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise over the same period. The stock showed notable volatility, highlighted by a strong gap-up and intraday surge on 3 February, followed by mixed technical signals amid fluctuating market conditions. This review analyses the key events shaping the stock’s performance and the implications for investors.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>ed033cb9a73ca3b8a6a84d79514e411b</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:36:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nila Spaces Ltd Gains 3.85%: 5 Key Factors Driving Mixed Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nila-spaces-ltd-gains-385-5-key-factors-driving-mixed-momentum-3826008</link><description>Nila Spaces Ltd recorded a moderate weekly gain of 3.85%, closing at ₹15.09 on 6 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise over the same period. The stock’s price action reflected a volatile week marked by shifts in technical momentum, a downgrade in rating, and mixed financial signals, all set against a backdrop of broader market fluctuations. Despite short-term uncertainty, the company’s long-term performance remains robust, underscoring a complex investment landscape for stakeholders.
Time: 4 minutes ago</description><guid>9f2f6ff8b0aa0115501039102616e6c3</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:36:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:36:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>