<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:47:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3844841</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has unfolded with a nuanced picture across Indian equities, as 4,075 companies reported results reflecting a cautious recovery. While the proportion of companies delivering positive earnings has inched up to 46.0%, this marks only a modest improvement from previous quarters, underscoring ongoing challenges amid a complex macroeconomic backdrop.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>dd98069f3d0ca4e5dfcdc6a79772b88d</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:47:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jainco Projects Q3 FY26: Micro-Cap Struggles with Minimal Revenue and Mounting Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/jainco-projects-q3-fy26-micro-cap-struggles-with-minimal-revenue-and-mounting-concerns-3844838</link><description>Jainco Projects (India) Ltd., a micro-cap trading and distribution company with a market capitalisation of just ₹5.00 crores, reported minimal financial activity in Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), with net sales of merely ₹0.11 crores and negligible net profit. The stock, currently trading at ₹5.29, remains in bearish technical territory and has declined 26.22% year-to-date, reflecting deep investor scepticism about the company's operational viability and future prospects.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>decadee94a79a8982d77c969ffd6f4a3</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:47:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Covance Softsol Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-covance-softsol-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3844828</link><description>Covance Softsol Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are strong, with a net profit increase of 64.19% and an operating margin of 33.37%. However, challenges in capital efficiency and a decline in promoter holding raise concerns about the sustainability of this growth.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>99444e9858b9b6e4d58fef08c9cd1aff</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:47:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Elegant Floriculture &amp; Agrotech (India) Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-elegant-floriculture-agrotech-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3844827</link><description>Elegant Floriculture &amp; Agrotech (India) Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, showing a 96.55% drop in net sales and a 93.33% decline in net profit compared to the previous quarter, raising questions about the sustainability of its business model despite a slight improvement in profit margin. The company's operational volatility and increasing liabilities indicate significant financial challenges ahead.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>7ce81e30191406de18949c83234e310d</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:47:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are AVG Logistics Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-avg-logistics-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3844826</link><description>AVG Logistics Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show a net profit of ₹5.40 crores, up 6.30% sequentially but down 2.00% year-on-year, alongside declining net sales for the third consecutive quarter. While operating margins improved to 19.46% due to cost management, rising interest costs raise concerns about financial flexibility amid ongoing revenue challenges.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>696aece0531a235856be111e0a882ba4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:47:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-orissa-bengal-carrier-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3844825</link><description>Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd's latest results are poor, showing a net loss of ₹2.39 crores in Q3 FY26 compared to a profit last year, with revenues down 16.15% year-on-year and significant declines in operating margins and profitability. The company is facing substantial operational challenges and increasing financial pressures.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>99f7edc0b8319891a0c4585aa74bae23</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:47:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are IFGL Refractories Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-ifgl-refractories-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3844824</link><description>IFGL Refractories Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 23.70% year-on-year, but the company reported a net loss of ₹3.08 crores and declining profitability, indicating significant operational challenges despite increased sales.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>d86f93c6950ae5eb987d36b9daf761bd</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:47:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Sinnar Bidi Udyog Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-sinnar-bidi-udyog-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3844823</link><description>Sinnar Bidi Udyog Ltd's latest results are concerning, showing a 47.65% decline in net sales and a net loss of ₹0.07 crores, indicating significant operational challenges and negative margins. Despite being debt-free, the company's financial health and investor interest are under pressure due to declining performance.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>baf1e61657ecc1765c57636ed1992a49</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:47:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Magnus Steel &amp; Infra Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-magnus-steel-infra-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3844822</link><description>Magnus Steel &amp; Infra Ltd's latest results show a net profit of ₹1.08 crores and a 260.47% year-on-year revenue growth, indicating a positive shift in profitability. However, concerns remain due to a 14.84% sequential revenue decline, reduced operating margins, negative shareholder funds, and a high debt-to-equity ratio, highlighting ongoing structural challenges.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>17480997e5a23c1e3a6bf20ffab2c0f8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:47:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Rama Paper Mills Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-rama-paper-mills-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3844821</link><description>Rama Paper Mills Ltd's latest results are concerning, showing a net loss of ₹1.62 crores and a drastic revenue decline of 96.72% quarter-on-quarter, indicating severe operational challenges and financial distress. The company faces significant risks to its viability due to negative shareholder funds and ongoing liquidity issues.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>8f77ad158b5b902c3a1db56825574350</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:47:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Supra Pacific Management Consultancy Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-supra-pacific-management-consultancy-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3844820</link><description>Supra Pacific Management Consultancy Ltd's latest results show impressive revenue growth of 104.45% year-on-year, with a record quarterly net profit of ₹2.09 crores; however, concerns about low return on equity and high debt levels suggest potential risks for investors.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>c76e25caff9113ed958dd56d7a168b2f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:47:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Kay Power &amp; Paper Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-kay-power-paper-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3844819</link><description>Kay Power &amp; Paper Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, showing a net loss of -₹0.09 crore and a 37.75% decline in revenue to ₹4.75 crores, indicating significant operational challenges and a precarious financial outlook. The company's stock has also dropped 71.25% over the past year, reflecting weakened investor sentiment.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>5ba6ea7729d19ac8463d46b927e2e9ff</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:47:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Alpine Housing Development Corporation Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-alpine-housing-development-corporation-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3844818</link><description>Alpine Housing Development Corporation Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show a net profit of ₹2.17 crores, up 26.91% year-on-year, and significant quarter-on-quarter improvements in revenue and margins. However, low return on equity and capital employed, along with a high debt-to-EBITDA ratio, indicate ongoing challenges in capital efficiency.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>41c9b4436ec25e7e420b76e4c8441c57</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:47:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Shraddha Prime Projects Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-shraddha-prime-projects-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3844817</link><description>Shraddha Prime Projects Ltd's latest results show strong year-on-year profit growth of 50.88% and impressive revenue growth of 194.75%, but declining operating margins and a high debt-to-equity ratio raise concerns about financial stability and sustainability. Overall, the performance is mixed, with significant positives and critical challenges to watch.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>4fec9d6b1d10337e8880a2d63738f084</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:47:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Magnum Ventures Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-magnum-ventures-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3844816</link><description>Magnum Ventures Ltd's latest results are concerning, with a 14.10% decline in net sales and a 78.33% drop in net profit due to high interest costs, despite a slight improvement in operating margin. The company faces significant challenges in maintaining profitability and market share.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>6f1957f0a56842b22a1c982a90d0ff08</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:47:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Thomas Scott India Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-thomas-scott-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3844815</link><description>Thomas Scott India Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth with net sales up 16.37% sequentially and 45.93% year-on-year, but profitability is under pressure as operating and profit margins have contracted. While the revenue performance is impressive, concerns about margin compression and lack of institutional interest suggest caution moving forward.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>5c94fc9dcacad1302c2fb74bf3445ed3</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:47:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Bannari Amman Spinning Mills Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-bannari-amman-spinning-mills-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3844814</link><description>Bannari Amman Spinning Mills Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show a mixed performance, with a net profit decline of 59.28% sequentially but a 113.21% increase year-over-year. While operating margins remained stable, declining sales and rising interest costs indicate significant operational challenges.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>30da51820ea4ecf523bd4cb6fc112415</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:47:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Modern Dairies Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-modern-dairies-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3844813</link><description>Modern Dairies Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show a 6.73% revenue growth to ₹87.48 crores, but net profit fell 27.81% to ₹1.22 crores, indicating profitability challenges and ongoing operational pressures despite slight revenue increases. Year-on-year revenue also declined by 1.44%, raising concerns about the company's sustainability in a competitive market.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>9250aeddb2e673b8f757674baff56535</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:47:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Lux Industries Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-lux-industries-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3844812</link><description>Lux Industries Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 21.72% to ₹672.64 crores, but profitability has significantly declined, with net profit down 59.73% to ₹12.91 crores, raising concerns about operational efficiency and financial sustainability.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>818fb815ab636d2ad197bedc2f11403d</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:47:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Tamil Nadu Telecommunications Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-tamil-nadu-telecommunications-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3844811</link><description>Tamil Nadu Telecommunications Ltd's latest results are concerning, showing a net loss of ₹3.46 crores in Q3 FY26 and zero revenue for seven consecutive quarters, leading to negative shareholder funds and a severe liquidity crisis. The company's financial health is classified as "RISKY," indicating significant operational and financial challenges.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ff51fd3bce98999e3b73a0b224ffd355</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:47:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:47:25 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>