<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 01:19:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is P N Gadgil Jewellers Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-p-n-gadgil-jewellers-ltd-fallingrising-3785008</link><description>On 07-Jan, P N Gadgil Jewellers Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 5.23% to close at ₹641.00. This upward movement reflects a combination of sector-wide gains, improved investor participation, and the company’s robust financial metrics, which together have contributed to renewed market confidence.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>039479283de4354864b6071ed1e40a1c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 01:19:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Virtual Galaxy Infotech Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-virtual-galaxy-infotech-ltd-fallingrising-3785007</link><description>On 07-Jan, Virtual Galaxy Infotech Ltd experienced a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹145.25, down ₹6.10 or 4.03% from the previous session. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock's underperformance relative to broader market benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>7ffdeaa1f020eefb5fc19644fc6eabbc</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 01:19:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is EMA Partners India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ema-partners-india-ltd-fallingrising-3785006</link><description>On 07-Jan, EMA Partners India Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 6.21% to close at ₹89.10. This drop reflects a broader pattern of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and waning investor interest.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>e9900bdb5d402085da200e29f61bea0f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 01:19:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is SPP Polymer Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-spp-polymer-ltd-fallingrising-3785005</link><description>On 07-Jan, SPP Polymer Ltd’s stock price fell by 2.55% to ₹15.30, continuing a trend of significant underperformance relative to the broader market and its sector peers.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>f322a2af44d6d888089f7ed32ce814a5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 01:19:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Gopal Snacks Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gopal-snacks-ltd-fallingrising-3785004</link><description>On 07-Jan, Gopal Snacks Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 4.29% to ₹335.30 by 09:26 PM, reflecting renewed investor enthusiasm despite the company’s ongoing fundamental challenges and subdued long-term growth prospects.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>25b837ec0ab37ae44952cba5585d0536</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 01:19:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sati Poly Plast Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sati-poly-plast-ltd-fallingrising-3785003</link><description>On 07-Jan, Sati Poly Plast Ltd’s stock price fell by 3.08% to ₹58.15, continuing a significant downward trajectory that has seen the share price approach its 52-week low and underperform both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>1cffad133aace9ea7f423650f3a67f5f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 01:19:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vibhor Steel Tubes Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vibhor-steel-tubes-ltd-fallingrising-3785002</link><description>On 07-Jan, Vibhor Steel Tubes Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling 4.11% to close at ₹129.65. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s underperformance relative to both its sector and broader market benchmarks, driven by deteriorating financial metrics and subdued investor sentiment.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>263c6a1bb97863d7207e51a6fbab05c7</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 01:19:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Tata Technologies Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-tata-technologies-ltd-fallingrising-3785001</link><description>On 07-Jan, Tata Technologies Ltd witnessed a notable price increase of 5.32%, closing at ₹683.45. This rise follows a two-day decline and reflects a short-term trend reversal despite the company’s longer-term challenges and mixed financial performance.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>d5d12f9cd588dcebe2f6da2c9ebfd871</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 01:19:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Senco Gold Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-senco-gold-ltd-fallingrising-3785000</link><description>On 07-Jan, Senco Gold Ltd witnessed a significant price rise of 11.69%, closing at ₹361.50, driven by robust sector performance and encouraging company fundamentals despite a challenging one-year return.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>2de527bdfbc0bcd977c6258a77febf30</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 01:19:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Cyient DLM Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-cyient-dlm-ltd-fallingrising-3784999</link><description>As of 07-Jan, Cyient DLM Ltd’s stock price has been on a downward trajectory, reflecting a combination of underwhelming market performance and cautious investor sentiment despite some positive financial indicators.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>bd4bc411f2decf89d18877db170adc91</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 01:19:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Mankind Pharma Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-mankind-pharma-ltd-fallingrising-3784998</link><description>On 07-Jan, Mankind Pharma Ltd's stock price rose by 2.82% to ₹2,305.00, reflecting a notable uptick driven by recent investor enthusiasm and positive short-term momentum despite underlying challenges in its financial performance over the past year.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>423094f3ecd3bdf6d3e9544b83b76dfe</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 01:19:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Pearl Green Clubs and Resorts Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-pearl-green-clubs-and-resorts-ltd-fallingrising-3784997</link><description>On 07-Jan, Pearl Green Clubs and Resorts Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹126.45, down ₹5.45 or 4.13% from the previous close. Despite opening with a positive gap, the stock succumbed to significant intraday volatility and selling pressure, reflecting a challenging trading session for investors.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>db3b0469d844dabd9695a5ef25419d15</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 01:19:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Padmanabh Alloys &amp; Polymers Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-padmanabh-alloys-polymers-ltd-fallingrising-3784996</link><description>On 07-Jan, Padmanabh Alloys &amp; Polymers Ltd recorded a 1.66% increase in its share price, closing at ₹16.49. This rise comes despite the company’s challenging long-term returns and subdued investor participation, reflecting a nuanced market response to its recent performance.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>c0672d3693b664a5d9c5206f450b18db</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 01:19:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vinny Overseas Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vinny-overseas-ltd-fallingrising-3784995</link><description>As of 07-Jan, Vinny Overseas Ltd’s stock price has continued its downward trajectory, reflecting sustained underperformance relative to market benchmarks and sector peers. The share price closed at ₹1.23, down 0.81% on the day, signalling persistent investor caution.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>102efd162327b439c80abf379398c8b5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 01:19:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Evans Electric Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-evans-electric-ltd-fallingrising-3784994</link><description>On 07-Jan, Evans Electric Ltd witnessed a significant rise in its share price, climbing by 9.54% to close at ₹132.00. This notable gain comes despite a broader market environment where the benchmark Sensex showed a slight decline, highlighting the stock's relative strength and investor interest on the day.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>2cd17f2e93b5fa63a1885e1a78921dab</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 01:19:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Rajnandini Metal Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-rajnandini-metal-ltd-fallingrising-3784993</link><description>As of 07-Jan, Rajnandini Metal Ltd’s stock price has fallen to ₹4.54, down 2.78% on the day, reflecting ongoing concerns over the company’s deteriorating financial health and subdued investor interest.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>4da11b760def49afcbc350020f1b85f4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 01:19:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Power &amp; Instrumentation (Gujarat) Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-power-instrumentation-gujarat-ltd-fallingrising-3784992</link><description>On 07-Jan, Power &amp; Instrumentation (Gujarat) Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling 2.75% to close at ₹116.50. This movement continues a broader downward trend that has seen the stock underperform significantly against the benchmark Sensex over multiple timeframes.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>24098f6d545269803d847d1750031613</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 01:19:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sandhar Technologies Limited falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sandhar-technologies-limited-fallingrising-3784991</link><description>On 07-Jan, Sandhar Technologies Limited's stock price rose by 1.09% to ₹582.65, reflecting robust financial performance and sustained market outperformance relative to benchmarks and peers.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>4f7cf1dac7239def91a2a900a723b6ca</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 01:19:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is National Standard (India) Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-national-standard-india-ltd-fallingrising-3784990</link><description>On 07-Jan, National Standard (India) Ltd witnessed a sharp rise in its share price, climbing 20.0% to close at ₹1,503.65, reversing a three-day decline and significantly outperforming both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>b5d7db01c85f60bc80ff4dbeac14140d</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 01:19:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Focus Lighting &amp; Fixtures Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-focus-lighting-fixtures-ltd-fallingrising-3784989</link><description>As of 07-Jan, Focus Lighting &amp; Fixtures Ltd has recorded a notable rise in its share price, climbing 3.56% to ₹82.65. This upward movement reflects a surge in investor interest and short-term optimism, despite the company’s ongoing struggles with profitability and underperformance over the past year.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>d65c60340b930d4cb787eb5e3338d968</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 01:19:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 01:19:09 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>