<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:36:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Inox India Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/inox-india-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3792247</link><description>Inox India Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's long-term strength amid a challenging market backdrop.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>b9d3a9fb90683bf397ef7101da2627dc</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Landmark Cars Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/landmark-cars-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3792248</link><description>Landmark Cars Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a sustained bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>3711dc9e2293df98447c55fd620152b6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Infibeam Avenues Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/infibeam-avenues-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3792250</link><description>Infibeam Avenues Ltd, a key player in the Financial Technology sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>57055b354773bc64215f670c8f358329</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dr Lal Pathlabs Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dr-lal-pathlabs-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3792244</link><description>Dr Lal Pathlabs Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term outlook within the healthcare services sector.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>fe2a6346a73fb3f3973258014f630b8e</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ekansh Concepts Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ekansh-concepts-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3792245</link><description>Ekansh Concepts Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development highlights a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raises concerns about its long-term strength amid mixed fundamental and technical signals.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>098bb3d7d1273cb7768cfefa533033fb</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Veljan Denison Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/veljan-denison-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3792251</link><description>Veljan Denison Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has recently formed a Death Cross—a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and raises concerns about the stock's medium to long-term momentum.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>0c5c79bff8a73f58a2106a15c0c7d57f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cil Securities Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cil-securities-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3792246</link><description>Cil Securities Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about its medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>3e3ed4888048d0f558ecd2fcbe2634dd</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AVT Natural Products Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/avt-natural-products-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3792249</link><description>AVT Natural Products Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>cead6182ce52c14a0c5d8b94ae69d3d9</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Huhtamaki India Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/huhtamaki-india-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3792239</link><description>Huhtamaki India Ltd, a key player in the packaging sector, has recently formed a Death Cross as its 50-day moving average (DMA) crossed below the 200-DMA, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This technical development, coupled with deteriorating fundamentals and weak price performance, raises concerns about the stock’s near- and long-term outlook.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>9704bb9cf578f52ec9ad215847780af5</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Filatex India Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/filatex-india-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3792241</link><description>Filatex India Ltd, a small-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>9f5c765503bc9571117ebfb02f9f7f1c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Munjal Auto Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/munjal-auto-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3792237</link><description>Munjal Auto Industries Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average, signalling a potential shift towards a prolonged bearish trend. This development reflects deteriorating momentum and raises concerns about the stock’s near- and long-term prospects amid already challenging market conditions.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>1ab10bee844b3c62a11f54a6e0bf31c7</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oil &amp; Natural Gas Corporation Ltd. Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/oil-natural-gas-corporation-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3792236</link><description>Oil &amp; Natural Gas Corporation Ltd. (ONGC) has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum, raising concerns among investors about potential weakness ahead.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>c5c92e407d9ef88e194ae171ce932bb1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Andhra Sugars Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/andhra-sugars-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3792235</link><description>Andhra Sugars Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>15d02686ccbeac0560952f83a391989b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AMD Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/amd-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3792242</link><description>AMD Industries Ltd, a micro-cap player in the packaging sector, has recently formed a Death Cross as its 50-day moving average crossed below the 200-day moving average. This technical development is widely regarded as a bearish signal, indicating a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raising concerns about its long-term outlook.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>fec282d7a8b593a54d84f7b93f47879c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tilak Ventures Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend and Long-Term Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tilak-ventures-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-and-long-term-weakness-3792238</link><description>Tilak Ventures Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>e6ecbb946ed4303dbc8ffd50ad8e3ea1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanginita Chemicals Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Indicating Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sanginita-chemicals-ltd-forms-golden-cross-indicating-potential-bullish-breakout-3792243</link><description>Sanginita Chemicals Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum for the micro-cap Chemicals &amp; Petrochemicals company, despite its challenging historical performance.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>5976a2a1e542b671bee5ea185942a370</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manaksia Aluminium Company Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/manaksia-aluminium-company-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3792240</link><description>Manaksia Aluminium Company Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a shift towards long-term upward momentum for the stock, which has already demonstrated impressive performance relative to the broader market.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>657d6f3f11b6ee3d9e48749c5a776339</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Robust Quarterly Earnings Drive Market Optimism as 72 Stocks Report Dec-2025 Results</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/robust-quarterly-earnings-drive-market-optimism-as-72-stocks-report-dec-2025-results-3792234</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has delivered a mixed yet encouraging picture, with 72 companies reporting results. While large caps showed restrained positive momentum, mid and small caps outperformed significantly, signalling a shift in market dynamics and sectoral strength as investors digest the latest financial disclosures.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>27e24ded876f62f31f10e47611d9b35b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pavna Industries Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pavna-industries-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3792220</link><description>Pavna Industries Ltd, a player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, recorded a fresh 52-week low of Rs.19.28 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid persistent downward momentum and underperformance relative to its sector and broader market indices.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>518282117baaa6b325d8c2e4e9c175a0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:36:38 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>