<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:22:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Craftsman Automation Ltd Hits All-Time High at Rs.8068.75, Marking a Milestone in Market Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/craftsman-automation-ltd-hits-all-time-high-at-rs806875-marking-a-milestone-in-market-performance-3783483</link><description>Craftsman Automation Ltd has reached an all-time high of Rs.8068.75, underscoring its robust performance within the Auto Components &amp; Equipments industry. This milestone reflects sustained growth and strong market positioning, as the stock continues to outperform both its sector and broader benchmarks.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>1f6a5ecc6f195078b9fd9b05709a69d8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:22:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Swiggy Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amidst Heightened Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/swiggy-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amidst-heightened-price-pressure-3783482</link><description>Swiggy Ltd’s shares declined sharply on 6 Jan 2026, hitting an intraday low of Rs 356.25, reflecting a significant price pressure that outpaced sector and benchmark indices. The stock’s performance today underscores ongoing challenges as it continues to trade below all key moving averages, signalling sustained bearish momentum.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>0478d9931479a060dfb51a6e65efb5fd</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:22:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kaynes Technology India Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kaynes-technology-india-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-3783484</link><description>Shares of Kaynes Technology India Ltd declined sharply on 6 Jan 2026, hitting an intraday low of Rs 3,710.4, marking a 7.21% drop from the previous close. The stock underperformed its sector and the broader market, reflecting immediate selling pressure and subdued market sentiment.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>eb121c6241eb834a5358728a8a8c9f9c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:22:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ITC Ltd. Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 6 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/itc-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-6-jan-2026-3783485</link><description>ITC Ltd. experienced a notable decline today, touching an intraday low of Rs 337.9, reflecting persistent price pressure amid broader sector weakness and subdued market sentiment. The stock’s performance aligns with ongoing downward trends in the FMCG sector, particularly within the cigarettes and tobacco segment.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>f6e9af7d2ef14cfb79635bdb97a44056</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:22:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Afcons Infrastructure Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/afcons-infrastructure-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amidst-prolonged-downtrend-3783480</link><description>Afcons Infrastructure Ltd’s stock plummeted to a new all-time low of Rs.376.15 on 6 Jan 2026, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The construction sector company has underperformed across multiple time frames, reflecting persistent pressures on its financial and market performance.
Time: 30 minutes ago</description><guid>c3c7ce9a8dcf2f17e717330bf2d7be0a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:22:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Julien Agro Infratech Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/julien-agro-infratech-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3783478</link><description>Julien Agro Infratech Ltd’s stock price declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.2.1 on 6 Jan 2026, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing downward trajectory. The stock has underperformed both its sector and the broader market, reflecting persistent challenges in its financial and market performance over the past year.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>288b5dc78d3f82ec32fdaee1e9af6c1c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:22:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Salzer Electronics Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/salzer-electronics-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3783479</link><description>Salzer Electronics Ltd, a player in the Other Electrical Equipment sector, has touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.675 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has underperformed both its sector and the broader market over the past year, reflecting ongoing pressures on its financial performance and valuation metrics.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>f5ff3dfc9ebff1f79d1f5c95c5e42fd9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:22:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ERP Soft Systems Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.69 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/erp-soft-systems-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs69-amidst-continued-downtrend-3783481</link><description>ERP Soft Systems Ltd has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.69, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing concerns about its financial metrics and valuation.
Time: 42 minutes ago</description><guid>50068cdd85704390a3a71416406824d0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:22:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Swiggy Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amidst Weak Price Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/swiggy-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amidst-weak-price-performance-3783476</link><description>Swiggy Ltd, a prominent player in the E-Retail and E-Commerce sector, witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this spike, the stock has underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting a cautious or bearish stance among traders.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>e29a76bc1acb6bab4100269e07d27b59</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:22:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Premier Energies Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Price Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/premier-energies-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-price-weakness-3783477</link><description>Premier Energies Ltd, a mid-cap player in the Other Electrical Equipment sector, has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, coinciding with a notable decline in its share price. This development signals heightened market activity and evolving positioning among traders, warranting a closer examination of the underlying dynamics and potential directional bets.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>b6d982f12c830f98eeaeeb018f823196</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:22:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Energy Exchange Ltd Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indian-energy-exchange-ltd-sees-notable-surge-in-derivatives-open-interest-amid-mixed-market-signals-3783475</link><description>Indian Energy Exchange Ltd (IEX) has witnessed a notable 12.06% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock hovering close to its 52-week low. This surge in open interest, coupled with mixed volume and price trends, suggests evolving market positioning and potential directional bets among traders in the capital markets sector.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>55150ba5e742960355ae3ec78d1f59fc</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:22:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>P I Industries Ltd Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Mixed Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/p-i-industries-ltd-sees-notable-surge-in-derivatives-open-interest-amid-mixed-price-action-3783473</link><description>P I Industries Ltd (PIIND), a key player in the Pesticides &amp; Agrochemicals sector, has witnessed a significant 10.8% rise in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this surge, the stock’s price movement remains subdued, reflecting a complex interplay of market forces and investor sentiment as the company navigates a challenging mid-cap landscape.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>aaddf10c892a48924dcbd7871cdc0be9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:22:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Phoenix Mills Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/phoenix-mills-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-market-momentum-3783470</link><description>Phoenix Mills Ltd., a prominent player in the realty sector, has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and investor interest. This development coincides with the stock hitting a new 52-week high of ₹1,958 and outperforming its sector peers, reflecting robust bullish sentiment and potential directional bets by market participants.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>d6f8c2bb84fafc16d17c2a15c40d3636</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:22:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IIFL Finance Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Price Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/iifl-finance-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-price-momentum-3783465</link><description>IIFL Finance Ltd (IIFL) has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market participation and a potential directional shift. The stock has outperformed its sector peers, hitting a fresh 52-week high of ₹675, supported by sustained buying interest and improving technical indicators.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>055ab604a097b94744e288d2690f8566</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:22:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Federal Bank Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/federal-bank-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3783467</link><description>Federal Bank Ltd has witnessed a significant 16.16% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this, the stock has underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting a complex interplay of bearish sentiment and speculative bets.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>7c9edd752f6b2e56bab56b1b778bd549</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:22:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shankara Building Products Ltd Surges 19% to Hit Upper Circuit Amid Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shankara-building-products-ltd-surges-19-to-hit-upper-circuit-amid-robust-buying-pressure-3783474</link><description>Shankara Building Products Ltd witnessed a remarkable surge on 6 Jan 2026, hitting its upper circuit limit with an 18.83% gain, driven by robust buying interest and significant unfilled demand. The stock outperformed its sector and the broader market, signalling renewed investor confidence despite a recent downgrade in its mojo grade.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>0902de4bf34bdac90aa155ccc41548a7</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:22:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Divis Laboratories Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Derivatives Activity</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/divis-laboratories-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-derivatives-activity-3783469</link><description>Divis Laboratories Ltd has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market interest and potential directional bets. The pharmaceutical giant’s stock outperformed its sector peers, supported by robust volume and positive price action, as investors recalibrate their positions amid evolving market dynamics.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>34c2e674a74be31b091dd2357e646846</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:22:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>National Aluminium Company Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/national-aluminium-company-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-market-momentum-3783471</link><description>National Aluminium Company Ltd (NATIONALUM) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, reflecting heightened market activity and a possible shift in investor sentiment. The stock’s recent price action, combined with robust volume and open interest growth, suggests strong directional bets and evolving market positioning among traders.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>2dddbf7d6f6e1f231f2d17cb949618ec</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:22:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manaksia Aluminium Company Ltd Surges 20% to Hit Upper Circuit Amid Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/manaksia-aluminium-company-ltd-surges-20-to-hit-upper-circuit-amid-robust-buying-pressure-3783472</link><description>Manaksia Aluminium Company Ltd witnessed a remarkable surge on 6 Jan 2026, hitting its upper circuit limit of 20% to close at ₹40.26, marking a new 52-week high. This extraordinary rally was driven by intense buying interest, resulting in a maximum permissible daily gain and triggering a regulatory trading freeze. The stock’s performance significantly outpaced its sector and benchmark indices, reflecting strong investor confidence amid sustained positive momentum.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>935f3fdef61f565ab9ba09ac4ef0e342</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:22:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dabur India Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dabur-india-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3783468</link><description>Dabur India Ltd., a prominent FMCG player, has witnessed a notable 10.8% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and evolving investor positioning. Despite this uptick, the stock has underperformed its sector and the broader Sensex, reflecting a complex interplay of bullish and bearish sentiments among traders.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>c6866ea2a8bee914e160fd7e38ca06e4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:22:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:22:26 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>