<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:18:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Orissa Minerals Joins Hidden Turnarounds List Amid Strong Quarterly Financials</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/mojo-premium/orissa-minerals-joins-hidden-turnarounds-list-on-strong-financial-upswing-3765995</link><description>Orissa Minerals, a small-cap player in the Minerals &amp; Mining sector, has been added to the Hidden Turnarounds list as of 22 December 2025, reflecting its recent positive financial trajectory and potential for sustained growth. The company’s latest quarterly results reveal notable improvements in profitability and operational efficiency, positioning it as a compelling candidate for investors seeking emerging turnaround opportunities.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>1092403d1fdd4f191ba00e72214d68ec</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:18:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are G V Films latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-g-v-films-latest-results-good-or-bad-3765980</link><description>G V Films' latest results are concerning, showing a 62.5% decline in net sales to ₹0.30 crores and a net loss of ₹0.05 crores, indicating ongoing operational and financial challenges, with significant accumulated losses and a lack of investor confidence.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3517bba63297dc7431a4df891c4ad5ba</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:18:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Medi Assist Healthcare Services Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/medi-assist-healthcare-services-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3765968</link><description>Medi Assist Healthcare Services, a small-cap player in the insurance sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price action over the longer term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ef3a9f3c31c1ad90e2d83ee30e0da71a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:18:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AWL Agri Business Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/awl-agri-business-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3765969</link><description>AWL Agri Business, a mid-cap player in the edible oil sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>10c7688af33f36560717a83d7f571c99</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:18:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MMP Industries Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mmp-industries-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3765967</link><description>MMP Industries, a micro-cap player in the Non - Ferrous Metals sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory over the medium to long term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>8118f2784c896e92f886e9015da5bc32</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:18:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Brand Concepts Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/brand-concepts-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3765965</link><description>Brand Concepts, a player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price action over the longer term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>3bae30b16e9d221358dd942140b6cec0</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:18:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Felix Industries Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/felix-industries-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3765964</link><description>Felix Industries, a micro-cap player in the miscellaneous sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development is widely regarded as a bearish signal, indicating a possible shift towards a weakening trend and long-term challenges for the stock’s price momentum.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>202e0d37d0c615a4dc012c7199e7bdbc</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:18:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Archit Organosys Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/archit-organosys-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3765966</link><description>Archit Organosys, a micro-cap player in the Commodity Chemicals sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory over the longer term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>5cc6b679c03820f1b904f6d25796772b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:18:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Enterprises Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-enterprises-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3765961</link><description>Adani Enterprises has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price action over the medium to long term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>704b8c3aa7dd7a0ec33f343ce28b418b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:18:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sindhu Trade Links Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sindhu-trade-links-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3765963</link><description>Sindhu Trade Links has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price movement over the medium to long term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>750d70593fb1812725e880c5176ccadc</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:18:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Axita Cotton Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/axita-cotton-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3765962</link><description>Axita Cotton, a player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has recently experienced a significant technical development as its 50-day moving average crossed above the 200-day moving average, forming what is commonly known as a Golden Cross. This event is widely regarded by market analysts as a bullish signal, indicating a possible shift in long-term momentum and a potential trend reversal for the stock.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>07da74bd96808f45efeb316b78740e56</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:18:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Triton Valves Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/triton-valves-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3765960</link><description>Triton Valves, a micro-cap player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential shift towards a bullish trend and long-term momentum change, attracting attention from market participants seeking evidence of a sustained uptrend.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>84f0baf3af5f617e55f6efdc9f8fbc9a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:18:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MMTC Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mmtc-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-ahead-3765959</link><description>MMTC, a key player in the Trading &amp; Distributors sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory over the medium to long term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b8895cd510271c3daa3db89d181f877a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:18:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Archies Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/archies-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3765958</link><description>Archies, a micro-cap player in the diversified consumer products sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting potential long-term weakness in the stock’s price movement.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>8a24135191e4dec8b12588aa50a3656c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:18:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Automotive Axles Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/automotive-axles-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3765949</link><description>Automotive Axles has recently experienced a significant technical development as its 50-day moving average crossed above the 200-day moving average, a formation widely recognised as a Golden Cross. This event often signals a potential shift in long-term momentum and a bullish trend reversal, attracting attention from investors and market analysts alike.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>6892142ba8fb06af7659cee92d64efac</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:18:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fertilizers &amp; Chemicals Travancore Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/fertilizers-chemicals-travancore-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3765957</link><description>Fertilizers &amp; Chemicals Travancore has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price movement over the longer term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>21c1d9de1b6886feb02d56b6ac8ca9bf</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:18:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Avanti Feeds Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/avanti-feeds-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3765948</link><description>Avanti Feeds, a prominent player in the FMCG sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, attracting attention from market participants and investors alike.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>5356c5e6754c058e063917114e590eed</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:18:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>India Tourism Development Corporation Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/india-tourism-development-corporation-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3765952</link><description>India Tourism Development Corporation (ITDC) has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory over the medium to long term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>7419e1142265f05e5ca2d910b0e8169e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:18:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Infosys Forms Golden Cross, Indicating Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/infosys-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3765951</link><description>Infosys has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential shift towards a bullish trend and suggests a long-term momentum change for the stock within the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>64ad173879be73ab0dd1518af1cf6549</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:18:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:18:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>