<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 02:06:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>A.K.Capital Services Q3 FY26: Strong Growth Momentum Continues Despite Sequential Dip</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/akcapital-services-q3-fy26-strong-growth-momentum-continues-despite-sequential-dip-3827032</link><description>A.K.Capital Services Ltd., a micro-cap non-banking financial company (NBFC) with a market capitalisation of ₹997.00 crores, reported consolidated net profit of ₹25.03 crores for Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), representing a robust year-on-year growth of 51.70% but a sequential decline of 16.93% from the previous quarter. The stock, trading at ₹1,520.00 as of February 6, 2026, has gained 0.61% in the most recent trading session, reflecting cautious investor sentiment following the mixed quarterly performance.
Time: Feb 07 2026 09:01 PM IST</description><guid>8a0af7313e60f7de72f4ecc10f1ffa7f</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 02:06:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3826999</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has revealed a nuanced picture across Indian equities, with 1712 companies reporting results. While the overall proportion of positive earnings surprises has improved marginally to 46.0%, mid-cap stocks continue to outperform their large- and small-cap counterparts, driving aggregate profit growth amid a challenging macroeconomic backdrop.
Time: Feb 07 2026 09:00 PM IST</description><guid>447603a985e127ef8a18ef39a22fdd15</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 02:06:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shradha AI Technologies Q2 FY26: Profit Decline Amid Volatile Revenue Performance Raises Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/shradha-ai-technologies-q2-fy26-profit-decline-amid-volatile-revenue-performance-raises-concerns-3827031</link><description>Shradha AI Technologies Ltd., a micro-cap software consulting firm with a market capitalisation of ₹187.00 crores, reported a consolidated net profit of ₹2.69 crores for Q2 FY26, marking an 18.48% sequential decline from ₹3.30 crores in Q1 FY26, though showing modest year-on-year growth of 3.86%. The company's shares have struggled significantly, declining 38.42% over the past year and currently trading at ₹30.70, down 40.96% from their 52-week high of ₹52.00.
Time: Feb 07 2026 08:49 PM IST</description><guid>16f5352003eec2c110cb2b4ccb79d884</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 02:06:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>VL E-Governance Q3 FY26: Losses Deepen as Revenue Plummets 70% YoY</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/vl-e-governance-q3-fy26-losses-deepen-as-revenue-plummets-70-yoy-3827030</link><description>VL E-Governance &amp; IT Solutions Ltd., a systems integrator and e-governance service provider, reported deeply troubling third-quarter results for FY2026, with the company sliding into losses as revenue collapsed by 70.55% year-on-year. The micro-cap company, with a market capitalisation of ₹152.00 crores, posted a net loss of ₹0.71 crores in Q3 FY26 compared to a profit of ₹0.94 crores in the same quarter last year, marking a complete reversal in profitability.
Time: Feb 07 2026 08:49 PM IST</description><guid>b0640c68324660cd4c534257b1e047dc</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 02:06:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MRP Agro Q3 FY26: Revenue Plunge Sparks Profitability Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/mrp-agro-q3-fy26-revenue-plunge-sparks-profitability-concerns-3827029</link><description>MRP Agro Ltd., a micro-cap food grains and commodities trading company with a market capitalisation of ₹103.00 crores, reported a concerning third quarter for FY2026, with net sales plummeting 41.69% quarter-on-quarter to ₹14.14 crores. Net profit declined 19.79% sequentially to ₹1.54 crores, raising questions about the sustainability of the company's recent growth trajectory. The stock, currently trading at ₹93.00, has underperformed significantly over the past year, down 35.42% whilst the Sensex gained 7.07%.
Time: Feb 07 2026 08:48 PM IST</description><guid>3eb57f2e1ba593b747995289a7243e83</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 02:06:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TARC Ltd Q3 FY26: Operational Losses Deepen Despite Revenue Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/tarc-ltd-q3-fy26-operational-losses-deepen-despite-revenue-surge-3827028</link><description>TARC Ltd., the Delhi-NCR focused real estate developer, reported a consolidated net loss of ₹21.03 crores for Q3 FY26, marking a 33.44% sequential deterioration from the ₹15.77 crores loss posted in Q2 FY26. Whilst revenue surged an impressive 458.66% quarter-on-quarter to ₹38.38 crores, the company's operational challenges remain deeply entrenched, with negative operating margins of 47.45% excluding other income highlighting fundamental profitability concerns. The stock, trading at ₹147.95 with a market capitalisation of ₹4,543 crores, has declined 5.79% following the results announcement, reflecting investor unease about the company's path to sustainable profitability.
Time: Feb 07 2026 08:48 PM IST</description><guid>c0526961890e8309760a46b1e37790de</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 02:06:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Veer Global Infraconstruction Q3 FY26: Sharp Profit Decline Amid Revenue Recovery Raises Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/veer-global-infraconstruction-q3-fy26-sharp-profit-decline-amid-revenue-recovery-raises-concerns-3827027</link><description>Veer Global Infraconstruction Ltd., a micro-cap realty player with a market capitalisation of ₹163.00 crores, reported a concerning performance for Q3 FY26, with net profit declining 52.17% quarter-on-quarter to ₹0.33 crores despite a 30.57% sequential revenue recovery. The stock has reacted sharply to the deteriorating financial trajectory, plunging 15.77% following the results announcement, trading at ₹91.55 and hovering dangerously close to its 52-week low of ₹91.00.
Time: Feb 07 2026 08:48 PM IST</description><guid>8de45018a03cb06f1b01c244cae219e4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 02:06:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GIC Re Q3 FY26: Profitability Dips Despite Revenue Growth as Other Income Volatility Weighs</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/gic-re-q3-fy26-profitability-dips-despite-revenue-growth-as-other-income-volatility-weighs-3827026</link><description>General Insurance Corporation of India Ltd. (GIC Re), India's sole domestic reinsurer, reported a consolidated net profit of ₹1,725.66 crores for Q3 FY26 (Oct-Dec'25), marking a sharp 39.95% decline sequentially from ₹2,873.54 crores in Q2 FY26. On a year-on-year basis, profit growth remained modest at 2.92% compared to ₹1,676.63 crores in Q3 FY25. The muted quarterly performance comes despite net sales advancing 12.97% YoY to ₹12,588.62 crores, highlighting profitability pressures from volatile other income and margin compression.
Time: Feb 07 2026 08:48 PM IST</description><guid>0cf9fc6c884c0bf669310a68fb24d181</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 02:06:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sikko Industries Q3 FY26: Profit Surge Masked by Margin Compression Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/sikko-industries-q3-fy26-profit-surge-masked-by-margin-compression-concerns-3827025</link><description>Sikko Industries Ltd., a micro-cap fertiliser manufacturer with a market capitalisation of ₹186.00 crores, reported net profit of ₹2.08 crores for Q3 FY26 ended December 2025, representing a 60.00% year-on-year surge but a concerning 27.02% sequential decline from the previous quarter. The stock, trading at ₹4.22 as of February 6, 2026, has delivered extraordinary returns of 754.25% over the past year, though it declined 0.71% in the most recent trading session following the results announcement.
Time: Feb 07 2026 08:48 PM IST</description><guid>695e8527b80aa94fb21afc72f1e49357</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 02:06:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahanagar Gas Q3 FY26: Margin Compression Overshadows Volume Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/mahanagar-gas-q3-fy26-margin-compression-overshadows-volume-growth-3827024</link><description>Mahanagar Gas Ltd., Mumbai's sole authorised city gas distribution company, reported a consolidated net profit of ₹201.15 crores for Q3 FY26, marking a sequential improvement of 5.11% from ₹191.37 crores in Q2 FY26, but representing a year-on-year decline of 9.08% from ₹221.24 crores in Q3 FY25. The ₹10,774-crore market capitalisation company's stock surged 7.66% following the results announcement, reflecting investor relief after a challenging period that saw the stock down 14.08% over the past year.
Time: Feb 07 2026 08:48 PM IST</description><guid>b8bd67dc6affc603d260798692f1b639</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 02:06:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bella Casa Fashion Q3 FY26: Seasonal Slowdown Dents Profitability Despite Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/bella-casa-fashion-q3-fy26-seasonal-slowdown-dents-profitability-despite-revenue-growth-3827023</link><description>Bella Casa Fashion &amp; Retail Ltd., a Jaipur-based garment and apparel manufacturer, reported a challenging Q3 FY26 performance marked by sequential revenue contraction and profitability pressures. Net profit for the quarter stood at ₹4.45 crores, declining 30.58% quarter-on-quarter from ₹6.41 crores in Q2 FY26, though improving 26.78% year-on-year from ₹3.51 crores in Q3 FY25. The micro-cap company, with a market capitalisation of ₹428 crores, witnessed its shares trading at ₹317.10 as of February 06, 2026, reflecting ongoing investor concerns about near-term momentum.
Time: Feb 07 2026 08:48 PM IST</description><guid>1f04498d79cee19fd71c99482616dba1</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 02:06:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Madhucon Projects Q3 FY26: Losses Deepen as Infrastructure Giant Struggles with Operational Challenges</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/madhucon-projects-q3-fy26-losses-deepen-as-infrastructure-giant-struggles-with-operational-challenges-3827020</link><description>Madhucon Projects Ltd., a Telangana-based infrastructure construction company, reported a consolidated net loss of ₹106.64 crores for Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), marking a deterioration from the ₹120.74 crores loss in the previous quarter. The micro-cap company, with a market capitalisation of just ₹39.00 crores, continues to face severe operational headwinds despite a 25.03% year-on-year revenue increase to ₹139.33 crores. The stock, trading at ₹5.02, has plunged 35.39% over the past year and remains deeply entrenched in bearish technical territory, reflecting investor concerns about the company's persistent inability to achieve profitability.
Time: Feb 07 2026 08:48 PM IST</description><guid>289e089d33156e396c3fb35b84115df5</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 02:06:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>L G Balakrishnan &amp; Bros Q3 FY26: Margin Compression Clouds Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/l-g-balakrishnan-bros-q3-fy26-margin-compression-clouds-revenue-growth-3827019</link><description>L G Balakrishnan &amp; Bros Ltd., a prominent auto components manufacturer with a market capitalisation of ₹5,884.00 crores, reported a consolidated net profit of ₹88.43 crores for Q3 FY26, marking a sequential decline of 5.54% from the previous quarter's ₹93.62 crores, though maintaining a healthy year-on-year growth of 17.44%. The Coimbatore-based chain and sprocket specialist saw its stock trading at ₹1,875.00 as of February 6, 2026, reflecting investor caution following the results announcement.
Time: Feb 07 2026 08:48 PM IST</description><guid>88f614fc46e053d281c465ef46afd8f3</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 02:06:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Balkrishna Paper Mills Q3 FY26: Losses Deepen Amid Persistent Operational Challenges</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/balkrishna-paper-mills-q3-fy26-losses-deepen-amid-persistent-operational-challenges-3827018</link><description>Balkrishna Paper Mills Ltd., a micro-cap paper manufacturer catering primarily to the packaging industry, reported a net loss of ₹1.89 crores for Q3 FY26, marking an 80.00% deterioration from the previous quarter. The company's shares have declined 24.65% over the past three months, reflecting investor concerns about the persistent operational challenges and negative profitability metrics that continue to plague the Mumbai-based enterprise.
Time: Feb 07 2026 08:48 PM IST</description><guid>ca3093ec277adaf7568677f43f3ac6c3</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 02:06:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Archit Organosys Q3 FY26: Stellar Turnaround Masks Underlying Margin Pressures</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/archit-organosys-q3-fy26-stellar-turnaround-masks-underlying-margin-pressures-3827017</link><description>Archit Organosys Ltd., a micro-cap commodity chemicals manufacturer, has delivered a remarkable turnaround in Q3 FY26, swinging from a loss to profitability with net profit surging to ₹2.43 crores. However, the stock remains under pressure, trading 19.36% below its 52-week high of ₹51.45, as investors grapple with persistent margin erosion and weak return ratios that continue to plague the ₹82-crore market capitalisation company.
Time: Feb 07 2026 08:47 PM IST</description><guid>7a4aad7100895270eaaa2b27840de4b7</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 02:06:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SEPC Ltd Q3 FY26: Strong Revenue Surge Masks Underlying Operational Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/sepc-ltd-q3-fy26-strong-revenue-surge-masks-underlying-operational-concerns-3827016</link><description>SEPC Limited, formerly Shriram EPC Limited, reported a robust revenue performance in Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), with net sales surging 156.29% year-on-year to ₹340.97 crores, marking a significant acceleration from the previous quarter's 38.85% growth. Net profit jumped 236.94% YoY to ₹14.96 crores, though this impressive headline figure conceals deeper operational challenges that warrant investor scrutiny.
Time: Feb 07 2026 08:47 PM IST</description><guid>414de3da95a136daafa8834d9889ff89</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 02:06:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Star Delta Transformers Q3 FY26: Revenue Surge Masks Profit Decline Amid Tax Anomalies</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/star-delta-transformers-q3-fy26-revenue-surge-masks-profit-decline-amid-tax-anomalies-3827015</link><description>Star Delta Transformers Ltd., a micro-cap manufacturer of distribution and power transformers, reported mixed Q3 FY26 results that highlighted a troubling disconnect between top-line momentum and bottom-line delivery. Whilst net sales surged 61.03% year-on-year to ₹52.77 crores—marking the highest quarterly revenue in the company's recent history—net profit declined 48.11% quarter-on-quarter to ₹2.06 crores, primarily due to an unusually elevated tax rate of 41.03%. The stock, trading at ₹506.00 as of February 6, 2026, has underperformed significantly, declining 32.80% over the past year against the Sensex's 7.07% gain, reflecting investor concerns about profitability consistency and operational execution.
Time: Feb 07 2026 08:47 PM IST</description><guid>92b5fbf3dd4b92e8433aa675f10ec0a8</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 02:06:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HBL Engineering Q2 FY26: Stellar Quarter Masks Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/hbl-engineering-q2-fy26-stellar-quarter-masks-valuation-concerns-3827014</link><description>HBL Engineering Ltd., the Hyderabad-based battery and power systems manufacturer, delivered an exceptional second quarter performance for FY2026, with consolidated net profit surging 170.31% quarter-on-quarter to ₹387.27 crores. The stellar results, driven by a massive 103.22% sequential revenue jump to ₹1,222.90 crores, propelled the stock up 0.91% to ₹785.80 on February 6, 2026, though it remains 29.96% below its 52-week high of ₹1,121.95.
Time: Feb 07 2026 08:47 PM IST</description><guid>08fec4f53553a850125e8f1c2d7f3968</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 02:06:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 02:06:15 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>