<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:57:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Exicom Tele-Systems Ltd Drops 9.64% Amidst 52-Week and All-Time Lows</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/exicom-tele-systems-ltd-drops-964-amidst-52-week-and-all-time-lows-3802843</link><description>Exicom Tele-Systems Ltd’s shares fell sharply by 9.64% over the week ending 23 January 2026, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 3.31% decline. The stock hit new 52-week and all-time lows amid persistent financial challenges, rising interest expenses, and weak profitability metrics, reflecting a sustained downtrend and bearish market sentiment.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>8f5dacef892b7c25b1848ef08e47b23f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mukka Proteins Gains 0.86%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mukka-proteins-gains-086-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3802844</link><description>Mukka Proteins Ltd’s stock showed a modest weekly gain of 0.86%, closing at Rs.22.26 on 23 January 2026, despite a turbulent week marked by multiple fresh 52-week and all-time lows. This performance notably outpaced the Sensex, which declined by 3.31% over the same period, reflecting a complex interplay of financial pressures, sectoral headwinds, and intermittent buying interest that shaped the stock’s volatile trajectory.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>95ce9cf5a87a372d80e2fa49f6a2e594</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>R K Swamy Ltd Falls 1.67% Amidst Persistent Downtrend and Technical Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/r-k-swamy-ltd-falls-167-amidst-persistent-downtrend-and-technical-weakness-3802845</link><description>R K Swamy Ltd’s stock closed the week at Rs.105.95, down 1.67% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.107.75, underperforming the Sensex which declined 3.31% over the same period. The week was marked by a continuation of the stock’s downward momentum, hitting fresh 52-week and all-time lows before a late-week recovery attempt. Despite some short-term technical signals suggesting mild bullishness, the overall trend remains bearish amid weak financial results and subdued investor sentiment.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>e1db6343c65cc39969f6aa21b5513ba3</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Popular Vehicles &amp; Services Ltd Falls 8.18%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/popular-vehicles-services-ltd-falls-818-5-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3802842</link><description>Popular Vehicles &amp; Services Ltd experienced a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its stock price declining by 8.18% to close at ₹107.75, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. The week was marked by a series of bearish technical developments, a downgrade to a Strong Sell rating, and deteriorating fundamentals, all contributing to sustained downward pressure on the stock.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>346fba5b2ac21d8d3107131a0c65d5bf</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Krystal Integrated Services Ltd Declines 3.06%: Mixed Technical Signals and Profitability Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/krystal-integrated-services-ltd-declines-306-mixed-technical-signals-and-profitability-pressure-3802839</link><description>Krystal Integrated Services Ltd closed the week down 3.06% at Rs.601.30, slightly outperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31%. The stock faced persistent selling pressure amid mixed technical signals and disappointing quarterly results, leading to a sideways to bearish trend throughout the week.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>dca947232c824006c8cfc1329365bf3c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharti Hexacom Ltd’s Mixed Week: -0.02% Price Change Amid Technical Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharti-hexacom-ltds-mixed-week--002-price-change-amid-technical-shifts-3802838</link><description>Bharti Hexacom Ltd ended the week marginally lower by 0.02% at Rs.1,614.60, contrasting sharply with the Sensex’s 3.31% decline over the same period. The stock’s performance was marked by a volatile week featuring a strong midweek rally followed by technical warning signals, including the formation of a Death Cross. Despite the sideways weekly close, Bharti Hexacom demonstrated resilience relative to the broader market, reflecting a complex interplay of bullish momentum and emerging bearish trends.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>73b0ade5d7403df318186704d4e55032</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JNK India Ltd’s 1.08% Weekly Decline: 5 Key Events Shaping the Stock’s Volatile Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jnk-india-ltds-108-weekly-decline-5-key-events-shaping-the-stocks-volatile-week-3802837</link><description>JNK India Ltd’s shares declined by 1.08% over the week ending 23 January 2026, closing at Rs.215.50, marginally outperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31%. The stock experienced a volatile week marked by a fresh 52-week and all-time low, followed by a sharp rebound midweek. Despite the recent price weakness, quarterly financials showed notable growth in sales and profits, contrasting with the longer-term downtrend and reduced institutional interest.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>ca152ca28cab4c4240a3b2588fd1ee21</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TBO Tek Ltd Falls 5.35%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tbo-tek-ltd-falls-535-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3802836</link><description>TBO Tek Ltd’s shares declined by 5.35% over the week ending 23 January 2026, underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% in the same period. The stock faced a challenging week marked by a downgrade to a Sell rating amid deteriorating technical momentum and valuation concerns, compounded by mixed signals from key technical indicators. Despite some short-term bullish hints, the overall trend remains cautious as the stock navigates volatility and sector headwinds.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>9bbf62508a5fafb8cd4479505a872d25</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kronox Lab Sciences Ltd Falls 3.65%: 5 Key Factors Behind the Steep Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kronox-lab-sciences-ltd-falls-365-5-key-factors-behind-the-steep-weekly-decline-3802835</link><description>Kronox Lab Sciences Ltd’s stock closed the week at Rs.124.00, down 3.65% from Rs.128.70 last Friday, slightly underperforming the Sensex which fell 3.31% over the same period. The week was marked by a persistent downtrend with multiple new 52-week and all-time lows amid subdued financial results, valuation concerns, and a downgrade to a ‘Sell’ rating by MarketsMOJO. Despite a modest rebound midweek, the stock struggled to regain footing, reflecting ongoing challenges in the specialty chemicals sector and company-specific headwinds.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>9a645d8b797db01323818ecaa93bfd58</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Borosil Scientific Ltd Falls 8.61%: 5 Key Factors Behind the Steep Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/borosil-scientific-ltd-falls-861-5-key-factors-behind-the-steep-weekly-decline-3802834</link><description>Borosil Scientific Ltd’s shares declined sharply over the week ending 23 January 2026, falling 8.61% from Rs.116.10 to Rs.106.10, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 3.31% drop. The stock faced persistent selling pressure amid weak financial results, technical downturns, and cautious market sentiment, culminating in fresh 52-week and all-time lows. Despite a modest upgrade in rating from Strong Sell to Sell early in the week, the company’s fundamentals and price momentum remained under strain, reflecting ongoing challenges in profitability and growth.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>1469a283febfb9fd63a5d96215e4309c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Forbes Precision Tools Falls 4.08%: 6 Key Factors Behind the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/forbes-precision-tools-falls-408-6-key-factors-behind-the-weekly-decline-3802832</link><description>Forbes Precision Tools &amp; Machine Parts Ltd experienced a challenging week ending 23 January 2026, with its share price declining 4.08% from Rs.135.90 to Rs.130.35. This underperformance slightly exceeded the Sensex’s 3.31% fall over the same period, reflecting persistent downward pressure amid weak financial results, new 52-week and all-time lows, and deteriorating profitability trends.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>6666e3d2fb7d71824537bedece3d46b2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Le Travenues Technology Ltd Falls 12.02%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/le-travenues-technology-ltd-falls-1202-5-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3802833</link><description>Le Travenues Technology Ltd experienced a turbulent week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its stock price plunging 12.02% to close at Rs.204.90, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 3.31% decline. The week was marked by sharp intraday volatility, rating upgrades and downgrades, mixed technical signals, and disappointing quarterly results, all contributing to the stock’s downward trajectory amid broader market weakness.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>e69006525894731602743c1bff4c29a9</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adtech Systems Ltd’s 1.81% Weekly Gain Amid Volatile Trading and Persistent Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adtech-systems-ltds-181-weekly-gain-amid-volatile-trading-and-persistent-downtrend-3802831</link><description>Adtech Systems Ltd’s stock exhibited notable volatility during the week ending 23 January 2026, closing with a modest gain of 1.81% to Rs.59.14, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 3.31%. The week was marked by a sharp midweek drop to a 52-week and all-time low of Rs.53, followed by a partial recovery in the final sessions. Key events including the stock’s new lows, technical positioning, and market sentiment shaped the trading dynamics throughout the week.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>0963ce5448b67169f5078ef97b6777f7</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Akme Fintrade Declines 11.41%: 5 Key Factors Behind the Steep Weekly Slide</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/akme-fintrade-declines-1141-5-key-factors-behind-the-steep-weekly-slide-3802830</link><description>Akme Fintrade (India) Ltd experienced a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its stock price falling sharply by 11.41% to close at Rs.4.97, significantly underperforming the Sensex which declined by 3.31% over the same period. The stock hit multiple 52-week and all-time lows amid persistent bearish momentum, despite reporting positive quarterly financial results. This review analyses the key events and market dynamics that shaped the stock’s performance during the week.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>4335fccd6c1bfa588e76961de9f799e5</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stanley Lifestyles Ltd Falls 5.92%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/stanley-lifestyles-ltd-falls-592-4-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-decline-3802825</link><description>Stanley Lifestyles Ltd’s stock endured a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, closing at Rs.175.50, down 5.92% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.186.55. This decline notably outpaced the Sensex’s 3.31% fall over the same period, reflecting intensified selling pressure amid deteriorating fundamentals and persistent downtrend signals. The stock hit fresh 52-week and all-time lows during the week, underscoring ongoing concerns about the company’s financial health and market positioning.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>6725f6e3a7e82b8cf78afcc7c5e21ee2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>National Peroxide Ltd Falls 4.88%: 4 Key Factors Behind the Steep Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/national-peroxide-ltd-falls-488-4-key-factors-behind-the-steep-decline-3802829</link><description>National Peroxide Ltd’s stock declined by 4.88% over the week ending 23 January 2026, closing at Rs.414.55 from Rs.435.80 the previous Friday. This underperformance was sharper than the Sensex’s 3.31% fall during the same period, reflecting persistent financial and operational challenges. The week saw the stock hit fresh 52-week and all-time lows, with volatility driven by weak earnings, deteriorating profitability metrics, and sustained bearish technical signals.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>41513a20c7518d8ccffb07e585262e98</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Emcure Pharmaceuticals Ltd Falls 2.44%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Move</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/emcure-pharmaceuticals-ltd-falls-244-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-move-3802827</link><description>Emcure Pharmaceuticals Ltd closed the week ending 23 January 2026 at Rs.1,520.95, down 2.44% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.1,559.05. Despite this decline, the stock outperformed the Sensex, which fell 3.31% over the same period. The week was marked by a new 52-week high, a significant upgrade in the company’s rating to Buy, and a bullish shift in technical momentum, all set against a volatile market backdrop.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>e721288ce9b94fda22695b608c05de7a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ola Electric Mobility Ltd Falls 14.23%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ola-electric-mobility-ltd-falls-1423-6-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3802826</link><description>Ola Electric Mobility Ltd endured a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its share price declining sharply by 14.23%, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 3.31% fall over the same period. Despite several days of exceptional trading volumes and intermittent short-term rallies, the stock remained entrenched in a downtrend, weighed down by persistent selling pressure and a strong sell rating from MarketsMOJO. This review analyses the key events and price movements that shaped the stock’s turbulent week.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>d7aae9a61a1ca6cd25947334e4827251</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bansal Wire Industries Ltd Falls 13.24%: 5 Key Factors Behind the Steep Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bansal-wire-industries-ltd-falls-1324-5-key-factors-behind-the-steep-decline-3802822</link><description>Bansal Wire Industries Ltd endured a challenging week from 19 to 23 January 2026, with its share price plunging 13.24% to close at Rs.264.30, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 3.31% decline over the same period. The stock hit multiple 52-week and all-time lows amid persistent sectoral headwinds, rising interest expenses, and deteriorating technical indicators, despite notable profit growth and steady sales expansion.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>c329cd57db67a1e642ba47268a0e99c5</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Saraswati Saree Depot Ltd Falls 6.48%: 7 Key Factors Driving the Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/saraswati-saree-depot-ltd-falls-648-7-key-factors-driving-the-downtrend-3802828</link><description>Saraswati Saree Depot Ltd’s shares declined sharply over the week ending 23 January 2026, falling 6.48% from Rs.72.35 to Rs.67.66. This underperformance was more pronounced than the Sensex’s 3.31% drop during the same period, reflecting persistent selling pressure amid weak sectoral and market conditions. The stock hit multiple 52-week and all-time lows throughout the week, underscoring a challenging environment for the company despite some positive financial metrics.
Time: 25 minutes ago</description><guid>24e17f762fdd3f1154e12750c2fddfae</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 03:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>