<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 04:22:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Apeejay Surrendra Park Hotels Ltd Edges Up 0.25% Despite All-Time Low</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/apeejay-surrendra-park-hotels-ltd-edges-up-025-despite-all-time-low-3812341</link><description>Apeejay Surrendra Park Hotels Ltd closed the week ending 30 Jan 2026 with a modest gain of 0.25%, marginally outperforming the broader Sensex which rose 1.62% over the same period. The stock experienced significant volatility, hitting a fresh 52-week and all-time low on 27 Jan before recovering in the subsequent sessions. Despite the slight weekly advance, the stock remains under pressure amid weak quarterly earnings, rising interest expenses, and reduced institutional participation, contrasting with the Sensex’s steady upward trajectory.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>630a9adcbf7d32c69d2c7a5f8dbf6fff</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 04:22:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jasch Gauging Technologies Ltd Drops 7.13% Amid Margin Pressure and 52-Week Low</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jasch-gauging-technologies-ltd-drops-713-amid-margin-pressure-and-52-week-low-3812339</link><description>Jasch Gauging Technologies Ltd experienced a challenging week ending 30 January 2026, with its stock price declining 7.13% from Rs.496.85 to Rs.461.40, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.62% over the same period. Despite early gains midweek, the stock faced significant selling pressure on the final trading day, hitting a 52-week low of Rs.433 amid margin pressures and flat quarterly performance, signalling a shift in the company’s recent growth trajectory.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>4ea2ecff68cdd22a64018bc25b7edd0a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 04:22:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Capital Small Finance Bank Gains 0.86%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/capital-small-finance-bank-gains-086-4-key-factors-driving-the-week-3812336</link><description>Capital Small Finance Bank Ltd recorded a modest weekly gain of 0.86%, closing at Rs.256.95 on 30 January 2026, despite facing margin pressures and flat quarterly performance. The stock slightly outperformed the Sensex, which rose 1.62% over the same period, reflecting mixed investor sentiment amid strong net interest income but subdued profitability.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>5695ba568be492ec337c6aded415dbcd</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 04:22:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jana Small Finance Bank Ltd Falls 3.63%: 5 Key Factors Behind the Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jana-small-finance-bank-ltd-falls-363-5-key-factors-behind-the-prolonged-downtrend-3812337</link><description>Jana Small Finance Bank Ltd’s shares declined by 3.63% over the week ending 30 January 2026, closing at Rs.360.15 from Rs.373.70 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasts sharply with the Sensex’s 1.62% gain during the same period, reflecting ongoing financial pressures and a sustained downtrend in the stock. The week was marked by multiple new 52-week and all-time lows, subdued quarterly earnings, and cautious market sentiment despite increased institutional interest.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>3fd7d3301df5f27057e4304ebd185a8b</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 04:22:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rashi Peripherals Gains 5.78%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rashi-peripherals-gains-578-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-momentum-3812335</link><description>Rashi Peripherals Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, rising 5.78% from ₹339.00 to ₹358.60 between 26 and 30 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% gain over the same period. The stock’s momentum was supported by a series of technical upgrades, strong financial results, and renewed investor confidence, culminating in a MarketsMOJO upgrade to a Buy rating. Despite some short-term volatility and mixed technical signals, the week closed on a positive note with the stock trading near its recent highs.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>e28bd14b591b70f9988dfc0f1c364cdd</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 04:22:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Juniper Hotels Ltd Gains 2.41%: Key Financial Pressures and Rebound Highlight Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/juniper-hotels-ltd-gains-241-key-financial-pressures-and-rebound-highlight-week-3812338</link><description>Juniper Hotels Ltd’s stock experienced a volatile week ending 30 January 2026, closing at Rs.226.95, up 2.41% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.221.60. Despite a strong late-week rebound, the stock underperformed the broader Sensex, which rose 1.62% over the same period. The week was marked by fresh 52-week and all-time lows early on, followed by a sharp intraday surge on the final trading day, reflecting a complex interplay of financial pressures and market sentiment.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>2e93338014d2d1641001826f65eb3f78</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 04:22:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gopal Snacks Gains 1.69%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Market Moves</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gopal-snacks-gains-169-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-market-moves-3812334</link><description>Gopal Snacks Ltd closed the week ending 30 January 2026 with a modest gain of 1.69%, slightly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% rise. The stock’s trajectory was shaped by a strong quarterly turnaround announcement, a sharp rally hitting the upper circuit, and mixed trading sessions reflecting cautious investor sentiment amid ongoing sector challenges.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>08a8b8859b2dcf8e1ae9110c2846cad5</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 04:22:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Exicom Tele-Systems Ltd Falls 0.55% Amid All-Time Low and Financial Struggles</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/exicom-tele-systems-ltd-falls-055-amid-all-time-low-and-financial-struggles-3812332</link><description>Exicom Tele-Systems Ltd’s stock closed the week at Rs.99.70, down 0.55% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.100.25, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.62% over the same period. The week was marked by the stock hitting fresh 52-week and all-time lows amid continued financial headwinds and deteriorating fundamentals, reflecting sustained bearish momentum despite broader market gains.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>fe115b32321dbb77eaac4030b7eb3347</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 04:22:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharti Hexacom Ltd Falls 4.34%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharti-hexacom-ltd-falls-434-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3812333</link><description>Bharti Hexacom Ltd experienced a challenging week ending 30 January 2026, with its share price declining 4.34% from Rs.1,614.60 to Rs.1,544.45, underperforming the Sensex which rose 1.62% over the same period. The stock faced sustained selling pressure amid a downgrade to a Sell rating, deteriorating technical momentum, and mixed market signals that weighed on investor sentiment throughout the week.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>1f36457fdbf6977de204e33fb85f2419</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 04:22:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JNK India Ltd Gains 5.99%: Key Drivers Behind the Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jnk-india-ltd-gains-599-key-drivers-behind-the-weekly-rally-3812330</link><description>JNK India Ltd’s stock recorded a notable 5.99% gain over the week ending 30 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% rise. The week was marked by a sharp recovery following a 52-week low on 28 January, culminating in a strong intraday surge of 7.31% on the final trading day. Despite lingering valuation concerns and prior underperformance, the stock’s recent momentum highlights a potential shift in investor sentiment amid mixed market conditions.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>2160089d4d81fc1c2dd8d105d40bb4a6</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 04:22:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indegene Ltd Gains 1.73%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indegene-ltd-gains-173-4-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3812331</link><description>Indegene Ltd’s stock exhibited a mixed performance during the week ending 30 January 2026, ultimately closing with a modest gain of 1.73% to Rs.482.20, slightly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% rise. The week was marked by significant volatility, including fresh 52-week and all-time lows, a notable quarterly earnings release, and fluctuating investor sentiment amid broader market pressures.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>dd7431864a791d914a2297740518b9d8</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 04:22:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aadhar Housing Finance Gains 4.78%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aadhar-housing-finance-gains-478-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3812329</link><description>Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd recorded a notable weekly gain of 4.78%, closing at Rs.490.60 on 30 January 2026, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% rise over the same period. The stock’s trajectory was shaped by a mix of technical developments, shifting momentum, and a strong quarterly earnings report, which together influenced investor sentiment and price action throughout the week.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>f25043ee72745ba835c42152100b7699</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 04:22:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TBO Tek Ltd Falls 3.54%: Mixed Signals and Technical Shift Mark the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tbo-tek-ltd-falls-354-mixed-signals-and-technical-shift-mark-the-week-3812327</link><description>TBO Tek Ltd’s stock declined by 3.54% over the week ending 30 January 2026, closing at Rs.1,389.85 from Rs.1,440.85 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s 1.62% gain during the same period, reflecting mixed investor sentiment amid an upgrade to a Hold rating and shifting technical momentum. The week was marked by a cautious reassessment of the company’s fundamentals and a complex technical outlook, which influenced daily price movements and volume trends.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>9a99a71d9ca06d7376ba1b27eac85053</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 04:22:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Akme Fintrade Declines 1.21%: Four Key Factors Behind the Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/akme-fintrade-declines-121-four-key-factors-behind-the-continued-downtrend-3812328</link><description>Akme Fintrade (India) Ltd’s stock closed the week at Rs.4.91, down 1.21% from Rs.4.97 at the start of the week, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.62% over the same period. The stock hit fresh 52-week and all-time lows during the week, reflecting ongoing challenges amid a prolonged downtrend despite some positive quarterly financial results. This review analyses the key events and price movements shaping the stock’s trajectory from 27 to 30 January 2026.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>f4304ad777637b680e54d116b942602a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 04:22:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adtech Systems Ltd Falls 1.93% Amidst New 52-Week and All-Time Lows</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adtech-systems-ltd-falls-193-amidst-new-52-week-and-all-time-lows-3812324</link><description>Adtech Systems Ltd experienced a challenging week ending 30 January 2026, with its share price declining by 1.93% from Rs.59.14 to Rs.58.00. This underperformance contrasted sharply with the Sensex, which rose 1.62% over the same period, highlighting the stock’s continued downward trajectory amid broader market strength. The week was marked by the stock hitting new 52-week and all-time lows, reflecting persistent financial and technical pressures.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>504eb57e6ffb3b15a318258ac64d639a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 04:22:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bansal Wire Industries Ltd Gains 3.92%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Move</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bansal-wire-industries-ltd-gains-392-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-move-3812326</link><description>Bansal Wire Industries Ltd closed the week ending 30 January 2026 with a 3.92% gain, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% rise over the same period. The stock experienced significant volatility, including a fresh 52-week and all-time low on 27 January, followed by a strong rebound on 28 January. Mixed technical signals and fundamental factors shaped the week’s price action, reflecting both challenges and tentative signs of recovery within the iron and steel products sector.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>93ca3b1b3c5291d39f870bc441e536b6</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 04:22:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Allied Blenders &amp; Distillers Gains 8.30%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/allied-blenders-distillers-gains-830-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-rally-3812325</link><description>Allied Blenders &amp; Distillers Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 8.30% from Rs.448.75 to Rs.486.00 between 27 and 30 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% gain over the same period. The stock’s rally was supported by a series of positive developments including an upgrade to a Hold rating by MarketsMOJO, robust quarterly results, and notable intraday price surges, despite some mixed technical signals and valuation concerns. This review analyses the key events that shaped the stock’s trajectory during the week and places its performance in the broader market context.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>9754b1e112ed7604d07726c9cdd637be</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 04:22:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>National Peroxide Ltd Falls 3.44% Amidst All-Time Low and Weak Financials</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/national-peroxide-ltd-falls-344-amidst-all-time-low-and-weak-financials-3812323</link><description>National Peroxide Ltd’s shares declined by 3.44% over the week ending 30 January 2026, closing at Rs.400.30 compared to Rs.414.55 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasts with the Sensex’s 1.62% gain during the same period, reflecting persistent financial and operational challenges for the company amid broader market resilience.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>2eece82eb928baa88592a19d7064311c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 04:22:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Brainbees Solutions Ltd Gains 2.14%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Recovery</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/brainbees-solutions-ltd-gains-214-4-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-recovery-3812321</link><description>Brainbees Solutions Ltd ended the week with a modest gain of 2.14%, closing at Rs.277.20 on 30 January 2026, outperforming the Sensex which rose 1.62% over the same period. The week was marked by significant volatility, including the stock hitting a new 52-week and all-time low on 27 January before recovering in the subsequent sessions. Despite the rebound, the stock remains under pressure amid weak fundamentals and a challenging sector environment.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>fe5bc028770648ff24b607a4834f9b3b</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 04:22:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Raymond Lifestyle Ltd Gains 14.39%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/raymond-lifestyle-ltd-gains-1439-3-key-factors-driving-the-surge-3812320</link><description>Raymond Lifestyle Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, surging 14.39% from Rs.911.95 to Rs.1,043.15 between 26 and 30 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% gain over the same period. The week was marked by a robust quarterly earnings report, mixed margin signals, and a notable intraday price surge, reflecting renewed investor interest amid operational improvements and active trading.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>f21805e6b714184e3d383ed52979706e</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 04:22:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 04:22:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>