<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:43:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Utkarsh Small Finance Bank Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/utkarsh-small-finance-bank-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amid-prolonged-downtrend-3818545</link><description>Utkarsh Small Finance Bank Ltd has reached a new all-time low of Rs.13.08, marking a significant decline amid sustained negative performance and underwhelming financial results over recent quarters.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>418467196cae7e08d088eced8e8db925</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:43:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blackbuck Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.03% Surge on 3 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/blackbuck-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-703-surge-on-3-feb-2026-3818543</link><description>Blackbuck Ltd demonstrated robust intraday strength on 3 Feb 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 592.3, marking a 7.73% increase from its previous close. This performance outpaced the broader Transport Services sector and the Sensex, reflecting notable trading momentum in the stock.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>b15ed3e618da7f46b6d7c8ef487b7f53</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:43:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PB Fintech Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 3 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pb-fintech-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-3-feb-2026-3818541</link><description>PB Fintech Ltd experienced a notable decline today, touching an intraday low of Rs 1,482.05, reflecting a 5.14% drop from its previous close. The stock underperformed its sector and broader market indices amid heightened volatility and persistent selling pressure.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>d0245b83b384a77ad98cba7aad226ab1</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:43:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Epigral Ltd Hits Intraday High with Strong 7.8% Surge on 3 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/epigral-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-strong-78-surge-on-3-feb-2026-3818542</link><description>Epigral Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 3 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 1001.65, marking a 7.98% increase from the previous close. The stock outperformed its sector and the broader market, reflecting notable trading momentum within the Specialty Chemicals industry.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>9e77adb1fd408e6a8891ce841a995770</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:43:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Avenue Supermarts Ltd Hits Intraday High with Strong 3.24% Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/avenue-supermarts-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-strong-324-surge-3818539</link><description>Avenue Supermarts Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 3 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of ₹3,779.9, marking a 2.83% increase during the session and closing with a notable 3.24% gain. This upward momentum outpaced the broader sector and key market indices, reflecting focused trading activity in the diversified retail stock.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>b5dcd3f6aeeefb4ee371f9a84f364090</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:43:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hind Rectifiers Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.81% Surge on 3 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hind-rectifiers-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-781-surge-on-3-feb-2026-3818540</link><description>Hind Rectifiers Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 3 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 1,348.8, marking a 7.81% gain. The stock outpaced its sector and broader market indices, reflecting notable trading momentum amid a mixed market backdrop.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>ca5969c85040218f9d2591d8feef7b53</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:43:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Motherson Sumi Wiring India Ltd Opens with Strong Gap Up, Reflecting Positive Market Sentiment</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/motherson-sumi-wiring-india-ltd-opens-with-strong-gap-up-reflecting-positive-market-sentiment-3818537</link><description>Motherson Sumi Wiring India Ltd commenced trading on 3 Feb 2026 with a notable gap up, opening 6.12% higher than its previous close, reflecting a strong start and positive market sentiment within the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>acfd414e446a89a06c48dd3600c269a7</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:43:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indus Towers Ltd Hits Intraday High with 3.54% Surge on 3 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indus-towers-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-354-surge-on-3-feb-2026-3818538</link><description>Indus Towers Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 3 February 2026, surging to an intraday high of ₹449.6, marking a 4.05% increase from its previous close. The stock’s upward momentum was supported by sustained gains over the past two sessions and trading above key moving averages, reflecting positive market sentiment within the telecom equipment sector.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>1af347cd5618eba73db611b2306e4cf1</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:43:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vodafone Idea Ltd. Hits Day High with Strong Intraday Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vodafone-idea-ltd-hits-day-high-with-strong-intraday-surge-3818535</link><description>Vodafone Idea Ltd. demonstrated a robust intraday performance on 3 Feb 2026, surging to its day high with a notable gain of 6.94%, outperforming both its sector and the broader market indices.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>9b5c10ece22fc3b737088c3e3352726e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:43:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lupin Ltd. Opens Strong with Significant Gap Up, Reflecting Positive Market Sentiment</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lupin-ltd-opens-strong-with-significant-gap-up-reflecting-positive-market-sentiment-3818536</link><description>Lupin Ltd. commenced trading on 3 Feb 2026 with a significant gap up, opening 5.67% higher and touching a new 52-week high of ₹2,249.3. This strong start underscores positive market sentiment amid a broader sectoral uptrend in Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>9def4d1e090d7bb414e9541ee50de171</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:43:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Waaree Energies Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/waaree-energies-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-market-momentum-3818534</link><description>Waaree Energies Ltd has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, coinciding with robust price gains and heightened market activity. The stock’s open interest jumped by 43.4% to 28,649 contracts, reflecting increased investor positioning and potential directional bets amid a bullish backdrop in the renewable energy sector.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>d50e2a84ad5f072e9cb04c7e2a456700</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:43:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PB Fintech Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Volatile Trading</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pb-fintech-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-volatile-trading-3818533</link><description>PB Fintech Ltd (POLICYBZR) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a recent downtrend in the stock price, the spike in open interest and trading volumes suggests that market participants are actively recalibrating their directional bets amid volatile price movements.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>6be54d83161c3d82c162bb8e46cdf790</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:43:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sona BLW Precision Forgings Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sona-blw-precision-forgings-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-market-positioning-3818531</link><description>Sona BLW Precision Forgings Ltd (SONACOMS) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor sentiment. The stock’s open interest jumped by 31.16% to 18,143 contracts, accompanied by a strong volume of 25,448 contracts, reflecting increased bullish positioning amid a recent price rally.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>3eb8dc5f7abe10c5f0cb88d5250af356</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:43:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>360 ONE WAM Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/360-one-wam-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-market-momentum-3818528</link><description>Shares of 360 ONE WAM Ltd have witnessed a notable surge in open interest in the derivatives segment, signalling increased market participation and potential directional bets. The stock outperformed its sector and broader indices, supported by rising volumes and positive price action, reflecting growing investor confidence amid a buoyant capital markets environment.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>1ef45d5f7af4834da728b20663540917</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:43:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baazar Style Retail Ltd Hits Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/baazar-style-retail-ltd-hits-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-momentum-3818529</link><description>Baazar Style Retail Ltd, a prominent player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, surged to hit its upper circuit limit on 3 February 2026, propelled by robust buying interest and a notable intraday price rally. The stock outperformed its sector and benchmark indices, signalling renewed investor confidence after a brief period of decline.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>4eb60e0ceefdb2ca918737e54188ff50</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:43:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Varun Beverages Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Positive Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/varun-beverages-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-positive-market-momentum-3818532</link><description>Varun Beverages Ltd (VBL) has witnessed a notable 10.3% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and potential directional bets. This surge accompanies a strong intraday performance, with the stock outperforming its sector and broader indices, suggesting renewed investor confidence in the beverage giant’s near-term prospects.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>ef4a30159010681f6d941ade4ec024a8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:43:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>A B M International Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/a-b-m-international-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-robust-buying-pressure-3818530</link><description>Shares of A B M International Ltd surged to hit the upper circuit limit on 3 Feb 2026, propelled by robust buying interest and a significant daily price gain of 6.1%. The stock closed at ₹40.00, marking a notable outperformance against its sector and the broader market, despite its micro-cap status and a recent downgrade to a Strong Sell rating by MarketsMOJO.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>55cdbe1f51774213d97b819cf913bd05</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:43:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Forge Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Signalling Strong Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-forge-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-signalling-strong-market-positioning-3818525</link><description>Bharat Forge Ltd. has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, coinciding with robust price gains and strong volume activity. The auto components heavyweight hit a fresh 52-week high of Rs 1,588, supported by a 21.99% increase in open interest, signalling heightened market participation and potential directional bets by investors.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>5eb03a617f0c42bc4acf91b6b111dff0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:43:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PB Fintech Ltd Sees Heavy Value Trading Amid Declining Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pb-fintech-ltd-sees-heavy-value-trading-amid-declining-momentum-3818527</link><description>PB Fintech Ltd, a prominent player in the financial technology sector, witnessed significant trading activity on 3 February 2026, marked by a steep decline in its share price despite robust volumes and heightened investor participation. The stock’s underperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices has raised concerns among market participants, reflecting a complex interplay of institutional selling and technical weakness.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>7e4cce8bb6ad32b5a8e7191557972004</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:43:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fischer Medical Ventures Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit on Robust Buying Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/fischer-medical-ventures-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-on-robust-buying-momentum-3818526</link><description>Fischer Medical Ventures Ltd, a small-cap player in the commodity chemicals sector, surged to hit its upper circuit limit on 3 February 2026, propelled by robust buying interest and a significant intraday gain of 4.98%. The stock’s performance outpaced both its sector and the broader Sensex, signalling renewed investor confidence despite a recent downgrade in its mojo grade.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>79dad337854496d87391c804862f9fcf</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:43:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:43:23 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>