<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:42:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Mid-Cap Segment Sees Sharp Decline Amid Broad Market Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/mid-cap-segment-sees-sharp-decline-amid-broad-market-weakness-3865425</link><description>The mid-cap segment, represented by the BSE Midcap index, experienced a notable decline on 2 March 2026, reflecting broader market challenges. The index slipped by 1.04% on the day, extending a recent downtrend with a 0.2% fall over the past five sessions. Market breadth was decidedly weak, with only eight stocks advancing against 136 decliners, signalling widespread selling pressure across the segment.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>aba912fa0e64e0a87b86ae44f87ac161</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:42:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Small-Cap Segment Faces Downward Pressure Amid Broad Market Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/small-cap-segment-faces-downward-pressure-amid-broad-market-weakness-3865424</link><description>The BSE Smallcap index has experienced a notable decline over recent sessions, reflecting broader market headwinds and sector-specific challenges. Despite pockets of strong individual stock performances, the overall small-cap segment has underperformed key benchmarks, signalling cautious investor sentiment amid volatile conditions.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>545504a0ebeb38bd6be749c8304e8a3e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:42:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Large-Cap Segment Faces Broad Sell-Off Amid Defensive Sector Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/large-cap-segment-faces-broad-sell-off-amid-defensive-sector-pressure-3865426</link><description>The large-cap segment, represented by the BSE 100 index, has experienced notable weakness over recent sessions, declining by 1.43% on the day and 2.17% over the past five trading days. This downturn reflects a broader market hesitation amid mixed sectoral performances and a clear divergence between defensive and cyclical stocks.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>15350470eb33ea640a434dd22211f4df</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:42:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Piramal Pharma Ltd Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/piramal-pharma-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3865452</link><description>Piramal Pharma Ltd commenced trading today with a pronounced gap down, opening at a price 8.45% lower than its previous close, reflecting heightened market apprehension following recent developments. The stock hit a new 52-week low of Rs.142.95, underperforming its sector and continuing a short-term downward trend.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>90e2c21b96e5ddafc293b92b7152b8c0</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:42:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prudent Corporate Advisory Services Ltd Opens with Sharp Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/prudent-corporate-advisory-services-ltd-opens-with-sharp-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3865449</link><description>Prudent Corporate Advisory Services Ltd commenced trading today with a significant gap down, opening at a price 16.92% lower than its previous close, reflecting heightened market apprehension. The stock’s weak start follows a series of declines amid broader sectoral pressures and a recent downgrade in its rating.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a754c16c074a8b22c1df846dba42c09d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:42:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oriental Hotels Ltd Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/oriental-hotels-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3865450</link><description>Oriental Hotels Ltd commenced trading today with a pronounced gap down, opening at a price 6.7% lower than its previous close, reflecting heightened market apprehension. The stock hit a fresh 52-week low of Rs 94.7, underperforming both its sector and the broader market indices amid ongoing downward momentum.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9b5afcdeb226a97dd4f57ead292cefc1</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:42:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Power Finance Corporation Ltd Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/power-finance-corporation-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3865451</link><description>Power Finance Corporation Ltd (PFC) commenced trading on 2 Mar 2026 with a pronounced gap down, opening at a price reflecting a 5.29% decline from its previous close. This weak start follows a series of declines over the past three sessions, signalling heightened market caution within the finance sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>65e79ac81f2c2ca1402faa18a795e2bb</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:42:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sun TV Network Ltd. Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sun-tv-network-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3865447</link><description>Sun TV Network Ltd. commenced trading today with a significant gap down, opening at an intraday low of Rs 520.85, reflecting a steep decline of 19.69% from its previous close. This weak start comes amid broader sectoral pressures and a downgrade in the company’s mojo grade, signalling heightened market concerns.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>47c11ac4702b19cee462bc78e4ab7889</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:42:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Bombay Burmah Trading Corporation Ltd Opens with Weak Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/the-bombay-burmah-trading-corporation-ltd-opens-with-weak-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3865448</link><description>The Bombay Burmah Trading Corporation Ltd experienced a sharp gap down at market open on 2 Mar 2026, reflecting heightened market concerns and a continuation of recent downward momentum. The stock opened 6.12% lower, underperforming both its sector and the broader market indices, signalling a weak start to the trading day.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>97c584613c027c6e2827e3571f76c459</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:42:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Ltd Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mahindra-mahindra-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3865446</link><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Ltd (M&amp;M) commenced trading on 2 Mar 2026 with a pronounced gap down, opening at a price 6.54% lower than its previous close. This weak start reflects ongoing market apprehensions, with the stock continuing its recent downward trajectory amid broader sectoral pressures.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5393ae40fd03255afdaa61ac6cbff042</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:42:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NMDC Ltd Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns and Weak Start</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nmdc-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-and-weak-start-3865445</link><description>NMDC Ltd commenced trading today with a pronounced gap down, opening 5.65% lower than its previous close, reflecting heightened market concerns within the Minerals &amp; Mining sector. The stock’s weak start follows two consecutive days of decline, signalling cautious sentiment among traders despite the company’s strong fundamental grading.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>066994bd815dc70d668983e237f13d52</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:42:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GAIL (India) Ltd Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gail-india-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3865444</link><description>Shares of GAIL (India) Ltd opened sharply lower on 2 Mar 2026, registering a gap down of 4.36% at the start of trading, reflecting heightened market apprehension following overnight developments. The stock’s weak opening set the tone for a cautious session amid broader sectoral pressures and technical indicators signalling subdued momentum.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6446f30a4d8e0bb96eb717eaa5cea857</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:42:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Heavy Electricals Ltd. Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-heavy-electricals-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3865443</link><description>Bharat Heavy Electricals Ltd. (BHEL) commenced trading today with a pronounced gap down, opening at an intraday low of Rs 252.8, reflecting a 4.55% decline from its previous close. This weak start comes amid broader sectoral pressures and follows recent adjustments in the company’s market grading, signalling cautious sentiment among market participants.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>051ae2fb7d027beb334f22510a4b6341</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:42:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank Of Baroda Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bank-of-baroda-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3865442</link><description>Bank Of Baroda (Stock ID: 824055) opened the trading session on 2 Mar 2026 with a pronounced gap down, declining by 5.79% from its previous close. This weak start reflects broader market apprehensions and sectoral pressures impacting the public sector banking space.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>db82a02e1ffa19c785da877938ec1ee9</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:42:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Privi Speciality Chemicals Ltd Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/privi-speciality-chemicals-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3865441</link><description>Privi Speciality Chemicals Ltd experienced a significant gap down at market open on 2 March 2026, reflecting heightened market concerns and a shift in investor sentiment. The stock opened sharply lower by 6.24%, underperforming its sector and broader indices amid a cautious trading environment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c43bfa5ded20950fdc6712263c86de71</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:42:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indraprastha Gas Ltd Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indraprastha-gas-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3865440</link><description>Indraprastha Gas Ltd (Stock ID: 616625) commenced trading today with a pronounced gap down, opening at a price 5.38% lower than its previous close. This weak start reflects ongoing market apprehensions, with the stock hitting a fresh 52-week low of Rs.161.95 amid broader sectoral and market pressures.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>eb5dd280f4dd40b25ef8ac8cd3664b30</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:42:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Orchid Pharma Ltd Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/orchid-pharma-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3865439</link><description>Orchid Pharma Ltd commenced trading today with a significant gap down, opening at an 18.85% lower price compared to its previous close, reflecting heightened market apprehension following recent developments. The stock hit a new 52-week low of Rs.503, underperforming its sector and broader indices amid sustained selling pressure.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d7e79ff99252122b8107ffe53a01d6be</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:42:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JM Financial Ltd Opens with Significant Gap Down Amid Market Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jm-financial-ltd-opens-with-significant-gap-down-amid-market-concerns-3865436</link><description>JM Financial Ltd experienced a sharp gap down at market open on 2 March 2026, reflecting heightened market concerns and a continuation of recent negative momentum. The stock opened 6.03% lower, extending its three-day losing streak amid broader sector weakness and technical indicators signalling bearish trends.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>214f17b5c4592208955a86bb6771519a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:42:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rategain Travel Technologies Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rategain-travel-technologies-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-3865437</link><description>Shares of Rategain Travel Technologies Ltd declined sharply on 2 Mar 2026, hitting an intraday low of Rs 489.55, reflecting significant price pressure amid a broader market downturn. The stock underperformed its sector and the benchmark Sensex, continuing a recent trend of weakness.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>548e0cbbe7afea6c385a0fe8f11c1dd0</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:42:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paisalo Digital Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 2 March 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/paisalo-digital-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-2-march-2026-3865438</link><description>Paisalo Digital Ltd experienced a significant intraday decline on 2 Mar 2026, touching a low of Rs 33.06, down 7.0% from the previous close. The stock underperformed its sector and the broader market, reflecting persistent selling pressure and subdued investor sentiment within the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) space.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2366c291b3c46861f0bf32041302159e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:42:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:42:28 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>