<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:31:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Winsome Yarns Ltd Falls 4.15%: 3 Key Events Shaping This Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/winsome-yarns-ltd-falls-415-3-key-events-shaping-this-weeks-volatility-3788572</link><description>Winsome Yarns Ltd experienced a turbulent week from 5 to 9 January 2026, closing at Rs.1.85, down 4.15% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.1.93. This decline notably outpaced the Sensex’s 2.62% fall over the same period, reflecting heightened volatility and mixed investor sentiment amid circuit limit hits and fluctuating trading volumes.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>4b2a1c2f433ae2c9bc04e485df64fccf</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jindal Drilling &amp; Industries Ltd Falls 4.83%: Bearish Momentum and Price Pressure Mark the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jindal-drilling-industries-ltd-falls-483-bearish-momentum-and-price-pressure-mark-the-week-3788570</link><description>Jindal Drilling &amp; Industries Ltd experienced a challenging week on the bourses, closing at Rs.543.75 on 9 January 2026, down 4.83% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.571.35. This decline outpaced the broader Sensex’s fall of 2.62% over the same period, reflecting company-specific pressures amid a volatile market backdrop. The week was marked by sharp intraday price drops and a technical downgrade that intensified bearish momentum, despite some short-term rebounds midweek.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>f5d0801c7969c410d867a8b0287375b8</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>National Aluminium Company Ltd Gains 5.37%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/national-aluminium-company-ltd-gains-537-6-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3788571</link><description>National Aluminium Company Ltd (NACL) delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 5.37% from Rs.330.25 to Rs.348.00 between 5 and 9 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 2.62% over the same period. The stock hit multiple new 52-week and all-time highs during the week, supported by robust volume, strong derivatives activity, and positive fundamental upgrades, despite a midweek price correction amid sectoral weakness.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>93f58854efd32d7eb12d7a8b1ee37185</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ADC India Communications Falls 13.62%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adc-india-communications-falls-1362-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3788569</link><description>ADC India Communications Ltd experienced a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, with its stock price declining by 13.62% to close at ₹1,313.20, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The week was marked by a shift from mild bullishness to bearish momentum, culminating in a downgrade to a Strong Sell rating amid deteriorating technical indicators and weakening financial results.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>3d8be347fa7fa99619b1960956ea515c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Electronics Ltd Gains 3.91%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-electronics-ltd-gains-391-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3788568</link><description>Bharat Electronics Ltd (BEL) delivered a robust weekly performance, rising 3.91% from Rs.403.10 to Rs.418.85 between 5 and 9 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 2.62% over the same period. The stock demonstrated resilience amid mixed market signals, buoyed by strong institutional interest, active options market positioning, and sustained technical momentum, despite a recent downgrade in its mojo rating to 'Hold'.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>fcad3df4db2ed5e0fe7d61df0a139d72</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Overseas Bank Falls 5.91%: Downgrade and Mixed Signals Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indian-overseas-bank-falls-591-downgrade-and-mixed-signals-shape-the-week-3788567</link><description>Indian Overseas Bank (IOB) endured a challenging week, with its share price declining 5.91% from ₹37.25 to ₹35.05, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 2.62% fall over the same period. The week was marked by a notable downgrade of the bank’s quality grade and investment rating to 'Sell' amid mixed financial signals and valuation concerns, which weighed heavily on investor sentiment and contributed to sustained selling pressure.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>211a3b2e844ddb7da1696b607c9fe0d3</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vintage Coffee &amp; Beverages Ltd Gains 2.96%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vintage-coffee-beverages-ltd-gains-296-6-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3788566</link><description>Vintage Coffee &amp; Beverages Ltd delivered a solid weekly gain of 2.96%, closing at Rs.165.25 on 9 January 2026, outperforming the Sensex which declined 2.62% over the same period. The stock showed notable volatility and strength midweek, hitting new 52-week and all-time highs before retreating slightly in the final sessions amid broader market weakness. This review analyses the key events and financial metrics that shaped the stock’s performance during the week.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>2dfff6d12cdf987a69368f395af10d93</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Borosil Renewables Declines 9.16%: Technical and Valuation Concerns Weigh</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/borosil-renewables-declines-916-technical-and-valuation-concerns-weigh-3788565</link><description>Borosil Renewables Ltd endured a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, with its stock price falling sharply by 9.16% to close at Rs.499.15, significantly underperforming the BSE Sensex which declined by 2.62% over the same period. The steep weekly decline was driven by a downgrade to a Sell rating amid mixed financials and deteriorating technical indicators, signalling increased caution among investors.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>53adc367c4f5346c58dfba41c83ee9dc</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Titan Company Ltd Gains 3.78%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/titan-company-ltd-gains-378-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-rally-3788564</link><description>Titan Company Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, gaining 3.78% from Rs.4,050.00 to Rs.4,203.00 between 5 and 9 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 2.62% over the same period. The stock hit multiple new 52-week and all-time highs early in the week, supported by strong financial results and sustained sector momentum, before closing slightly lower on the final two trading days amid broader market weakness.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>823c05a22e379e5727f227b2f8fb500c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oberoi Realty Declines 2.36% Amid Mixed Signals and Rising Open Interest</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/oberoi-realty-declines-236-amid-mixed-signals-and-rising-open-interest-3788562</link><description>Oberoi Realty Ltd closed the week ending 9 January 2026 at Rs.1,689.00, down 2.36% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.1,729.75. This decline slightly outperformed the broader Sensex, which fell 2.62% over the same period. The week was marked by a notable downgrade to a Sell rating amid mixed financials and bearish technicals, followed by a surge in open interest signalling renewed market activity and cautious optimism despite underlying risks.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>8b52cef1e16db8ca09543bab4b1bf443</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Setubandhan Infrastructure Ltd Falls 2.08% Amid Persistent Selling Pressure and Weak Fundamentals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/setubandhan-infrastructure-ltd-falls-208-amid-persistent-selling-pressure-and-weak-fundamentals-3788561</link><description>Setubandhan Infrastructure Ltd’s shares declined by 2.08% over the week ending 9 January 2026, closing at Rs.0.47 compared to Rs.0.48 the previous Friday. This underperformance came despite the Sensex falling 2.62% over the same period, indicating a slightly better relative resilience. The stock faced persistent selling pressure, hitting multiple 52-week lows and lower circuit limits amid weak financial metrics and subdued investor interest.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>8569f59e304ddd6b544bf8379e0d2d50</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Visaka Industries Falls 7.59%: Technical Shifts and Financial Metrics Underpin Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/visaka-industries-falls-759-technical-shifts-and-financial-metrics-underpin-weekly-decline-3788563</link><description>Visaka Industries Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its stock price declining by 7.59% from ₹72.30 on 2 January 2026 to ₹66.81 on 9 January 2026. This underperformance was notably sharper than the Sensex’s 2.62% fall over the same period, reflecting mixed technical signals and cautious investor sentiment despite an upgrade to a Hold rating early in the week.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>ce611d2eac85ada5c662a9392b858df7</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jay Bharat Maruti Ltd Falls 3.54%: Technical Upgrades Amid Market Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jay-bharat-maruti-ltd-falls-354-technical-upgrades-amid-market-weakness-3788559</link><description>Jay Bharat Maruti Ltd experienced a volatile week ending 9 January 2026, with its share price declining 3.54% from Rs.100.20 to Rs.96.65, underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. Despite the weekly loss, the stock saw a significant technical upgrade early in the week, reflecting improved momentum and valuation metrics. However, subsequent market weakness and profit-taking led to a steady decline in price through the latter half of the week.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>f38bcd8f326b03459206389bf1fabd60</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Subex Ltd Falls 9.02% This Week: 2 Key Events Mark Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/subex-ltd-falls-902-this-week-2-key-events-mark-continued-downtrend-3788560</link><description>Subex Ltd’s stock endured a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, declining 9.02% to close at Rs.10.69, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 2.62% fall. The week was marked by a continuation of bearish technical momentum and a fresh 52-week low, reflecting persistent financial and market headwinds.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>3d6330a25e5f23619e1ada46754d0361</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Havells India Gains 1.82% Amid Mixed Technical Signals and Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/havells-india-gains-182-amid-mixed-technical-signals-and-market-volatility-3788558</link><description>Havells India Ltd. closed the week ending 9 January 2026 with a modest gain of 1.82%, outperforming the Sensex which declined 2.62% over the same period. The stock demonstrated notable intraday strength on 6 January, surging 3.28% to an intraday high of Rs.1,500.95, despite a broadly weak market. However, technical indicators present a mixed picture, with momentum shifting from bearish to mildly bearish, reflecting cautious investor sentiment amid sectoral and market volatility.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>0997e3b13966fd842a973ec3208670db</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CG Power Declines 8.54%: 5 Key Factors Behind the Sharp Weekly Drop</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cg-power-declines-854-5-key-factors-behind-the-sharp-weekly-drop-3788557</link><description>CG Power &amp; Industrial Solutions Ltd experienced a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, with its stock price declining by 8.54% to close at Rs.595.75, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 2.62% fall over the same period. The stock faced sustained selling pressure, technical headwinds including a bearish Death Cross formation, and mixed market signals amid heavy derivatives activity. Despite a brief intraday rebound on 8 January, the overall trend remained negative, reflecting sectoral weakness and cautious investor sentiment.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>ed170ee66b7fbcb76fab2df61d453ecd</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gokaldas Exports Ltd Falls 9.32%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gokaldas-exports-ltd-falls-932-5-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3788556</link><description>Gokaldas Exports Ltd experienced a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, with its share price declining by 9.32% to close at Rs.653.25, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The stock faced sustained selling pressure amid bearish technical signals, fresh 52-week lows, and deteriorating financial metrics, reflecting mounting investor caution in the garments and apparels sector.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>7334b21d947b5467d0a4039869832156</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ITC Ltd Falls 3.73%: 7 Key Factors Behind the Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/itc-ltd-falls-373-7-key-factors-behind-the-prolonged-downtrend-3788553</link><description>ITC Ltd experienced a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, with its stock price declining by 3.73% to close at Rs.337.10, underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62%. The stock hit multiple 52-week lows amid sustained selling pressure, heavy trading volumes, and a downgrade to a Sell rating by MarketsMOJO. Despite strong fundamentals such as robust ROE and steady sales growth, technical weakness and sector headwinds dominated investor sentiment throughout the week.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>f5bd3a1bc2f9a3d9dd928e15f949d1ad</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lux Industries Ltd Falls 8.08%: 5 Key Factors Behind the Steep Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lux-industries-ltd-falls-808-5-key-factors-behind-the-steep-weekly-decline-3788555</link><description>Lux Industries Ltd’s stock endured a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, declining 8.08% to close at Rs.1,020.35, significantly underperforming the Sensex’s 2.62% fall over the same period. The stock repeatedly hit fresh 52-week lows amid deteriorating financials, bearish technical signals, and cautious market sentiment, underscoring persistent headwinds for the garment and apparel company.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>ade82b56ede57f57a001ca531a529cc2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Infosys Ltd’s Mixed Week: -1.58% Price Change Amid Divergent Options Activity</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/infosys-ltds-mixed-week--158-price-change-amid-divergent-options-activity-3788551</link><description>Infosys Ltd experienced a mixed trading week from 5 to 9 January 2026, closing with a modest decline of 1.58% to Rs.1,614.75, outperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The stock showed volatility amid heavy options market activity ahead of the 27 January expiry, reflecting a complex interplay of bullish and bearish investor sentiment. Institutional interest remained robust, supported by strong liquidity and a recent upgrade to a Buy rating by MarketsMOJO.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>c726c202ea7ce4c0fc488e59e02e6f3c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:31:03 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>