<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:53:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nuvama-wealth-management-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3844789</link><description>Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development highlights a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raises concerns about its medium to long-term outlook amid weakening price action and technical signals.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>56ffe750e9d15997b4e75d8fde3630dd</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:53:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Varun Beverages Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/varun-beverages-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3844784</link><description>Varun Beverages Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>7922285638e75792240aaf47d15ac711</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:53:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cubical Financial Services Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cubical-financial-services-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3844788</link><description>Cubical Financial Services Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a prolonged bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>bb4fe325f4525164e61d4fb0dd369a87</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:53:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Satchmo Holdings Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/satchmo-holdings-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3844782</link><description>Satchmo Holdings Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Diversified Commercial Services sector, has recently formed a Death Cross—a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average—indicating a potential shift towards a bearish trend and signalling long-term weakness in the stock’s price momentum.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>f2dc05ae72ad0f66690ac7a50b3d65fe</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:53:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wipro Ltd. Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/wipro-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3844783</link><description>Wipro Ltd. (Stock ID: 531139), a major player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>a6217fc75e20205d5216669cb0d48127</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:53:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Felix Industries Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/felix-industries-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3844787</link><description>Felix Industries Ltd has recently experienced a significant technical event known as the Golden Cross, where its 50-day moving average has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development is widely regarded as a bullish signal, indicating a potential long-term trend reversal and a shift in momentum that could favour investors seeking growth opportunities in the Miscellaneous sector.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>458d69d5b5813a3a59e35ab225ea6581</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:53:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cigniti Technologies Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cigniti-technologies-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3844785</link><description>Cigniti Technologies Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s near-term outlook amid broader market pressures.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>7ab95a713cbf8ee96ead0870f16519ad</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:53:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PG Foils Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pg-foils-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3844781</link><description>PG Foils Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non - Ferrous Metals sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, suggesting that the stock may be poised for an upward trend despite its recent challenges.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>cf2ed1c0fb98e0459ae0c5f008e7a576</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:53:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Himadri Speciality Chemical Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/himadri-speciality-chemical-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3844780</link><description>Himadri Speciality Chemical Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development suggests a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium-term momentum and raising concerns about long-term weakness despite its strong historical performance.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>1df82982c664954133bcfca5dbd8ea71</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:53:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Torrent Power Ltd. Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/torrent-power-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3844786</link><description>Torrent Power Ltd. has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-DMA. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout, signalling a shift in long-term momentum and a possible trend reversal for the power sector company.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>d5c56a61a95b602ba6bb7fd07067846b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:53:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Reveal Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-reveal-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3844779</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has unfolded with a nuanced performance across Indian equities, as 4,075 companies declared results. While the proportion of positive earnings surprises has edged up marginally to 46.0%, the underlying trends reveal a complex interplay of sectoral strengths and market cap dynamics that investors must carefully analyse.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>94ddbd60d72fb2ef2aab0f3b9b8826d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:53:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Large-Cap Segment Edges Higher Led by Bank of Baroda; Defensive Stocks Show Mixed Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/large-cap-segment-edges-higher-led-by-bank-of-baroda-defensive-stocks-show-mixed-trends-3844633</link><description>The large-cap segment, represented by the BSE 100 index, recorded a modest gain of 0.23% on 17 Feb 2026, reflecting a cautious but positive market mood. While heavyweight stocks such as Bank of Baroda led the advance with a robust 3.66% return, some defensive names like Kwality Wall's lagged, declining by 4.98%. The advance-decline ratio of 1.63x, with 62 stocks advancing against 38 declining, underscores a broadly constructive environment amid mixed sectoral trends.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>026e97631bb52b65a1a1564ec0f5fc34</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:53:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mid-Cap Segment Surges 0.62% Led by Strong Sectoral Gains and Broad Market Breadth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/mid-cap-segment-surges-062-led-by-strong-sectoral-gains-and-broad-market-breadth-3844631</link><description>The BSE Midcap index advanced by 0.62% on 17 Feb 2026, outperforming broader market segments as select stocks demonstrated robust momentum. Aegis Vopak Term emerged as the top performer with a notable 5.81% return, while Brainbees Solutions lagged with a 4.22% decline. The segment’s breadth remained positive with an advance-decline ratio of 1.48, signalling broad-based participation amid mixed sectoral trends.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>7b03dbb3a235c62bb4c3239f3519026f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:53:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Small-Cap Segment Sees Mixed Performance Amid Sectoral Divergence</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/small-cap-segment-sees-mixed-performance-amid-sectoral-divergence-3844632</link><description>The BSE Smallcap index has experienced a modest decline of 0.4% today, extending a recent five-day slide of 2.75%, signalling a cautious mood among investors in the small-cap segment. Despite this, select stocks within the index have delivered notable returns, reflecting a nuanced market environment shaped by sectoral divergences and evolving technical outlooks.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ce8580f1c1c9e73e45d9e63a9319cab3</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:53:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ind-Agiv Commerce Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.66.5 Amidst Weak Fundamentals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ind-agiv-commerce-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs665-amidst-weak-fundamentals-3844630</link><description>Ind-Agiv Commerce Ltd’s shares declined sharply to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.66.5 on 17 Feb 2026, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory. This new low reflects persistent pressures on the company’s valuation amid subdued financial performance and challenging market conditions within the Trading &amp; Distributors sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>65964266d316818bfaddc24302ea5136</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:53:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Megri Soft Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/megri-soft-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3844627</link><description>Megri Soft Ltd, a player in the Commercial Services &amp; Supplies sector, has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.84.99, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid broader market gains. This drop reflects ongoing concerns about the company’s financial performance and valuation metrics.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>9fe0bad9185ba46c84f93af8b8eba77b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:53:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chemtech Industrial Valves Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.65</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/chemtech-industrial-valves-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs65-3844620</link><description>Chemtech Industrial Valves Ltd has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.65 today, marking a significant decline in its share price amid a sustained downward trajectory over recent sessions.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>3719a30a2b0dc85162c2e633ed2ac8d1</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:53:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Yuken India Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.694.1 Amidst Continued Financial Pressures</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/yuken-india-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs6941-amidst-continued-financial-pressures-3844626</link><description>Yuken India Ltd, a key player in the Compressors, Pumps &amp; Diesel Engines sector, touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.694.1 today, marking a significant decline amid ongoing financial headwinds and market volatility. The stock’s performance contrasts sharply with broader market gains, reflecting persistent challenges within the company’s financial metrics and valuation.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>d07db8b6200170e0c2a9d0ef79715caf</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:53:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shalibhadra Finance Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.90.4 Amid Market Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shalibhadra-finance-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs904-amid-market-underperformance-3844622</link><description>Shalibhadra Finance Ltd, a Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC), has touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.90.4 today, marking a significant decline amid broader market gains. The stock has underperformed its sector and the benchmark indices, reflecting ongoing pressures despite positive quarterly results and rising promoter confidence.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>2721d03e27d2fd95f71c676d2fc66844</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:53:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pharmaids Pharmaceuticals Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs 35</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pharmaids-pharmaceuticals-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs-35-3844628</link><description>Pharmaids Pharmaceuticals Ltd has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.35 today, marking a significant decline in its share price amid broader market gains. The stock underperformed its sector and the benchmark indices, reflecting ongoing concerns about the company’s financial health and market position.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>787880a821995e9552c9686103ea8fc5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:53:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:53:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>