<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:48:17 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Systematix Corporate Services Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/systematix-corporate-services-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3820941</link><description>Systematix Corporate Services Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s near- to medium-term outlook.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>ab6cfcc15271db5b51892b68fa29a872</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:48:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shahi Shipping Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shahi-shipping-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3820940</link><description>Shahi Shipping Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>b89e240690934703b0131348f2b9413d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:48:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coromandel International Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/coromandel-international-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3820937</link><description>Coromandel International Ltd, a prominent player in the Fertilizers sector, has recently formed a Death Cross as its 50-day moving average (DMA) crossed below the 200-DMA. This technical development is widely regarded as a bearish signal, indicating a possible deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term trend and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>b32fe1772e5431b4323f953f4bc2a18d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:48:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Redington Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/redington-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3820938</link><description>Redington Ltd, a prominent player in the Trading &amp; Distributors sector, has recently formed a Death Cross as its 50-day moving average (DMA) crossed below the 200-day moving average. This technical development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend, indicating potential deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raising concerns about long-term weakness despite its strong historical performance.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>36b91c028e1af27b1ba01cd40ad655bb</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:48:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Man Industries (India) Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/man-industries-india-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3820942</link><description>Man Industries (India) Ltd, a small-cap player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, has recently formed a Death Cross—a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, raising concerns about the stock’s near-term momentum and long-term strength amid a deteriorating technical landscape.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>75896045304dd9185e904a72965f4828</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:48:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Varun Beverages Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/varun-beverages-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3820939</link><description>Varun Beverages Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-DMA. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, suggesting that the stock may be poised for an upward trend reversal despite recent underperformance against the broader market.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>6c2f72b5107b3d1426608918f1e2b82d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:48:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mangalam Cement Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mangalam-cement-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3820936</link><description>Mangalam Cement Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout, indicating a possible trend reversal and a shift towards long-term upward momentum for the stock.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>d2b5f343d0639b15596c6a1f2551cda3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:48:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3820935</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has revealed a nuanced picture of corporate performance across Indian markets, with 1,201 companies reporting results. While aggregate profit growth remains modest, sectoral and market-cap-based disparities have emerged, highlighting the varied pace of recovery and growth among large, mid, and small cap stocks.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>879860063776a7bda3b64d5125561ce3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:48:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Emami Q3 FY26: Strong Quarter Masks Deeper Concerns About Long-Term Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/emami-q3-fy26-strong-quarter-masks-deeper-concerns-about-long-term-growth-3820948</link><description>Emami Ltd., the Kolkata-based FMCG major with a market capitalisation of ₹20,902 crores, reported a robust consolidated net profit of ₹319.48 crores in Q3 FY26, representing a sharp sequential surge of 115.36% from ₹148.35 crores in Q2 FY26 and a modest year-on-year growth of 14.51% from ₹278.99 crores in Q3 FY25. However, the impressive quarterly performance failed to arrest the stock's downward trajectory, with shares trading at ₹488.05 as of February 04, 2026, down 16.86% over the past year and 25.53% below the 52-week high of ₹655.40.
Time: 32 minutes ago</description><guid>026f70da25d827b804ccb074159b03b0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:48:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Zenith Fibres Q3 FY26: Other Income Masks Operational Struggles as Core Business Bleeds</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/zenith-fibres-q3-fy26-other-income-masks-operational-struggles-as-core-business-bleeds-3820947</link><description>Zenith Fibres Ltd., the Mumbai-based textile manufacturer specialising in polypropylene staple fibres, reported a net profit of ₹2.61 crores for Q3 FY26, a dramatic turnaround from a loss of ₹0.06 crores in Q2 FY26. However, beneath this headline figure lies a troubling reality: the company's core operations remain deeply unprofitable, with operating profit before other income standing at negative ₹0.06 crores. The profit surge was entirely driven by exceptional other income of ₹3.71 crores, which accounted for 107.85% of profit before tax—raising serious questions about earnings quality and sustainability.
Time: 32 minutes ago</description><guid>bd318f4eed62c4b2bd8877ae786ff74a</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:48:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aro Granite Industries Q3 FY26: Mounting Losses Signal Deepening Operational Crisis</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/aro-granite-industries-q3-fy26-mounting-losses-signal-deepening-operational-crisis-3820945</link><description>Aro Granite Industries Ltd., one of India's largest processed granite exporters, reported a dismal third quarter for FY2026, with losses deepening significantly as operational challenges intensified. The company posted a net loss of ₹2.97 crores in Q3 FY26, marking a deterioration from the ₹2.49 crore loss in Q2 FY26 and a stark reversal from the negligible profit of ₹0.00 crores reported in Q3 FY25. With a market capitalisation of just ₹44.00 crores, the micro-cap granite manufacturer is grappling with collapsing revenues, negative operating margins, and mounting interest burdens that threaten its financial viability.
Time: 32 minutes ago</description><guid>0f8365541ca4b05d26d466a0bc5f6821</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:48:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Binny Mills Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.169.35 on 4 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/binny-mills-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs16935-on-4-feb-2026-3820907</link><description>Binny Mills Ltd’s shares declined sharply to a new 52-week low of Rs.169.35 on 4 Feb 2026, marking a significant drop amid a prolonged downtrend. The stock opened with a gap down of 4.99% and despite an intraday high of Rs.187.15, it closed near its lowest point, reflecting persistent pressures on the counter.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b21f840f325d81030426349e41d9cb1c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:48:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eureka Forbes Ltd Reports Flat Quarterly Performance Amid Margin Pressures</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eureka-forbes-ltd-reports-flat-quarterly-performance-amid-margin-pressures-3820902</link><description>Eureka Forbes Ltd, a key player in the Electronics &amp; Appliances sector, has reported a flat financial performance for the quarter ended December 2025, marking a significant shift from its previously positive growth trajectory. The company’s financial trend score has declined sharply from 19 to -1 over the past three months, reflecting challenges in sustaining revenue growth and margin expansion amid a competitive market environment.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ccb89fee39e5c05c68b168df7fa7fcd9</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:48:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Devyani International Ltd Reports Flat Quarterly Performance Amid Mixed Financial Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/devyani-international-ltd-reports-flat-quarterly-performance-amid-mixed-financial-signals-3820901</link><description>Devyani International Ltd has posted a flat financial performance for the quarter ended December 2025, signalling a pause in its recent downward trend. While net sales and operating profits reached record highs, key return metrics and non-operating income continue to weigh on investor sentiment, prompting a cautious outlook despite a recent upgrade in the company’s rating.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>736008884fcc44024c295474d7969fb0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:48:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DRC Systems India Ltd Reports Strong Quarterly Gains Amid Financial Trend Shift</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/drc-systems-india-ltd-reports-strong-quarterly-gains-amid-financial-trend-shift-3820899</link><description>DRC Systems India Ltd has demonstrated a marked turnaround in its financial performance for the quarter ended December 2025, posting record-high revenues and profitability metrics that signal a positive shift from its previously flat trend. Despite a challenging broader market environment and a subdued long-term stock return, the company’s latest results reflect operational improvements and margin expansion that have caught investor attention.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>2a64338f99811d76ce9297c0149e113f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:48:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Investment &amp; Precision Castings Ltd Reports Very Positive Quarterly Performance Amid Strong Financial Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/investment-precision-castings-ltd-reports-very-positive-quarterly-performance-amid-strong-financial-trend-3820903</link><description>Investment &amp; Precision Castings Ltd has demonstrated a marked improvement in its financial performance for the quarter ended December 2025, signalling a shift from a positive to a very positive financial trend. The company’s latest quarterly results reveal record-breaking revenue and profitability metrics, underscoring its robust operational efficiency and strengthening market position within the Castings &amp; Forgings sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>40dbd254d9244f3ddfbf6e91a39a9457</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:48:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Equity Markets Show Mixed Trends as Utilities Surge and IT Slumps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/indian-equity-markets-show-mixed-trends-as-utilities-surge-and-it-slumps-3820892</link><description>Indian equity benchmarks closed modestly higher on 4 February 2026, with the Sensex gaining 78.56 points (0.09%) to 83,817.69 and the Nifty rising 48.45 points (0.19%) to 25,776.00. Market breadth was positive, supported by strong advances in the utilities sector, while IT stocks faced significant pressure. Mid and small caps underperformed, reflecting selective investor caution ahead of key corporate earnings next week.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>4fec00eece84ead8997a3f931d738328</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:48:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DCW Ltd Hits Intraday High with Strong 8.1% Surge on 4 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dcw-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-strong-81-surge-on-4-feb-2026-3820860</link><description>DCW Ltd demonstrated a strong intraday performance on 4 February 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 50.14, marking an 8.93% increase from its previous close. The petrochemicals company outpaced the broader market and its sector peers, reflecting notable trading momentum during the session.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ca54a3e1fa86631ef30874e8f2a22012</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:48:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SAB Events &amp; Governance Now Media Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.13.62</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sab-events-governance-now-media-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs1362-3820858</link><description>SAB Events &amp; Governance Now Media Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.13.62, marking a strong rally in the Media &amp; Entertainment sector. This achievement reflects sustained momentum, with the stock demonstrating robust gains over the past several weeks.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>8c58cbb12d6e55fafce4d4ed22069bbe</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:48:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:48:17 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>