<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 12:29:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Tata Steel, FSN E-Commerce, Shaily Engineer and Orissa Minerals Lead Market Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/q2-fy2026-earnings-review-mixed-results-across-market-caps-with-notable-sectoral-performances-3764619</link><description>As the Sep-2025 quarter earnings season concludes with 3,990 companies reporting, the market reveals a nuanced picture of corporate performance across sectors and market capitalisations. Positive results were recorded by 43.0% of companies, marking a slight rise from 40.0% in the previous quarter, reflecting a cautious but steady trend in earnings growth. Large caps, mid caps and small caps displayed varied outcomes, with mid caps showing the highest proportion of positive results at 50.0%.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>0254842dc149305037c7ed20bd38179d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 12:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Tata Steel, FSN E-Commerce, Orissa Minerals and Market Trends for Sep 2025</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/q2-fy2026-earnings-review-mixed-results-across-market-caps-with-select-sectoral-strength-3764606</link><description>As the Sep-2025 quarter earnings season concludes with 3,990 companies reporting, the market reveals a nuanced picture of corporate performance across sectors and market capitalisations. Tata Steel, FSN E-Commerce, and Orissa Minerals Development Company Ltd stand out among the top performers, while overall positive result proportions show subtle shifts compared to previous quarters.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>41d89e3c0ede2b78f66f6d00764625ec</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 12:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanghvi Movers Sees Revision in Market Evaluation Amid Mixed Financial Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sanghvi-movers-downgraded-to-sell-by-marketsmojo-amidst-weak-financial-trends-3764451</link><description>Sanghvi Movers, a small-cap player in the automobile sector, has experienced a revision in its market evaluation reflecting a nuanced view of its recent financial and technical performance. This shift comes amid a backdrop of mixed operational results and fluctuating stock returns, prompting a reassessment of the company’s standing within its sector.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>9ff8807587cc141400391e8f0f88e312</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 12:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ugro Capital Sees Revision in Market Evaluation Amid Mixed Financial Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ugro-capital-upgraded-from-sell-to-hold-by-marketsmojo-on-19-dec-2025-3764452</link><description>Ugro Capital, a small-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently undergone a revision in its market evaluation metrics. This shift reflects nuanced changes across several key analytical parameters, including quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook, providing investors with a refreshed perspective on the stock’s current standing.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>f26c3311a952bbc7bc653d8133bb756b</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 12:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BLS E-Services Sees Revision in Market Assessment Amid Positive Financial Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/bls-e-services-upgraded-to-buy-by-marketsmojo-on-strong-fundamentals-3764453</link><description>BLS E-Services has experienced a revision in its market evaluation, reflecting a more favourable analytical perspective driven by recent financial performance and market dynamics. This shift highlights the company’s evolving position within the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector and offers investors a refreshed outlook on its prospects.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>9963fcf790b6a318abf196605a101483</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 12:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 12:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>