<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:57:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec 2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3857084</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has concluded with 4,087 companies reporting results, revealing a nuanced picture of corporate performance across market capitalisations. While aggregate profit growth remains modest, sectoral and size-based disparities continue to shape investor sentiment as the market navigates a complex macroeconomic backdrop.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>faa94dd4a8906bffe023b43e4141140e</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:57:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Star Health &amp; Allied Insurance Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/star-health-allied-insurance-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3856008</link><description>Star Health &amp; Allied Insurance Company Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term momentum and investor sentiment.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>f283137f2a3b2246e29297a978a641cb</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:57:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Artemis Medicare Services Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/artemis-medicare-services-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3856009</link><description>Artemis Medicare Services Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum. Investors should carefully analyse the implications of this event amid the company’s current financial and market performance.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>fa0c102b5c0d0a89b2910d50321a1e9a</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:57:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nila Spaces Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nila-spaces-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3856002</link><description>Nila Spaces Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Realty sector, has recently formed a Death Cross as its 50-day moving average (DMA) crossed below the 200-DMA, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This technical development, coupled with deteriorating momentum indicators and a downgrade in its Mojo Grade to Sell, raises concerns about the stock’s near to medium-term outlook despite its strong historical performance.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>5d7efb4fd67ef1da2f26d7c30c1beb4e</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:57:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Varroc Engineering Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/varroc-engineering-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3855992</link><description>Varroc Engineering Ltd, a key player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has recently formed a Death Cross—a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>aeb87f9d6db7b422d570d42cccaff944</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:57:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Best Agrolife Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/best-agrolife-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3855989</link><description>Best Agrolife Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Pesticides &amp; Agrochemicals sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ca9d7cf5a121b80b7eb0860976940fc2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:57:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Parag Milk Foods Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/parag-milk-foods-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3855996</link><description>Parag Milk Foods Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>5c3f3d0eada31f584236837fdef02355</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:57:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sujala Trading &amp; Holdings Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sujala-trading-holdings-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3855993</link><description>Sujala Trading &amp; Holdings Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about sustained bearish momentum in the near to medium term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>9de39eb7108fe2980ee81d7ceb2500a0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:57:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Diligent Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/diligent-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3855994</link><description>Diligent Industries Ltd, a micro-cap player in the edible oil sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development is widely regarded as a bearish signal, indicating a potential deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term trend and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>2b8149f46c580aa489515d47c98a7680</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:57:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Veerhealth Care Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/veerhealth-care-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3855990</link><description>Veerhealth Care Ltd (Stock ID: 631680) has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, raising concerns about the stock’s near-term momentum and long-term strength within the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>c19416fff874bfbd23e0a70ea73d1740</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:57:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Longspur International Ventures Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/longspur-international-ventures-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3855991</link><description>Longspur International Ventures Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>6b0b63b5af29594920778e6718cf0d71</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:57:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Balkrishna Industries Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/balkrishna-industries-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3855995</link><description>Balkrishna Industries Ltd (BIL), a prominent player in the Tyres &amp; Rubber Products sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross—a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-DMA. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, offering investors a fresh perspective on the stock’s future trajectory.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>4b05e30ee668659319f77389fb358fee</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:57:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Petronet LNG Ltd. Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/petronet-lng-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3855988</link><description>Petronet LNG Ltd., a prominent player in the gas sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross—a technical event where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average—indicating a potential shift towards a sustained bullish trend and renewed investor optimism.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>30c39b96299949edb0f7c3f21044e686</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:57:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec 2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3855940</link><description>The December 2025 quarterly earnings season has delivered a nuanced picture of corporate performance across India’s stock market, with 4,087 companies reporting results. While aggregate profit growth remains modest, sectoral and market cap-wise disparities highlight evolving dynamics in corporate earnings momentum.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>c0c183b6675572a5c0264a2dcaed68d8</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:57:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dev Information Technology Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs 22.57</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dev-information-technology-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs-2257-3855883</link><description>Dev Information Technology Ltd’s stock price declined sharply to a new 52-week and all-time low of Rs.22.57 on 25 Feb 2026, marking a significant downturn amid continued underperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>2012fce9803a0d3191705e2e97dde7de</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:57:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uma Exports Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/uma-exports-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3855884</link><description>Uma Exports Ltd has reached a new 52-week low, with its share price touching an intraday low of ₹27.51, just 1.98% above its lowest level of ₹27.25 recorded over the past year. This marks a significant decline for the stock, which has been on a downward trajectory for the last nine consecutive trading sessions, losing 15.91% in returns during this period.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>45c9d1bb29ea583de9e005816f3605e7</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:57:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Abbott India Ltd. Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/abbott-india-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-underperformance-3855882</link><description>Abbott India Ltd. has recently touched a 52-week low, closing just 1.49% above its lowest price point of Rs 26,006.3. This marks a significant moment for the pharmaceutical and biotechnology company as it continues to face headwinds reflected in its stock performance and valuation metrics.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>7d18485710c45d17f37a33618f1932e6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:57:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Integra Essentia Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/integra-essentia-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3855875</link><description>Integra Essentia Ltd’s shares have declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing at ₹1.32 on 25 Feb 2026, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory. This new low reflects persistent headwinds faced by the FMCG company amid broader market dynamics and company-specific performance factors.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>ff3b3988de8f4f5a7bf54aaa7588b61b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:57:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:57:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>