<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:18:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Are G M Breweries Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-g-m-breweries-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3783595</link><description>G M Breweries Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are strong, with net sales up 21.89% year-on-year and net profit increasing by 91.22%, marking the highest quarterly revenue in the company's history and showcasing improved operational efficiency and profitability. The company maintains a debt-free balance sheet and strong profitability metrics, indicating a positive financial trajectory.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4e9e030922ab86b878e1a8ed24278bd5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:18:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Axita Cotton Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-axita-cotton-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3783594</link><description>Axita Cotton Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results show modest revenue growth of 1.14% year-on-year, but profitability has significantly declined, with a net profit drop of 61.22% and an operating profit margin of -0.32%. Overall, the company faces serious operational challenges despite a strong balance sheet.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>113f583a5ea848f150179fe3763b52ba</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:18:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cello World Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cello-world-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3783588</link><description>Cello World Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about long-term weakness amid a challenging market backdrop.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>2365882e03dc395651b0781f80fbe852</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:18:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Innovana Thinklabs Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/innovana-thinklabs-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3783587</link><description>Innovana Thinklabs Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b8f6e57d1c58d0be7fddd78bd842ebaa</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:18:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahindra Logistics Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mahindra-logistics-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3783589</link><description>Mahindra Logistics Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>09d4fb7592f5f31c5746cc77813ef264</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:18:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dishman Carbogen Amcis Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dishman-carbogen-amcis-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3783585</link><description>Dishman Carbogen Amcis Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend, suggesting potential long-term weakness and a deterioration in the stock’s momentum.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>e6a3dec3e669df1fe7cd606f11abef2d</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:18:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pfizer Ltd. Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pfizer-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3783584</link><description>Pfizer Ltd., a key player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>c2ea4a2730eb9cd74a1543b5ad51811c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:18:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GFL Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gfl-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3783586</link><description>GFL Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development underscores a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raises concerns about its long-term outlook amid ongoing weakness in performance metrics and market sentiment.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>5f6bf291038bbac4f904c2da715e4fb3</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:18:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bombay Burmah Trading Corporation Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bombay-burmah-trading-corporation-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3783582</link><description>Bombay Burmah Trading Corporation Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raising concerns about its medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>f558f33d7ba8d18f477a1ebef56f9d0d</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:18:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kovai Medical Center &amp; Hospital Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kovai-medical-center-hospital-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3783580</link><description>Kovai Medical Center &amp; Hospital Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average has crossed below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s near to medium-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>89a0f831f95685632b16c418450ca586</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:18:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cipla Ltd. Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cipla-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3783576</link><description>Cipla Ltd., a leading player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>f1335ca43cfb52053b3ee4a401dd126b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:18:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Smruthi Organics Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/smruthi-organics-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3783575</link><description>Smruthi Organics Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s long-term strength.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>fab4b90441c122f90fae75c282eac90b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:18:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kajaria Ceramics Ltd. Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kajaria-ceramics-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3783577</link><description>Kajaria Ceramics Ltd., a key player in the diversified consumer products sector, has recently formed a Death Cross—a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium- to long-term momentum and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>d3e01862f5512a38dc9e0a162e3388c7</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:18:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mallcom (India) Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mallcom-india-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3783578</link><description>Mallcom (India) Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>7b6378dfd0522c68b4fcf1661ec35c73</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:18:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gokaldas Exports Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gokaldas-exports-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3783579</link><description>Gokaldas Exports Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's near-term prospects amid ongoing weakness in the garments and apparels sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>293c700af3788d86d30753d78e9734e4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:18:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sundaram Finance Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Indicating Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sundaram-finance-ltd-forms-golden-cross-indicating-potential-bullish-breakout-3783583</link><description>Sundaram Finance Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development is widely regarded as a bullish signal, suggesting a potential trend reversal and a shift towards long-term upward momentum for the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) stock.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>41fd5d78c7dc4d969dcab8b29a9258e4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:18:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Natco Pharma Ltd. Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/natco-pharma-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3783581</link><description>Natco Pharma Ltd., a key player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-DMA. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, offering investors a fresh perspective on the stock’s future trajectory.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>833620882852ccd5b30db1a9f47c272a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:18:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Q3 FY2026 Earnings Review: Mixed Results Across Market Caps with Mid Caps Leading Profit Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/q3-fy2026-earnings-review-mixed-results-across-market-caps-with-mid-caps-leading-profit-growth-3783574</link><description>The September 2025 quarter earnings season has revealed a nuanced picture across Indian equities, with 4,047 companies reporting results. While the overall proportion of positive earnings outcomes remains moderate at 42.0%, sectoral and market capitalisation distinctions underscore pockets of strength and emerging opportunities for investors.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b6a4102aa38525734805aa3266e9894a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:18:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Airan Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/airan-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3783542</link><description>Airan Ltd, a player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has reached a new 52-week low, reflecting ongoing pressures on its share price. The stock’s latest decline underscores a challenging period marked by subdued financial performance and valuation concerns.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>205e283bb27f7e6b6210225fb848a9a0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:18:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sensex and Nifty Slip Amid Mixed Sectoral Trends; Pharma Leads Gains</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-and-nifty-slip-amid-mixed-sectoral-trends-pharma-leads-gains-3783541</link><description>Indian equity markets closed lower on 6 Jan 2026, with the Sensex retreating 376.28 points (-0.44%) to 85,063.34 and the Nifty 50 shedding 71.6 points (-0.27%) to finish at 26,178.70. Despite the modest declines, the Nifty remains within striking distance of its 52-week high, trading just 0.74% below the peak of 26,373.20. Market breadth was weak, with declines outnumbering advances across the BSE500 index, reflecting cautious investor sentiment amid mixed sectoral trends and subdued foreign institutional activity.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>b74c69dd4ffa866eca0591ed1c648150</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:18:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:18:13 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>