<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:16:12 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Gujarat Narmada Valley Fertilizers &amp; Chemicals Ltd. Declines 2.71% Amid Mixed Technical Signals and Hold Upgrade</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gujarat-narmada-valley-fertilizers-chemicals-ltd-declines-271-amid-mixed-technical-signals-and-hold-upgrade-3788325</link><description>Gujarat Narmada Valley Fertilizers &amp; Chemicals Ltd. (GNFC) closed the week ending 9 January 2026 at Rs.479.65, down 2.71% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.493.00. This decline slightly outpaced the Sensex’s 2.62% fall over the same period, reflecting a week of mixed technical signals and valuation-driven investor sentiment amid broader market weakness.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>b5bc5d00e46604ee98dda8c41f60eb76</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:16:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Copper Ltd Falls 3.89%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-copper-ltd-falls-389-5-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3788326</link><description>Hindustan Copper Ltd experienced a volatile week from 5 to 9 January 2026, closing down 3.89% at Rs.520.95 despite hitting multiple 52-week highs early in the week. The stock outperformed the Sensex’s 2.62% decline, reflecting mixed investor sentiment amid strong volume surges and sector headwinds. Key events included a series of new highs on 5, 6, and 7 January, followed by profit-taking and sector weakness that pressured prices towards the week’s close.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>a5e66554cf11be361667f841618322c2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:16:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Universal Cables Ltd. Falls 11.83%: 2 Key Events Shaping the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/universal-cables-ltd-falls-1183-2-key-events-shaping-the-week-3788323</link><description>Universal Cables Ltd. experienced a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, with its stock price declining sharply by 11.83% to close at Rs.841.30, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The week was marked by sustained selling pressure, technical momentum shifts, and heightened volatility, culminating in a notable intraday low and a complex technical outlook that investors should carefully analyse.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>efb16d86ebb7837d73ce8602f9720428</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:16:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>J K Cements Gains 2.64%: Technical Shift and Financial Strength Drive Weekly Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/j-k-cements-gains-264-technical-shift-and-financial-strength-drive-weekly-momentum-3788324</link><description>J K Cements Ltd recorded a modest weekly gain of 2.64%, closing at Rs.5,721.70 on 9 January 2026, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 2.62% over the same period. The week was marked by a technical momentum shift and an upgrade in the company’s investment rating, both contributing to the stock’s relative strength amid broader market weakness.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>a8d3b2e11639252467c3288030a071fe</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:16:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DCM Shriram Industries Ltd Falls 10.41%: Technical Headwinds and Valuation Shifts Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dcm-shriram-industries-ltd-falls-1041-technical-headwinds-and-valuation-shifts-shape-the-week-3788322</link><description>DCM Shriram Industries Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its stock price declining by 10.41% from Rs.54.75 to Rs.49.05, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. Despite a technical upgrade from 'Strong Sell' to 'Sell' reflecting some stabilisation in valuation and momentum indicators, the company faced persistent financial headwinds and bearish price action throughout the week.
Time: 40 minutes ago</description><guid>8b86cd8ff2d0fed04d32c12d631045ae</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:16:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>L G Balakrishnan &amp; Bros Ltd Gains 4.65%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/l-g-balakrishnan-bros-ltd-gains-465-3-key-factors-driving-the-week-3788321</link><description>L G Balakrishnan &amp; Bros Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 4.65% from ₹1,778.20 to ₹1,860.80 between 5 and 9 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 2.62% over the same period. The stock’s resilience amid a broadly negative market was supported by a series of technical momentum shifts and a cautious but positive fundamental reassessment, reflecting a complex but ultimately bullish narrative for the week.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>02211bbf3fc938f7f5365c008e418b23</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:16:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Info Edge Declines 3.12% Despite Intraday Surge and Open Interest Spike</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/info-edge-declines-312-despite-intraday-surge-and-open-interest-spike-3788319</link><description>Info Edge (India) Ltd experienced a volatile week ending 9 January 2026, closing at Rs.1,321.60, down 3.12% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.1,364.15. This decline slightly underperformed the Sensex’s 2.62% fall over the same period. The stock showed resilience midweek with a strong intraday surge on 7 January, supported by a significant rise in open interest, but profit-taking and broader market weakness weighed on the closing sessions.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>a2b69c8d074754877774fe3a1775c990</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:16:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Navneet Education Ltd Gains 1.08%: 4 Key Technical Shifts Shape Weekly Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/navneet-education-ltd-gains-108-4-key-technical-shifts-shape-weekly-performance-3788320</link><description>Navneet Education Ltd closed the week with a modest gain of 1.08%, rising from Rs.147.65 to Rs.149.25 between 5 and 9 January 2026, outperforming the Sensex which declined by 2.62% over the same period. The stock showed early-week strength with a notable technical upgrade and bullish momentum shifts, though it faced selling pressure towards the end of the week amid mixed technical signals and broader market weakness.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>a123f8afcbd3381e80e7f86ec7ac7988</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:16:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Banganga Paper Industries Falls 9.41%: Technical Shifts and Downgrade Drive Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/banganga-paper-industries-falls-941-technical-shifts-and-downgrade-drive-weekly-decline-3788317</link><description>Banganga Paper Industries Ltd experienced a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, with its stock price declining by 9.41% to close at Rs.49.11, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell by 2.62%. The week was marked by a notable downgrade to a Strong Sell rating amid deteriorating technical and fundamental indicators, alongside a shift to mildly bearish momentum that weighed heavily on investor sentiment.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>b14adc39e5a547c2e9cd0117e85047aa</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:16:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manaksia Steels Ltd Falls 8.63%: 3 Key Factors Behind the Sharp Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/manaksia-steels-ltd-falls-863-3-key-factors-behind-the-sharp-weekly-decline-3788318</link><description>Manaksia Steels Ltd experienced a turbulent week from 5 to 9 January 2026, closing at Rs.62.38, down 8.63% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.68.27. This decline notably outpaced the Sensex’s 2.62% fall over the same period, reflecting significant volatility driven by sharp swings in investor sentiment and regulatory circuit triggers. The stock’s week was marked by an initial surge to upper circuit limits followed by consecutive days of heavy selling pressure culminating in two lower circuit hits.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>7156ed7816d96791952bb6b3d8f36d1e</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:16:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indo Rama Synthetics Falls 8.58%: Downgrade and Technical Shift Mark a Cautious Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indo-rama-synthetics-falls-858-downgrade-and-technical-shift-mark-a-cautious-week-3788314</link><description>Indo Rama Synthetics (India) Ltd endured a challenging week on the bourses, with its stock price declining by 8.58% from Rs.48.50 to Rs.44.34 between 5 and 9 January 2026. This underperformance was notably sharper than the Sensex’s 2.62% drop over the same period, reflecting investor caution amid a downgrade to Hold and a marked shift in technical momentum. The week was characterised by mixed financial signals and increased volatility, culminating in subdued market sentiment for the stock.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>86cf2e08ebb3265a60e0251a99c9c07d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:16:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Housing Development &amp; Infrastructure Ltd Falls 7.88%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/housing-development-infrastructure-ltd-falls-788-6-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-decline-3788312</link><description>Housing Development &amp; Infrastructure Ltd (HDIL) endured a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, with its share price declining by 7.88% to close at Rs.2.22, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The stock repeatedly hit fresh 52-week lows amid heavy selling pressure, lower circuit hits, and deteriorating fundamentals, underscoring persistent investor concerns and sectoral headwinds.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>1ed6567c671e3e89391eacab45abd3e3</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:16:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Hume Pipe Falls 3.63%: Mixed Technical Signals and Financials Shape Weekly Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indian-hume-pipe-falls-363-mixed-technical-signals-and-financials-shape-weekly-trend-3788315</link><description>Indian Hume Pipe Company Ltd ended the week down 3.63% at Rs.407.75, underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The stock experienced a volatile week marked by shifts in technical momentum and a significant upgrade in its investment rating from Sell to Hold, reflecting a complex interplay of bullish and bearish signals amid improving quarterly financials. Despite the overall decline, the stock outperformed the benchmark on two trading days, highlighting investor interest amid mixed market conditions.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>8701e3dce5cc56ea88c98e60115020e7</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:16:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sun Pharmaceutical Edges Lower -0.02% Despite Bullish Derivatives Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sun-pharmaceutical-edges-lower--002-despite-bullish-derivatives-surge-3788313</link><description>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd closed the week almost flat at Rs.1,729.95, down a marginal 0.02% from Rs.1,730.30 last Friday, while the Sensex declined sharply by 2.62%. The stock outperformed the broader market significantly, buoyed by strong bullish momentum in its derivatives segment and sustained investor optimism despite some volatility in delivery volumes.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>5ee37762868182339f3ae8942cf2c469</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:16:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Elxsi Gains 6.57%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-elxsi-gains-657-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3788316</link><description>Tata Elxsi Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance from 5 to 9 January 2026, rising 6.57% to close at Rs.5,687.65, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined 2.62% over the same period. The stock’s rally was marked by a remarkable intraday surge on 7 January, robust institutional interest, and heightened derivatives activity, reflecting a complex interplay of bullish momentum and cautious sentiment amid mixed market conditions.
Time: 41 minutes ago</description><guid>ae9cdcf68a058e0f699ce8f23c3fc53a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:16:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Falls 4.32%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-motors-passenger-vehicles-falls-432-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3788310</link><description>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd (TMPV) experienced a challenging week from 5 to 9 January 2026, with its share price declining by 4.32% to close at Rs.354.30, underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. Despite robust trading volumes and significant put option activity signalling bearish sentiment, the stock faced persistent selling pressure amid sector headwinds and technical resistance levels.
Time: 42 minutes ago</description><guid>10f2255ba1ab6f587786756e18bdfe40</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:16:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Expo Engineering Falls 13.77%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Sharp Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/expo-engineering-falls-1377-2-key-factors-driving-the-sharp-decline-3788308</link><description>Expo Engineering and Projects Ltd experienced a steep decline of 13.77% over the week ending 9 January 2026, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% in the same period. The stock’s slide was marked by a series of bearish technical signals and a downgrade to a Strong Sell rating, reflecting growing concerns over its financial health and momentum. Despite some valuation appeal, the week’s events underscored mounting risks for the micro-cap stock.
Time: 42 minutes ago</description><guid>ac259ba0a75b7d911b8f8c627cb2ddd7</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:16:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Britannia Industries Ltd’s Mixed Week: -0.21% Price Change Amid Technical Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/britannia-industries-ltds-mixed-week--021-price-change-amid-technical-shifts-3788309</link><description>Britannia Industries Ltd closed the week marginally lower by 0.21% at Rs.5,977.65, underperforming its early-week gains but significantly outperforming the Sensex, which fell 2.62% over the same period. The stock showed resilience amid a volatile market, with technical momentum shifting bullish midweek before succumbing to price pressure on 8 January 2026. This review analyses the key events and price movements shaping Britannia’s performance during the week ending 9 January 2026.
Time: 42 minutes ago</description><guid>0bf39780491d31e2cc00505a1adb4f00</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:16:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flexituff Ventures Declines 0.46%: 2 Key Events Highlight Persistent Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/flexituff-ventures-declines-046-2-key-events-highlight-persistent-downtrend-3788307</link><description>Flexituff Ventures International Ltd’s stock closed the week at Rs.12.88, down 0.46% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.12.94, underperforming the Sensex which declined 2.62% over the same period. The week was marked by significant bearish developments including a fresh 52-week low and a lower circuit hit, underscoring ongoing financial and technical challenges for the micro-cap garment and apparel company.
Time: 42 minutes ago</description><guid>2d2bc81dae2eaa6e6c5d55cbb0a448fc</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:16:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ABB India Ltd Declines 2.01%: Mixed Signals Amid Heavy Options Activity</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/abb-india-ltd-declines-201-mixed-signals-amid-heavy-options-activity-3788306</link><description>ABB India Ltd closed the week at Rs.5,092.70, down 2.01% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.5,197.00, slightly outperforming the Sensex which fell 2.62% over the same period. The week was marked by volatile price action, with the stock experiencing a sharp intraday low on 8 January amid sectoral weakness, but also robust call option activity signalling mixed investor sentiment ahead of the January expiry.
Time: 43 minutes ago</description><guid>eb2fec40ee4143f1d6e243e4b16b0104</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:16:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:16:12 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>