<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:42:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Adani Green Energy Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-green-energy-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-market-positioning-3844602</link><description>Adani Green Energy Ltd (ADANIGREEN) has witnessed a notable surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market participation and potential directional bets. The stock’s recent outperformance relative to its sector and sustained gains over consecutive sessions have attracted heightened investor attention, reflected in a 10.55% rise in OI and robust volume activity.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>fe1dbf534bc040f47767303ea43404d7</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:42:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KFin Technologies Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Rising Market Activity</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kfin-technologies-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-rising-market-activity-3844603</link><description>KFin Technologies Ltd (KFINTECH) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened investor interest and potential shifts in market positioning. The stock outperformed its sector peers, gaining 1.92% on 17 Feb 2026, supported by a 20.34% jump in open interest and robust volume activity, indicating fresh directional bets emerging among traders.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>904d09114582b46f9cdaf1e7d9c7e1f5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:42:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Union Bank of India Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/union-bank-of-india-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-market-momentum-3844605</link><description>Union Bank of India has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, reflecting heightened market activity and shifting investor sentiment. The bank’s stock recently hit a new 52-week high of Rs 190, buoyed by strong volume and positive price momentum, signalling renewed confidence among traders and investors alike.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>8f47a0b7009575de2cfd164cc98d6235</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:42:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank Of India Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Signalling Strong Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bank-of-india-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-signalling-strong-market-positioning-3844601</link><description>Bank Of India (BANKINDIA) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, reflecting heightened market activity and shifting investor sentiment. The stock hit a fresh 52-week high of ₹171 on 17 Feb 2026, supported by robust volume and positive price momentum, signalling renewed bullishness among traders and institutional participants.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>8e9da09fd81207beb91c8599faf0fda3</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:42:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Godrej Consumer Products Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Positive Price Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/godrej-consumer-products-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-positive-price-momentum-3844600</link><description>Godrej Consumer Products Ltd (GODREJCP) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market interest and potential directional bets. The 13.96% increase in OI, coupled with rising volumes and price momentum, suggests evolving market positioning that investors and traders should closely monitor.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>652f698be8a7f41951e83fc2a99e0f1f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:42:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shree Cement Ltd. Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shree-cement-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3844604</link><description>Shree Cement Ltd. has witnessed a notable 10.15% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock trading near its 52-week low. This surge in open interest, coupled with subdued price movement and falling investor participation, suggests a complex positioning landscape that investors and traders should carefully analyse.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>fb23ac88a5fef9ad1b2537399255ffdb</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:42:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3844590</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has unfolded with a nuanced picture across Indian equities, as 4,075 companies reported results reflecting a modest improvement in profitability and mixed sectoral performances. While mid-cap stocks continue to outperform with a 52.0% positive result ratio, large caps lag behind at 43.0%, underscoring divergent momentum across market capitalisations.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>a74ad90cd7d7b1baa5f7f92048c510cb</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:42:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Compuage Infocom Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/compuage-infocom-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3844599</link><description>Compuage Infocom Ltd, a micro-cap player in the IT - Hardware sector, witnessed a sharp decline on 17 Feb 2026, hitting its lower circuit limit as intense selling pressure gripped the stock. The share price plummeted by 4.83%, closing at ₹1.38, marking the maximum permissible daily loss and signalling panic selling among investors.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>bbddb71b06e16dff334e04135c617944</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:42:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Small-Cap Segment Sees Mixed Performance Amid Broader Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/small-cap-segment-sees-mixed-performance-amid-broader-market-volatility-3844593</link><description>The BSE Smallcap index has experienced a modest decline of 0.4% today, extending a recent five-day slide of 2.75%, signalling a cautious phase for the small-cap segment. Despite this, select stocks within the index have delivered notable returns, underscoring a mixed performance landscape shaped by sectoral divergences and evolving technical outlooks.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>32e91480d1bfb055953bfb788b18d14c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:42:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Globe International Carriers Ltd Hits Upper Circuit Amid Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/globe-international-carriers-ltd-hits-upper-circuit-amid-robust-buying-pressure-3844598</link><description>Shares of Globe International Carriers Ltd surged to hit the upper circuit limit on 17 Feb 2026, propelled by strong buying interest and heightened investor participation. The stock closed at ₹48.00, marking a maximum daily gain of 4.69%, significantly outperforming its sector and benchmark indices amid robust volumes and unfilled demand.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>eef86cf8519eda11c876ca10bd8e7bde</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:42:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>APL Apollo Tubes Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/apl-apollo-tubes-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-price-action-3844595</link><description>APL Apollo Tubes Ltd (APLAPOLLO), a key player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, has witnessed a notable 13.3% surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting positioning among traders. Despite a recent four-day price decline, the stock remains close to its 52-week high, reflecting a complex interplay of bullish and bearish sentiments in the market.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>bf23387e5da001dfb3dd8b8a5fca3acf</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:42:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharti Airtel Ltd Sees High-Value Trading Amid Mixed Technical Signals and Institutional Caution</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharti-airtel-ltd-sees-high-value-trading-amid-mixed-technical-signals-and-institutional-caution-3844596</link><description>Bharti Airtel Ltd, a dominant player in the Indian telecom sector, witnessed significant trading activity on 17 Feb 2026, with a total traded value exceeding ₹567 crore. Despite this high-value turnover, the stock closed marginally lower, reflecting a nuanced market sentiment amid fluctuating investor participation and mixed technical indicators.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>6415fb709b9a06fe647daa48fc4eb681</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:42:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eurotex Industries and Exports Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eurotex-industries-and-exports-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3844594</link><description>Eurotex Industries and Exports Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, surged to hit its upper circuit limit on 17 Feb 2026, registering a maximum daily gain of 4.98%. This sharp price movement was driven by robust buying interest, despite the stock trading below its key moving averages and a modest market capitalisation of ₹11.00 crores.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>8a25078cc125da112d5e9d2cb5cfce84</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:42:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aurobindo Pharma Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aurobindo-pharma-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3844597</link><description>Aurobindo Pharma Ltd. has witnessed a significant 33.06% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this, the stock underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting a complex interplay of bullish and bearish sentiments among traders.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>7cc3a61bcead2b12ae265c93ae8effe9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:42:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mid-Cap Segment Advances 0.62% Led by Strong Sectoral Gains and Broad Market Breadth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/mid-cap-segment-advances-062-led-by-strong-sectoral-gains-and-broad-market-breadth-3844592</link><description>The BSE Midcap index advanced by 0.62% on 17 Feb 2026, outperforming broader market segments as a majority of stocks within the segment registered gains. With 91 stocks advancing against 53 decliners, the advance-decline ratio stood at a healthy 1.72x, signalling broad-based participation. Select mid-cap stocks and sectors contributed decisively to this resilient performance amid mixed global cues and domestic economic data.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>205350cf5667ebe103165b44d684ec1b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:42:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Large-Cap Segment Edges Higher Amid Mixed Sector Trends on 17 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/large-cap-segment-edges-higher-amid-mixed-sector-trends-on-17-feb-2026-3844591</link><description>The large-cap segment demonstrated a modest gain on 17 Feb 2026, with the BSE 100 index inching up by 0.16%. While heavyweight stocks such as Bank of Baroda delivered robust returns, some consumer staples like Kwality Wall's lagged, reflecting a divergence between defensive and cyclical sectors amid cautious investor sentiment.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>f9a4525260a4fc1e412098b100c5a707</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:42:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sadhana Nitro Chem Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Financial Struggles</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sadhana-nitro-chem-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-financial-struggles-3844586</link><description>Sadhana Nitro Chem Ltd’s shares declined sharply to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.5.52 on 17 Feb 2026, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory. The stock has underperformed its sector and benchmark indices amid a series of disappointing financial results and deteriorating fundamentals.
Time: 30 minutes ago</description><guid>62c3dc22443d369a53d0d73b4e56dd30</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:42:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oxford Industries Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.7.99</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/oxford-industries-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs799-3844585</link><description>Oxford Industries Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.7.99 today, marking a notable surge in its stock price and reflecting strong momentum over recent sessions.
Time: 31 minutes ago</description><guid>64e79243961e428198f8aaa7a31f3d33</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:42:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dhunseri Ventures Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Earnings Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dhunseri-ventures-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-earnings-pressure-3844587</link><description>Dhunseri Ventures Ltd has touched a new 52-week low, closing just 0.4% above its lowest price of Rs 249, reflecting ongoing pressures on the stock amid a challenging financial performance and subdued market sentiment.
Time: 31 minutes ago</description><guid>e2c90ce93670247b71da0797c1813cb4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:42:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vashu Bhagnani Industries Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.50.2</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vashu-bhagnani-industries-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs502-3844588</link><description>Shares of Vashu Bhagnani Industries Ltd have declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.50.2, marking a significant downturn amid broader market gains. The stock’s recent performance highlights ongoing concerns within the company’s financial metrics and valuation, contrasting with the positive trajectory of the Sensex and its sector peers.
Time: 31 minutes ago</description><guid>c032ef6953e4ad2b991a2a576f75457f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:42:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:42:04 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>