<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 01:22:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Are Avenue Supermarts Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-avenue-supermarts-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3789076</link><description>Avenue Supermarts Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are strong, with record net sales of ₹18,100.88 crores and a net profit of ₹855.92 crores, reflecting significant year-on-year growth. However, the company faces challenges with operating margins and capital efficiency amid competitive pressures.
Time: Jan 11 2026 07:11 PM IST</description><guid>72103ab7b57057cc323147f841631c76</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 01:22:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Integra Essentia Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-integra-essentia-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3789075</link><description>Integra Essentia Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show strong sales growth of 12.37% year-on-year, but profitability remains a concern with low operating margins and reliance on non-operating income, raising questions about long-term sustainability. Overall, the financial health indicates significant challenges despite the sales increase.
Time: Jan 11 2026 07:11 PM IST</description><guid>ce622036b66e54da8d25e83cd128e24b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 01:22:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Gretex Corporate Services Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-gretex-corporate-services-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3789074</link><description>Gretex Corporate Services Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, showing a significant decline in net profit to ₹1.61 crores and negative operating margins, indicating operational challenges and a downward trend in financial performance. The company needs to reassess its strategy to address these issues.
Time: Jan 11 2026 07:10 PM IST</description><guid>f9d4c0a3cac6013dcd102eb8015c6746</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 01:22:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 01:22:01 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>