<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:23:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Kokuyo Camlin Gains 1.05%: Key Financial Shifts and Market Pressures This Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kokuyo-camlin-gains-105-key-financial-shifts-and-market-pressures-this-week-3812897</link><description>Kokuyo Camlin Ltd’s stock posted a modest gain of 1.05% over the week ending 30 January 2026, closing at Rs.83.38 compared to Rs.82.51 the previous Friday. This performance, however, lagged behind the Sensex’s stronger 1.62% advance during the same period. The week was marked by a sharp intraday dip to a 52-week low and a subsequent rebound supported by improved quarterly profitability, reflecting a mixed but cautiously optimistic market response.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>36fe8ce5f0047ac51dba0cbda773fcd9</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Copper Ltd Surges 28.20% in a Week: 5 Key Drivers Behind the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-copper-ltd-surges-2820-in-a-week-5-key-drivers-behind-the-rally-3812896</link><description>Hindustan Copper Ltd delivered a remarkable weekly performance, surging 28.20% from Rs.535.55 to Rs.686.55 between 26 and 30 January 2026, vastly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 1.62% gain over the same period. The stock’s rally was marked by multiple new 52-week and all-time highs, strong volume spikes, and robust fundamental updates that collectively fuelled investor enthusiasm amid a cautiously optimistic market backdrop.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>5256b8d72068abbfe7d64a0e2b1ce67c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Universal Cables Ltd Gains 9.17%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/universal-cables-ltd-gains-917-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3812894</link><description>Universal Cables Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 9.17% from Rs.666.10 to Rs.727.15 between 26 and 30 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% gain over the same period. The week was marked by a notable technical momentum shift, a downgrade followed by an upgrade in investment ratings, and robust quarterly financial results that influenced investor sentiment and price action.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>4763551fea268729082aeed4f4eebe8e</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Integra Essentia Ltd Gains 37.01%: 2 Key Events Driving the Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/integra-essentia-ltd-gains-3701-2-key-events-driving-the-surge-3812895</link><description>Integra Essentia Ltd delivered a remarkable weekly performance, surging 37.01% from Rs.1.27 to Rs.1.74 between 27 and 30 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 1.62% gain over the same period. The stock’s volatile week was marked by a fresh 52-week low followed by a strong rebound culminating in an upper circuit hit, reflecting a complex interplay of market sentiment and company-specific developments.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>8ca653477793984d6ca4399ea55f329a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adcon Capital Services Ltd Falls 1.72%: Death Cross and Downgrade Signal Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adcon-capital-services-ltd-falls-172-death-cross-and-downgrade-signal-weakness-3812890</link><description>Adcon Capital Services Ltd ended the week marginally lower by 1.72%, closing at Rs.0.57 on 30 January 2026, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.62% over the same period. The week was marked by significant bearish technical signals and a downgrade to a Strong Sell rating, reflecting deteriorating fundamentals and weak market sentiment.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>b284ebeb23716458909b986b4ab43363</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Procter &amp; Gamble Hygiene &amp; Health Care Ltd Falls 3.10%: 3 Key Factors Behind the Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/procter-gamble-hygiene-health-care-ltd-falls-310-3-key-factors-behind-the-decline-3812891</link><description>Procter &amp; Gamble Hygiene &amp; Health Care Ltd. (P&amp;G Hygiene) experienced a challenging week ending 30 January 2026, with its stock declining 3.10% from Rs.12,158.40 to Rs.11,781.75, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.62% over the same period. The stock hit fresh 52-week lows on consecutive days amid subdued growth momentum, valuation pressures, and weak market sentiment, despite the broader market’s resilience.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>20737cb96b8a6c24037d715075e41f66</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Paushak Ltd Falls 5.13%: Quarterly Profit Slide and Margin Pressures Weigh</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/paushak-ltd-falls-513-quarterly-profit-slide-and-margin-pressures-weigh-3812893</link><description>Paushak Ltd’s stock declined by 5.13% over the week ending 30 January 2026, closing at Rs.500.05 from Rs.527.10 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted sharply with the Sensex’s 1.62% gain during the same period, reflecting investor concerns following the company’s disappointing quarterly results and mounting margin pressures. The week was marked by a steady slide in share price amid worsening profitability and operational challenges.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>db517e583a7d63669c51445a42ed683b</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trigyn Technologies Gains 0.25%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/trigyn-technologies-gains-025-3-key-factors-driving-the-week-3812892</link><description>Trigyn Technologies Ltd closed the week ending 30 January 2026 with a modest gain of 0.25%, rising from Rs.56.86 to Rs.57.00. This performance, however, lagged behind the broader Sensex, which advanced 1.62% over the same period. The week was marked by significant volatility, including fresh 52-week lows early in the week and a sharp rebound with an upper circuit surge on 29 January, reflecting a complex interplay of market sentiment and company-specific developments.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>b4d45ef6412b64c17c1abd8ac85d0447</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Navneet Education Gains 1.67%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Move</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/navneet-education-gains-167-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-move-3812889</link><description>Navneet Education Ltd closed the week ending 30 January 2026 with a modest gain of 1.67%, slightly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% rise. The stock experienced notable volatility midweek, including a sharp rebound on 28 January and a technical upgrade on 29 January, before settling near Rs.143.30 on Friday. Despite mixed financial signals and cautious technical indicators, the stock demonstrated resilience amid broader market gains.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>6376e9389f6bede560db6a3944213349</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Veljan Denison Ltd Gains 1.69%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/veljan-denison-ltd-gains-169-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-momentum-3812888</link><description>Veljan Denison Ltd closed the week ending 30 January 2026 with a modest gain of 1.69%, slightly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% rise over the same period. The stock exhibited mixed technical signals throughout the week, navigating shifts between mildly bearish and bullish momentum amid sectoral headwinds and valuation reassessments. Key events including a rating upgrade and fluctuating technical indicators influenced price movements, resulting in a cautious but positive weekly performance.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>3236bd19b9e5fea89b62b0f912667a35</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Banganga Paper Industries Ltd Gains 8.22%: Technical Momentum Shift Drives Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/banganga-paper-industries-ltd-gains-822-technical-momentum-shift-drives-weekly-rally-3812887</link><description>Banganga Paper Industries Ltd delivered a volatile yet ultimately positive week, closing at Rs.53.87 on 30 January 2026, up 8.22% from Rs.49.78 the previous Friday. This performance notably outpaced the Sensex’s 1.62% gain over the same period, driven by a sharp 20.00% surge on 28 January amid technical momentum shifts and a cautious upgrade in the stock’s rating. Despite fundamental challenges, the stock’s price action reflected renewed investor interest and a complex interplay of technical signals.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>603841b463ab11343484d0572d12e807</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Olectra Greentech Gains 9.52%: Key Price Swings and Market Dynamics This Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/olectra-greentech-gains-952-key-price-swings-and-market-dynamics-this-week-3812886</link><description>Olectra Greentech Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 9.52% from Rs.989.60 to Rs.1,083.80 between 27 and 30 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% gain over the same period. The week was marked by a sharp rebound following a 52-week low on 27 January and an impressive intraday surge on 28 January, reflecting a volatile but ultimately positive trading environment for the stock.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>0d6c51bae727dbf03224cc2b7a490dd6</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Housing Development &amp; Infrastructure Ltd Falls 4.31%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/housing-development-infrastructure-ltd-falls-431-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3812885</link><description>Housing Development &amp; Infrastructure Ltd (HDIL) experienced a challenging week ending 30 January 2026, with its stock price declining 4.31% from Rs.2.09 to Rs.2.00, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.62% over the same period. The week was marked by a new 52-week low, a brief surge to the upper circuit, and persistent fundamental weaknesses that continue to weigh on investor sentiment.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>d2e0e463f765d9204ae294644660a3b2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indowind Energy Ltd Falls 16.21%: Four Key Factors Driving the Steep Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indowind-energy-ltd-falls-1621-four-key-factors-driving-the-steep-decline-3812883</link><description>Indowind Energy Ltd’s shares declined sharply by 16.21% over the week ending 30 January 2026, closing at Rs.11.94 from Rs.14.25 the previous Friday. This significant fall occurred despite the Sensex gaining 1.62% during the same period, highlighting the stock’s pronounced underperformance amid persistent operational and financial challenges.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>7ccd5d0fd883e93f17d6b4882be1453c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ipca Laboratories Gains 0.42%: Mixed Technical Signals Shape Weekly Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ipca-laboratories-gains-042-mixed-technical-signals-shape-weekly-momentum-3812878</link><description>Ipca Laboratories Ltd closed the week ending 30 January 2026 with a modest gain of 0.42%, rising from Rs.1,463.05 to Rs.1,469.25. This performance trailed the broader Sensex, which advanced 1.62% over the same period, reflecting a week of mixed technical signals and cautious investor sentiment amid fluctuating daily price movements.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>6c7b71869c7c81454f760efeeb7ecffe</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Valor Estate Ltd Gains 4.05%: Key Intraday Moves and Volatility Shape Weekly Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/valor-estate-ltd-gains-405-key-intraday-moves-and-volatility-shape-weekly-performance-3812884</link><description>Valor Estate Ltd’s stock recorded a 4.05% gain over the week ending 30 January 2026, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% rise. The week was marked by significant volatility, with the stock hitting a 52-week low on 27 January before rebounding sharply to an intraday high on 29 January. These contrasting moves reflected mixed investor sentiment amid broader market fluctuations and sector-specific challenges.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>ea63f601d07d0784f7271c4dd571080f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aditya Birla Real Estate Ltd Falls 1.76%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aditya-birla-real-estate-ltd-falls-176-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-decline-3812882</link><description>Aditya Birla Real Estate Ltd’s stock declined by 1.76% over the week ending 30 January 2026, closing at Rs.1,262.55 against a 1.62% gain in the Sensex. The week was marked by fresh 52-week lows, severe quarterly losses, and sustained bearish momentum, reflecting ongoing financial and operational challenges amid a resilient broader market.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>56c7f76982fbfc528be946c2f7ddcd4b</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Madhucon Projects Ltd Gains 8.73%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/madhucon-projects-ltd-gains-873-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3812880</link><description>Madhucon Projects Ltd experienced a turbulent week marked by sharp price swings, ultimately closing with a strong gain of 8.73% from ₹4.81 to ₹5.23, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.62% rise. The stock’s volatility was driven by a mix of heavy selling pressure, a fresh 52-week low, and a sudden surge to the upper circuit, reflecting both investor caution and speculative interest amid ongoing financial challenges.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>d27d6ad3c88c716601de2aaa2e235e46</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Canara Bank’s 2.87% Weekly Decline Amid Mixed Momentum and Derivatives Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/canara-banks-287-weekly-decline-amid-mixed-momentum-and-derivatives-surge-3812879</link><description>Canara Bank’s stock experienced a turbulent week ending 30 January 2026, closing at Rs.147.40, down 2.87% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.151.75. This decline contrasted with the Sensex’s 1.62% gain over the same period, reflecting a week of mixed technical signals, heightened derivatives market activity, and fluctuating investor sentiment. Despite hitting a new 52-week high midweek, the stock faced profit-taking and short-term selling pressure, underscoring a cautious outlook amid strong long-term fundamentals.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>8ce2f161bed12287438047a995bd3dc5</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DCW Ltd’s Volatile Week: -0.58% Despite 7.1% Intraday Surge and 52-Week Low</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dcw-ltds-volatile-week--058-despite-71-intraday-surge-and-52-week-low-3812876</link><description>DCW Ltd’s stock experienced a turbulent week ending 30 January 2026, closing marginally lower by 0.58% at Rs.45.95 despite a sharp intraday rally of 7.1% on 28 January. The stock underperformed the Sensex, which gained 1.62% over the same period, reflecting ongoing volatility amid mixed market signals and sectoral pressures.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>4463e26030180602e5c968049cc50efc</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:23:29 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>