<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:52:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Rategain Travel Technologies Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.87% Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rategain-travel-technologies-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-787-surge-3844499</link><description>Rategain Travel Technologies Ltd demonstrated a robust intraday performance on 17 Feb 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 582.5, marking a significant 7.97% increase. This surge outpaced the broader IT - Software sector and the Sensex, reflecting a notable rebound after a five-day decline.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>73db88293439ca4a73899ad6ddc4fcb2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>VST Tillers Tractors Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.05% Surge on 17 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vst-tillers-tractors-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-705-surge-on-17-feb-2026-3844500</link><description>VST Tillers Tractors Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 17 Feb 2026, surging 7.05% to touch a day’s high of Rs 6,036.1. This marked a significant rebound following two consecutive days of decline, with the stock outperforming its sector and the broader market indices.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>5a2405bb38fe09a0e0944c462003beb4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Max Financial Services Ltd Hits New 52-Week High of Rs.1858.5</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/max-financial-services-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-of-rs18585-3844497</link><description>Max Financial Services Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs.1858.5 today, marking a continuation of its strong upward momentum in the insurance sector.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>45bf6e9f2cde16853bedf6c15dc1c487</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chennai Ferrous Industries Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/chennai-ferrous-industries-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3844498</link><description>Chennai Ferrous Industries Ltd has reached a new 52-week low, reflecting ongoing challenges in its financial performance and market positioning. The stock’s recent decline to this significant price level underscores persistent pressures within the non-ferrous metals sector and the company’s relative underperformance against broader market indices.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>dc60d3911969150c238227ace0dbe4ec</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Union Bank of India Hits Intraday High with 3.36% Surge on 17 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/union-bank-of-india-hits-intraday-high-with-336-surge-on-17-feb-2026-3844494</link><description>Union Bank of India demonstrated robust intraday performance on 17 Feb 2026, surging to a new 52-week high of Rs.189.65, marking a 3.36% gain on the day and outperforming its sector peers and the broader market.
Time: 20 minutes ago</description><guid>0b1f086e4b00ce376e8087dd76868b2a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank Of Baroda Hits Intraday High with 3.78% Surge on 17 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bank-of-baroda-hits-intraday-high-with-378-surge-on-17-feb-2026-3844493</link><description>Bank Of Baroda demonstrated robust intraday strength on 17 Feb 2026, surging 3.78% to touch a high of ₹303, marking a notable outperformance against its sector and the broader market.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>9b0907d790a703cd1b5c6431998d1ecf</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Genesys International Corporation Ltd Hits Intraday High with 11.8% Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/genesys-international-corporation-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-118-surge-3844492</link><description>Genesys International Corporation Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 17 Feb 2026, surging 11.8% to touch a day’s high of ₹322, significantly outperforming its sector and the broader market.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>404beab6d6d274282637d1c8c8908a68</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shrenik Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shrenik-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3844489</link><description>Shrenik Ltd, a micro-cap player in the miscellaneous sector, witnessed a robust rally on 17 Feb 2026, hitting its upper circuit limit with a 2.27% gain. The stock’s surge was driven by intense buying interest, resulting in a freeze on further trading and highlighting unfulfilled demand among investors.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>73843ba7d389058ae5edde04404a2256</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manaksia Aluminium Company Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/manaksia-aluminium-company-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3844491</link><description>Manaksia Aluminium Company Ltd (Stock ID: 740084) surged to its upper circuit limit on 17 Feb 2026, closing at ₹29.98, marking a maximum daily gain of 4.97%. This sharp rally was driven by robust buying interest despite an initial gap down opening, signalling renewed investor confidence in the non-ferrous metals micro-cap stock.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>adc014fce0be670812d580a4eef2ba0f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>One 97 Communications Ltd Sees Robust Value Trading Amid Sector Outperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/one-97-communications-ltd-sees-robust-value-trading-amid-sector-outperformance-3844490</link><description>One 97 Communications Ltd, the parent company of Paytm, emerged as one of the most actively traded stocks by value on 17 Feb 2026, reflecting renewed investor interest and a notable reversal in its recent downtrend. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, buoyed by strong institutional participation and significant order flow, signalling potential shifts in market sentiment towards this fintech heavyweight.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>2b1a3e0997ce12920d38baf0bb19aaa1</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sikko Industries Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sikko-industries-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3844488</link><description>Sikko Industries Ltd, a micro-cap player in the fertilisers sector, witnessed a sharp decline on 17 Feb 2026, hitting its lower circuit limit of ₹5.07, marking a maximum daily loss of 4.88%. The stock underperformed its sector and the broader market amid intense selling pressure and panic-driven trading activity.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>dde3dd886f0c0f31624b19354e660cbc</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jaiprakash Associates Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit on Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jaiprakash-associates-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-on-robust-buying-pressure-3844487</link><description>Shares of Jaiprakash Associates Ltd surged to hit the upper circuit limit on 17 Feb 2026, registering a maximum daily gain of 4.97% to close at ₹3.38. This sharp rally was driven by robust buying interest, despite the company’s ongoing challenges and a recent downgrade to a Strong Sell rating by MarketsMOJO. The stock outperformed its sector and the broader market, signalling renewed investor attention in the micro-cap construction firm.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>3656aa9882666a77ce4462909a9c3efb</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KFin Technologies Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Rising Market Activity</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kfin-technologies-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-rising-market-activity-3844485</link><description>KFin Technologies Ltd (KFINTECH) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market participation and evolving investor positioning. The stock’s recent outperformance relative to its sector and a notable increase in delivery volumes underscore a developing narrative of renewed investor interest and potential directional bets.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>f3078ad632c76378e40be3ca30ca3eac</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Premier Ltd Shares Plunge to Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/premier-ltd-shares-plunge-to-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3844479</link><description>Shares of Premier Ltd, a micro-cap player in the industrial manufacturing sector, plunged to their lower circuit limit on 17 Feb 2026, reflecting intense selling pressure and panic among investors. The stock closed at ₹3.04, down 1.3% on the day, marking its maximum permissible daily loss and signalling unfilled supply overwhelming demand.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>67bef5ab945dcf6c040798f00cbb2251</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Newgen Software Technologies Ltd Sees Surge in Value Trading Amid Sector Outperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/newgen-software-technologies-ltd-sees-surge-in-value-trading-amid-sector-outperformance-3844486</link><description>Newgen Software Technologies Ltd witnessed a remarkable spike in trading activity on 17 Feb 2026, emerging as one of the most actively traded stocks by value in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector. The stock surged 12.04% intraday, outperforming its sector by 7.8%, driven by robust institutional interest and significant order flow despite trading below key moving averages.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>d42fb8e728c386e039464792f431c6d6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3844476</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has revealed a nuanced picture of corporate performance across Indian markets, with 4,073 companies reporting results. While the overall proportion of positive earnings has inched up to 46.0%, the distribution across market capitalisation segments and sectors highlights varied momentum and emerging trends.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>b14b7d06291b3719d4e79b708e557617</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Norben Tea &amp; Exports Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit on Robust Buying Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/norben-tea-exports-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-on-robust-buying-momentum-3844484</link><description>Norben Tea &amp; Exports Ltd (NSE: BE) surged to its upper circuit limit on 17 Feb 2026, closing at ₹84.80, marking a maximum daily gain of 4.99%. The stock’s sharp rally was driven by strong buying interest, with volumes and delivery percentages signalling heightened investor participation despite a micro-cap market cap of ₹130 crores. This performance notably outpaced the FMCG sector and broader market indices, underscoring renewed optimism in the company’s near-term prospects.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>87e0ef0a59ef9767eef510aa1919302f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Davangere Sugar Company Ltd Sees Exceptional Volume Surge Amid Mixed Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/davangere-sugar-company-ltd-sees-exceptional-volume-surge-amid-mixed-technical-signals-3844482</link><description>Davangere Sugar Company Ltd (DAVANGERE) emerged as one of the most actively traded stocks on 17 Feb 2026, registering a remarkable surge in volume and price movement. Despite a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade to 'Sell', the stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, signalling a complex interplay of investor sentiment and technical factors.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>b9444c9abe301d2592456f3225e8047d</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eastern Silk Industries Ltd Plunges to Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eastern-silk-industries-ltd-plunges-to-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3844480</link><description>Eastern Silk Industries Ltd witnessed a sharp decline on 17 Feb 2026, hitting its lower circuit limit of 5% and closing at ₹57.46. The stock faced intense selling pressure, marking its fourth consecutive day of losses and continuing a prolonged downtrend that has wiped out nearly 18% of its value in just four sessions.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>12a700ad82622307699f714257e6d6d7</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Union Bank of India Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Signalling Strong Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/union-bank-of-india-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-signalling-strong-market-positioning-3844478</link><description>Union Bank of India has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, reflecting a notable shift in market sentiment and positioning. The bank’s stock has recently hit a new 52-week high of Rs 189.6, supported by robust volume and positive price momentum, suggesting that investors are increasingly optimistic about its near-term prospects.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>680c2c95d9874d6f7cb34a54f9735af8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:52:56 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>