<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:46:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Coral India Finance &amp; Housing Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/coral-india-finance-housing-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3824428</link><description>Shares of Coral India Finance &amp; Housing Ltd have declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing near Rs 33.91, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory. This new low reflects persistent pressures on the company’s financial performance and market valuation amid a challenging environment for the diversified commercial services sector.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>9cb366ba4601dcae09f7f008d7156eb9</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:46:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Technologies Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-technologies-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-price-action-3824429</link><description>Tata Technologies Ltd (TATATECH) has witnessed a notable 10.23% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s recent underperformance. This increase in open interest, coupled with falling prices and volume patterns, suggests a shift in market positioning and potential directional bets by traders.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>5344916303a9a3997eab4d5dbb57ca16</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:46:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Life Insurance Corporation of India Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/life-insurance-corporation-of-india-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-momentum-3824425</link><description>Life Insurance Corporation of India (LICI) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling a notable shift in market positioning. The stock outperformed its sector and broader indices, buoyed by increased volumes and a strong price rally, prompting a reassessment of its near-term outlook despite a recent downgrade in its Mojo Grade to Sell.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>7777d107c7beb482273b0ceb45f3e030</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:46:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FSN E-Commerce Ventures Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Price Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/fsn-e-commerce-ventures-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-price-momentum-3824426</link><description>FSN E-Commerce Ventures Ltd, the parent company of NYKAA, has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. The stock has simultaneously hit a new 52-week high of Rs 273.3, reflecting strong bullish sentiment amid robust volume and price action.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>507058d3f89627976c3bc82dcebd21bb</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:46:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hitachi Energy India Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Strong Market Outperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hitachi-energy-india-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-market-outperformance-3824427</link><description>Hitachi Energy India Ltd (POWERINDIA) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and potential directional bets. The stock outperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting strong investor confidence amid a robust price rally and shifting market positioning.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>4897694fbafcb27fe83cac38e411a756</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:46:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tube Investments of India Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Downward Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tube-investments-of-india-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-downward-price-pressure-3824424</link><description>Tube Investments of India Ltd (TIINDIA) has witnessed a notable 10.2% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s recent underperformance. This surge in open interest, coupled with rising volumes and bearish price trends, suggests a complex positioning shift among traders, with implications for near-term directional bets.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>960669da9a2663fdb5a0f0cb812e5c6c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:46:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Elxsi Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-elxsi-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-momentum-3824422</link><description>Tata Elxsi Ltd., a mid-cap player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has witnessed a notable 14.8% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, even as the stock underperformed its sector and broader indices. This divergence between rising open interest and declining price action signals shifting market positioning and potential directional bets among traders.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>c16a720ae1d700a1755a72895915e311</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:46:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Panache Digilife Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/panache-digilife-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3824421</link><description>Shares of Panache Digilife Ltd, a micro-cap player in the IT - Hardware sector, plunged to their lower circuit limit on 6 February 2026, closing at ₹328.50, down 4.06% on the day. The stock underperformed its sector and the broader market, reflecting intense selling pressure and a sharp decline in investor participation.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>aac65081d0c34039a352e26e972d6023</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:46:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Orchasp Ltd Shares Plunge to Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/orchasp-ltd-shares-plunge-to-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3824420</link><description>Orchasp Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, witnessed a sharp decline on 6 Feb 2026, hitting its lower circuit limit amid intense selling pressure. The stock closed at a new 52-week and all-time low of ₹2.07, marking a maximum daily loss of 8.42%, as panic selling gripped investors and supply remained largely unfilled.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>7980f0632ea88a03809e1fa6080a3cb8</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:46:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uno Minda Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amidst Weak Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/uno-minda-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amidst-weak-price-action-3824423</link><description>Uno Minda Ltd, a key player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, witnessed a notable 13.4% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment on 6 February 2026, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. This increase comes amid a broader market environment marked by volatility and sector underperformance, prompting investors to reassess directional bets on the mid-cap stock.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>d8d030c47528bec01a6a4efd1fe3c250</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:46:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arshiya Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/arshiya-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3824415</link><description>Shares of Arshiya Ltd surged to their upper circuit limit on 6 February 2026, propelled by robust buying interest and a maximum daily gain of 3.2%. The stock closed at ₹1.29, marking a significant outperformance against its sector and the broader market, despite a backdrop of falling investor participation and regulatory trading restrictions.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>049944a4513c2162b06e4b69cc7bcf43</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:46:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HDFC Bank Sees Heavy Put Option Activity Amid Bearish Sentiment</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hdfc-bank-sees-heavy-put-option-activity-amid-bearish-sentiment-3824417</link><description>HDFC Bank Ltd., one of India’s leading private sector banks, has witnessed a notable increase in put option trading activity, signalling growing bearish sentiment among investors. The surge in put contracts, particularly at the ₹950 strike price expiring on 24 February 2026, reflects cautious positioning and potential hedging strategies amid recent price underperformance and sector headwinds.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>1ec8c5c18cd80a984c72507c96d20f0b</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:46:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Godfrey Phillips India Ltd. Sees Surge in Value Trading Amid Mixed Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/godfrey-phillips-india-ltd-sees-surge-in-value-trading-amid-mixed-technical-signals-3824419</link><description>Godfrey Phillips India Ltd. (GODFRYPHLP) emerged as one of the most actively traded stocks by value on 6 February 2026, registering a remarkable 11.75% gain intraday. Despite a downgrade in its Mojo Grade from Hold to Sell at the end of December 2025, the stock demonstrated robust price action, outperforming its sector and broader market indices amid a volatile trading session.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>d0c32420fbe2b57fc602d44f9ae3a859</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:46:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oracle Financial Services Software Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/oracle-financial-services-software-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-momentum-3824416</link><description>Oracle Financial Services Software Ltd (OFSS) has witnessed a notable 10.38% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s recent underperformance. This surge in open interest, coupled with declining prices and volume patterns, suggests a complex interplay of bearish positioning and speculative bets among traders.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>6488f8f93dc5066ccdfd7a88a2292d05</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:46:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Davangere Sugar Company Ltd Sees Exceptional Volume Surge Amid Mixed Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/davangere-sugar-company-ltd-sees-exceptional-volume-surge-amid-mixed-technical-signals-3824414</link><description>Davangere Sugar Company Ltd (symbol: DAVANGERE) emerged as one of the most actively traded stocks on 6 February 2026, registering a remarkable volume surge with over 2.13 crore shares exchanging hands by mid-morning. Despite a modest price gain of 0.24%, the stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, signalling renewed investor interest amid a complex technical backdrop and a recent upgrade in its Mojo Grade from Strong Sell to Sell.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>590dc804bc511475c57482b9d1795582</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:46:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AXISCADES Technologies Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/axiscades-technologies-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3824411</link><description>Shares of AXISCADES Technologies Ltd plunged to their lower circuit limit on 6 Feb 2026, closing at ₹1,121.7, marking a maximum daily loss of 5.0%. The stock faced intense selling pressure, with volumes skewed towards the day’s low, signalling panic selling and unfilled supply in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>e0afe548c23a928f5baf152a0af723c0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:46:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tijaria Polypipes Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit on Robust Buying Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tijaria-polypipes-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-on-robust-buying-momentum-3824406</link><description>Tijaria Polypipes Ltd witnessed a robust surge in its share price on 6 Feb 2026, hitting the upper circuit limit of 8.37% to close at ₹6.73. This sharp rally was driven by intense buying interest, with the stock outperforming its sector and broader market indices despite its micro-cap status and a recent downgrade to a Strong Sell rating by MarketsMOJO.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>9c73fa7808e93913f9fc6da493da32c0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:46:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3824404</link><description>The December 2025 quarterly earnings season has unfolded with a nuanced picture across market capitalisation segments, revealing a modest improvement in positive results and a notable surge in mid-cap profitability. With 1,471 companies reporting, the quarter saw 47.0% of results beating expectations, marking a steady rise from the 42.0% recorded in September 2025 and the 40.0% in June 2025, signalling cautious optimism among investors.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>a3d883201aece994118dfbeb2e76ba79</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:46:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ITC Ltd Sees Surge in Call Option Activity Ahead of February Expiry</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/itc-ltd-sees-surge-in-call-option-activity-ahead-of-february-expiry-3824418</link><description>ITC Ltd., a stalwart in the FMCG sector, has witnessed a notable spike in call option trading, signalling increased bullish positioning among investors ahead of the 24 February 2026 expiry. The surge in activity, particularly at strike prices near the current market value, reflects growing optimism despite the stock’s recent underperformance relative to its sector peers.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>bed93e1fe5efdba232c1d5af97d65687</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:46:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tera Software Ltd Hits Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tera-software-ltd-hits-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3824409</link><description>Tera Software Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, surged to hit its upper circuit limit on 6 February 2026, closing at ₹427.55 with a maximum daily gain of 5.0%. This sharp rally was driven by robust buying interest, resulting in a regulatory freeze on further trading and signalling strong investor confidence despite recent volatility.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>0105a5deb5749090398b61e18ddf63cb</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:46:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:46:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>