<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:07:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Arfin India Ltd Stock Hits All-Time High Amid Strong Market Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/arfin-india-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-amid-strong-market-performance-3777230</link><description>Arfin India Ltd, a key player in the Non - Ferrous Metals sector, has surged to a new all-time high of Rs.74.78, reflecting a significant achievement in its market journey. This milestone underscores the company’s robust performance and sustained upward momentum over recent periods.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>de2a08a02a2d38e95f3e590a85ea5bdb</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trade-Wings Ltd Stock Hits Record High of Rs.443.9 on 1 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/trade-wings-ltd-stock-hits-record-high-of-rs4439-on-1-jan-2026-3777229</link><description>Trade-Wings Ltd has reached an all-time high of Rs.443.9 today, reflecting a remarkable surge in its stock price and underscoring the company’s strong performance over recent months. This milestone marks a significant achievement in the company’s market journey, with the stock demonstrating sustained upward momentum and outperforming key benchmarks.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>781607e7f6f9b4bb3f14b3fed5cbf358</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Synthiko Foils Ltd Stock Hits All-Time High at Rs.1770.3</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/synthiko-foils-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-at-rs17703-3777232</link><description>Synthiko Foils Ltd has reached an all-time high price of Rs.1770.3 today, underscoring a remarkable ascent in its market valuation and reflecting sustained strong performance across multiple timeframes.
Time: 5 minutes ago</description><guid>8878f4d3da7901af3a00bc52b2551621</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>APL Apollo Tubes Ltd Hits All-Time High, Marking a Milestone in Market Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/apl-apollo-tubes-ltd-hits-all-time-high-marking-a-milestone-in-market-performance-3777234</link><description>APL Apollo Tubes Ltd has reached a new all-time high, underscoring its robust performance and sustained growth in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector. The stock’s recent surge reflects a combination of strong fundamentals, consistent earnings growth, and market outperformance, setting a significant milestone for the company and its investors.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>8bf0c7e134ced8837482c3a59e1c9c40</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahamaya Steel Industries Ltd Hits All-Time High at Rs.1033.05</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mahamaya-steel-industries-ltd-hits-all-time-high-at-rs103305-3777231</link><description>Mahamaya Steel Industries Ltd has reached an all-time high of Rs.1033.05 today, underscoring a remarkable phase of growth and resilience in the iron and steel products sector. This milestone reflects the company’s sustained upward momentum, outperforming both its sector and the broader market indices over multiple time horizons.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>2ddc7c8df6d30d5e0a2cf8067da45468</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Titan Company Ltd Hits All-Time High at Rs.4064.4 Mark</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/titan-company-ltd-hits-all-time-high-at-rs40644-mark-3777236</link><description>Titan Company Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting a new all-time high of Rs.4064.4, underscoring its robust performance in the Gems, Jewellery and Watches sector. This achievement reflects the company’s sustained growth trajectory and strong fundamentals amid a competitive market environment.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>79bbd661f6faebaedf0d7e3db4c3e3d6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spice Islands Industries Ltd Stock Hits Record High of Rs.198.55</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/spice-islands-industries-ltd-stock-hits-record-high-of-rs19855-3777237</link><description>Spice Islands Industries Ltd, a key player in the Gems, Jewellery and Watches sector, reached an all-time high of Rs.198.55 today, reflecting a remarkable surge in its stock price and underscoring its strong market performance over recent months.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>4e018b6f9172180164328600d24dc28c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pankaj Polymers Ltd Stock Hits All-Time High at Rs.42.25</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pankaj-polymers-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-at-rs4225-3777235</link><description>Pankaj Polymers Ltd, a key player in the packaging sector, achieved a significant milestone today by reaching a new all-time high of Rs.42.25. This peak reflects the company’s robust performance over recent months, with the stock demonstrating remarkable gains and consistently outperforming both its sector and the broader market indices.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>588a481f06b607988f98264552595345</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd Hits All-Time High at Rs.386.8</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-petroleum-corporation-ltd-hits-all-time-high-at-rs3868-3777233</link><description>Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd (BPCL) has reached a significant milestone by hitting a new all-time high of Rs.386.8, reflecting its robust performance and sustained growth in the oil sector. This achievement underscores the company’s strong fundamentals and consistent upward trajectory over recent periods.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>f39cb5db0f1401190386f4087b9ffa2b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sensex Edges Higher as Small Caps Lead; ITC Drags Amid Mixed Sector Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-edges-higher-as-small-caps-lead-itc-drags-amid-mixed-sector-performance-3777227</link><description>The Indian equity market closed marginally higher on 1 January 2026, with the Sensex gaining 82.68 points, or 0.10%, to settle at 85,303.28. Market breadth remained positive as 262 stocks advanced against 234 decliners on the BSE500, reflecting cautious optimism among investors amid mixed sectoral performances and subdued midcap activity.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>6b4f07ed2b4ac8ebde789ec608dd7fea</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Motisons Jewellers Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/motisons-jewellers-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3777225</link><description>Motisons Jewellers Ltd, a player in the Gems, Jewellery and Watches sector, has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.14.51 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend over recent sessions. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing concerns about its performance and valuation.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>fc3934b3b633f27aefb4d78a21bf7d30</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamdhenu Ventures Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.5.95</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kamdhenu-ventures-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs595-3777224</link><description>Kamdhenu Ventures Ltd, a player in the paints sector, has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.5.95 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid ongoing downward momentum. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting persistent challenges in its financial performance and investor participation.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>d38b792f14ba7b6cf52a765323c5ae18</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dharan Infra-EPC Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.0.23</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dharan-infra-epc-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs023-3777222</link><description>Dharan Infra-EPC Ltd, a player in the Realty sector, has touched a new 52-week and all-time low of Rs.0.23 today, marking a significant downturn in its stock performance amid a broader market that remains resilient.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>0817e5f17630e5881d53226d9b2e53e1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vantage Knowledge Academy Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.1.04</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vantage-knowledge-academy-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs104-3777221</link><description>Vantage Knowledge Academy Ltd, a player in the Other Consumer Services sector, has reached a new 52-week and all-time low of Rs.1.04, marking a significant decline amid a broader market that remains relatively stable. The stock’s recent performance contrasts sharply with the positive trends seen in the Sensex and small-cap indices.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>bdeeb5ba05bf8a3fa9415747b287d35b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TeleCanor Global Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.44.64</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/telecanor-global-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs4464-3777223</link><description>TeleCanor Global Ltd, a prominent player in the Software Products sector, reached a significant milestone today by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.44.64. This achievement marks a continuation of the stock’s robust upward momentum, reflecting sustained gains over the past several weeks.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>4e0d966ac6e43c00aa6ccf303ec9ebc5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ISL Consulting Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.34.39</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/isl-consulting-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs3439-3777220</link><description>ISL Consulting Ltd, a player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, reached a significant milestone today by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.34.39. This achievement underscores the stock’s recent momentum, driven by robust gains and favourable trading dynamics within the sector.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>d99212535bcf2823a03178866969cb99</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TVS Motor Company Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.3752</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tvs-motor-company-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs3752-3777218</link><description>TVS Motor Company Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs.3752, reflecting strong momentum in the automobile sector and sustained performance over the past year.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>2ff33ef5fd9d357a395ce9c9669b5766</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eternal Ltd Faces Challenges Despite Nifty 50 Membership and Large Cap Status</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eternal-ltd-faces-challenges-despite-nifty-50-membership-and-large-cap-status-3777202</link><description>Eternal Ltd, a prominent player in the E-Retail and E-Commerce sector, continues to navigate a challenging market environment despite its prestigious inclusion in the Nifty 50 index. Recent institutional holding changes and a downgrade in its Mojo Grade to Sell have added complexity to the stock’s outlook, even as it remains a large-cap heavyweight with a market capitalisation exceeding ₹2.68 lakh crores.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>c2b05a930d211d094221fee6470d01b5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Max Healthcare Institute Ltd Faces Sell Grade Amidst Nifty 50 Membership Significance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/max-healthcare-institute-ltd-faces-sell-grade-amidst-nifty-50-membership-significance-3777201</link><description>Max Healthcare Institute Ltd, a prominent hospital sector player and constituent of the Nifty 50 index, has experienced a mixed performance trajectory amid evolving market dynamics. Despite its large-cap status and benchmark inclusion, the stock’s recent financial metrics and institutional holding trends suggest caution for investors navigating the healthcare space.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>08e697371218307f8c1a9b2777d2918a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Integrated Industries Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.35</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/integrated-industries-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs35-3777219</link><description>Integrated Industries Ltd, a key player in the FMCG sector, reached a significant milestone today by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.35. This achievement underscores the stock’s robust momentum, driven by consistent financial performance and favourable market conditions.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>c69f545f269ddc07f9057f17bfafb916</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:07:29 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>