<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:15:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Royal Arc Electrodes Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-royal-arc-electrodes-ltd-fallingrising-3776864</link><description>On 31 Dec, Royal Arc Electrodes Ltd witnessed a significant price appreciation of 6.16%, closing at ₹169.85, driven by robust trading volumes and positive technical indicators that outpaced both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 51 minutes ago</description><guid>ff8b834ce0c89c790f770f69a38427e6</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ventive Hospitality Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ventive-hospitality-ltd-fallingrising-3776863</link><description>As of 31 Dec, Ventive Hospitality Ltd's stock price has risen by 1.78% to ₹753.00, reflecting investor optimism driven by robust sales growth and encouraging quarterly earnings, despite some valuation concerns and reduced institutional participation.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>1eac3674267d5e09309ec290cf82679d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Property Share Investment Trust- Propshare Platina falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-property-share-investment-trust--propshare-platina-fallingrising-3776862</link><description>On 31 Dec, Property Share Investment Trust- Propshare Platina witnessed a notable price increase of 2.24%, closing at ₹10,48,000, reflecting a robust performance that outpaced both its sector and key market benchmarks.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>fc2fdf1b51022358d41e109079963029</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sanstar Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sanstar-ltd-fallingrising-3776861</link><description>On 31-Dec, Sanstar Ltd’s stock price rose sharply by 5.84% to close at ₹98.48, marking a notable rebound after a period of underperformance. This surge comes despite the company’s ongoing challenges with profitability and long-term growth, highlighting a complex interplay between market sentiment and fundamental factors.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>ded1e510904462f0168cefaf8b970e9c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Entero Healthcare Solutions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-entero-healthcare-solutions-ltd-fallingrising-3776860</link><description>On 31-Dec, Entero Healthcare Solutions Ltd saw its share price rise by 1.4% to ₹1,019.90, continuing a short-term upward trend despite a challenging year marked by significant underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>5f0cae94d629bd79a292c567aaca0fa0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shanti Spintex Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shanti-spintex-ltd-fallingrising-3776859</link><description>On 31 Dec, Shanti Spintex Ltd’s stock price fell by 3.17% to close at ₹58.10, continuing a trend of underperformance relative to the broader market and its sector peers.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>67801e6a984c4f4c0e0351641aca0091</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Flair Writing Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-flair-writing-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3776858</link><description>As of 31 Dec, Flair Writing Industries Ltd’s stock price has risen by 2.9% to ₹314.50, reflecting a sustained upward momentum driven by robust quarterly earnings and growing institutional participation.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>8f74ec6d53ee8d9d515dd6a32e557ddb</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Fedbank Financial Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-fedbank-financial-services-ltd-fallingrising-3776857</link><description>On 31 Dec, Fedbank Financial Services Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 4.79% to close at ₹151.00. This upward movement reflects a combination of strong long-term fundamentals, recent positive quarterly results, and market-beating returns that have outpaced broader indices and sector peers.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>6060bc9e1cfa1b277c8fd107226d73d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sangani Hospitals Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sangani-hospitals-ltd-fallingrising-3776856</link><description>On 31 Dec, Sangani Hospitals Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling 5.0% to ₹54.15 by 09:14 PM, reflecting a broader trend of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and technical indicators.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>72778b0c5cf8e4f0d854a7ecdce09c17</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Yasons Chemex Care Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-yasons-chemex-care-ltd-fallingrising-3776855</link><description>On 31 Dec, Yasons Chemex Care Ltd witnessed a notable uptick in its share price, rising by 1.91% to close at ₹13.35. This movement reflects a combination of strong technical indicators and heightened investor participation, despite the stock's challenging year-to-date performance.
Time: 52 minutes ago</description><guid>667b18b09a9c4893ae9734043a98dc64</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Metro Brands Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-metro-brands-ltd-fallingrising-3776854</link><description>On 31 Dec, Metro Brands Ltd saw its share price rise by 1.42% to ₹1,199.70, continuing a three-day gaining streak that has delivered a 4.75% return over this short period, despite the company’s longer-term challenges and recent profit declines.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>dcfced9c686060e9396b5170a4f91c91</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Mihika Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-mihika-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3776853</link><description>As of 31 Dec, Mihika Industries Ltd’s stock price has fallen sharply, reflecting persistent operational challenges and sustained underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>09e7caf4e008af46c0dcaa033eb241f4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Upsurge Seeds of Agriculture Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-upsurge-seeds-of-agriculture-ltd-fallingrising-3776852</link><description>On 31 Dec, Upsurge Seeds of Agriculture Ltd witnessed a notable intraday price increase of 4.61%, closing at ₹159.00. This rise comes despite the stock's underperformance over longer time horizons and reflects a complex interplay of short-term market dynamics and technical factors.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>52710a1351ccfb755616cc631d12fdd8</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Rajnandini Metal Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-rajnandini-metal-ltd-fallingrising-3776851</link><description>As of 31-Dec, Rajnandini Metal Ltd’s stock price rose by 6.5% to ₹4.75, marking a notable short-term rally despite persistent long-term fundamental weaknesses and underperformance against market benchmarks.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>ebb3fbef87e6fe8e8de8c227987f4607</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-orissa-bengal-carrier-ltd-fallingrising-3776850</link><description>As of 31-Dec, Orissa Bengal Carrier Ltd’s stock price has fallen sharply by 9.4% to ₹53.00, reflecting ongoing challenges in the company’s financial performance and market sentiment.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>1e6f7c568a16e266dddf7e8994a3fd3b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shree Tirupati Balajee FIBC Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shree-tirupati-balajee-fibc-ltd-fallingrising-3776849</link><description>On 31 Dec, Shree Tirupati Balajee FIBC Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 4.9% to close at ₹680.00. This drop reflects a broader trend of underperformance relative to both its sector and benchmark indices over recent periods.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>9d7d35aee691f4dd04839909a61d1274</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Rander Corporation Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-rander-corporation-ltd-fallingrising-3776848</link><description>On 31 Dec, Rander Corporation Ltd’s stock price fell by 1.92% to close at ₹11.22, continuing a downward trend driven by weak financial performance and persistent underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>ba58d8fe24785529a7c283373d1078be</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ascom Leasing &amp; Investments Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ascom-leasing-investments-ltd-fallingrising-3776847</link><description>On 31 Dec, Ascom Leasing &amp; Investments Ltd witnessed a notable uptick in its share price, closing at ₹126.50, marking a 1.93% increase and setting a new 52-week high. This rise reflects a strong short-term momentum despite the stock's subdued performance over the past year.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>6c881856f9f5a179455bde3eb5039964</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Swojas Foods Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-swojas-foods-ltd-fallingrising-3776846</link><description>On 31 Dec, Swojas Foods Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹10.04, down by ₹0.21 or 2.05%. This drop reflects a continuation of recent negative momentum, with the stock hitting a fresh 52-week low and underperforming its sector peers.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>faf27a0d27f013f1330e145f5df672fe</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is AAA Technologies Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-aaa-technologies-ltd-fallingrising-3776845</link><description>On 31 Dec, AAA Technologies Ltd witnessed a notable 5.0% rise in its share price, closing at ₹104.19. This upward movement reflects a continuation of recent positive momentum, with the stock outperforming its sector and broader market benchmarks in the short term.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>f1c92c5437ff27d0acf65c5b48afeee2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 21:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>