<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Sensex and Nifty Slip Nearly 1% Amid Broad-Based Sector Declines</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-and-nifty-slip-nearly-1-amid-broad-based-sector-declines-3804467</link><description>Indian equity benchmarks Sensex and Nifty closed sharply lower on 26 Jan 2026, dragged down by widespread selling across sectors and heavy losses in select large caps. The market breadth was weak with all 38 sectors declining, led by utilities and energy stocks, while foreign institutional investors remained net sellers amid cautious global cues.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>220afd09026bb9841aa9046aaf159509</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharti Hexacom Ltd Downgraded to Sell Amid Mixed Financials and Bearish Technicals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/bharti-hexacom-ltd-downgraded-to-sell-amid-mixed-financials-and-bearish-technicals-3804455</link><description>Bharti Hexacom Ltd, a prominent player in the telecom services sector, has seen its investment rating downgraded from Hold to Sell as of 23 January 2026. This shift is primarily driven by a deterioration in technical indicators, despite the company’s robust financial performance and healthy long-term growth prospects. The downgrade reflects a nuanced assessment across four key parameters: Quality, Valuation, Financial Trend, and Technicals.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>38989ea391d93a8033b95574dcf43d43</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nuvama Wealth Management Downgraded to Sell Amid Technical and Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/nuvama-wealth-management-downgraded-to-sell-amid-technical-and-valuation-concerns-3804457</link><description>Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd has seen its investment rating downgraded from Hold to Sell as of 23 January 2026, reflecting a combination of deteriorating technical indicators, expensive valuation metrics, and flat recent financial performance. Despite strong long-term fundamentals and market-beating returns over the past year, the stock faces headwinds from subdued quarterly earnings, high promoter share pledging, and a shift in technical momentum that have collectively pressured investor sentiment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>39f729f80c91984e1a542bf5a47792d5</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SBFC Finance Ltd Downgraded to Sell Amid Bearish Technicals Despite Strong Fundamentals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sbfc-finance-ltd-downgraded-to-sell-amid-bearish-technicals-despite-strong-fundamentals-3804454</link><description>SBFC Finance Ltd has seen its investment rating downgraded from Hold to Sell as of 24 Jan 2026, primarily driven by deteriorating technical indicators despite robust financial performance and fair valuation metrics. The downgrade reflects a cautious stance amid bearish technical trends, even as the company continues to demonstrate strong long-term growth and healthy fundamentals.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>332f0abc8b47b1a3077bc41bb92d0181</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rategain Travel Technologies Downgraded to Sell Amid Technical Weakness and Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/rategain-travel-technologies-downgraded-to-sell-amid-technical-weakness-and-valuation-concerns-3804458</link><description>Rategain Travel Technologies Ltd has seen its investment rating downgraded from Hold to Sell, reflecting a combination of deteriorating technical indicators, flat financial performance, and valuation pressures. Despite healthy long-term growth metrics, the company’s recent quarterly results and underperformance relative to the broader market have prompted a reassessment of its investment appeal.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c5378c8cdb8fba028187bc91c7bc96d4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ujjivan Small Finance Bank Upgraded to Buy on Strong Fundamentals and Improved Financial Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ujjivan-small-finance-bank-upgraded-to-buy-on-strong-fundamentals-and-improved-financial-trend-3804459</link><description>Ujjivan Small Finance Bank Ltd has seen its investment rating upgraded from Hold to Buy, reflecting significant improvements across key parameters including quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. The upgrade, announced on 23 January 2026, follows a period of flat financial performance in Q3 FY25-26 but is underpinned by robust long-term fundamentals and market-beating returns.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ef574cd7c1a237cf447a3b01bfb2da54</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sona BLW Precision Forgings Downgraded to Sell Amid Mixed Financial and Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sona-blw-precision-forgings-downgraded-to-sell-amid-mixed-financial-and-technical-signals-3804456</link><description>Sona BLW Precision Forgings Ltd has seen its investment rating downgraded from Hold to Sell as of 24 January 2026, reflecting a combination of deteriorating technical indicators, expensive valuation metrics, and subdued long-term growth prospects despite recent positive quarterly financial results.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b52a0cbd0131e8e3119e3f46ba175ead</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tirupati Foam Ltd Upgraded to Sell on Technical Improvement Despite Lingering Fundamental Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/tirupati-foam-ltd-upgraded-to-sell-on-technical-improvement-despite-lingering-fundamental-concerns-3804451</link><description>Tirupati Foam Ltd has seen its investment rating upgraded from Strong Sell to Sell as of 23 January 2026, driven primarily by a shift in technical indicators despite persistent fundamental challenges. The company’s stock price has gained 3.41% on the day, reflecting renewed investor interest amid a mildly bearish technical outlook. However, long-term financial metrics and valuation factors continue to weigh on the stock’s appeal.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>75af7de01b832ce37f85f75649e312ab</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BLS International Services Ltd Downgraded to Sell Amid Technical Weakness and Market Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/bls-international-services-ltd-downgraded-to-sell-amid-technical-weakness-and-market-underperformance-3804446</link><description>BLS International Services Ltd has seen its investment rating downgraded from Hold to Sell, driven primarily by deteriorating technical indicators and sustained underperformance relative to the broader market. Despite robust financial results and attractive valuation metrics, the stock’s bearish technical trend and weak market sentiment have prompted a reassessment of its outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>bc4b97adac4f040384f6a7d3e9ad199e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Response Informatics Ltd Downgraded to Strong Sell Amid Weak Fundamentals and Bearish Technicals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/response-informatics-ltd-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-weak-fundamentals-and-bearish-technicals-3804444</link><description>Response Informatics Ltd has seen its investment rating downgraded from Sell to Strong Sell as of 23 January 2026, reflecting deteriorating technical indicators, flat financial performance, and weak long-term fundamentals. The software products company’s stock has underperformed key benchmarks, prompting a reassessment of its quality, valuation, financial trend, and technical outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8016e5a895f6bf5d952c1d3eb7b4e514</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Galactico Corporate Services Ltd Upgraded to Sell on Technical Improvements Despite Weak Fundamentals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/galactico-corporate-services-ltd-upgraded-to-sell-on-technical-improvements-despite-weak-fundamentals-3804450</link><description>Galactico Corporate Services Ltd has seen its investment rating upgraded from Strong Sell to Sell, reflecting a nuanced shift driven primarily by technical indicators, even as fundamental challenges persist. The company’s financial trends remain subdued, but recent technical signals suggest a mild improvement in market sentiment, prompting a reassessment of its outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>027025a5c916a4e5f8c8c1305b0c3af8</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prism Johnson Ltd. Upgraded to Sell on Improved Valuation and Financial Trends</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/prism-johnson-ltd-upgraded-to-sell-on-improved-valuation-and-financial-trends-3804453</link><description>Prism Johnson Ltd., a key player in the Cement &amp; Cement Products sector, has seen its investment rating upgraded from Strong Sell to Sell as of 23 January 2026. This revision reflects a notable improvement in the company’s valuation metrics and financial trends, despite ongoing challenges in quality and technical indicators. The upgrade comes amid a complex backdrop of mixed performance data and sector comparisons, signalling a cautious but more optimistic outlook for investors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8941f3154c5fe903b65de884b136aee1</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Patels Airtemp Downgraded to Strong Sell Amid Weak Financials and Bearish Technicals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/patels-airtemp-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-weak-financials-and-bearish-technicals-3804448</link><description>Patels Airtemp (India) Ltd, a key player in the industrial manufacturing sector, has seen its investment rating downgraded from Sell to Strong Sell as of 23 January 2026. This shift reflects deteriorating financial performance, unfavourable valuation metrics, and a worsening technical outlook, signalling heightened risks for investors amid sustained underperformance relative to benchmarks like the Sensex.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0cd9035f0f7f8011d94368f47f437cc3</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Ports Downgraded to Sell Amid Technical Weakness and Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/adani-ports-downgraded-to-sell-amid-technical-weakness-and-valuation-concerns-3804447</link><description>Adani Ports &amp; Special Economic Zone Ltd has seen its investment rating downgraded from Hold to Sell, reflecting a shift in technical indicators and valuation metrics despite solid financial performance and long-term growth prospects. The downgrade, effective from 23 January 2026, is primarily driven by deteriorating technical trends and expensive valuation parameters, signalling caution for investors amid recent price volatility.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f047763b593d340ee46f462979a1fde0</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Oil Corporation Ltd Downgraded to Hold Amid Mixed Technical and Valuation Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/indian-oil-corporation-ltd-downgraded-to-hold-amid-mixed-technical-and-valuation-signals-3804445</link><description>Indian Oil Corporation Ltd (IOC) has seen its investment rating downgraded from Buy to Hold as of 23 January 2026, reflecting a nuanced reassessment across quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical indicators. Despite robust financial performance and attractive valuation metrics, evolving technical signals and market dynamics have prompted a more cautious stance from analysts.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a421d4c159820b98d03ed51de29dc51e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Swarnsarita Jewels India Ltd Upgraded to Hold on Technical and Financial Improvements</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/swarnsarita-jewels-india-ltd-upgraded-to-hold-on-technical-and-financial-improvements-3804452</link><description>Swarnsarita Jewels India Ltd has seen its investment rating upgraded from Sell to Hold, reflecting a notable shift in technical indicators and valuation metrics. The upgrade, announced on 23 January 2026, follows a series of positive developments across quality, valuation, financial trends, and technical parameters, signalling a cautious but optimistic outlook for this micro-cap player in the Gems, Jewellery and Watches sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>38a71bac84451fd45aec2af696ce45c9</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Anka India Ltd Downgraded to Strong Sell Amid Technical Weakness and Flat Financials</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/anka-india-ltd-downgraded-to-strong-sell-amid-technical-weakness-and-flat-financials-3804449</link><description>Anka India Ltd, a player in the diversified consumer products sector, has seen its investment rating downgraded from Sell to Strong Sell as of 23 January 2026. This shift reflects deteriorating technical indicators, flat financial performance, and weak long-term fundamentals despite notable promoter confidence and impressive stock returns over the past year.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>18280dd257b5f206a2c79b571e50a648</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lupin Ltd. Upgraded to Strong Buy on Robust Financials and Bullish Technicals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/lupin-ltd-upgraded-to-strong-buy-on-robust-financials-and-bullish-technicals-3804443</link><description>Lupin Ltd., a leading player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, has seen its investment rating upgraded from Buy to Strong Buy as of 23 January 2026. This upgrade reflects significant improvements across four key parameters: quality, valuation, financial trend, and technicals. The company’s strong financial performance, attractive valuation metrics, and bullish technical indicators have collectively driven this positive reassessment, positioning Lupin as a compelling investment opportunity amid a challenging market backdrop.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>48c90a034425072c1d27bd0a3bfc8aef</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jindal Photo Ltd Upgraded to Hold as Technicals Improve Amid Mixed Financials</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/jindal-photo-ltd-upgraded-to-hold-as-technicals-improve-amid-mixed-financials-3804440</link><description>Jindal Photo Ltd has seen its investment rating upgraded from Sell to Hold as of 23 January 2026, driven primarily by a marked improvement in technical indicators despite recent negative financial results. The company’s long-term growth prospects remain intact, supported by strong sales and operating profit growth, while valuation concerns and short-term financial setbacks temper enthusiasm. This comprehensive analysis explores the four key parameters influencing the rating change: Quality, Valuation, Financial Trend, and Technicals.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7643303a2a6792b4417bdf43470be9fa</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Onward Technologies Downgraded to Hold Amid Mixed Technicals and Valuation Insights</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/onward-technologies-downgraded-to-hold-amid-mixed-technicals-and-valuation-insights-3804441</link><description>Onward Technologies Ltd, a player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has seen its investment rating downgraded from Buy to Hold as of 23 January 2026. This adjustment reflects a nuanced reassessment across four key parameters: quality, valuation, financial trend, and technical indicators. Despite strong financial performance and attractive valuation metrics, evolving technical signals and cautious institutional participation have tempered enthusiasm among analysts.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7983be94ac21d548e1d433ae5d61aa11</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:14:02 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>