<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:39:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Divgi Torqtransfer Systems Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/divgi-torqtransfer-systems-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3808175</link><description>Divgi Torqtransfer Systems Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's long-term strength within the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>ca36ed5520acfe7a59c34339e63ab81f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Viviana Power Tech Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/viviana-power-tech-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3808176</link><description>Viviana Power Tech Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raising concerns about its medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>e2563e764863074edd59f3f1434b17bc</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vijaya Diagnostic Centre Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vijaya-diagnostic-centre-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3808174</link><description>Vijaya Diagnostic Centre Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>0edec095fc975778d0924f5c204adf39</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Exxaro Tiles Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/exxaro-tiles-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3808170</link><description>Exxaro Tiles Ltd, a micro-cap player in the diversified consumer products sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>b3778ac3f099f59f43e0927d4e846cc1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arvind Fashions Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/arvind-fashions-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3808172</link><description>Arvind Fashions Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>799ad5829e60af34d98c777e4b633b16</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HDFC Asset Management Company Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hdfc-asset-management-company-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3808169</link><description>HDFC Asset Management Company Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>be64d631d3a6cd2ba39cee3039b0a89d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Adani Green Energy Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adani-green-energy-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3808171</link><description>Adani Green Energy Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>f85adfd0997215af8b0c3b9ca8cf673b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Road Network Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-road-network-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3808167</link><description>Bharat Road Network Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential sustained bearish trend for the construction sector micro-cap, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness amid challenging market conditions.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>e6940928246a3da9fbc704fbf80e4e23</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Regency Fincorp Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/regency-fincorp-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3808173</link><description>Regency Fincorp Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>c2cfae5e337da46bf46dd02ec799a797</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hind Rectifiers Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hind-rectifiers-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3808168</link><description>Hind Rectifiers Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>99acd12c94e1e9733ab65ed6a87df76b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RIR Power Electronics Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rir-power-electronics-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3808166</link><description>RIR Power Electronics Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raising concerns about its medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>e7adea99fdd51dc9aeedb809b5efe6eb</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thomas Scott India Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/thomas-scott-india-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3808165</link><description>Thomas Scott India Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>15e1c286f30af2d34ecf9d7844d5d2bb</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Central Bank of India Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/central-bank-of-india-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3808161</link><description>Central Bank of India has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum and raising concerns about sustained weakness in the public sector bank’s share price.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>57bba136171b0627f49234885010a501</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Motilal Oswal Financial Services Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/motilal-oswal-financial-services-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3808160</link><description>Motilal Oswal Financial Services Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>78099ce2c3fe9e8a2411031ea34e02b9</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kalpataru Projects International Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kalpataru-projects-international-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3808162</link><description>Kalpataru Projects International Ltd, a prominent player in the construction sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, indicating a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>faad68cb7aa7d308392794c7912ac566</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HDFC Bank Ltd. Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hdfc-bank-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3808164</link><description>HDFC Bank Ltd., a leading player in the private sector banking industry, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, raising concerns about the stock's near-term momentum and long-term strength.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>2418adbc747735ae435e082247f74ff9</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Astral Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/astral-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3808159</link><description>Astral Ltd, a prominent player in the Plastic Products - Industrial sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>0465f960b3952b54e936bb7574ed9946</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Avantel Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/avantel-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3808156</link><description>Avantel Ltd, a notable player in the Aerospace &amp; Defense sector, has recently formed a Death Cross—a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average—indicating a potential shift towards a bearish trend and signalling long-term weakness in the stock’s price momentum.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>89f0177a1b9cd2554f3f74df8db62a11</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GTT Data Solutions Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gtt-data-solutions-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3808157</link><description>GTT Data Solutions Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>6c3d229d550751f620d0609789f13852</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nagreeka Capital &amp; Infrastructure Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nagreeka-capital-infrastructure-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3808163</link><description>Nagreeka Capital &amp; Infrastructure Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a prolonged bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>cd4ae64e5fe805ee5823ca9081032a86</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:39:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>