<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:28:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>KPI Green Energy Q3 FY26: Strong Growth Momentum Continues Despite Margin Pressures</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/kpi-green-energy-q3-fy26-strong-growth-momentum-continues-despite-margin-pressures-3798413</link><description>KPI Green Energy Ltd., a Gujarat-based renewable energy solutions provider, delivered another quarter of robust top-line expansion in Q2 FY26, though the company's shares have struggled to maintain momentum, trading at ₹436.90 as of January 21, 2026—down 22.34% from its 52-week high of ₹562.60. The company reported consolidated net profit of ₹109.11 crores for Q2 FY26, marking a sequential increase of 4.96% from Q1 FY26's ₹103.95 crores and a substantial year-on-year surge of 56.03% from Q2 FY25's ₹69.93 crores.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>4f5c96d24356ba533a700ff92c5aa44f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:28:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>K.P. Energy Q3 FY26: Strong Growth Momentum Masks Technical Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/kp-energy-q3-fy26-strong-growth-momentum-masks-technical-weakness-3798369</link><description>K.P. Energy Ltd., a leading provider of Balance of Plant (BoP) solutions for the wind energy industry, reported robust financial performance for Q2 FY26 (July-September 2025), with consolidated net profit surging 44.11% year-on-year to ₹35.94 crores. The small-cap company, with a market capitalisation of ₹2,076.46 crores, demonstrated strong operational execution with net sales climbing 51.39% YoY to ₹300.69 crores. However, the stock has been under severe pressure, trading at ₹310.35 as of January 21, 2026, down 46.85% from its 52-week high of ₹583.90, reflecting broader market concerns despite solid fundamental performance.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>5dcb3fdfcf105850c988160d2fb119a4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:28:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Refex Industries Q2 FY26: Strong Profit Surge Masks Revenue Concerns as Stock Tumbles 48%</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/refex-industries-q2-fy26-strong-profit-surge-masks-revenue-concerns-as-stock-tumbles-48-3798350</link><description>Refex Industries Ltd., a Chennai-based refrigerant gas manufacturer, reported a robust 76.85% quarter-on-quarter surge in consolidated net profit to ₹37.44 crores for Q2 FY26, yet the company's shares have plummeted 48.36% over the past year, trading at ₹235.95 and reflecting deep investor concerns about sustainability and valuation. With a market capitalisation of ₹3,235.57 crores, the small-cap chemical company faces a challenging narrative: impressive quarterly profit growth juxtaposed against stagnant revenue performance and deteriorating market sentiment.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>4cd08f8950bc1f789e9de146a7d6158b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:28:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mastek Q3 FY26: Profit Surge Masks Margin Pressure and Revenue Stagnation</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/mastek-q3-fy26-profit-surge-masks-margin-pressure-and-revenue-stagnation-3798346</link><description>Mastek Ltd., a trusted digital engineering and cloud transformation partner serving healthcare, retail, manufacturing, financial services, and government sectors, reported a mixed Q3 FY26 performance that showcased robust profit growth but exposed underlying operational challenges. The company posted a consolidated net profit of ₹108.35 crores for the quarter ended December 2025, marking an 11.19% sequential increase and a 14.40% year-on-year gain. However, this profit expansion came despite a 3.69% quarter-on-quarter revenue decline to ₹905.68 crores, raising concerns about demand momentum and pricing power in a competitive IT services landscape.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>2752b0f90a40d1cdf7916a690f0324a8</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:28:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sundrop Brands Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sundrop-brands-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3798911</link><description>Sundrop Brands Ltd, a key player in the edible oil sector, recorded a fresh 52-week low of Rs.606.8 today, marking a significant milestone in its recent price trajectory. The stock has been on a downward path, reflecting a series of challenges and market dynamics that have influenced investor sentiment and valuation.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>de390ee2c3025aa077a274a89e23b346</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:28:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sundrop Brands Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.606.8 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sundrop-brands-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs6068-amidst-continued-downtrend-3798909</link><description>Sundrop Brands Ltd, a key player in the edible oil sector, recorded a fresh 52-week low of Rs.606.8 today, marking a significant milestone in its recent price trajectory. The stock has declined steadily over the past three days, shedding 9.67% in returns during this period, reflecting ongoing pressures within the market and company-specific factors.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b867bfdea7dd13e17f9eedebb9311500</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:28:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Garware Technical Fibres Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/garware-technical-fibres-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-prolonged-downtrend-3798910</link><description>Garware Technical Fibres Ltd has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.589.55 today, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock has been on a downward trajectory for the past 11 consecutive trading sessions, resulting in a cumulative loss of 13.48% over this period, despite outperforming its sector by 1.6% on the day.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>0ee324ee2fbcb9272cb159115e981cc1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:28:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Garware Technical Fibres Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/garware-technical-fibres-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-prolonged-downtrend-3798907</link><description>Garware Technical Fibres Ltd has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.589.55 today, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock has been on a downward trajectory for the past 11 consecutive trading sessions, resulting in a cumulative loss of 13.48% during this period.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>e84c87b25f2e7d9f93c475b444e734f7</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:28:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Orient Press Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/orient-press-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-weakness-3798908</link><description>Orient Press Ltd’s shares declined sharply to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.62.03 on 21 Jan 2026, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory. The packaging sector company has seen its stock price fall by over 40% in the past year, underperforming the broader market and its sector peers amid persistent financial headwinds.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ee2a8ec403fa0e581c0f4af486198538</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:28:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Orient Press Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/orient-press-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3798906</link><description>Orient Press Ltd, a key player in the packaging sector, recorded a fresh 52-week low today, with its stock price falling to Rs.62.03. This marks a significant milestone in the company’s ongoing decline, reflecting persistent pressures on its financial and market performance.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>c8078edde417eca484f6c268a1aa3572</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:28:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mohit Industries Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.23.18</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mohit-industries-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs2318-3798905</link><description>Mohit Industries Ltd, a player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.23.18 today, marking a significant decline amid ongoing market pressures and company-specific headwinds. The stock’s recent performance reflects a sustained downtrend, with notable volatility and underperformance relative to its sector and broader market indices.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>8a49b61b27b69b3431839c41a40ea713</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:28:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mohit Industries Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.23.18</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mohit-industries-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs2318-3798904</link><description>Mohit Industries Ltd, a player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs 23.18 on 21 Jan 2026, marking a significant decline amid ongoing market pressures and company-specific challenges. The stock has underperformed both its sector and broader market indices over the past year, reflecting persistent headwinds.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>93fc07b892a18a4010dc400cd1893061</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:28:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>B N Rathi Securities Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/b-n-rathi-securities-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3798903</link><description>B N Rathi Securities Ltd has touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.14.9 today, marking a significant decline in its share price amid a sustained downward trajectory over recent sessions. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing pressures on its financial performance and valuation metrics.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>7c1691ac3111682bc4356183dbe90bf1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:28:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>B N Rathi Securities Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.14.9 Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/b-n-rathi-securities-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs149-amid-continued-downtrend-3798901</link><description>B N Rathi Securities Ltd has touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.14.9 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing pressures on its financial performance and valuation metrics.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>72522be4a5b4e481581127d3343cc4c3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:28:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kellton Tech Solutions Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.14.86</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kellton-tech-solutions-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs1486-3798902</link><description>Kellton Tech Solutions Ltd’s share price declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.14.86 on 21 Jan 2026, marking a significant downturn amid broader market pressures and company-specific performance trends. This new low reflects a continuation of the stock’s downward trajectory over the past year, contrasting sharply with the broader market’s positive returns.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>2b3825fb8356816ba497acf6d458de66</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:28:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kokuyo Camlin Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low at Rs.80.25</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kokuyo-camlin-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-at-rs8025-3798899</link><description>Kokuyo Camlin Ltd’s shares declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.80.25 on 21 Jan 2026, marking a continuation of the stock’s downward trajectory amid broader market pressures and sectoral weakness.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>9f4c26e339fd6f06523f25ae2c34c201</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:28:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rishiroop Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rishiroop-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3798900</link><description>Rishiroop Ltd, a player in the Industrial Products sector, touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.90 today, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing downward trajectory. This new low comes amid a broader market environment where the Sensex has been under pressure, and the stock continues to trade well below its key moving averages.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>7de5fd2e33156bcc99b6026889a23c04</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:28:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rishiroop Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.90 Amid Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rishiroop-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs90-amid-continued-underperformance-3798896</link><description>Rishiroop Ltd, a player in the Industrial Products sector, recorded a fresh 52-week low of Rs.90 today, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing price decline. The stock’s recent performance reflects a sustained downward trajectory amid broader market pressures and company-specific financial trends.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>32f45292d48e3e82f55411591db1fc7b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:28:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Srestha Finvest Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/srestha-finvest-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3798897</link><description>Srestha Finvest Ltd, a Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC), recorded a new 52-week and all-time low of Rs.0.26 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid ongoing financial headwinds and subdued market sentiment.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>e544e18ee92493e2457d15d15f4e908c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:28:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>La Opala RG Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.188.25</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/la-opala-rg-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs18825-3798895</link><description>La Opala RG Ltd, a key player in the diversified consumer products sector, recorded a fresh 52-week low of Rs.188.25 today, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing price decline. The stock has been under pressure for several sessions, reflecting broader market trends and company-specific performance factors.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>740d07638369dbcf0fd7f65b2d489375</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:28:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:28:15 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>