<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:30:30 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Sensex and Nifty Slip Sharply as Market Breadth Deteriorates; Adani Stocks Lead Losses</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-and-nifty-slip-sharply-as-market-breadth-deteriorates-adani-stocks-lead-losses-3804723</link><description>Indian equity markets closed sharply lower on 26 Jan 2026, with the Sensex and Nifty both retreating nearly 1% amid widespread selling pressure. All sectors ended in the red, led by utilities and realty, while heavyweight Adani Group stocks suffered steep declines. Market breadth was weak, and foreign institutional investors remained net sellers as global cues weighed on sentiment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>049660f5ac309ebc7a41dc198ad09ba1</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lexus Granito (India) Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/lexus-granito-india-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3804533</link><description>Lexus Granito (India) Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 24 December 2024. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock’s current position as of 26 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trend, and technical outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>71c683c004e734c91b9e214623a58a30</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MRC Agrotech Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/mrc-agrotech-ltd-is-rated-sell-3804534</link><description>MRC Agrotech Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 01 Dec 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 January 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0d443cdff71392181307f59962d609e3</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bandaram Pharma Packtech Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/bandaram-pharma-packtech-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3804532</link><description>Bandaram Pharma Packtech Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 15 Dec 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed below reflect the stock’s current position as of 26 January 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1631e3ce1f819b4addf64139770ac599</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Josts Engineering Company Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/josts-engineering-company-ltd-is-rated-sell-3804531</link><description>Josts Engineering Company Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 11 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5447edd579ff30020426051df60d9202</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Balkrishna Industries Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/balkrishna-industries-ltd-is-rated-sell-3804528</link><description>Balkrishna Industries Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 02 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3140958d3d73f738670f8d120637a2c1</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SMT Engineering Ltd is Rated Buy</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/smt-engineering-ltd-is-rated-buy-3804530</link><description>SMT Engineering Ltd is rated 'Buy' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 08 Dec 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company's performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3eddc34790ede2355bab8dbf0e589e20</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rudrabhishek Enterprises Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/rudrabhishek-enterprises-ltd-is-rated-sell-3804529</link><description>Rudrabhishek Enterprises Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 18 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e6ced90332b061a6cf8827f0b9a7107b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Felix Industries Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/felix-industries-ltd-is-rated-hold-3804527</link><description>Felix Industries Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 01 Jan 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 January 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>da0bcc305f7d3c4f63da8a35bcb6e53d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sahyadri Industries Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sahyadri-industries-ltd-is-rated-sell-3804525</link><description>Sahyadri Industries Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 24 September 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 January 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1ed43451dd3c5664cf81990357432bc2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Byke Hospitality Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/the-byke-hospitality-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3804523</link><description>The Byke Hospitality Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 01 August 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company's fundamentals, returns, and market performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>30a780f5cd3f3ed1b41a9f3e74282f53</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Saraswati Saree Depot Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/saraswati-saree-depot-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3804526</link><description>Saraswati Saree Depot Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 11 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>982931ceeeef3aed5039f8f72c11f4c6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Conart Engineers Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/conart-engineers-ltd-is-rated-sell-3804522</link><description>Conart Engineers Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 18 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of its fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8b87ef3c83787eb1533965fdb30c09ea</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bata India Ltd. is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/bata-india-ltd-is-rated-sell-3804524</link><description>Bata India Ltd. is currently rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 11 Nov 2025. While the rating change occurred then, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's present position as of 26 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d98a72af1ca260d779348e25eada6968</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manugraph India Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/manugraph-india-ltd-is-rated-sell-3804521</link><description>Manugraph India Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 23 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 January 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>650d4bfb4cce06ca2e87acf467541366</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Damodar Industries Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/damodar-industries-ltd-is-rated-sell-3804520</link><description>Damodar Industries Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 16 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 January 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date perspective on the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9138d02f9526f011601718fbbd0b86c2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Panasonic Energy India Company Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/panasonic-energy-india-company-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3804518</link><description>Panasonic Energy India Company Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 04 Nov 2025, reflecting a reassessment of the stock’s outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here are current as of 26 January 2026, providing investors with the latest view of the company’s position in the market.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>761a31933376fd94f9499b6e2615356c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DMR Engineering Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/dmr-engineering-ltd-is-rated-sell-3804519</link><description>DMR Engineering Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 20 August 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed below reflect the stock's current position as of 26 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ad6f389bced7dd57b9b24934dc2638e8</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quick Heal Technologies Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/quick-heal-technologies-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3804517</link><description>Quick Heal Technologies Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 02 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>62f0e7ef6d725a3b2da12985c2632100</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SEPC Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sepc-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3804516</link><description>SEPC Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 02 Dec 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 January 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>54920c62ec069eb505fa31066f5b0f91</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:30:30 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>