<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 09:20:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>JHS Svendgaard Retail Ventures Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Weak Fundamentals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jhs-svendgaard-retail-ventures-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-weak-fundamentals-3775153</link><description>JHS Svendgaard Retail Ventures Ltd has reached a new 52-week low, reflecting ongoing pressures on the stock amid a challenging financial backdrop. The share price decline to this significant level underscores persistent headwinds faced by the company within the diversified retail sector.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>c687df61aef33b352016ef616c7c4521</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 09:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deepak Builders &amp; Engineers India Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/deepak-builders-engineers-india-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amidst-prolonged-downtrend-3775151</link><description>Shares of Deepak Builders &amp; Engineers India Ltd have declined to an all-time low, reflecting a sustained period of underperformance and financial strain. The stock’s recent fall underscores significant pressures within the construction sector and highlights the company’s ongoing difficulties in reversing its downward trajectory.
Time: 29 minutes ago</description><guid>fba830e956aa1fada5e196b65b501adf</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 09:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Callista Industries Ltd Stock Hits All-Time High, Marking a Significant Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/callista-industries-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-marking-a-significant-milestone-3775150</link><description>Callista Industries Ltd has reached an all-time high, closing just 0.02% shy of its 52-week peak at Rs 111.32, underscoring a remarkable phase of growth and market performance. This milestone reflects the company’s sustained upward momentum across multiple timeframes and its ability to outperform key benchmarks.
Time: 31 minutes ago</description><guid>41043b87b99bef77466006fa37c155da</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 09:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ashok Leyland Ltd. Stock Hits All-Time High of Rs.178.5 on 30 Dec 2025</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ashok-leyland-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-of-rs1785-on-30-dec-2025-3775148</link><description>Ashok Leyland Ltd., a prominent player in the Indian automobile sector, has reached a new all-time high of Rs.178.5, reflecting a robust performance trajectory and sustained investor confidence. This milestone underscores the company’s strong market position and consistent growth over multiple time horizons.
Time: 32 minutes ago</description><guid>69fd9f95225bfb1b6281c7d5385f8269</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 09:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Laurus Labs Ltd Stock Hits All-Time High at Rs.1095 on 30 Dec 2025</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/laurus-labs-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-at-rs1095-on-30-dec-2025-3775149</link><description>Laurus Labs Ltd has reached a new pinnacle, hitting an all-time high of Rs.1095 on 30 Dec 2025, reflecting a remarkable trajectory in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector. This milestone underscores the company’s sustained growth and robust financial performance over recent years.
Time: 32 minutes ago</description><guid>e5d39eb3b64ed7dd9dbf23c33744f232</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 09:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jindal Steel Ltd. Hits Intraday High with 3.31% Surge on 30 Dec 2025</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jindal-steel-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-331-surge-on-30-dec-2025-3775152</link><description>Jindal Steel Ltd. demonstrated robust intraday performance on 30 Dec 2025, surging to an intraday high of Rs 1,024.6, marking a 3.47% increase from its previous close. The stock outperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting notable trading momentum in the ferrous metals segment.
Time: 37 minutes ago</description><guid>543de2aac47da1f51ce7de71ab54e7fd</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 09:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HP Adhesives Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hp-adhesives-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amid-prolonged-downtrend-3775145</link><description>HP Adhesives Ltd has reached an all-time low in its stock price, reflecting a sustained period of underperformance relative to the broader market and its sector peers. The stock’s recent decline underscores ongoing difficulties faced by the company within the specialty chemicals industry, as evidenced by deteriorating financial metrics and subdued investor participation.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>615de41b455dda1383668b38ca4f4972</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 09:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Max Healthcare Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amidst Weak Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/max-healthcare-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amidst-weak-price-action-3775143</link><description>Max Healthcare Institute Ltd has witnessed a notable 10.18% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s recent underperformance. This surge in open interest, coupled with declining prices and volume patterns, suggests a complex shift in market positioning that investors should carefully analyse.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>b6753af65d71a118033be10785b1c3de</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 09:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UPL Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Signalling Bullish Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/upl-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-signalling-bullish-market-positioning-3775142</link><description>UPL Ltd., a leading player in the Pesticides &amp; Agrochemicals sector, has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, reflecting a shift in market sentiment and positioning. The increase in open interest by over 12% alongside robust volume patterns suggests growing investor confidence and potential directional bets on the stock’s near-term trajectory.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>ba6255476d4da6282589eab752de8c09</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 09:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Forge Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-forge-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-market-positioning-3775147</link><description>Bharat Forge Ltd., a prominent player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has witnessed a notable surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and potential directional bets. The stock’s recent performance, coupled with increased investor participation and robust volume patterns, suggests a bullish sentiment taking shape as it nears its 52-week high.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>d3e090a270b6763d484c1a420897ff43</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 09:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Steel Authority Of India Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/steel-authority-of-india-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-momentum-3775146</link><description>Steel Authority Of India Ltd. (SAIL) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. The stock’s recent outperformance, combined with rising volumes and a notable increase in open interest, suggests growing bullish sentiment among traders and investors alike.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>40da2a8d988932adda2c4257d97e0408</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 09:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Power Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Weak Price Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tata-power-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-weak-price-momentum-3775140</link><description>Tata Power Company Ltd has witnessed a notable 12.5% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s recent underperformance. This surge in open interest, coupled with declining prices and falling investor participation, suggests a complex positioning landscape with potential directional bets emerging among traders.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>f93e8f8529f1f4c38c797bc41d3b0d78</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 09:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Solar Industries India Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Price Weakness</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/solar-industries-india-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-price-weakness-3775141</link><description>Solar Industries India Ltd (SOLARINDS) has witnessed a significant 14.3% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, rising from 38,713 to 44,247 contracts. This surge comes despite the stock’s recent underperformance, with prices falling over 5% in the last five trading sessions, signalling a complex interplay of market positioning and investor sentiment.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>4d970f8600e5eeabc393b9bbd5eb50fd</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 09:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Surge in Open Interest Signals Shifting Market Sentiment for Sammaan Capital Ltd</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/surge-in-open-interest-signals-shifting-market-sentiment-for-sammaan-capital-ltd-3775144</link><description>Sammaan Capital Ltd, a key player in the housing finance sector, has witnessed a notable surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling a potential shift in market positioning and investor sentiment. The 11.36% increase in OI, coupled with rising volumes and delivery participation, suggests evolving directional bets amid a cautious yet opportunistic trading environment.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>54d8840c27bf1d9a8ddc91c661a5a9bf</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 09:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HCL Technologies Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Price Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hcl-technologies-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-price-momentum-3775136</link><description>HCL Technologies Ltd (HCLTECH) has witnessed a notable 10.35% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and evolving positioning among traders. Despite a recent four-day price decline, the surge in open interest alongside robust volumes suggests a complex interplay of directional bets and hedging strategies within the large-cap software and consulting stock.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>b07cfa9f592ff50d8a35a51643d7dbd2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 09:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arfin India Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit on Strong Buying Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/arfin-india-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-on-strong-buying-momentum-3775132</link><description>Arfin India Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non-Ferrous Metals sector, surged to a new 52-week and all-time high on 30 Dec 2025, hitting its upper circuit limit with a strong 3.76% gain. The stock’s impressive performance was driven by intense buying interest, significant unfilled demand, and a regulatory freeze on further trading, underscoring renewed investor confidence in the company’s prospects.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>e78916234bf8866399b1cd57fdda32dc</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 09:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NRB Industrial Bearings Ltd Surges 20% to Hit Upper Circuit Amid Strong Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nrb-industrial-bearings-ltd-surges-20-to-hit-upper-circuit-amid-strong-buying-pressure-3775131</link><description>NRB Industrial Bearings Ltd witnessed a remarkable rally on 30 Dec 2025, hitting its upper circuit limit with a 19.98% gain to close at ₹34.65. This surge was driven by intense buying interest, significant volatility, and a sharp reversal after two days of decline, underscoring renewed investor confidence in this micro-cap industrial products stock.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>4e585da27e320d17945ff252e536c070</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 09:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bosch Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bosch-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3775137</link><description>Bosch Ltd., a key player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has witnessed a notable 12.6% rise in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market activity despite the stock’s recent underperformance. This surge in open interest, coupled with volume patterns and shifting investor positioning, offers insights into potential directional bets and market sentiment heading into the new year.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>391b2d8cac03672b1366a38fb8b4d890</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 09:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spacenet Enterprises India Ltd Surges to Upper Circuit Amid Robust Buying Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/spacenet-enterprises-india-ltd-surges-to-upper-circuit-amid-robust-buying-pressure-3775130</link><description>Spacenet Enterprises India Ltd witnessed a robust surge in its share price on 30 Dec 2025, hitting the upper circuit limit as strong buying interest propelled the stock to its maximum daily gain. The micro-cap company outperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting heightened investor enthusiasm despite a regulatory freeze on further trades.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>69365f2cd7e67837722371c5cf7dcb82</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 09:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indo Thai Securities Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indo-thai-securities-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3775134</link><description>Indo Thai Securities Ltd, a notable player in the capital markets sector, witnessed a sharp decline on 30 Dec 2025, hitting its lower circuit limit with a maximum daily loss of 4.99%. The stock closed at ₹312.05, down from an intraday high of ₹336.6, reflecting intense selling pressure and panic among investors amid heightened volatility and unfilled supply.
Time: 50 minutes ago</description><guid>e81567e22c425d6adccd899e16e10724</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 09:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 09:20:53 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>