<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:52:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Swati Projects Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/swati-projects-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3822793</link><description>Swati Projects Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Death Cross as its 50-day moving average (DMA) crossed below the 200-DMA. This technical development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>696ab2858425249f3a1126407a3fccb8</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:52:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindprakash Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindprakash-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3822792</link><description>Hindprakash Industries Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>f18b6c9dd9d29197fd8adf46c9a84935</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:52:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ceigall India Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ceigall-india-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3822788</link><description>Ceigall India Ltd, a key player in the construction sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross—a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-DMA. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, offering investors a fresh perspective on the stock’s future trajectory.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>24f83fb31f126ce1f29abb3554a56924</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:52:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RRIL Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rril-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3822784</link><description>RRIL Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels industry, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about its medium to long-term outlook amid ongoing sectoral and market challenges.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>c59887fa6b19c73026382432fe4efdb6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:52:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Krishna Ventures Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Indicating Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/krishna-ventures-ltd-forms-golden-cross-indicating-potential-bullish-breakout-3822783</link><description>Krishna Ventures Ltd, a micro-cap player in the realty sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, offering investors a fresh perspective on the stock’s future trajectory.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>3006de08afb596ab3258174c40639974</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:52:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Banaras Beads Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/banaras-beads-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3822790</link><description>Banaras Beads Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Gems, Jewellery And Watches sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>6dcb2f9699da10d7910ab5b780298b6c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:52:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Veljan Denison Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Indicating Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/veljan-denison-ltd-forms-golden-cross-indicating-potential-bullish-breakout-3822789</link><description>Veljan Denison Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross—a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, attracting the attention of investors and market analysts alike.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>66b807b1e2422fe52b854ec038679ed7</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:52:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Capri Global Capital Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/capri-global-capital-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-momentum-3822787</link><description>Capri Global Capital Ltd, a small-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>f5dab772144e0a281986b6bb83d69d64</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:52:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oil &amp; Natural Gas Corporation Ltd. Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/oil-natural-gas-corporation-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-bullish-breakout-3822791</link><description>Oil &amp; Natural Gas Corporation Ltd. (ONGC) has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-DMA. This development is widely regarded as a bullish signal, suggesting a potential long-term upward momentum shift and a possible trend reversal for the stock within the oil sector.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>7cf96962a4d820f50a8eecefec9cd489</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:52:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>H T Media Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/h-t-media-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3822785</link><description>H T Media Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum and raising concerns about sustained weakness in the coming months.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>d2c9c8c1f9be7efa542300917e869b73</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:52:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ind-Swift Laboratories Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ind-swift-laboratories-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3822786</link><description>Ind-Swift Laboratories Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a bullish breakout and a potential long-term shift in momentum, suggesting renewed investor confidence in the pharmaceutical and biotechnology company.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>9d29b3ce54ff116a53e94ad87fa6da40</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:52:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Reveal Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-reveal-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3822782</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has unfolded with a nuanced picture across Indian equities, as 1,351 companies declared results reflecting a cautious improvement in profitability and sales growth. While mid-cap stocks continue to outperform with a 54.0% positive result ratio, large caps lag behind at 36.0%, signalling a divergence in earnings momentum across market capitalisation segments.
Time: 21 minutes ago</description><guid>81e308d16ded7c6d965978e4ef2f0768</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:52:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cochin Minerals Q3 FY26: Margin Pressure Intensifies as Revenue Declines</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/cochin-minerals-q3-fy26-margin-pressure-intensifies-as-revenue-declines-3822801</link><description>Cochin Minerals and Rutile Ltd., a specialty chemicals manufacturer focused on titanium-based products, reported a net profit of ₹2.98 crores for Q3 FY26, representing a marginal 1.02% increase quarter-on-quarter but a concerning 40.64% decline year-on-year. The Kerala-based company, with a market capitalisation of ₹216.00 crores, continues to face significant headwinds as revenue contraction and margin compression persist into the third quarter.
Time: 36 minutes ago</description><guid>083e25f70bc50c86329ce2868db7f58d</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:52:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Imagicaaworld Entertainment Q3 FY26: Seasonal Weakness Returns, Losses Mount Despite Revenue Uptick</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/imagicaaworld-entertainment-q3-fy26-seasonal-weakness-returns-losses-mount-despite-revenue-uptick-3822797</link><description>Imagicaaworld Entertainment Ltd., India's second-largest leisure services company with a market capitalisation of ₹2,810 crores, reported a net loss of ₹5.17 crores for Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), marking a sharp reversal from the previous quarter's loss of ₹38.91 crores but deteriorating significantly from the ₹3.22 crores profit recorded in Q3 FY25. The company's shares traded at ₹49.14 on February 5, 2026, down 1.36% on the day, reflecting investor concerns over the company's inability to sustain profitability despite sequential revenue improvements.
Time: 36 minutes ago</description><guid>b222c032da40eb0e937916c278d28ba3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:52:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Unichem Laboratories Q3 FY26: Exceptional Gain Masks Operational Struggles</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/unichem-laboratories-q3-fy26-exceptional-gain-masks-operational-struggles-3822796</link><description>Unichem Laboratories Ltd., the Mumbai-based pharmaceutical manufacturer with a market capitalisation of ₹2,926 crores, reported a staggering net profit of ₹264.29 crores for Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), representing an extraordinary 356.85% year-on-year surge. However, this headline-grabbing figure conceals a troubling operational reality: the company's core business continues to struggle with declining margins and shrinking profitability, whilst the reported profit stems primarily from a one-time exceptional gain rather than sustainable business performance.
Time: 36 minutes ago</description><guid>8e66e1fae7e999a229918c5382cbaf47</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:52:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FDC Ltd Q3 FY26: Profit Margins Crumble as Other Income Props Up Bottom Line</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/fdc-ltd-q3-fy26-profit-margins-crumble-as-other-income-props-up-bottom-line-3822795</link><description>FDC Ltd., the Mumbai-based pharmaceutical company specialising in formulations and active pharmaceutical ingredients, delivered a disappointing Q3 FY26 performance, with net profit declining 23.60% year-on-year to ₹28.30 crores despite relatively flat revenue growth. The stock has plunged 28.90% from its 52-week high of ₹528.30, currently trading at ₹375.60 with a market capitalisation of ₹6,202 crores, reflecting mounting investor concerns over deteriorating operational efficiency and margin compression.
Time: 36 minutes ago</description><guid>740ce78a1f87b7d66281d45985a32081</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:52:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>R M Drip &amp; Sprinklers Systems Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.110.4</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/r-m-drip-sprinklers-systems-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs1104-3822667</link><description>R M Drip &amp; Sprinklers Systems Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.110.4 today, marking a notable surge in its stock price and reflecting sustained positive momentum over recent trading sessions.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b47f7266b597ce0873c0fa9ebdbc154b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:52:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Xchanging Solutions Ltd Reports Flat Quarterly Performance Amid Margin Pressures</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/xchanging-solutions-ltd-reports-flat-quarterly-performance-amid-margin-pressures-3822666</link><description>Xchanging Solutions Ltd, a player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has reported a flat financial performance for the quarter ended December 2025, marking a notable shift from its previously positive growth trajectory. The company’s latest quarterly results reveal a contraction in profitability and earnings per share, signalling challenges in sustaining margin expansion despite a robust return on capital employed in the half-year period.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>0f96c5084e58ae371ab5c76e6512bb4a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:52:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/awfis-space-solutions-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3822657</link><description>AWFIS Space Solutions Ltd witnessed a significant decline today, hitting a new 52-week low of Rs.370.6. This marks a notable downturn for the diversified commercial services company, reflecting ongoing pressures in its stock performance despite broader market movements.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>6edefd30c18d3736c86ca323f7ad51c3</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:52:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Samrat Forgings Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.182.2 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/samrat-forgings-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs1822-amidst-continued-downtrend-3822659</link><description>Samrat Forgings Ltd’s shares declined sharply to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.182.2 on 5 Feb 2026, marking a significant drop of 8.99% on the day and underperforming its sector by 8.26%. This new low reflects ongoing pressures on the stock, which has now fallen nearly 48% over the past year, contrasting with the Sensex’s 6.44% gain during the same period.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>fa01e18b52ae951a107aa1fbc6e9bae7</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:52:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:52:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>