<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:18:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>SG Finserve Joins MomentumNow Stocks Amid Strong Quarterly Financials</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/mojo-premium/sg-finserve-joins-momentumnow-stocks-following-robust-q3-financials-3762931</link><description>SG Finserve, a small-cap Non-Banking Financial Company (NBFC), has been added to the MomentumNow Stocks list as of 18 December 2025, reflecting its notable financial performance in the September 2025 quarter. The company’s recent quarterly results highlight significant growth across key metrics, positioning it as a compelling candidate for investors seeking momentum-driven opportunities in the NBFC sector.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>5e8e9cc8b0fe26ec226fe9f64a29bbe7</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IFCI Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ifci-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-amid-weakening-momentum-3762923</link><description>IFCI Ltd., a key player in the finance sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting potential long-term weakness and a deterioration in price momentum.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b70398f718b1edaba066c12ed27d3803</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Bijlee Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-bijlee-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3762922</link><description>Bharat Bijlee, a key player in the Other Electrical Equipment sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a potential weakening in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>3a023eaf239020d19088026ca0b23fe5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Deepak Builders &amp; Engineers India Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/deepak-builders-engineers-india-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3762920</link><description>Deepak Builders &amp; Engineers India has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting potential long-term weakness in the stock’s price movement amid broader market challenges.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b72b48c0ed6bf50190720db95a0d3ec0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Premier Energies Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/premier-energies-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3762919</link><description>Premier Energies, a mid-cap player in the Other Electrical Equipment sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>09866352728237e3b6189a3512ee775e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>J.G.Chemicals Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jgchemicals-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3762921</link><description>J.G.Chemicals, a player in the Commodity Chemicals sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>85c66f52348b6e4940df9a6504bddd6e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Veranda Learning Solutions Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/veranda-learning-solutions-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3762918</link><description>Veranda Learning Solutions has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting potential long-term weakness in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>a6b871d5193a313764a2052e84115254</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UTI Asset Management Company Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/uti-asset-management-company-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3762917</link><description>UTI Asset Management Company has recently experienced a significant technical development as its 50-day moving average crossed below the 200-day moving average, a pattern commonly referred to as a Death Cross. This event often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>9ab1e508ec2e880e5c3869c40b8c1a72</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TAAL Enterprises Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/taal-enterprises-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3762912</link><description>TAAL Enterprises, a micro-cap player in the airline sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price action over the longer term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>a0a2f258ff6fa0e3cef606c3876a415b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ingersoll-Rand (India) Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ingersoll-rand-india-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3762911</link><description>Ingersoll-Rand (India) has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average, often interpreted as a signal of weakening momentum and a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development comes amid a backdrop of subdued performance relative to broader market indices and mixed technical indicators, raising questions about the stock’s near-term trajectory.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>c3a700a067b55f0357934d8cdcc6ad78</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Citadel Realty &amp; Developers Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/citadel-realty-developers-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3762910</link><description>Citadel Realty &amp; Developers has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average, often interpreted as a signal of potential long-term weakness and a bearish trend in the stock’s price movement.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>e29aa42768202951d6d20c0d8ecec12d</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rashtriya Chemicals &amp; Fertilizers Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rashtriya-chemicals-fertilizers-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3762913</link><description>Rashtriya Chemicals &amp; Fertilizers has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price movement over the medium to long term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b6292adafd1a9dca7083c197785521c7</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manaksia Aluminium Company Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/manaksia-aluminium-company-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3762914</link><description>Manaksia Aluminium Company, a player in the Non-Ferrous Metals sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend, indicating potential long-term weakness in the stock’s price movement.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>30995ad9203a49501d2e7c9ca0b608fc</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chennai Ferrous Industries Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/chennai-ferrous-industries-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3762909</link><description>Chennai Ferrous Industries, a micro-cap player in the Non-Ferrous Metals sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests potential long-term weakness in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>5d3ee157fc4cc94d352bc4fc0c1ea98f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indraprastha Gas Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indraprastha-gas-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3762908</link><description>Indraprastha Gas has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price action over the longer term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ea6be8d9c891370f55fd7d8be60c010f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Remsons Industries Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/remsons-industries-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3762907</link><description>Remsons Industries, a micro-cap player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a weakening momentum in the stock’s price trajectory over the medium to long term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>51814e0dfe92a6d447431b8dd7ffa5f1</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Atul Auto Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/atul-auto-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3762915</link><description>Atul Auto, a micro-cap player in the automobile sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting potential long-term weakness and a deterioration in the stock’s momentum.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>3332cb404b16f146a4e3964a3d434e99</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UltraTech Cement Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ultratech-cement-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3762916</link><description>UltraTech Cement has recently experienced a significant technical development as its 50-day moving average crossed below the 200-day moving average, forming what is commonly known as a Death Cross. This event is widely regarded as a bearish indicator, suggesting a possible shift towards a weakening trend in the stock’s price movement over the medium to long term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>957f8599917be794cacbec85e3426374</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kovilpatti Lakshmi Roller Flour Mills Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kovilpatti-lakshmi-roller-flour-mills-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3762902</link><description>Kovilpatti Lakshmi Roller Flour Mills has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests potential long-term weakness in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>afc60619b0d1ed2877910148a16e17da</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nagreeka Exports Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nagreeka-exports-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3762900</link><description>Nagreeka Exports, a micro-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and highlights potential long-term weakness in the stock’s price momentum.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>e37bf2573021c6f3591dc6cee006aa6b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>