<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:26:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>RBL Bank Joins Hidden Turnarounds List Following Robust Q3 Financials</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/mojo-premium/rbl-bank-joins-hidden-turnarounds-list-following-robust-q3-financials-3797024</link><description>RBL Bank has been added to the Hidden Turnarounds list as of 20 January 2026, following a robust quarterly performance that signals a promising recovery trajectory. The private sector bank’s recent financial results demonstrate significant growth in profitability and asset quality, positioning it as a compelling small-cap opportunity for investors seeking early-stage turnaround plays.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d71940f31cb3c7f3c5d556612ebfbc6f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:26:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Asian Warehousing Q3 FY26: Micro-Cap Struggles Under Weight of Debt and Operational Challenges</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/asian-warehousing-q3-fy26-micro-cap-struggles-under-weight-of-debt-and-operational-challenges-3797030</link><description>Asian Warehousing Limited, a micro-cap player in the consumer services sector with a market capitalisation of just ₹13.00 crores, has reported virtually flat net profit for Q3 FY26, underscoring the operational and financial challenges that have plagued the company. The stock has been under severe pressure, plunging 7.44% to ₹34.10 following the results announcement, reflecting deep investor scepticism about the company's ability to generate meaningful returns in a highly leveraged capital structure.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>152c8c3470f6e2d060a716a1a3044172</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:26:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AU Small Finance Bank Q3 FY26: Stellar Profit Growth Masks Margin Pressures</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/au-small-finance-bank-q3-fy26-stellar-profit-growth-masks-margin-pressures-3797029</link><description>AU Small Finance Bank Ltd. delivered an impressive 26.34% year-on-year surge in net profit for Q3 FY26, posting ₹667.66 crores against ₹528.45 crores in the same quarter last year. The mid-cap lender, with a market capitalisation of ₹75,544 crores, demonstrated robust earnings momentum with a 19.04% sequential jump from Q2 FY26's ₹560.87 crores. However, the stellar profit performance comes alongside persistent margin compression, with Net Interest Margin (NIM) declining to 5.7% from 5.9% a year ago, raising questions about the sustainability of growth quality.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4e90948d3a8ab91e9b14251352cebee4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:26:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BIGBLOC Construction Q3 FY26: Margin Pressures Mount Despite Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/bigbloc-construction-q3-fy26-margin-pressures-mount-despite-revenue-growth-3797028</link><description>BIGBLOC Construction Ltd., one of India's largest manufacturers of Aerated Autoclaved Concrete (AAC) blocks, reported a consolidated net profit of ₹1.85 crores for Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), representing a sharp 15.14% decline year-on-year from ₹2.18 crores in Q3 FY25. The results revealed persistent margin pressures despite robust revenue growth, triggering an 8.18% stock price decline to ₹62.50 on January 20, 2026. With a market capitalisation of ₹963.00 crores, the micro-cap cement products manufacturer faces mounting operational challenges that have overshadowed its impressive top-line expansion.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f4d2de6e97e050f1da6001fab713dbdb</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:26:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Roselabs Finance Q3 FY26: Mounting Losses Deepen Financial Distress</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/roselabs-finance-q3-fy26-mounting-losses-deepen-financial-distress-3797027</link><description>Roselabs Finance Limited, the micro-cap non-banking financial company under the Lodha Group umbrella, reported a quarterly net loss of ₹0.04 crores for Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), marking a marginal improvement from the ₹0.06 crore loss in Q2 FY26. With a market capitalisation of just ₹27.00 crores and a deeply negative book value of ₹-4.73 per share, the company remains entrenched in severe financial distress despite sporadic revenue generation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f8ab3907d0c40b70ecbf3b67ed1bd349</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:26:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TBZ Q3 FY26: Jewellery Retailer Delivers Stunning 170% Profit Surge on Festive Demand</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/tbz-q3-fy26-jewellery-retailer-delivers-stunning-170-profit-surge-on-festive-demand-3797026</link><description>Tribhovandas Bhimji Zaveri Ltd. (TBZ), the Mumbai-based jewellery retailer with a 150-year legacy, has reported exceptional third-quarter results for FY2026, with net profit surging 169.85% year-on-year to ₹80.63 crores. The small-cap company, currently valued at ₹1,123 crores, has demonstrated remarkable operational improvement during the critical festive season, with operating margins expanding to 12.36% from 6.48% in the same quarter last year.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f416a14040c00d9596e4344d55fcf37b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:26:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DCM Shriram Q3 FY26: Strong Operational Rebound Despite Margin Pressures</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/dcm-shriram-q3-fy26-strong-operational-rebound-despite-margin-pressures-3797025</link><description>DCM Shriram Ltd., a diversified conglomerate with interests across chemicals, fertilisers, sugar, and textiles, reported a mixed Q3 FY26 performance with net profit declining 19.09% year-on-year to ₹212.11 crores despite robust revenue growth. The ₹17,572-crore market capitalisation company saw its stock trade at ₹1,113.65 on January 20, 2026, down 1.96% from the previous close, reflecting investor concerns over margin compression despite strong top-line momentum.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>bda7cb6cbeb98fe61947ab89d21db132</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:26:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Bansal Wire Industries Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-bansal-wire-industries-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3797023</link><description>Bansal Wire Industries Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show a net profit increase of 12.92% to ₹43.27 crore, but a 2.50% decline in net sales raises concerns about demand sustainability. While operating margins improved, rising interest costs and below-average return on equity indicate ongoing challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>971d8c534a54626c1e67dbb1fd470bdc</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:26:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Senores Pharmaceuticals Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-senores-pharmaceuticals-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3797022</link><description>Senores Pharmaceuticals Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth with net sales up 69.44% year-on-year, but profitability has slightly declined sequentially, and negative operating cash flow raises concerns about sustainability. Overall, the company demonstrates growth potential, though operational challenges remain.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>89586c02edcd6fe9f319ed60175dfeca</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:26:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Sai Silks (Kalamandir) Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-sai-silks-kalamandir-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3797021</link><description>Sai Silks (Kalamandir) Ltd's latest results show mixed performance, with a 7.44% decline in net sales to ₹411.25 crores and a net profit drop of 4.84% to ₹38.14 crores. However, improved operating margins indicate effective cost management, suggesting resilience despite ongoing revenue challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d7728ac6e5e3adf00725321d69435c79</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:26:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Cyient DLM Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-cyient-dlm-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3797020</link><description>Cyient DLM Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are mixed; while net profit increased 2.18% year-on-year to ₹11.23 crores, it fell 65.07% sequentially, and net sales dropped 31.71% year-on-year. The company faces ongoing revenue challenges despite improved cost management and a stronger balance sheet.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>bba4d52f356c93b6c320add8ceacf202</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:26:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Asian Warehousing Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-asian-warehousing-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3797019</link><description>Asian Warehousing Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results show modest growth in net sales and profit, but overall performance is concerning due to low revenue figures, declining stock value, and inefficiencies in capital utilization, indicating ongoing challenges in achieving sustainable growth.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9039126c66575c38389e9677f370d4bd</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:26:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Quicktouch Technologies Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-quicktouch-technologies-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3797018</link><description>Quicktouch Technologies Ltd's latest results are poor, showing a net loss of ₹3.48 crores and a dramatic revenue drop to ₹0.91 crores, indicating severe operational challenges and inefficiencies. The company's financial situation is critical, necessitating immediate corrective actions.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f128c243c80dcd79a71d04b0265ccd82</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:26:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are National Standard (India) Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-national-standard-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3797017</link><description>National Standard (India) Ltd's latest results show a significant increase in sales but reveal operational weaknesses, with an operating loss and heavy reliance on non-operating income, raising concerns about long-term viability. The company's stock has also declined significantly, underperforming the sector.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9a45c64621d064663581181676fb02a6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:26:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Ksolves India Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-ksolves-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3797016</link><description>Ksolves India Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show revenue growth of 12.20% year-on-year to ₹42.30 crores, but net profit declined 5.04% year-on-year to ₹9.80 crores, with significant margin pressures due to rising employee costs, indicating challenges in maintaining profitability despite strong sales.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>73753a1e4085339a1c9e694e6ab1c08e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:26:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Mega Nirman &amp; Industries Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-mega-nirman-industries-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3797015</link><description>Mega Nirman &amp; Industries Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth with net sales increasing by 36.40% sequentially, but the company still faces operational challenges with negative operating margins and reliance on non-recurring other income for profitability, raising concerns about long-term sustainability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>fc5a630759c762b8a6cafbee26dbaef6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:26:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are LTI Mindtree Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-lti-mindtree-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3797014</link><description>LTIMindtree Ltd's Q2 FY26 results are strong, with a 12% year-on-year net profit growth and a 10% revenue increase, alongside improved operating margins. However, the stock's high price-to-earnings ratio suggests elevated market expectations, warranting cautious consideration.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4b57c3639f1a1e3cd848d386d5da12bc</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:26:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Newgen Software Technologies Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-newgen-software-technologies-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3797013</link><description>Newgen Software Technologies Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show a 5.03% increase in net sales to ₹400.28 crores, but a significant 29.42% decline in net profit to ₹62.82 crores, raising concerns about profitability and operational sustainability despite strong operational metrics and a debt-free balance sheet. Investors should monitor the company's ability to stabilize margins and improve revenue growth moving forward.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>83aecb60c2a11e4b3eaf674ebbe82ee8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:26:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Aarti Surfactants Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-aarti-surfactants-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3797012</link><description>Aarti Surfactants Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results show mixed performance, with net sales up 18.78% year-on-year but down 17.01% sequentially, and a significant net profit decline of 46.94%, raising concerns about profitability and operational challenges despite some year-over-year improvements.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>eb414b2171eacbdf2152d250e4da7837</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:26:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are V R Films &amp; Studios Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-v-r-films-studios-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3797011</link><description>V R Films &amp; Studios Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show mixed signals: while net sales grew 44.76% sequentially and net profit increased 69.23% from the prior quarter, year-on-year growth is modest at 2.87%, and the company continues to face significant financial challenges, including negative return on equity and declining shareholder equity. Overall, there are signs of recovery, but persistent operational issues raise concerns about sustainability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>bcc5c334fbc77756a9b0e514d34ab0ed</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:26:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:26:18 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>