<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:29:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Yuranus Infrastructure Ltd Stock Hits All-Time High Amidst Remarkable Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/yuranus-infrastructure-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-high-amidst-remarkable-growth-3807685</link><description>Yuranus Infrastructure Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting an all-time high, reflecting its sustained strong performance in the construction sector. This achievement underscores the company’s impressive growth trajectory over multiple time horizons, outpacing key market benchmarks.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>be145a89971ac0afc700e4325d6fb97b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Data Patterns (India) Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.77% Surge on 28 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/data-patterns-india-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-777-surge-on-28-jan-2026-3807682</link><description>Data Patterns (India) Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 28 Jan 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 2,485, marking an 8.14% increase from its previous close. The stock outperformed its sector and the broader market, reflecting strong trading momentum within the Aerospace &amp; Defense industry.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>0a9e1f2ab5f5d3b439adc6cf7acfd657</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Britannia Industries Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/britannia-industries-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-3807683</link><description>Britannia Industries Ltd experienced a notable decline today, touching an intraday low of Rs 5,680, reflecting a 3.45% drop as the stock faced significant price pressure amid broader market dynamics and sector underperformance.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>0bd5a684a6bc1c44eb28aad9b7036244</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BN Agrochem Ltd Surges 12.72% in Strong Intraday Rally on 28 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bn-agrochem-ltd-surges-1272-in-strong-intraday-rally-on-28-jan-2026-3807681</link><description>BN Agrochem Ltd recorded a robust intraday rally on 28 Jan 2026, surging 12.72% to hit its day high amid a broadly positive market backdrop, despite recent short-term declines.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>b822e0241f79ba89acfae02590ede9a7</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shilchar Technologies Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.03% Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shilchar-technologies-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-703-surge-3807680</link><description>Shilchar Technologies Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 28 Jan 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 3,080, marking a 7.03% increase and outperforming its sector and the broader market indices.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>80822cba0a227309461fcce6b2cf9d22</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bosch Home Comfort India Ltd Hits Intraday High with 10% Surge on 28 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bosch-home-comfort-india-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-10-surge-on-28-jan-2026-3807684</link><description>Bosch Home Comfort India Ltd demonstrated a robust intraday performance on 28 Jan 2026, surging 10.0% to touch an intraday high of Rs 1393.05, marking a significant rebound after two consecutive days of decline.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>8a6466265d7b068a9c3863d9a2bf79f4</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Medi Assist Healthcare Services Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.399.15</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/medi-assist-healthcare-services-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs39915-3807678</link><description>Medi Assist Healthcare Services Ltd has declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.399.15, marking a significant downturn in its stock performance amid broader market gains. The stock’s recent slide reflects a series of financial and valuation pressures that have weighed on investor sentiment over the past year.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>e3551da8f693b376d773e6c41cfd15db</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Epigral Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/epigral-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3807675</link><description>Epigral Ltd, a player in the Specialty Chemicals sector, recorded a fresh 52-week low of Rs.1044.1 today, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing price decline. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting persistent pressures on its valuation and performance metrics.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>9c24d61326014782fa6c6393cc411427</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dhruv Consultancy Services Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.38.5</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dhruv-consultancy-services-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs385-3807679</link><description>Dhruv Consultancy Services Ltd’s stock touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.38.5 today, marking a significant decline amid continued underperformance relative to its sector and broader market indices. The stock has now fallen for two consecutive days, registering an 8.77% loss over this period, reflecting ongoing pressures on the company’s valuation and financial metrics.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>98d9f9c376ba6638e4fe7d93b4a86776</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meera Industries Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.84.9</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/meera-industries-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs849-3807677</link><description>Meera Industries Ltd, a key player in the Industrial Manufacturing sector, reached a significant milestone today by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.84.9. This marks a notable surge in the stock’s performance, reflecting strong momentum over recent sessions and outpacing sector benchmarks.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>3cfcdb1600ad8647207595d9905e3235</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Unipro Technologies Ltd Hits New 52-Week High of Rs.13.57</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/unipro-technologies-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-of-rs1357-3807673</link><description>Unipro Technologies Ltd achieved a significant milestone on 28 Jan 2026, reaching a new 52-week high of Rs.13.57. This marks a notable peak in the stock’s price trajectory, reflecting sustained momentum over the past several weeks.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>9dee4bf389deb89684cf4d628f0d1c54</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Zinc Ltd Hits New 52-Week High of Rs.732.6 on 28 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-zinc-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-of-rs7326-on-28-jan-2026-3807674</link><description>Hindustan Zinc Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.732.6 today, reflecting strong momentum in the non-ferrous metals sector amid broader market gains.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>7dbda7b040e287a93cc55a09dca26af9</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Galaxy Bearings Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.444 Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/galaxy-bearings-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs444-amid-continued-downtrend-3807672</link><description>Galaxy Bearings Ltd has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.444 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid ongoing underperformance relative to its sector and broader market indices.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>ae86932711690d97054df521a45a1fd5</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kati patang Lifestyle Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kati-patang-lifestyle-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3807670</link><description>Kati patang Lifestyle Ltd, a company in the Software Products sector, recorded a fresh 52-week low of Rs.15.8 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing concerns about its financial health and market positioning.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>6a396d29bf495da8961be2824e21e0f2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jindal Steel Ltd. Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.1106</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jindal-steel-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs1106-3807671</link><description>Jindal Steel Ltd. has reached a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs.1106, reflecting robust momentum in the ferrous metals sector. The stock’s recent gains underscore a notable rally supported by sustained buying interest and favourable market conditions.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>40e3e6e0fb7fb6f8f88fa86466921692</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cambridge Technology Enterprises Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.33.83</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cambridge-technology-enterprises-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs3383-3807676</link><description>Cambridge Technology Enterprises Ltd has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.33.83, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid ongoing market pressures and company-specific factors. This latest low reflects a continuation of the stock’s downward trajectory over recent sessions.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>127381e7996597066e6b105a1cf044bd</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vishal Mega Mart Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 28 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vishal-mega-mart-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-28-jan-2026-3807666</link><description>Shares of Vishal Mega Mart declined sharply on 28 Jan 2026, touching an intraday low of Rs 118.15, reflecting a significant price correction amid broader market dynamics and sector-specific pressures.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>5c59c523800981e4e08bf3b0d1d11c54</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cartrade Tech Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 28 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cartrade-tech-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-28-jan-2026-3807665</link><description>Cartrade Tech Ltd experienced a notable intraday decline on 28 Jan 2026, hitting its day low as selling pressure intensified despite outperforming its sector. The stock closed with a significant drop of 7.59%, reflecting immediate market pressures amid mixed technical signals and broader market dynamics.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>108a35b0e7fbbdea58fdc255f161fca1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Power Finance Corporation Hits Intraday High with 3.08% Surge on 28 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/power-finance-corporation-hits-intraday-high-with-308-surge-on-28-jan-2026-3807667</link><description>Power Finance Corporation (PFC) demonstrated robust intraday performance on 28 Jan 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 371.85, marking a 3.08% increase and outperforming its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>d1d41e8bf8ee455ab5b21635da15669b</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Karma Energy Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.37.95 Amidst Weak Financial Metrics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/karma-energy-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs3795-amidst-weak-financial-metrics-3807668</link><description>Karma Energy Ltd, a player in the power sector, recorded a new 52-week low of Rs.37.95 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid ongoing financial headwinds and underperformance relative to the broader market and sector benchmarks.
Time: 29 minutes ago</description><guid>5769cd06984c7d3485942051c9a832f2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:29:45 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>