<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:24:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Prakash Industries Gains 2.22%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/prakash-industries-gains-222-3-key-factors-driving-the-week-3863244</link><description>Prakash Industries Ltd closed the week ending 20 February 2026 with a 2.22% gain, outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% rise. Despite a challenging start marked by a sharp 3.67% drop on Monday, the stock rebounded strongly through the week, supported by stabilising quarterly results and mixed but improving technical signals. This review analyses the key events shaping the stock’s performance and the implications for investors navigating a volatile ferrous metals sector.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>beb60798989319ca3d648731b15e1d34</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aurobindo Pharma Gains 0.98%: 5 Key Factors Driving This Week’s Mixed Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aurobindo-pharma-gains-098-5-key-factors-driving-this-weeks-mixed-momentum-3863246</link><description>Aurobindo Pharma Ltd. closed the week ending 20 February 2026 with a modest gain of 0.98%, outperforming the Sensex’s 0.39% rise. The stock exhibited a volatile trading pattern marked by sharp swings in derivatives activity, technical momentum shifts, and notable put option volumes. Despite these fluctuations, the stock ended slightly higher at Rs.1,159.75 from Rs.1,148.50, reflecting a cautious but active market environment amid mixed signals from both spot and derivatives markets.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>0cb3ffca7079f9fad40ba20ca781d6b2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Brahmaputra Infrastructure Ltd Falls 1.95%: Key Events Behind the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/brahmaputra-infrastructure-ltd-falls-195-key-events-behind-the-weeks-volatility-3863245</link><description>Brahmaputra Infrastructure Ltd experienced a volatile week ending 20 February 2026, closing at Rs.160.80, down 1.95% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.164.00. This contrasted with the Sensex’s modest gain of 0.39% over the same period, indicating a relative underperformance. The week was marked by a significant milestone as the stock hit a new 52-week and all-time high intraday price of Rs.170.7 on 16 February, followed by a series of price fluctuations influenced by strong quarterly financial results and market sentiment shifts.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>bbdb06befdad524177ba772b049e4ade</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oil India Ltd Gains 4.43%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/oil-india-ltd-gains-443-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3863242</link><description>Oil India Ltd delivered a solid weekly performance, rising 4.43% from Rs.455.20 to Rs.475.35 between 16 and 20 February 2026, comfortably outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain over the same period. The stock demonstrated resilience amid mixed market conditions, buoyed by strong intraday rallies, a sharp surge in derivatives open interest, and robust institutional participation. These factors collectively underscore a week of notable momentum and technical strength for the mid-cap oil sector player.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>ce31da149e06fa83f9c7bcaadcb6d99e</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>NTPC Ltd Gains 2.78%: Technical Shift and New 52-Week High Drive Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ntpc-ltd-gains-278-technical-shift-and-new-52-week-high-drive-momentum-3863241</link><description>NTPC Ltd delivered a solid weekly performance, gaining 2.78% from Rs.362.95 on 13 February to Rs.373.05 on 20 February 2026, comfortably outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% rise over the same period. The week was marked by a technical upgrade to a 'Hold' rating and a fresh 52-week high, signalling renewed investor confidence despite mixed financial fundamentals.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>864bcf477b4dc84f6aa990f58e5e67cb</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Energy Development Company Ltd Falls 5.60%: 4 Key Factors Behind the Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/energy-development-company-ltd-falls-560-4-key-factors-behind-the-decline-3863243</link><description>Energy Development Company Ltd’s stock declined by 5.60% over the week ending 20 Feb 2026, closing at Rs.16.52 against a 0.39% gain in the Sensex. The stock hit multiple 52-week lows amid heavy selling pressure and technical weakness, reflecting persistent financial and operational challenges despite some recent profitability improvements.
Time: 53 minutes ago</description><guid>d36660080a39219212148cd2d99db9ab</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vaibhav Global Ltd Falls 7.20%: Downgrade and Technical Shift Shape Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vaibhav-global-ltd-falls-720-downgrade-and-technical-shift-shape-weekly-decline-3863240</link><description>Vaibhav Global Ltd experienced a challenging week on the bourses, with its stock price declining by 7.20% from Rs.252.85 to Rs.234.65 between 16 and 20 February 2026. This underperformance contrasted sharply with the Sensex, which gained 0.39% over the same period, underscoring the stock’s relative weakness amid a downgrade to a Sell rating and a shift in technical momentum. The week was marked by significant volatility and mixed signals from both fundamental and technical perspectives.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>95b217808c137ebba9ceb5b226880b84</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Siemens Ltd Gains 2.86%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/siemens-ltd-gains-286-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3863239</link><description>Siemens Ltd delivered a solid weekly performance, rising 2.86% from Rs.3,118.35 on 13 February to close at Rs.3,207.40 on 20 February 2026, comfortably outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain over the same period. The stock demonstrated notable intraday strength on multiple occasions, supported by robust derivatives activity and technical resilience, despite a cautious fundamental outlook reflected in its 'Sell' mojo rating.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>74ea894c2596f9287a75700fafce5868</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GTL Infrastructure Ltd Falls 9.30%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gtl-infrastructure-ltd-falls-930-5-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3863238</link><description>GTL Infrastructure Ltd experienced a turbulent week from 16 to 20 February 2026, with its stock price declining sharply by 9.30% to close at Rs.1.17, contrasting with the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain over the same period. Despite several days of exceptional trading volumes and intermittent price rallies, the stock’s overall trajectory was weighed down by persistent selling pressure and deteriorating technical indicators, reflecting ongoing challenges in the telecom equipment sector and company-specific headwinds.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>dc878b0334fda4dac68cf7fb54da5cf7</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Himadri Speciality Chemical Ltd Gains 8.91%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/himadri-speciality-chemical-ltd-gains-891-3-key-factors-driving-the-week-3863237</link><description>Himadri Speciality Chemical Ltd delivered a robust weekly gain of 8.91%, closing at Rs.490.05 on 20 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% rise over the same period. The stock’s performance was marked by notable volatility and mixed technical signals, including a bearish Death Cross formation and a subsequent downgrade to a Sell rating by MarketsMOJO. Despite these cautionary indicators, the share price showed resilience, buoyed by strong volume spikes and a late-week rally.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>9d6e05dce97ae5190bb97bfb3d335d70</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gala Global Products Ltd Falls 3.75% Amid All-Time Low and Persistent Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gala-global-products-ltd-falls-375-amid-all-time-low-and-persistent-downtrend-3863236</link><description>Gala Global Products Ltd’s shares declined by 3.75% over the week ending 20 Feb 2026, closing at Rs.1.54 from Rs.1.60 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain during the same period, reflecting ongoing financial challenges and a persistent downtrend that saw the stock hit fresh 52-week and all-time lows midweek.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>832a69a32dd56669932208d20f2f40ea</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dabur India Ltd Declines 0.49% Despite Technical Upgrade: 5 Key Market Signals This Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dabur-india-ltd-declines-049-despite-technical-upgrade-5-key-market-signals-this-week-3863235</link><description>Dabur India Ltd closed the week marginally lower by 0.49% at Rs.509.90, underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The stock experienced a mixed week marked by a significant upgrade to a Buy rating by MarketsMOJO, notable shifts in technical momentum, and heightened derivatives market activity. Despite short-term price volatility and some bearish signals, the company’s strong fundamentals and improving technical indicators suggest a cautiously optimistic outlook for this mid-cap FMCG player.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>1023bb7ec04f6feff1f300ef4be673d4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Garg Furnace Ltd Gains 15.70%: Key Drivers Behind the Strong Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/garg-furnace-ltd-gains-1570-key-drivers-behind-the-strong-weekly-rally-3863234</link><description>Garg Furnace Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, surging 15.70% from Rs.141.75 to Rs.164.00 between 16 and 20 February 2026, significantly outpacing the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain. The stock’s rally was propelled by a strong quarterly profit report and a notable valuation upgrade amid heightened investor interest, despite lingering sector headwinds and a cautious overall rating.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>6ab7572a523e51ea9c12a8b9f4b91163</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Axel Polymers Gains 1.65%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/axel-polymers-gains-165-2-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3863233</link><description>Axel Polymers Ltd closed the week with a modest gain of 1.65%, outperforming the Sensex’s 0.39% rise. The stock experienced notable volatility, including a sharp 7.06% drop midweek following a downgrade to Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, before recovering to close at Rs.45.68 on 20 February 2026. This review analyses the key events and market reactions shaping the stock’s performance over the week.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>7e97b0025f2ee66a6ccc702c831afff8</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jyoti Structures Ltd Gains 16.45%: 2 Key Drivers Behind the Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jyoti-structures-ltd-gains-1645-2-key-drivers-behind-the-surge-3863232</link><description>Jyoti Structures Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance from 16 to 20 February 2026, surging 16.45% from Rs.10.76 to Rs.12.53, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain over the same period. The stock’s rally was fuelled by robust intraday momentum midweek and exceptional trading volumes towards the week’s close, signalling renewed investor interest amid a mixed broader market backdrop.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>11db6db77ce768334ee3e7c3649065bf</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bloom Industries Ltd Declines 2.86% Amid Financial Struggles and Valuation Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bloom-industries-ltd-declines-286-amid-financial-struggles-and-valuation-shifts-3863231</link><description>Bloom Industries Ltd experienced a challenging week ending 20 Feb 2026, with its share price declining 2.86% from ₹35.00 to ₹34.00, underperforming the Sensex which rose 0.39% over the same period. The week was marked by a sharp financial downturn announcement on 17 Feb, followed by a contrasting valuation upgrade signalling renewed price attractiveness amid ongoing market volatility.
Time: 54 minutes ago</description><guid>3a655022ba615e609d34e6ec64d9cb57</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DCM Shriram Ltd. Falls 1.87%: Technical Weakness and Growth Concerns Weigh on Stock</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dcm-shriram-ltd-falls-187-technical-weakness-and-growth-concerns-weigh-on-stock-3863220</link><description>DCM Shriram Ltd. closed the week down 1.87% at Rs.1,092.80, underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The week was marked by a significant downgrade to a Sell rating amid technical weakness and growth concerns, alongside a clear shift to bearish momentum in the stock’s technical indicators. Despite a modest recovery on the final trading day, the overall sentiment remained cautious as the stock struggled to maintain upward momentum against a broadly positive market backdrop.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8ab65706c5b8059eccf72d2c3f0604bf</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bosch Ltd. Declines 1.40% Amid Technical Bearish Shift and Downgrade</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bosch-ltd-declines-140-amid-technical-bearish-shift-and-downgrade-3863225</link><description>Bosch Ltd. ended the week down 1.40% at Rs.35,214.30, underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The stock faced mounting technical headwinds amid flat financial results and a downgrade to a Sell rating by MarketsMOJO, signalling increasing caution among investors despite the company’s strong long-term fundamentals.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>6253246d304970dc421e3392b2586bc8</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Steel Strips Wheels Ltd Falls 0.92%: Mixed Technical Signals and Downgrade Shape Weekly Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/steel-strips-wheels-ltd-falls-092-mixed-technical-signals-and-downgrade-shape-weekly-trend-3863221</link><description>Steel Strips Wheels Ltd closed the week ending 20 February 2026 at ₹221.15, marking a decline of 0.92% from the previous Friday’s close of ₹223.20. This performance contrasted with the Sensex’s 0.39% gain over the same period, reflecting a week of mixed technical signals and cautious investor sentiment amid a downgrade to a Sell rating by MarketsMOJO. The stock’s price oscillated within a narrow range, influenced by shifts in momentum indicators and flat financial trends reported recently.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9adc3aa2f71025b2a433a94625f1993d</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:24:55 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>