<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:18:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Mangalam Worldwide Stock Hits All-Time High Amid Robust Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mangalam-worldwide-stock-hits-all-time-high-marking-a-significant-milestone-3770741</link><description>Mangalam Worldwide, a key player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, has reached an all-time high, marking a significant milestone in its market journey. The stock's recent performance reflects a strong trajectory supported by consistent gains across multiple time frames and a notable outperformance relative to broader market indices.
Time: 3 minutes ago</description><guid>9723eddabdd60ea1b5a04d49b1e0d243</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:18:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Craftsman Automation Stock Hits All-Time High Amid Robust Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/craftsman-automation-stock-hits-all-time-high-amid-robust-financial-performance-3770742</link><description>Craftsman Automation has reached a new all-time high, marking a significant milestone in its market journey. The stock’s recent performance reflects strong financial metrics and sustained growth, positioning it prominently within the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector.
Time: 3 minutes ago</description><guid>8b5321be832586bf553ca11643096d56</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:18:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Variman Global Enterprises Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.6.5 Amid Market Pressures</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/variman-global-enterprises-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3770740</link><description>Variman Global Enterprises has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.6.5, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid ongoing market volatility and sectoral pressures. This level reflects a continuation of the stock’s subdued performance relative to broader market indices and its sector peers.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>754e75f3fc9b39777a55e46a888be768</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:18:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JNK India Hits Intraday High with Strong Trading Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jnk-india-hits-intraday-high-with-871-surge-on-26-dec-2025-3770738</link><description>JNK India demonstrated robust intraday performance on 26 Dec 2025, touching a day’s high of Rs 248.6, reflecting a 9.35% rise during trading hours. This surge outpaced the broader industrial manufacturing sector and occurred amid a generally subdued market environment.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>34d66ee57e1b5d9aa4d9ddccaba8294a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:18:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Robust Hotels Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Market Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/robust-hotels-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3770739</link><description>Robust Hotels has reached a 52-week low, with its share price touching Rs 182.7, marking a significant decline amid broader market fluctuations and sectoral underperformance.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>72a4b70812a2b05554fa0529b79eb763</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:18:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>G M Breweries Hits Intraday High with Strong 7.4% Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/g-m-breweries-hits-intraday-high-with-707-surge-on-26-dec-2025-3770737</link><description>G M Breweries demonstrated robust intraday performance on 26 Dec 2025, reaching a day’s high of Rs 1,193.7, marking a 7.41% rise from its previous close. This surge outpaced the broader Beverages sector and the Sensex, reflecting notable trading momentum despite a subdued market backdrop.
Time: 26 minutes ago</description><guid>6987dd72210360f7d10797a6db63008c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:18:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dolphin Offshore Enterprises (India) Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dolphin-offshore-enterprises-india-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-3770736</link><description>Dolphin Offshore Enterprises (India) experienced a notable decline in intraday trading on 26 Dec 2025, touching a low of Rs 410, reflecting a price pressure that outpaced sector and benchmark indices. The stock’s performance today highlights immediate market pressures amid a broader cautious sentiment in the oil sector.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>4aece02744ec03b53169e46100ad7ff3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:18:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Diligent Media Corporation Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/diligent-media-corporation-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3770731</link><description>Diligent Media Corporation has reached a 52-week low, reflecting a sustained period of subdued performance in the Media &amp; Entertainment sector. The stock's recent trading levels highlight ongoing pressures amid broader market movements and company-specific financial indicators.
Time: 36 minutes ago</description><guid>34db1f014eb0855daed825626e787058</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:18:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jagjanani Textiles Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.5 Amidst Market Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jagjanani-textiles-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs5-amidst-weak-fundamentals-3770734</link><description>Jagjanani Textiles has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.5, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid broader market fluctuations and sectoral underperformance. The stock’s current position reflects ongoing challenges within the company’s financial and operational landscape.
Time: 36 minutes ago</description><guid>39b1156ba884f4f99e0c49028596b400</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:18:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Citadel Realty &amp; Developers Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.40.21</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/citadel-realty-developers-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3770732</link><description>Citadel Realty &amp; Developers has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.40.21, marking a significant decline in its share price amid broader market fluctuations and company-specific factors.
Time: 37 minutes ago</description><guid>1f2e5ec9c0a6e26a4ea7358b7d5aee02</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:18:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HFCL Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.62.6 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hfcl-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs626-amid-continued-downtrend-3770733</link><description>HFCL has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.62.6 today, marking a significant point in its ongoing price decline. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting a challenging period for the telecom equipment company.
Time: 37 minutes ago</description><guid>5583c9ec8b3e665a15c81e0d05cab127</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:18:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PB Fintech Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pb-fintech-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3770730</link><description>PB Fintech Ltd has experienced a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and evolving investor positioning. This development comes amid a backdrop of subdued price movement and sector-wide trends, prompting closer examination of volume patterns and potential directional bets.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>857f989b9a6ccc62dc1b130b408c51a3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:18:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FSN E-Commerce Ventures Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/fsn-e-commerce-ventures-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amidst-steady-price-gains-3770727</link><description>FSN E-Commerce Ventures Ltd, operating under the symbol NYKAA, has experienced a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and evolving investor positioning. This development coincides with the stock’s steady gains over recent sessions and reflects shifting dynamics in the e-retail sector.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>8543e57d836f1b90a7bc566ccbdb7e7e</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:18:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lodha Developers Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lodha-developers-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-momentum-3770728</link><description>Lodha Developers has experienced a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and evolving investor positioning. This development comes amid a backdrop of subdued price performance and declining investor participation, raising questions about potential directional bets and market sentiment towards the realty heavyweight.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>5da470ddb743e808b56eaf01f0c53a6d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:18:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kalyan Jewellers India Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kalyan-jewellers-india-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3770723</link><description>Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd has experienced a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, reflecting heightened market activity and evolving investor positioning. Despite this surge, the stock's price movement and volume patterns present a nuanced picture amid broader sector and market trends.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>c1eac72a617d6f6aed77d195283f8420</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:18:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Railway Catering &amp; Tourism Corporation Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/irctc-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-rising-market-momentum-3770729</link><description>Indian Railway Catering &amp; Tourism Corporation Ltd (IRCTC) has experienced a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and evolving investor positioning. This development coincides with a positive price movement and increased trading volumes, reflecting a shift in market dynamics for the tour and travel related services sector.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>94166d4a428ace2aa51ecafcf3b12855</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:18:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SBI Cards &amp; Payment Services Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Rising Market Activity</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sbi-cards-payment-services-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-market-positioning-3770725</link><description>SBI Cards &amp; Payment Services has experienced a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, reflecting heightened market participation and evolving investor positioning. This development coincides with the stock’s recent outperformance relative to its sector and broader indices, signalling increased attention from traders and investors alike.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>489504a6efbdae959ce013b5afaec284</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:18:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Dynamics Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Rising Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-dynamics-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-strong-derivatives-activity-3770724</link><description>Bharat Dynamics Ltd (BDL), a key player in the Aerospace &amp; Defense sector, has experienced a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, reflecting heightened market activity and evolving investor positioning. This development coincides with a sustained upward trend in the stock price and increased trading volumes, signalling a potential shift in market sentiment towards the company.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>052b4bfee8cc2c9806e9021ce03db1a6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:18:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tube Investments of India Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Market Activity</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tube-investments-of-india-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3770726</link><description>Tube Investments of India has registered a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, reflecting a shift in market positioning and investor sentiment. This development comes alongside a modest price gain and a divergence from sector and benchmark indices, signalling evolving dynamics in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>b2d796e6892caebceb5f1de1b75e250d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:18:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HDFC Life Insurance Company Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hdfc-life-insurance-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3770721</link><description>HDFC Life Insurance Company Ltd has experienced a significant rise in open interest within its derivatives segment, signalling a shift in market positioning and investor sentiment. This development comes amid a backdrop of subdued price movement and declining investor participation, raising questions about potential directional bets and underlying market dynamics.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>343ded8565567d310dbc0ef088147c48</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:18:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:18:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>