<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:16:21 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Sai Life Sciences Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sai-life-sciences-ltd-fallingrising-3782434</link><description>On 05-Jan, Sai Life Sciences Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 3.76% to ₹954.65 by 09:22 PM, reaching a fresh 52-week and all-time high of ₹966.1. This upward momentum reflects a combination of robust financial performance, strong institutional backing, and positive market sentiment.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>6176c456e38e6be0c495de07926c0602</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:16:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is National Peroxide Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-national-peroxide-ltd-fallingrising-3782433</link><description>On 05-Jan, National Peroxide Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, falling by 4.94% to close at ₹446.70. This drop comes after a period of four consecutive days of gains and marks a new 52-week and all-time low of ₹441.1, reflecting ongoing challenges faced by the company both in the short and long term.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>1fe02e8f9bb1e66fbe8fdf785ef6f26d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:16:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Diensten Tech Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-diensten-tech-ltd-fallingrising-3782432</link><description>On 05-Jan, Diensten Tech Ltd's shares fell sharply by 4.11% to close at ₹140.00, continuing a downward trend driven by weak financial fundamentals, poor long-term growth, and underwhelming market performance relative to benchmarks.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>4cc08e80fbdcb00df6cb6b36f5ee10f2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:16:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Divine Power Energy Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-divine-power-energy-ltd-fallingrising-3782431</link><description>On 05-Jan, Divine Power Energy Ltd’s stock price rose sharply by 5.0%, closing at ₹285.70, reflecting robust investor interest and significant outperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>18e1eef38202a56af7149999b8d373de</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:16:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Quest Laboratories Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-quest-laboratories-ltd-fallingrising-3782430</link><description>As of 05-Jan, Quest Laboratories Ltd’s stock price has fallen by 4.13% to ₹104.50, reflecting a complex interplay of strong operational metrics and recent disappointing quarterly results that have weighed on investor sentiment.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>cf331deeef0af07c85f53c1aa4998790</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:16:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Rashi Peripherals Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-rashi-peripherals-ltd-fallingrising-3782429</link><description>On 05-Jan, Rashi Peripherals Ltd witnessed a significant price increase of 6.56%, closing at ₹381.55, driven by robust quarterly performance and heightened investor participation.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>09d60fd24f1e02f8a1fb8ee7701ac40f</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:16:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Italian Edibles Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-italian-edibles-ltd-fallingrising-3782428</link><description>On 05-Jan, Italian Edibles Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 3.28% to ₹29.95 by 09:18 PM, outperforming its sector and the broader market despite a challenging longer-term performance record.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>c620173643191e322e2f522f5db793ec</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:16:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Enser Communications Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-enser-communications-ltd-fallingrising-3782427</link><description>On 05-Jan, Enser Communications Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 7.08% to close at ₹15.75. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s underperformance relative to key market benchmarks and sector peers, driven by subdued investor participation and technical weaknesses.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>218b4e03d1b16e1657e811e7edace974</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:16:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Muthoot Microfin Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-muthoot-microfin-ltd-fallingrising-3782426</link><description>On 05-Jan, Muthoot Microfin Ltd witnessed a significant rise in its share price, climbing 6.83% to ₹189.15 by 09:18 PM. This upward movement reflects a combination of robust financial performance, positive market sentiment, and increased investor participation.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>1979f1e9727a2fb5dce4d637217853af</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:16:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Amic Forging Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-amic-forging-ltd-fallingrising-3782425</link><description>On 05-Jan, Amic Forging Ltd’s stock price fell sharply by 3.36% to close at ₹1,446.70, continuing a recent downward trend that has seen the share price underperform both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>612977730f4908850383a4861aceecb5</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:16:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Fedbank Financial Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-fedbank-financial-services-ltd-fallingrising-3782424</link><description>On 05-Jan, Fedbank Financial Services Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 2.61% to ₹165.20 as of 09:17 PM. This upward momentum reflects a combination of robust long-term fundamentals, impressive recent performance, and strong investor interest, positioning the stock well ahead of its benchmark indices.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>99bef06b4679e8be585e23fda01364e5</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:16:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Marco Cables &amp; Conductors Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-marco-cables-conductors-ltd-fallingrising-3782423</link><description>On 05-Jan, Marco Cables &amp; Conductors Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 4.0% to close at ₹37.20. This downturn reflects a continuation of the stock's underperformance relative to key market benchmarks and sector peers, underscoring persistent challenges faced by the company in recent periods.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>1451510d66e27eabc14de45cb7849acf</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:16:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shradha AI Technologies Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shradha-ai-technologies-ltd-fallingrising-3782422</link><description>On 05-Jan, Shradha AI Technologies Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹30.90, down by ₹1.60 or 4.92%. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s underperformance relative to market benchmarks and sector peers despite some encouraging financial metrics.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>b77a219fd025d8cb6bd0fe27debfa100</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:16:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Samhi Hotels Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-samhi-hotels-ltd-fallingrising-3782421</link><description>On 05-Jan, Samhi Hotels Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 3.22% to close at Rs 190.85. This upward movement reflects a combination of strong recent performance metrics and growing investor participation, despite some underlying concerns about management efficiency and debt servicing capacity.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>c8e04834c5af947523331324d66f4150</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:16:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Yudiz Solutions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-yudiz-solutions-ltd-fallingrising-3782420</link><description>On 05-Jan, Yudiz Solutions Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹25.70, down by ₹1.20 or 4.46%. This drop marks a continuation of a significant downward trend that has persisted over the past year, reflecting ongoing challenges for the company’s stock relative to broader market benchmarks.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>04f92ee5b75eec966630ae5e12949762</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:16:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Proventus Agrocom Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-proventus-agrocom-ltd-fallingrising-3782419</link><description>On 05-Jan, Proventus Agrocom Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 7.53% to close at ₹1,290.00. This drop reflects a broader pattern of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and waning investor interest.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>0ab3fa78b4abbcf63540380f6ac7885a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:16:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Senco Gold Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-senco-gold-ltd-fallingrising-3782418</link><description>On 05-Jan, Senco Gold Ltd’s stock price rose by 1.92% to ₹329.70, continuing a three-day gaining streak that has seen the share appreciate by 3.63%. This upward momentum outpaced both its sector and the broader Sensex benchmark, reflecting growing investor confidence despite the stock’s significant decline over the past year.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>6bcf093fda2236ee21bf48060ea06e35</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:16:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is AWL Agri Business Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-awl-agri-business-ltd-fallingrising-3782417</link><description>As of 05-Jan, AWL Agri Business Ltd’s stock price has fallen by 1.91% to ₹233.85, continuing a downward trend influenced by disappointing quarterly earnings, reduced promoter confidence, and persistent underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>06acc6db48e664de23661ad23f681aaa</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:16:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Mega Flex Plastics Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-mega-flex-plastics-ltd-fallingrising-3782416</link><description>On 05-Jan, Mega Flex Plastics Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 4.76% to close at ₹121.15. This drop contrasts with the broader market's modest gains and reflects a combination of short-term technical pressures and waning investor engagement.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>9fde5340096739a6cddedeaefffe9a95</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:16:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Aditya Birla Sun Life AMC Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-aditya-birla-sun-life-amc-ltd-fallingrising-3782415</link><description>On 05-Jan, Aditya Birla Sun Life AMC Ltd's stock price rose by 2.39% to ₹852.80, reflecting robust market performance and solid underlying fundamentals that have supported investor confidence despite some decline in trading volumes.
Time: 18 minutes ago</description><guid>4408f1d562a6ef2abefa58cbf23b394b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:16:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 21:16:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>