<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:58:24 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Veljan Denison Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/veljan-denison-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3833293</link><description>Veljan Denison Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has recently formed a Death Cross—a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average—indicating a potential shift towards a bearish trend and signalling deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum.
Time: 7 minutes ago</description><guid>99dfa61bad85d64b20c37da183f9d8fd</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:58:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Le Travenues Technology Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/le-travenues-technology-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3833276</link><description>Le Travenues Technology Ltd, a key player in the Tour and Travel Related Services sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>9e7c7c8796302038f63f065bc74adefa</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:58:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BLS E-Services Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bls-e-services-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3833278</link><description>BLS E-Services Ltd, a player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>279f1029561f23d3a317831d46a25b34</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:58:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hitachi Energy India Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hitachi-energy-india-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3833275</link><description>Hitachi Energy India Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development suggests a deterioration in the stock’s short-term momentum relative to its long-term trend, raising concerns about sustained weakness despite the company’s strong historical performance.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>9aef1d5d6d05fc89981f15f8422edeaf</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:58:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Latteys Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/latteys-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3833277</link><description>Latteys Industries Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development highlights a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raises concerns about its medium to long-term outlook amid already subdued fundamentals and weak price performance.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>a2a660e43df65ce0bf18fff0bbef23b2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:58:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tamil Nadu Petro Products Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tamil-nadu-petro-products-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3833268</link><description>Tamil Nadu Petro Products Ltd (Stock ID: 990473) has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium-term momentum and raising concerns about its long-term strength within the petrochemicals sector.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>07cf62fd754ea6f793f76e324a151432</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:58:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gennex Laboratories Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gennex-laboratories-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3833273</link><description>Gennex Laboratories Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about sustained weakness in the near to medium term.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>f29c615d41ca07e115010fbc16c34391</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:58:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Noida Toll Bridge Company Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/noida-toll-bridge-company-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3833267</link><description>Noida Toll Bridge Company Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a sustained bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>a2d2aad47c487f49ffeff039edd091c2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:58:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tuni Textile Mills Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tuni-textile-mills-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3833274</link><description>Tuni Textile Mills Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about its medium to long-term outlook amid already challenging fundamentals and market performance.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>092848546d15ac94021b78f7f93bf752</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:58:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>California Software Company Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/california-software-company-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3833270</link><description>California Software Company Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>191c60b425cb536a1a0e7a11e97fa328</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:58:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aastamangalam Finance Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aastamangalam-finance-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3833269</link><description>Aastamangalam Finance Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical pattern where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>910f4fdc8ef8979663d64ceb1cb89c24</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:58:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Filmcity Media Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Indicating Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/filmcity-media-ltd-forms-golden-cross-indicating-potential-bullish-breakout-3833272</link><description>Filmcity Media Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, attracting the attention of investors and market analysts alike.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>3d892b40eb545b5e4bbe7198cd85ff43</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:58:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>UltraTech Cement Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ultratech-cement-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3833266</link><description>UltraTech Cement Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development is widely regarded as a bullish signal, suggesting a potential trend reversal and a shift towards long-term upward momentum for the stock.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>d10b719f204dc54c0f20cbe68c48ec17</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:58:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Baid Finserv Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/baid-finserv-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3833271</link><description>Baid Finserv Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross—a significant technical event where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, attracting investor attention despite the stock’s mixed recent performance and a current Mojo Grade of Sell.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>7b89d458f907393f123494b6cb59fed3</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:58:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec 2025 Results Reveal Mixed Market Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-reveal-mixed-market-momentum-3833265</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has unfolded with a mixed bag of results across 2315 companies, reflecting a cautious yet gradually improving corporate performance landscape. While the proportion of companies reporting positive results has inched up to 47.0%, sectoral and market-capitalisation-wise disparities remain evident, underscoring the uneven recovery and growth trajectories across the Indian equity market.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>698418ec2c65f9604ca978859a815a7f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:58:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Super Spinning Mills Q3 FY26: Profit Surge Masks Underlying Structural Weaknesses</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/super-spinning-mills-q3-fy26-profit-surge-masks-underlying-structural-weaknesses-3833292</link><description>Super Spinning Mills Ltd., a micro-cap textile manufacturer with a market capitalisation of ₹45.00 crores, reported a striking 132% quarter-on-quarter surge in net profit to ₹1.16 crores for Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), yet the company's shares continued their downward trajectory, declining 2.0% to ₹7.84 following the announcement. The quarterly profit jump, whilst impressive on the surface, comes against a backdrop of stagnant revenue growth and deteriorating long-term fundamentals that have left investors increasingly sceptical about the sustainability of this performance.
Time: 42 minutes ago</description><guid>83216ad51dea3dd6d0d610e0fd7eaa86</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:58:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>B.L.Kashyap Q3 FY26: Profit Surge Masks Underlying Weakness in Construction Major</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/blkashyap-q3-fy26-profit-surge-masks-underlying-weakness-in-construction-major-3833291</link><description>B.L.Kashyap &amp; Sons Ltd., a civil construction and EPC contracting company, reported a sharp turnaround in Q3 FY26 with net profit of ₹11.83 crores, marking a dramatic recovery from the previous quarter's loss of ₹8.62 crores. However, the stock tumbled 6.33% to ₹54.12 on February 11, 2026, as investors looked beyond the headline numbers to concerning trends in revenue momentum and margin sustainability. With a market capitalisation of ₹1,275 crores, the micro-cap construction firm faces mounting scrutiny over its ability to sustain profitability amid operational challenges and elevated debt levels.
Time: 42 minutes ago</description><guid>4f5e48527f6e126babbedd75123a46f9</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:58:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Emami Realty Q3 FY26: Mounting Losses Deepen as Revenue Collapses 91%</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/emami-realty-q3-fy26-mounting-losses-deepen-as-revenue-collapses-91-3833290</link><description>Emami Realty Ltd., the Kolkata-headquartered real estate developer, reported deeply troubling third-quarter results for FY2026, with net losses widening to ₹37.28 crores and revenue plummeting 91.45% year-on-year to just ₹4.89 crores. The micro-cap company, valued at ₹346.00 crores, continues to struggle with operational challenges that have now persisted across multiple quarters, raising serious questions about its business model sustainability.
Time: 42 minutes ago</description><guid>6c119680f174d913da2255522e3fd92c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:58:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kairosoft AI Solutions Q3 FY26: Operational Turnaround Overshadowed by Structural Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/kairosoft-ai-solutions-q3-fy26-operational-turnaround-overshadowed-by-structural-concerns-3833288</link><description>Kairosoft AI Solutions Ltd., a micro-cap player in the auto components and equipments sector, reported a net profit of ₹0.75 crores for Q3 FY26 (October-December 2025), marking a sequential improvement of 7.14% from Q2 FY26's ₹0.70 crores. However, the company's shares remain under severe pressure, trading at ₹51.15 with a market capitalisation of just ₹6.00 crores—down 78.99% over the past year and 84.49% below its 52-week high of ₹329.75.
Time: 42 minutes ago</description><guid>5a5cedb4967a79790a18c208a6836e85</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:58:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Asian Star Company Q3 FY26: Margin Pressures Mount Amid Demand Slowdown</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/asian-star-company-q3-fy26-margin-pressures-mount-amid-demand-slowdown-3833286</link><description>Asian Star Company Ltd., one of India's established diamantaires engaged in diamond cutting, polishing, and jewellery manufacturing, reported a challenging third quarter for FY2026, with consolidated net profit declining 18.70% year-on-year to ₹9.78 crores. The micro-cap company, with a market capitalisation of ₹1,013 crores, saw its stock trading at ₹640.50 on February 11, 2026, reflecting a modest 1.18% gain for the day but remaining 26.38% below its 52-week high of ₹870.
Time: 42 minutes ago</description><guid>286a838fa488bee2622a9a3ac74db4bc</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:58:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:58:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>