<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:34:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Tejas Networks Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.19% Surge on 30 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tejas-networks-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-719-surge-on-30-jan-2026-3811626</link><description>Tejas Networks Ltd demonstrated robust intraday strength on 30 Jan 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 351.55, marking a 7.84% increase from its previous close. This performance notably outpaced the broader Telecom - Equipment &amp; Accessories sector and the Sensex, underscoring significant trading momentum amid a volatile market backdrop.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>49b1b7d96464f882f3196b68725d1ad1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:34:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Multi Commodity Exchange of India Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/multi-commodity-exchange-of-india-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-3811625</link><description>Multi Commodity Exchange of India Ltd (MCX) experienced a notable intraday decline on 30 Jan 2026, touching a low of Rs 2,542.5, reflecting a 5.5% drop from previous levels. This downturn occurred despite the stock’s strong longer-term performance and prevailing positive moving average trends, signalling immediate pressures impacting its intraday trading session.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>57e65846c84c8a955768cab0f4a342a8</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:34:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ambuja Cements Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 30 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ambuja-cements-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-30-jan-2026-3811627</link><description>Ambuja Cements Ltd experienced a notable intraday decline on 30 Jan 2026, touching a low of Rs 511.5, reflecting a 4.57% drop from its previous close. The stock underperformed its sector and broader market indices, weighed down by prevailing market pressures and a reversal in its recent upward trend.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>432c983d0a7fa200b158eedab20de288</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:34:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KDDL Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.82% Surge on 30 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kddl-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-782-surge-on-30-jan-2026-3811624</link><description>KDDL Ltd demonstrated a strong intraday performance on 30 Jan 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 2,312, marking an 8.62% increase from its previous close. The stock outpaced its sector and broader market indices, reflecting notable trading momentum amid a mixed market backdrop.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>bbe23c0b767c32dfbee60e5726fb929f</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:34:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dolphin Offshore Enterprises (India) Ltd Hits Intraday High with 8.95% Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dolphin-offshore-enterprises-india-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-895-surge-3811628</link><description>Dolphin Offshore Enterprises (India) Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 30 Jan 2026, surging 8.95% to touch a day’s high of Rs 450, significantly outperforming the broader Sensex which declined by 0.41% during the session.
Time: 17 minutes ago</description><guid>286ba751be8e8a34a2c80f1815c71dfb</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:34:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pearl Polymers Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pearl-polymers-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3811623</link><description>Pearl Polymers Ltd has reached a fresh 52-week low, closing near Rs 18.3, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid ongoing pressures. The stock’s recent performance highlights persistent challenges within the company’s financial and market metrics, reflecting a broader trend of underperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 23 minutes ago</description><guid>baefcc9313c8e472b3d0fe8f0dc82d35</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:34:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Saptak Chem &amp; Business Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.45.92</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/saptak-chem-business-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs4592-3811622</link><description>Saptak Chem &amp; Business Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.45.92 today, marking a continuation of its strong upward momentum in the Trading &amp; Distributors sector.
Time: 27 minutes ago</description><guid>c6e3954f917d1d00844b773de5fe5366</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:34:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aruna Hotels Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.6.42</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aruna-hotels-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs642-3811620</link><description>Aruna Hotels Ltd touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.6.42 on 30 Jan 2026, marking a significant decline in its share price amid ongoing challenges in the Hotels &amp; Resorts sector. The stock’s performance continues to lag behind key benchmarks, reflecting persistent pressures on the company’s valuation and market sentiment.
Time: 28 minutes ago</description><guid>770074b0c9de0c578091e75a21d3656a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:34:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elcid Investments Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.114000 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/elcid-investments-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs114000-amidst-continued-downtrend-3811621</link><description>Elcid Investments Ltd has touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.114000 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trajectory over recent sessions. The stock’s performance contrasts sharply with broader market trends, reflecting ongoing concerns about its financial metrics and valuation.
Time: 29 minutes ago</description><guid>bce2c2eda09e35e65914528225301d8a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:34:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lakshmi Electrical Control Systems Q3 FY26: Profitability Collapse Raises Serious Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/lakshmi-electrical-control-systems-q3-fy26-profitability-collapse-raises-serious-concerns-3811630</link><description>Lakshmi Electrical Control Systems Limited (LECSL), a Coimbatore-based manufacturer of control panels and plastic components, reported deeply troubling Q3 FY26 results that have sent alarm bells ringing among investors. The company plunged into a net loss of ₹1.05 crores for the quarter ended December 2025, marking a dramatic reversal from the ₹0.48 crores profit reported in Q2 FY26 and a stark 892.30% collapse compared to the ₹0.13 crores profit in Q3 FY25. The stock reacted sharply, declining 5.53% to close at ₹756.50 on January 30, 2026, as the micro-cap company's market capitalisation stood at ₹185.95 crores.
Time: 31 minutes ago</description><guid>749c0de1dfd871ddcd882ab45f423888</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:34:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ideaforge Technology Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.84% Surge on 30 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ideaforge-technology-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-784-surge-on-30-jan-2026-3811618</link><description>Ideaforge Technology Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 30 Jan 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 459.6, marking a 7.37% increase from its previous close. This strong upward movement outpaced the broader Aerospace &amp; Defense sector and the benchmark Sensex, reflecting notable trading momentum amid a volatile market session.
Time: 31 minutes ago</description><guid>499ee59b468ab45dd70668b4919e3bd2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:34:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Saptak Chem &amp; Business Ltd Hits All-Time High at Rs.45.92</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/saptak-chem-business-ltd-hits-all-time-high-at-rs4592-3811619</link><description>Saptak Chem &amp; Business Ltd has reached an all-time high of Rs.45.92 today, underscoring a remarkable rally that has propelled the stock to new heights within the Trading &amp; Distributors sector. This milestone reflects sustained strong performance and significant gains over multiple timeframes, positioning the company prominently in the market landscape.
Time: 31 minutes ago</description><guid>6667822123c476638492b7d497597117</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:34:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Arvind Ltd Q3 FY26: Margin Expansion Drives Steady Performance Despite Volume Pressures</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/arvind-ltd-q3-fy26-margin-expansion-drives-steady-performance-despite-volume-pressures-3811629</link><description>Arvind Ltd., one of India's leading vertically integrated textile manufacturers with nearly eight decades of industry presence, delivered a stable performance in Q3 FY26 with consolidated net profit of ₹97.59 crores, registering a marginal decline of 5.62% quarter-on-quarter but down 5.64% year-on-year. The ₹7,951 crore market capitalisation company, which operates across denim, shirting, knits and garments, demonstrated operational resilience through margin expansion even as revenue growth remained muted. The stock rallied 4.62% following the results announcement, closing at ₹311.30 on January 30, 2026, as investors responded positively to the improved profitability metrics.
Time: 32 minutes ago</description><guid>4483f7425eca1a40beac683a032b81c1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:34:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Toyam Sports Ltd Stock Hits All-Time Low Amid Continued Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/toyam-sports-ltd-stock-hits-all-time-low-amid-continued-decline-3811617</link><description>Toyam Sports Ltd, a Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC), has reached a new all-time low price of Rs.0.88, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock’s performance continues to lag behind both its sector and the broader market, reflecting persistent difficulties in its financial and operational metrics.
Time: 36 minutes ago</description><guid>b296306c5efd56f9f574b62751f335c3</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:34:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shree Tirupati Balajee Agro Trading Co. Ltd Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shree-tirupati-balajee-agro-trading-co-ltd-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3811616</link><description>Shree Tirupati Balajee Agro Trading Co. Ltd, a player in the packaging sector, has recorded a new 52-week and all-time low price of Rs.32.48 as of 30 Jan 2026, marking a significant decline in its stock value amid broader market fluctuations.
Time: 44 minutes ago</description><guid>1d0fce76d5c562b00b0d48d6e32b9075</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:34:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Unipro Technologies Ltd Hits New 52-Week High of Rs.14.11</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/unipro-technologies-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-of-rs1411-3811615</link><description>Unipro Technologies Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.14.11 today, marking a notable surge in its stock price and reflecting sustained momentum over the past month.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>cd2057dcf1b82d2f32dcc64cb13b1db1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:34:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>G R Infraprojects Ltd Hits Intraday High with 9.11% Surge on 30 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/g-r-infraprojects-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-911-surge-on-30-jan-2026-3811610</link><description>G R Infraprojects Ltd recorded a robust intraday performance on 30 Jan 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 982, marking a 9.11% increase. This strong upward movement outpaced the broader construction sector and the Sensex, reflecting notable trading momentum in the stock.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>70187c59b9efacc42f3e46ea9ce06bc2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:34:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thinkink Picturez Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.0.19 Amidst Weak Financial Metrics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/thinkink-picturez-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs019-amidst-weak-financial-metrics-3811606</link><description>Shares of Thinkink Picturez Ltd, a company operating in the Media &amp; Entertainment sector, touched a new 52-week low of Rs.0.19 today, marking a significant decline from its 52-week high of Rs.0.46. This drop reflects ongoing pressures on the stock amid subdued financial performance and valuation concerns.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>d3dce99efdfaef7232324c5313369a21</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:34:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Yarn Syndicate Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.11.23 Amidst Weak Financials</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/yarn-syndicate-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs1123-amidst-weak-financials-3811608</link><description>Yarn Syndicate Ltd’s stock touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.11.23 today, marking a significant decline amid ongoing financial pressures and subdued market sentiment. This new low reflects a sharp downturn from its 52-week high of Rs.44.80, underscoring the challenges faced by the company over the past year.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>9684504d05bb933576e0d80a43864c58</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:34:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Virat Crane Industries Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/virat-crane-industries-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3811613</link><description>Virat Crane Industries Ltd, a player in the FMCG sector, has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.30.15 today, marking a significant decline amid a challenging market environment. The stock’s recent performance reflects ongoing pressures, with a notable underperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>3938e6bad0e317d40e1a057ba250797b</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:34:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:34:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>