<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:24:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Power Finance Corporation Ltd Gains 2.31%: Valuation and Technical Shifts Drive Market Interest</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/power-finance-corporation-ltd-gains-231-valuation-and-technical-shifts-drive-market-interest-3849698</link><description>Power Finance Corporation Ltd (PFC) recorded a 2.31% gain over the week ending 20 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex which rose 0.39% in the same period. The stock showed strong early-week momentum with consecutive daily gains before retreating midweek amid mixed technical signals and valuation shifts. This review analyses the key events and market dynamics that shaped PFC’s price action during the week.
Time: 47 minutes ago</description><guid>6b01949966f836e0b5efdfd4269341d6</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:24:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Repco Home Finance Declines 3.61%: Technical Shifts and Mixed Financial Signals Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/repco-home-finance-declines-361-technical-shifts-and-mixed-financial-signals-shape-the-week-3849697</link><description>Repco Home Finance Ltd’s stock declined by 3.61% over the week ending 20 February 2026, closing at ₹390.10 from ₹404.70, while the Sensex gained 0.39% in the same period. The week was marked by a technical downgrade early on, a brief recovery in momentum midweek, and a subsequent upgrade to Hold on improved technicals and valuation. These developments, combined with mixed financial signals and fluctuating market sentiment, shaped the stock’s volatile performance.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>b7329461d6080098135374f22a67d44c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:24:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Patanjali Foods Gains 2.54%: 4 Key Factors Driving This Week’s Mixed Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/patanjali-foods-gains-254-4-key-factors-driving-this-weeks-mixed-momentum-3849696</link><description>Patanjali Foods Ltd recorded a modest weekly gain of 2.54%, closing at Rs.535.55 on 20 Feb 2026, outperforming the Sensex’s 0.39% rise over the same period. The week was marked by a downgrade to a Sell rating amid technical weakness and valuation concerns, fluctuating technical momentum, and a sharp surge in derivatives open interest. Despite strong quarterly financials, the stock faced mixed market signals, reflecting cautious investor sentiment and heightened volatility potential.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>b8f126ad9ba53c66bafc554db34c2689</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:24:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Finserv Gains 1.67%: 5 Key Factors Driving This Week’s Market Moves</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-finserv-gains-167-5-key-factors-driving-this-weeks-market-moves-3849694</link><description>Bajaj Finserv Ltd closed the week ending 20 February 2026 with a 1.67% gain, outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% rise. The stock demonstrated resilience amid mixed technical signals and heightened derivatives market activity, reflecting a complex interplay of investor sentiment and positioning. Key events this week included significant open interest surges, a rating upgrade by MarketsMOJO, and shifts in technical momentum that collectively shaped the stock’s performance trajectory.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>a95146a8c32a5d2bcfc15fb6d293126a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:24:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MM Forgings Gains 2.04%: Key Drivers Behind the Weekly Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mm-forgings-gains-204-key-drivers-behind-the-weekly-momentum-3849690</link><description>MM Forgings Ltd delivered a modest weekly gain of 2.04%, outperforming the Sensex’s 0.39% rise during 16 to 20 February 2026. The stock rebounded strongly after an initial sharp decline on Monday, buoyed by a rating upgrade and a new 52-week high midweek, reflecting mixed but generally positive investor sentiment amid volatile market conditions.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>34e2a2393262f1dfd49889293f33836b</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:24:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SRF Ltd Falls 5.13%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Bearish Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/srf-ltd-falls-513-5-key-factors-driving-the-bearish-momentum-3849695</link><description>SRF Ltd experienced a challenging week, closing down 5.13% to Rs.2,687.95, underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39%. The stock faced a downgrade to a Sell rating amid technical weakness and valuation concerns, accompanied by heavy put option activity and a sharp surge in open interest. These developments reflect a cautious market sentiment and heightened bearish positioning as the stock navigated volatile trading sessions from 16 to 20 February 2026.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>c2e7a3d9eec0bebb9a12a5dccb266ad1</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:24:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank Of Baroda Gains 7.50%: 5 Key Factors Driving This Week’s Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bank-of-baroda-gains-750-5-key-factors-driving-this-weeks-rally-3849689</link><description>Bank Of Baroda delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 7.50% from ₹287.40 to ₹308.95 between 16 and 20 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain over the same period. The stock’s rally was supported by a series of positive technical shifts, a mojo grade upgrade, and increased market positioning, underscoring renewed investor confidence in this public sector banking stalwart.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>a4d5b1fc55b2ebdfcd25e406a0e93ceb</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:24:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thomas Scott India Ltd Gains 0.13%: Quality Upgrade and Mixed Technicals Shape Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/thomas-scott-india-ltd-gains-013-quality-upgrade-and-mixed-technicals-shape-week-3849693</link><description>Thomas Scott India Ltd closed the week marginally higher by 0.13%, ending at Rs.319.40 on 20 February 2026, despite a volatile trading session marked by mixed price movements and a broader Sensex gain of 0.39%. The week saw a notable quality upgrade for the company, reflecting improved business fundamentals, while technical indicators suggested caution amid short-term bearish trends. The stock’s performance diverged from the Sensex on several days, highlighting investor focus on company-specific developments amid a fluctuating market backdrop.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>1c0eb763ebcd65b0a9c82d4aea6a8dd4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:24:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>La Opala RG Ltd Gains 1.36%: 3 Key Technical Shifts Shape Weekly Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/la-opala-rg-ltd-gains-136-3-key-technical-shifts-shape-weekly-performance-3849692</link><description>La Opala RG Ltd closed the week with a modest gain of 1.36%, outperforming the Sensex’s 0.39% rise between 16 and 20 February 2026. The stock’s journey was marked by a sharp initial decline, followed by a steady recovery driven by mixed technical signals and resilient quarterly results. Despite the positive weekly close at Rs.201.15, the stock’s technical outlook remains cautious amid ongoing volatility and sector challenges.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>59580b0455a466fadbe014a1bfaa8c00</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:24:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Elecon Engineering Falls 2.50%: Valuation Shift and Mixed Financials Shape Weekly Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/elecon-engineering-falls-250-valuation-shift-and-mixed-financials-shape-weekly-trend-3849691</link><description>Elecon Engineering Company Ltd experienced a challenging week on the bourses, with its share price declining by 2.50% from Rs.434.45 to Rs.423.60 between 16 and 20 February 2026. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s modest gain of 0.39% over the same period, reflecting mixed investor sentiment amid valuation improvements and disappointing quarterly financial results. The week was marked by a cautious upgrade in the stock’s rating to 'Sell' from 'Strong Sell' by MarketsMOJO, driven primarily by a moderation in valuation multiples despite ongoing operational headwinds and volatile price action.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>03b933ae6922ffe2a02d23e89bd984d1</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:24:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sadhana Nitro Chem Ltd Plunges 68.70%: 5 Key Events Shaping the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sadhana-nitro-chem-ltd-plunges-6870-5-key-events-shaping-the-week-3849688</link><description>Sadhana Nitro Chem Ltd endured a tumultuous week from 16 to 20 February 2026, with its share price plunging 68.70% from Rs.6.39 to Rs.2.00, sharply underperforming the Sensex which rose 0.39% over the same period. The stock hit multiple 52-week lows amid persistent financial struggles and volatile trading marked by consecutive upper circuit hits in the final sessions, reflecting intense but speculative buying interest against a backdrop of deteriorating fundamentals.
Time: 48 minutes ago</description><guid>a26b6c8e2dcd4d4bd03b5a70134fc0da</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:24:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Greenply Industries Ltd Declines 1.85%: Bearish Momentum and Valuation Shifts Define Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/greenply-industries-ltd-declines-185-bearish-momentum-and-valuation-shifts-define-week-3849687</link><description>Greenply Industries Ltd closed the week down 1.85% at Rs.222.75, underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The stock experienced mixed technical signals amid valuation improvements but faced persistent financial challenges and sector headwinds, resulting in a cautious market stance throughout the week.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>bb8a27b8b9a5a444f8b72ec9cf80989c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:24:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Larsen &amp; Toubro Ltd Gains 4.97%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/larsen-toubro-ltd-gains-497-5-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-rally-3849685</link><description>Larsen &amp; Toubro Ltd. (L&amp;T) delivered a strong weekly performance, gaining 4.97% from Rs.4,172.90 on 13 Feb 2026 to Rs.4,380.25 on 20 Feb 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% rise over the same period. The stock hit multiple new 52-week and all-time highs during the week, supported by robust financials, technical momentum, and increased market participation, reflecting sustained investor confidence amid a mixed broader market backdrop.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>2146018648a664ba466cd105238e8f1e</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:24:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Ltd Falls 3.42%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mahindra-mahindra-ltd-falls-342-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3849686</link><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Ltd (M&amp;M) closed the week ending 20 February 2026 at Rs.3,413.00, down 3.42% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.3,533.80. This decline contrasted with the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain over the same period, highlighting a week of underperformance amid mixed market signals and heightened derivatives activity. Despite strong trading volumes and institutional interest, the stock faced short-term technical resistance and sectoral headwinds, resulting in a volatile week for investors.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>6631b4ead4f99bbc6a2ed99d5c9f0f0f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:24:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Precision Electronics Ltd Falls 10.18%: Technical and Fundamental Concerns Drive Sharp Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/precision-electronics-ltd-falls-1018-technical-and-fundamental-concerns-drive-sharp-decline-3849684</link><description>Precision Electronics Ltd experienced a sharp decline of 10.18% over the week ending 20 February 2026, closing at Rs.148.30 from Rs.165.10 the previous Friday. This contrasted with the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain during the same period, highlighting the stock’s significant underperformance amid deteriorating technical indicators and a downgrade to a Strong Sell rating by MarketsMOJO.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>8755ec2c9b942ab240f5f7d9ed98f496</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:24:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SEPC Ltd Falls 16.27%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sepc-ltd-falls-1627-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3849681</link><description>SEPC Ltd endured a challenging week from 16 to 20 February 2026, with its share price declining sharply by 16.27% to close at Rs.8.08, significantly underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. Despite sporadic volume surges and some relative outperformance on individual days, the stock remained under sustained selling pressure amid a bearish technical backdrop and sector headwinds.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>3ed710915f02c256edd04f3565aff76f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:24:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kama Holdings Ltd Gains 8.29%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kama-holdings-ltd-gains-829-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-rally-3849678</link><description>Kama Holdings Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 8.29% from ₹2,534.60 on 13 February to ₹2,744.65 on 20 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain over the same period. The stock’s rally was supported by a series of valuation upgrades, robust intraday price surges, and mixed but cautiously optimistic technical signals, reflecting a complex but promising outlook amid broader market volatility.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>ebc68ee463aebf12b32e91fde2621468</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:24:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RTS Power Corporation Ltd Falls 1.94%: Quality Upgrade Amid Bearish Technicals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rts-power-corporation-ltd-falls-194-quality-upgrade-amid-bearish-technicals-3849680</link><description>RTS Power Corporation Ltd’s stock declined by 1.94% over the week ending 20 February 2026, closing at Rs.123.90 compared to Rs.126.35 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain during the same period, reflecting mixed business fundamentals and bearish technical signals that weighed on investor sentiment throughout the week.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>4209c48e299b396420caf2c08d17c045</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:24:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Godfrey Phillips India Ltd Gains 19.66%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/godfrey-phillips-india-ltd-gains-1966-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-rally-3849683</link><description>Godfrey Phillips India Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, surging 19.66% from ₹2,081.80 to ₹2,491.00 between 16 and 20 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain. The stock’s rally was marked by heightened trading volumes, technical momentum shifts, and a notable upgrade in analyst sentiment, despite some volatility and profit-taking towards the week’s close.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>fa47337b43c02180033e4207dc4bc758</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:24:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Zinc Ltd’s Mildly Bullish Shift: -0.60% Weekly Dip Amid Mixed Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-zinc-ltds-mildly-bullish-shift--060-weekly-dip-amid-mixed-signals-3849682</link><description>Hindustan Zinc Ltd closed the week ending 20 February 2026 at Rs.589.60, down 0.60% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.593.15, underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The week was marked by a technical momentum shift and a downgrade in the company’s mojo rating from Buy to Hold, reflecting mixed signals from valuation, fundamentals, and technical indicators amid ongoing market volatility.
Time: 49 minutes ago</description><guid>2c733f258efaaee32a13962fb58ae283</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:24:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:24:57 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>