<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:23:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>When is the next results date for Simbhaoli Sugars Ltd?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/when-is-the-next-results-date-for-simbhaoli-sugars-ltd-3768691</link><description>The next results date for Simbhaoli Sugars Ltd is 29 December 2025.
Time: 37 minutes ago</description><guid>8faf0cb4b330b8b2d4ad8e9f642954ce</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:23:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nestle India Joins Market Coverage: Key Investment Merits and Strategic Fit</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/mojo-premium/nestle-india-added-to-mojo-stocks-a-strategic-inclusion-in-fmcg-large-caps-3768686</link><description>Nestle India has been added to the list of stocks under active coverage as of 24 December 2025, reflecting its standing as a large-cap FMCG company with notable financial metrics. This inclusion highlights the company’s stable market position, robust sales figures, and strong cash reserves, making it a significant consideration for investors seeking exposure in the fast-moving consumer goods sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>6cab4a490917fa9c0c8aeb0327e36095</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:23:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Reveal Mixed Trends Across Market Caps with Tata Steel Leading Large Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-mixed-results-across-4005-stocks-in-sep-2025-quarter-3768681</link><description>The September 2025 quarterly results season has unfolded with a nuanced pattern across market capitalisations, reflecting a cautious yet varied corporate performance landscape. Among 4,005 stocks reporting, the proportion of companies registering positive results hovered around 43%, indicating a slight shift compared to previous quarters. Tata Steel emerged prominently among large caps, while mid and small caps displayed divergent outcomes, underscoring sectoral and size-based dynamics in earnings trends.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>31193365eafaed80250d6ec3b74160dc</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:23:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vijay Solvex Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/vijay-solvex-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3768499</link><description>Vijay Solvex Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 20 October 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>a2c14a749a01adee3a5bca4342abfaef</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:23:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Unison Metals Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/unison-metals-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3768496</link><description>Unison Metals Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 01 Dec 2025, reflecting a reassessment of the stock’s outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here are current as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with the latest view on the company’s position in the market.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>32b5aa591de3b63375231a4e80e106fc</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:23:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aptus Value Housing Finance India Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/aptus-value-housing-finance-india-ltd-is-rated-sell-3768492</link><description>Aptus Value Housing Finance India Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 08 Dec 2025, reflecting a reassessment of the stock’s outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here are current as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with the latest perspective on the company’s position in the market.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>d8b4ff95267ee0a000e6421c1a7ff3fb</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:23:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Multibase India Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/multibase-india-ltd-is-rated-sell-3768494</link><description>Multibase India Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 14 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>e48fd2608d9df79c45f9d9500c616822</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:23:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>M K Proteins Ltd is Rated Sell by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/m-k-proteins-ltd-is-rated-sell-by-marketsmojo-3768488</link><description>M K Proteins Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 24 November 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company's performance and outlook.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>962de1974dd2d97976a460ca0c90de52</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:23:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mid East Portfolio Management Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/mid-east-portfolio-management-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3768493</link><description>Mid East Portfolio Management Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 01 Dec 2025, reflecting a reassessment of the stock’s outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here are current as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with the latest perspective on the company’s position.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>2163eb8155190d786cd313b0e0b42aec</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:23:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Syschem (India) Ltd is Rated Buy</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/syschem-india-ltd-is-rated-buy-3768491</link><description>Syschem (India) Ltd is rated Buy by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 09 Dec 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock’s current position as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>0790fbd34fb50392e72781b02c3e7b50</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:23:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sinclairs Hotels Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sinclairs-hotels-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3768490</link><description>Sinclairs Hotels Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 02 Dec 2025, reflecting a reassessment of the stock’s outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed below are current as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with the latest view of the company’s position in the market.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>339c0947733cec66fdae8ae77349f77f</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:23:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Liberty Shoes Ltd is Rated Sell by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/liberty-shoes-ltd-is-rated-sell-by-marketsmojo-3768486</link><description>Liberty Shoes Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 11 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>6a9dacca53112d7e151223bd81f7ffad</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:23:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aveer Foods Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/aveer-foods-ltd-is-rated-sell-3768487</link><description>Aveer Foods Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 16 Dec 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed below reflect the stock's current position as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>ec924d8db47f01125da3cb82b154dd43</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:23:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Last Mile Enterprises Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/last-mile-enterprises-ltd-is-rated-sell-3768489</link><description>Last Mile Enterprises Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 03 Dec 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company's performance and outlook.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>c4d5c1da4774d2490b8067b47e345eee</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:23:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Veritas (India) Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/veritas-india-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3768482</link><description>Veritas (India) Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 17 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>78b6bdf8a3f65e1fd0396c790ad6ba0c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:23:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BMW Industries Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/bmw-industries-ltd-is-rated-sell-3768484</link><description>BMW Industries Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 11 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company's fundamentals, returns, and market performance.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>75f84d3c1331dda115689692343e1ed1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:23:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ircon International Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ircon-international-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3768485</link><description>Ircon International Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 17 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market performance.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>5cd9aaf5f7bc9a7f18ae9f3cc6ffba24</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:23:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamdhenu Ventures Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/kamdhenu-ventures-ltd-is-rated-sell-3768483</link><description>Kamdhenu Ventures Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 28 Oct 2025. While the rating was revised on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market performance.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>768d59af5ac05cda3e36c69d6c217098</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:23:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indostar Capital Finance Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/indostar-capital-finance-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3768481</link><description>Indostar Capital Finance Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 11 Nov 2025, reflecting a reassessment of the stock’s outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed below are current as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with the latest perspective on the company’s position.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>450ba8a9aaef99eca6d4becbf237a0b9</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:23:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>D.P. Abhushan Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/dp-abhushan-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3768621</link><description>D.P. Abhushan Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 24 December 2025. While the rating change occurred on this date, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the company’s current position as of 24 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the stock’s fundamentals, returns, and technical outlook.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>23ec8c92b0859057210cddd7d6a530a0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:23:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:23:49 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>