<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:23:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Brawn Biotech Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/brawn-biotech-ltd-is-rated-sell-3771488</link><description>Brawn Biotech Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 09 Dec 2025. While the rating was revised on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>fc63d9fb55eb583a6bba392103831b2d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:23:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manor Estates &amp; Industries Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/manor-estates-industries-ltd-is-rated-sell-3771487</link><description>Manor Estates &amp; Industries Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 27 Oct 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company's fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>e58b76d393ef29c0d64579224ac400a5</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:23:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SAB Events &amp; Governance Now Media Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sab-events-governance-now-media-ltd-is-rated-sell-3771486</link><description>SAB Events &amp; Governance Now Media Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 12 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>83bf9892428452615eb6275ec14713a5</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:23:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Modella Woollens Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/modella-woollens-ltd-is-rated-sell-3771485</link><description>Modella Woollens Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 03 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>9870beddd9e64ac0cafefdfadf2abfc0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:23:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ISF Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/isf-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3771483</link><description>ISF Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, a rating that was last updated on 08 May 2024. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 26 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>9ae1fbcea14c3d3633c4b8e9bfb0256f</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:23:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Heera Ispat Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/heera-ispat-ltd-is-rated-sell-3771481</link><description>Heera Ispat Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, a rating that was last updated on 12 June 2025. While this rating change occurred mid-year, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 26 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into the stock’s performance and outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>eed66a996766d220352b3340af9b486c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:23:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rajputana Investment &amp; Finance Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/rajputana-investment-finance-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3771480</link><description>Rajputana Investment &amp; Finance Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 08 Dec 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed below reflect the stock’s current position as of 26 December 2025, providing investors with the most up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>eae277975877513c2aacf908fe632fa4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:23:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Padmanabh Industries Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/padmanabh-industries-ltd-is-rated-sell-3771484</link><description>Padmanabh Industries Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 02 Dec 2024. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company's fundamentals, returns, and market standing.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>10e46ff6968edb3418d27d5f1858dc7a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:23:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Supertex Industries Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/supertex-industries-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3771479</link><description>Supertex Industries Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 31 May 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 26 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>8c833874c10cdbbd54ae8fd4500e69ad</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:23:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vallabh Steels Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/vallabh-steels-ltd-is-rated-sell-3771482</link><description>Vallabh Steels Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 06 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>90446ef9cbe0555979e13f4fe77990df</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:23:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Olympic Cards Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/olympic-cards-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3771476</link><description>Olympic Cards Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 25 February 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 26 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>613f626b8a651790d059e6952c5a383c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:23:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Konndor Industries Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/konndor-industries-ltd-is-rated-sell-3771477</link><description>Konndor Industries Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 01 September 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>e37b3b4f144f8300a2f769c40e8f5d2a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:23:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ashish Polyplast Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ashish-polyplast-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3771478</link><description>Ashish Polyplast Ltd is rated 'Strong Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 12 February 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>097ff4cd21e246d988f2373396892791</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:23:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shukra Jewellery Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/shukra-jewellery-ltd-is-rated-sell-3771473</link><description>Shukra Jewellery Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 17 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 26 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b912430ea1a00562aa4e681869179fdd</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:23:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nihar Info Global Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/nihar-info-global-ltd-is-rated-sell-3771474</link><description>Nihar Info Global Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 08 Dec 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b8d647b02705d589ca2df4a4f33665e1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:23:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>V B Desai Financial Services Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/v-b-desai-financial-services-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3771472</link><description>V B Desai Financial Services Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 18 Jul 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b785c91b4895991261ac71ed1fe8a7e2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:23:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aditya Ispat Ltd. is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/aditya-ispat-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3771475</link><description>Aditya Ispat Ltd. is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 08 Dec 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 26 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>232de40732fab9f676a5adac27a3317d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:23:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uniroyal Marine Exports Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/uniroyal-marine-exports-ltd-is-rated-sell-3771469</link><description>Uniroyal Marine Exports Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 11 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 December 2025, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>721f3245f99ea2802f8b5aea424a83f1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:23:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>C J Gelatine Products Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/c-j-gelatine-products-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3771471</link><description>C J Gelatine Products Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 28 February 2025, reflecting a reassessment of the stock’s outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here are current as of 26 December 2025, providing investors with the latest view on the company’s position in the market.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>2765b15b582a3446eaf07e019449ff6d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:23:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IGC Industries Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/igc-industries-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3771468</link><description>IGC Industries Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 18 Aug 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock’s current position as of 26 December 2025, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>2763f2825308bbb7746b1e090e327aa7</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:23:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:23:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>