<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:19:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Are CDG Petchem Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-cdg-petchem-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3782233</link><description>CDG Petchem Ltd's latest results show mixed performance, with improved profitability but a significant decline in net sales, which fell 49.91% year-on-year. While the company achieved its highest PBT and PAT in recent quarters, ongoing operational challenges remain evident.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f0b67c485b9bbf6e8e42672f039ebd5b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:19:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nitta Gelatin India Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nitta-gelatin-india-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3782226</link><description>Nitta Gelatin India Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>877a75fae1be4a9a64d49db0bb69e04f</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:19:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IOL Chemicals &amp; Pharmaceuticals Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/iol-chemicals-pharmaceuticals-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3782227</link><description>IOL Chemicals &amp; Pharmaceuticals Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>e71f7744c74e55d5a55823607a722495</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:19:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IRM Energy Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/irm-energy-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3782223</link><description>IRM Energy Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>f4c73d81ee55c9d686b781eb4ae2f512</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:19:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Art Nirman Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/art-nirman-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3782224</link><description>Art Nirman Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Realty sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price trajectory.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>1427f6fa7c2f4a6044430ca4554bdb6d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:19:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Expo Engineering and Projects Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/expo-engineering-and-projects-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3782221</link><description>Expo Engineering and Projects Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>d4c86902392217eea53c756a89301d92</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:19:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mercantile Ventures Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mercantile-ventures-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3782222</link><description>Mercantile Ventures Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Diversified Commercial Services sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>8d573068d46c6c360c5badbd7b7af16e</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:19:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Telogica Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/telogica-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3782220</link><description>Telogica Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Telecom - Equipment &amp; Accessories sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about sustained bearish momentum in the near to medium term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>83659a31593baf10f5891dffb4dd65d6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:19:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Khaitan Chemicals &amp; Fertilizers Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/khaitan-chemicals-fertilizers-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3782219</link><description>Khaitan Chemicals &amp; Fertilizers Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s near- to medium-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>766a585d66c7838581931c9e33eb61cf</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:19:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kothari Products Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kothari-products-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3782214</link><description>Kothari Products Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>93cb8d7e46040dc864c16034544062c1</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:19:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>EIH Ltd. Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eih-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3782218</link><description>EIH Ltd., a prominent player in the Hotels &amp; Resorts sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>7be293600d67c656c75ea47ad90376e2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:19:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Himadri Speciality Chemical Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/himadri-speciality-chemical-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3782212</link><description>Himadri Speciality Chemical Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a shift towards a bearish trend and suggests a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum. Investors should carefully analyse the implications of this event amid the company’s recent performance and broader market context.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>63a88a7642d6b609ec2e938127ed29f6</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:19:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Piccadily Agro Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/piccadily-agro-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3782217</link><description>Piccadily Agro Industries Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ba601c7546ea047320703c2ba8943d8a</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:19:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Wonder Electricals Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Indicating Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/wonder-electricals-ltd-forms-golden-cross-indicating-potential-bullish-breakout-3782215</link><description>Wonder Electricals Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development often signals a potential bullish breakout, suggesting a shift in long-term momentum and a possible trend reversal for the small-cap electronics and appliances company.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b90e48ca40f2a4a39ca236e0d84f8ff2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:19:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Repro India Ltd. Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/repro-india-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3782211</link><description>Repro India Ltd. has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development highlights a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raises concerns about its long-term strength amid already challenging fundamentals.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>3b61a77fd64d97f6e73797e8713a3147</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:19:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tuni Textile Mills Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tuni-textile-mills-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3782216</link><description>Tuni Textile Mills Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum for the garment and apparel company, which has shown mixed performance against the broader market indices.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>5e8c48eca9ce84d662a771abcb7939d4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:19:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ajanta Pharma Ltd. Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ajanta-pharma-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3782213</link><description>Ajanta Pharma Ltd., a key player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, attracting renewed investor interest amid mixed market signals.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>e4aabdb2293adc0016d311a96899f377</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:19:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Oxford Industries Ltd Hits New 52-Week High of Rs.4.81 on 5 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/oxford-industries-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-of-rs481-on-5-jan-2026-3782177</link><description>Oxford Industries Ltd reached a significant milestone on 5 Jan 2026, hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.4.81. This achievement underscores the stock’s recent momentum as it outperformed its sector and maintained strength across key moving averages.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>9795ea6393f7b07602b55455af66d5c7</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:19:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>National General Industries Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.38.38</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/national-general-industries-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs3838-3782169</link><description>National General Industries Ltd, a player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, recorded a fresh 52-week low of Rs.38.38 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid a challenging market environment and company-specific headwinds.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>5d85d67c556f66fc14b37fe1743e996f</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:19:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:19:13 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>