<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:39:32 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Prozone Realty Ltd Falls 11.62%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/prozone-realty-ltd-falls-1162-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3863204</link><description>Prozone Realty Ltd’s stock declined sharply over the week ending 20 February 2026, falling 11.62% from ₹57.38 to ₹50.71, while the Sensex gained 0.39%. The week was marked by a downgrade in the company’s Mojo Grade from Buy to Hold, mixed technical signals, and a recalibration of valuation metrics, all contributing to investor caution amid broader market volatility.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>aa565b70954ea72676330d4d513f623c</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:39:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahindra Lifespace Developers Ltd’s Mixed Week: 0.35% Gain Amid Bearish Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mahindra-lifespace-developers-ltds-mixed-week-035-gain-amid-bearish-technical-signals-3863203</link><description>Mahindra Lifespace Developers Ltd closed the week ending 20 Feb 2026 with a modest gain of 0.35%, slightly underperforming the Sensex’s 0.39% rise. Despite this marginal positive price movement, the week was marked by a notable downgrade in the company’s technical and fundamental outlook, reflecting growing caution among investors amid mixed signals and financial challenges.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>f6c296a0de6cb535dd8ed1f1aaaa38a2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:39:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Byke Hospitality Ltd Falls 4.75%: Downgrade and 52-Week Low Mark a Challenging Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/the-byke-hospitality-ltd-falls-475-downgrade-and-52-week-low-mark-a-challenging-week-3863200</link><description>The Byke Hospitality Ltd experienced a difficult week from 16 to 20 February 2026, with its share price declining 4.75% to close at Rs.48.29, significantly underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The stock faced a downgrade to a Strong Sell rating amid mixed financial signals and deteriorating technical indicators, culminating in a fresh 52-week low of Rs.45 on 18 February. Despite some short-term financial improvements, the overall market sentiment remained bearish, reflecting ongoing challenges for the company.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>b1679720488d76e5d4535d51dc8fa658</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:39:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nectar Lifescience Declines 6.08%: Five Key Factors Behind the Steep Slide</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nectar-lifescience-declines-608-five-key-factors-behind-the-steep-slide-3863201</link><description>Nectar Lifescience Ltd’s shares declined sharply by 6.08% over the week ending 20 February 2026, closing at Rs.12.67 from Rs.13.49 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasts with the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain during the same period, reflecting persistent financial and operational challenges that weighed heavily on investor sentiment and drove the stock to fresh 52-week lows multiple times throughout the week.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>f72bef86b8d8f6b1d9864097840988ac</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:39:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mold-Tek Packaging Gains 1.56%: Valuation Shift and Technical Headwinds Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mold-tek-packaging-gains-156-valuation-shift-and-technical-headwinds-shape-the-week-3863202</link><description>Mold-Tek Packaging Ltd closed the week ending 20 February 2026 with a modest gain of 1.56%, outperforming the Sensex’s 0.39% rise. The stock experienced a mixed week marked by a valuation upgrade signalling renewed price attractiveness, counterbalanced by a technical downgrade reflecting bearish momentum. These contrasting forces influenced daily price movements amid a volatile market backdrop.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>26e8729a20798a373ec55fb7145c3146</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:39:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jaiprakash Associates Ltd Falls 10.62%: 3 Key Events Shaping the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jaiprakash-associates-ltd-falls-1062-3-key-events-shaping-the-week-3863199</link><description>Jaiprakash Associates Ltd experienced a turbulent week from 16 to 20 February 2026, closing down 10.62% at Rs.3.03 despite the Sensex gaining 0.39% over the same period. The stock’s volatile swings included hitting both lower and upper circuit limits amid heavy selling and buying pressures, reflecting persistent sectoral challenges and investor uncertainty.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>8ee0adae0f1d052c410d3e9f275ae929</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:39:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Reveal Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-reveal-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3863187</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has concluded with 4,095 companies reporting results, revealing a nuanced landscape of corporate performance marked by modest profit growth and varied sectoral outcomes. While mid-cap firms continue to outperform with a 53.0% positive results ratio, large caps lag behind at 43.0%, underscoring divergent momentum across market capitalisations.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>69139886bb09d7b415cd16f7b59968b3</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:39:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nestle India Gains 0.84%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Market Moves</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nestle-india-gains-084-4-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-market-moves-3863198</link><description>Nestle India Ltd closed the week ending 20 February 2026 with a modest gain of 0.84%, outperforming the Sensex’s 0.39% rise. The stock exhibited mixed price action amid shifting market sentiment, a significant surge in derivatives open interest, and a recent downgrade in its investment rating. Despite short-term technical headwinds, the company’s strong fundamentals and active market positioning kept investor interest alive throughout the week.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>86d85fc84d60da032c274ff7eecd067e</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:39:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Supreme Holdings &amp; Hospitality Ltd Gains 1.48%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/supreme-holdings-hospitality-ltd-gains-148-3-key-factors-driving-the-week-3863197</link><description>Supreme Holdings &amp; Hospitality Ltd recorded a modest weekly gain of 1.48%, closing at Rs.57.51 on 20 Feb 2026, outperforming the Sensex’s 0.39% rise over the same period. The week was marked by significant volatility, including fresh 52-week lows and a downgrade to a Strong Sell rating by MarketsMOJO, reflecting ongoing financial and technical challenges amid a mixed market backdrop.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>a8f02b822b44311d601f7a77d360aeab</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:39:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gujarat Industries Power Falls 2.62%: Technical Weakness and Valuation Shift Define Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gujarat-industries-power-falls-262-technical-weakness-and-valuation-shift-define-week-3863196</link><description>Gujarat Industries Power Co Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its share price declining by 2.62% from ₹141.25 to ₹137.55, underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The week was marked by a continuation of bearish technical momentum, a downgrade to a Strong Sell rating, and a notable shift in valuation metrics signalling increased price attractiveness amid market volatility.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>6679fed912a86e5af288b51a7171ae38</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:39:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>True Green Bio Energy Ltd Falls 4.58%: Key Financial Shifts and Valuation Recalibration</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/true-green-bio-energy-ltd-falls-458-key-financial-shifts-and-valuation-recalibration-3863195</link><description>True Green Bio Energy Ltd’s shares declined by 4.58% over the week ending 20 Feb 2026, closing at Rs.67.65 compared to Rs.70.90 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain during the same period, reflecting a mixed market response amid strong quarterly results, valuation adjustments, and sector challenges.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>0f38bbf3c76bcdcc1b0e27a7efc8e63e</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:39:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hindustan Oil Exploration Drops 6.94%: 4 Key Factors Behind the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hindustan-oil-exploration-drops-694-4-key-factors-behind-the-weekly-decline-3863194</link><description>Hindustan Oil Exploration Company Ltd’s stock declined by 6.94% over the week ending 20 February 2026, closing at Rs.132.15 from Rs.142.00 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain during the same period, reflecting a challenging week marked by a new 52-week low, technical downgrades, and valuation concerns that weighed heavily on investor sentiment.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>739aeca6ec2056fbcfca6db71948cb29</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:39:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Peninsula Land Ltd Falls 8.60% Amid Bearish Momentum and Valuation Pressures</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/peninsula-land-ltd-falls-860-amid-bearish-momentum-and-valuation-pressures-3863193</link><description>Peninsula Land Ltd experienced a challenging week from 16 to 20 February 2026, with its stock price declining sharply by 8.60% to close at Rs.19.02, significantly underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The week was marked by intensified bearish momentum, deteriorating valuation metrics, and a fresh 52-week low, reflecting ongoing financial struggles and market pressure on the realty company.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>f28375493b6491e85042ace90bc17dbf</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:39:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kamat Hotels Edges Lower by 0.03%: Downgrade and Valuation Shift Mark a Mixed Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kamat-hotels-edges-lower-by-003-downgrade-and-valuation-shift-mark-a-mixed-week-3863192</link><description>Kamat Hotels (India) Ltd closed the week nearly unchanged at Rs.188.10, a marginal decline of 0.03% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.188.15, underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The week was marked by a significant downgrade to a Strong Sell rating amid deteriorating financial metrics, alongside an upgrade in valuation attractiveness, reflecting a complex interplay of operational challenges and market perceptions.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>733d23fc0ec2993b7d5613f5d5ffba15</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:39:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Future Lifestyle Fashions Ltd Gains 3.88%: 4 Key Events Shaping the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/future-lifestyle-fashions-ltd-gains-388-4-key-events-shaping-the-week-3863191</link><description>Future Lifestyle Fashions Ltd recorded a 3.88% gain over the week ending 20 Feb 2026, outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% rise. The stock exhibited significant volatility, hitting upper circuit limits on three separate days before succumbing to heavy selling pressure and a lower circuit hit on 19 Feb. Despite a strong sell rating and micro-cap status, the week’s price action reflected intense trading interest and shifting investor sentiment amid constrained liquidity.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>fd3f94a9fd1bb5bb2aaab52145f69978</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:39:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Voltas Ltd Gains 1.31%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/voltas-ltd-gains-131-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3863190</link><description>Voltas Ltd. closed the week with a 1.31% gain, outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% rise from 16 to 20 February 2026. The stock demonstrated resilience amid mixed market conditions, hitting new 52-week highs midweek and concluding with a strong surge in derivatives activity signalling potential shifts in market sentiment.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>f9ec60987aaf12ce11fffe233a618dd1</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:39:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alldigi Tech Ltd Gains 3.11%: Valuation Upgrade and Market Volatility Shape Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/alldigi-tech-ltd-gains-311-valuation-upgrade-and-market-volatility-shape-week-3863189</link><description>Alldigi Tech Ltd closed the week ending 20 February 2026 with a 3.11% gain, outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% rise. The week was marked by a significant upgrade in the company’s valuation and investment rating by MarketsMOJO, alongside mixed price movements and volume fluctuations. Despite early weakness, the stock rebounded strongly on the final trading day, reflecting renewed investor interest amid improved fundamentals.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>7d4ff9f5f9d7d249f6e79b6501d570fd</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:39:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Saven Technologies Ltd Falls 16.41%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Sharp Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/saven-technologies-ltd-falls-1641-3-key-factors-driving-the-sharp-decline-3863181</link><description>Saven Technologies Ltd experienced a steep decline of 16.41% over the week ending 20 February 2026, closing at Rs.39.94 from Rs.47.78 the previous Friday. This sharp fall contrasted with the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain during the same period, highlighting significant underperformance amid mixed fundamentals, a downgrade to a Strong Sell rating, and a fresh 52-week low.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0775eb50d40fb6a1dbb9c4863f97d544</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:39:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Neuland Laboratories Falls 2.99%: 3 Key Technical and Fundamental Factors Driving the Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/neuland-laboratories-falls-299-3-key-technical-and-fundamental-factors-driving-the-decline-3863179</link><description>Neuland Laboratories Ltd experienced a challenging week from 16 to 20 February 2026, with its stock price declining by 2.99% to close at Rs.12,654.10, underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. Despite early gains on 16 and 17 February, the stock faced mounting pressure amid a downgrade to a Sell rating, deteriorating financial metrics, and a shift in technical momentum towards bearishness. This review analyses the key events and price movements that shaped the week for Neuland Laboratories.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>cdfd2055ff0d5d2d3f012fb8d29633ea</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:39:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vaghani Techno-Build Ltd Gains 1.72%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vaghani-techno-build-ltd-gains-172-5-key-factors-driving-the-rally-3863180</link><description>Vaghani Techno-Build Ltd closed the week at Rs.289.90, marking a 1.72% gain from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.285.00, outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% rise over the same period. The stock demonstrated strong momentum with multiple new 52-week and all-time highs, supported by a 21-day consecutive gain streak and an upgraded Mojo Grade of ‘Hold’. Despite a midweek dip, the company’s shares showed resilience amid mixed market conditions, reflecting sustained investor confidence and robust technical indicators.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f667807285a01016120e2193eda96224</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:39:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:39:32 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>