<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:42:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Ultracab (India) Ltd Falls 3.45% Amid Downgrade and Profitability Pressures</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ultracab-india-ltd-falls-345-amid-downgrade-and-profitability-pressures-3827421</link><description>Ultracab (India) Ltd’s stock declined by 3.45% over the week ending 6 February 2026, closing at Rs.7.56, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.51% during the same period. The week was marked by a new 52-week low, deteriorating financial quality, and a downgrade to a Strong Sell rating by MarketsMOJO, reflecting mounting concerns over profitability, leverage, and operational efficiency despite a backdrop of broader market gains.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>9fbf0356a1858149864fdd768e4ec987</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Omaxe Ltd Gains 6.57%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/omaxe-ltd-gains-657-4-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-momentum-3827420</link><description>Omaxe Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, rising 6.57% from ₹74.44 to ₹79.33 between 2 and 6 February 2026, significantly outpacing the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period. The stock’s trajectory was shaped by a series of technical shifts, a notable gap up on 4 February, and the release of challenging quarterly results, reflecting a complex interplay of market sentiment and operational realities.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>18e607b7363457506429511b7bcba4b2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sunshield Chemicals Declines 2.00% Amid Mixed Quarterly Results and Margin Pressures</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sunshield-chemicals-declines-200-amid-mixed-quarterly-results-and-margin-pressures-3827419</link><description>Sunshield Chemicals Ltd experienced a challenging week on the bourses, closing at Rs.833.45 on 6 February 2026, down 2.00% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.850.45. This decline contrasted with the broader Sensex, which advanced 1.51% over the same period, highlighting the stock’s underperformance amid mixed quarterly results and margin pressures reported early in the week.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>2e9312c9916491c6e69220db10216c56</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Future Lifestyle Fashions Ltd Gains 1.59%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/future-lifestyle-fashions-ltd-gains-159-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-volatility-3827417</link><description>Future Lifestyle Fashions Ltd’s stock recorded a modest weekly gain of 1.59%, closing at ₹1.28 on 6 February 2026, marginally outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise over the same period. The week was marked by significant price swings, including multiple fresh 52-week and all-time lows, interspersed with sharp rallies hitting upper circuit limits. These volatile movements reflect a complex interplay of weak fundamentals, speculative buying, and market sentiment shifts within a challenging sector environment.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>550aa40d71c7e9ddd4ef2be276c61759</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Nestle India Ltd Falls 2.19%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Move</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/nestle-india-ltd-falls-219-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-move-3827415</link><description>Nestle India Ltd’s shares declined by 2.19% over the week ending 6 February 2026, closing at ₹1,302.35 compared to ₹1,331.45 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s 1.51% gain during the same period, reflecting a week marked by mixed technical signals, valuation concerns, and cautious investor sentiment amid broader market volatility.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>2f79f9a4df919a5dec19b7a6397fc80d</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Voltas Ltd Gains 8.08%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/voltas-ltd-gains-808-4-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3827418</link><description>Voltas Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 8.08% from ₹1,328.45 to ₹1,435.80 between 2 and 6 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period. The stock’s trajectory was shaped by a series of technical momentum shifts, an upgrade in analyst ratings, and improving financial trends, despite some lingering caution from mixed indicator signals. This review analyses the key events and price movements that defined Voltas’s week.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>69f900ae5b28e15574c50b140eb413cf</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>John Cockerill India Ltd Gains 2.92%: Mixed Signals and Strong Gap Up Define the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/john-cockerill-india-ltd-gains-292-mixed-signals-and-strong-gap-up-define-the-week-3827416</link><description>John Cockerill India Ltd closed the week at Rs.4,933.65, marking a 2.92% gain from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.4,793.85. This outperformance came against a Sensex rise of 1.51% over the same period, reflecting a week of mixed technical signals and a strong gap-up rally that captured positive market sentiment. The stock’s price action was shaped by a shift in momentum and a notable surge on 3 February, underscoring a nuanced but cautiously optimistic outlook.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>ecb16f756a4b448f6e11cadca139c260</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Saven Technologies Gains 4.57%: Technical Shift and Valuation Drive Weekly Move</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/saven-technologies-gains-457-technical-shift-and-valuation-drive-weekly-move-3827414</link><description>Saven Technologies Ltd recorded a solid weekly gain of 4.57%, closing at Rs.44.59 on 6 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex which rose 1.51% over the same period. The stock showed consistent daily advances, buoyed by technical improvements and valuation appeal despite ongoing challenges in profitability. This review analyses the key events and price movements shaping the stock’s performance during the week.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>bcfc1de6d99dec49ec11f2f19f57f37f</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Peninsula Land Ltd Falls 3.51%: Earnings Pressure and Valuation Concerns Weigh</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/peninsula-land-ltd-falls-351-earnings-pressure-and-valuation-concerns-weigh-3827410</link><description>Peninsula Land Ltd’s stock closed the week down 3.51%, ending at Rs.19.54 on 6 Feb 2026, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.51% over the same period. The week was marked by a sharp rally early on, followed by a steep decline after the company reported deepening losses in its Q3 FY26 results and faced valuation challenges highlighted by a downgraded MarketsMOJO grade to Strong Sell.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>f5ff377a72ced9b57d52d5da9aa8caf4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Neuland Laboratories Declines 1.56% Despite Hold Upgrade: 5 Key Factors Shaping the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/neuland-laboratories-declines-156-despite-hold-upgrade-5-key-factors-shaping-the-week-3827412</link><description>Neuland Laboratories Ltd closed the week ending 6 February 2026 at ₹13,036.15, down 1.56% from the previous Friday’s close of ₹13,242.75, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.51% over the same period. The week was marked by a MarketsMOJO upgrade from Sell to Hold, a strong gap up on 3 February, and mixed technical momentum signals that reflected cautious investor sentiment amid ongoing volatility.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>17b06a5c6bdaee35826538f0236a21c1</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Vaghani Techno-Build Ltd Gains 8.78%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vaghani-techno-build-ltd-gains-878-5-key-factors-driving-the-rally-3827411</link><description>Vaghani Techno-Build Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 8.78% from Rs.242.00 to Rs.263.25 between 2 and 6 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period. The stock marked multiple new 52-week and all-time highs during the week, culminating in a 12-day consecutive gain streak that underscored robust momentum amid a mixed broader market backdrop.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>b2349f27c7aedd2aa5d578edcaa2404c</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Welspun Living Ltd Gains 13.46%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/welspun-living-ltd-gains-1346-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-rally-3827413</link><description>Welspun Living Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 13.46% from Rs.123.70 to Rs.140.35 between 2 and 6 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 1.51% gain. The week was marked by a dramatic intraday surge on 3 February, hitting an intraday high of Rs.147, followed by mixed technical signals and exceptional trading volumes that shaped the stock’s volatile trajectory.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>bff51beb3bf5e865a72ee598c19256c0</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Persistent Systems Ltd Falls 3.12%: 7 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/persistent-systems-ltd-falls-312-7-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3827409</link><description>Persistent Systems Ltd closed the week ending 6 February 2026 at Rs.5,845.55, marking a 3.12% decline from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.6,033.80. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period, reflecting a challenging week for the mid-cap software and consulting firm amid mixed technical signals, elevated volatility, and shifting market sentiment.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>821ba9136e2ca223eb1268723e95d1fd</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>MT Educare Ltd Gains 2.13%: 4 Key Events Shaping the Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mt-educare-ltd-gains-213-4-key-events-shaping-the-weeks-volatility-3827408</link><description>MT Educare Ltd’s stock closed the week at ₹1.44, marking a 2.13% gain from the previous Friday’s close of ₹1.41, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise over the same period. The week was characterised by sharp volatility, with the stock hitting a 52-week low and lower circuit on 3 February before rebounding strongly to upper circuit limits on 4 and 6 February amid fluctuating investor sentiment and subdued liquidity.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>963dd9e8cb5b2ad17dafab9197996daa</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trent Ltd Gains 8.80%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/trent-ltd-gains-880-5-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-rally-3827407</link><description>Trent Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 8.80% from Rs.3,785.60 to Rs.4,118.90 between 2 and 6 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period. The stock rebounded from a 52-week low early in the week to hit multiple intraday highs, supported by robust quarterly results and shifting technical momentum amid mixed market signals.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>d755deefaf9e319960dd711f8ffdfcff</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Navkar Urbanstructure Ltd Falls 7.86%: 5 Key Events Shaping the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/navkar-urbanstructure-ltd-falls-786-5-key-events-shaping-the-week-3827406</link><description>Navkar Urbanstructure Ltd experienced a turbulent week from 2 to 6 February 2026, closing the period down 7.86% at Rs.1.29, sharply underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.51%. The stock’s volatile swings included multiple upper circuit hits amid strong buying pressure, yet the overall trend remained bearish due to persistent fundamental concerns and a downgrade to a Strong Sell rating by MarketsMOJO.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>539130a76f375843565da09a78bdc0e1</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ashapura Minechem Ltd Falls 6.77%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Sharp Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ashapura-minechem-ltd-falls-677-6-key-factors-driving-the-sharp-weekly-decline-3827405</link><description>Ashapura Minechem Ltd closed the week ending 6 February 2026 at Rs.608.85, marking a 6.77% decline from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.653.05. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period, reflecting a challenging week for the stock amid volatile trading, sector pressures, and mixed technical signals.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>921d2f9415c1b1fa087f2e119ddeb76c</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sreeleathers Ltd Falls 3.22%: 3 Key Factors Behind the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sreeleathers-ltd-falls-322-3-key-factors-behind-the-weekly-decline-3827404</link><description>Sreeleathers Ltd. closed the week down 3.22% at Rs.209.05, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.51% over the same period. The stock experienced a volatile week marked by a technical momentum shift, a fresh 52-week low, and mixed market signals, reflecting ongoing challenges despite intermittent short-term gains.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>7b6a60190be587df87ec73495f681768</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Balaji Amines Ltd Gains 0.60%: 6 Key Factors Driving This Week’s Mixed Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/balaji-amines-ltd-gains-060-6-key-factors-driving-this-weeks-mixed-momentum-3827403</link><description>Balaji Amines Ltd experienced a modest weekly gain of 0.60% from ₹1,117.75 to ₹1,124.50 between 2 and 6 February 2026, underperforming the Sensex which rose 1.51% over the same period. The stock’s price action was marked by significant volatility and mixed technical signals, reflecting ongoing challenges in the specialty chemicals sector amid cautious investor sentiment. Despite a strong gap up on 3 February, the stock faced bearish momentum later in the week, closing near its recent lows.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>7ad1a0fbe09f3f6ab6af8f4d0a71599e</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ram Ratna Wires Ltd Gains 4.02%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Move</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ram-ratna-wires-ltd-gains-402-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-move-3827402</link><description>Ram Ratna Wires Ltd experienced a mixed week with a modest overall gain of 0.39% closing at Rs.296.65 on 6 Feb 2026, slightly underperforming the Sensex which rose 1.51%. The stock faced early bearish momentum and technical downgrades but showed signs of stabilisation midweek before ending on a positive note following strong Q3 FY26 revenue growth despite margin pressures and debt concerns.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>70e3cc73c82ce0778a92db28ff9d98bf</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:42:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>