<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:20:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Are Galaxy Agrico Exports Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-galaxy-agrico-exports-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3784851</link><description>Galaxy Agrico Exports Ltd's latest results are concerning, showing a 39.78% year-on-year decline in net sales and deteriorating profitability metrics, indicating significant operational challenges and questions about the company's sustainability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>eb41d5a4129913f821a3521a9df84d69</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:20:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Galaxy Agrico Exports Q2 FY26: Mounting Losses Raise Serious Concerns</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/galaxy-agrico-exports-q2-fy26-mounting-losses-raise-serious-concerns-3784850</link><description>Galaxy Agrico Exports Ltd., a micro-cap industrial manufacturing company with a market capitalisation of ₹15.00 crores, continues to struggle with operational challenges as reflected in its Q2 FY26 results. The company posted a net profit of ₹0.04 crores for the quarter ended September 2018, representing a 50.00% sequential increase but a troubling 86.21% year-on-year decline. Trading at ₹55.89, the stock has declined 0.29% in the latest session, reflecting investor concerns about the company's deteriorating fundamentals and persistent profitability challenges.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>1761a6b33b3804078cd1046fae73c7be</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:20:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Alpex Solar Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/alpex-solar-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3784848</link><description>Alpex Solar Ltd, a small-cap player in the Other Electrical Equipment sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s long-term strength.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b035f26e10b929f0367cbb6a46fd587d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:20:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ASK Automotive Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ask-automotive-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3784849</link><description>ASK Automotive Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>d170344d4beb6ad01eee14efeec64a75</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:20:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Life Insurance Corporation of India Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/life-insurance-corporation-of-india-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3784847</link><description>Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC) has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about long-term weakness amid a challenging market backdrop.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>8538297dffa7e31c0c5a25be54135a8c</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:20:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Gland Pharma Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gland-pharma-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3784846</link><description>Gland Pharma Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's long-term strength amid a challenging market backdrop.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>5a589fdd0f1c21690e34d00c5bf79f06</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:20:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hi-Tech Pipes Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hi-tech-pipes-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3784841</link><description>Hi-Tech Pipes Ltd, a small-cap player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about sustained weakness in the near to medium term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>8f95e030539ec10f587b659f7befb231</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:20:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cholamandalam Financial Holdings Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cholamandalam-financial-holdings-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3784842</link><description>Cholamandalam Financial Holdings Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium to long-term momentum and raising concerns about sustained weakness ahead.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>9c461b02250128e9d664bd7ccdfde467</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:20:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mindteck (India) Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mindteck-india-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3784843</link><description>Mindteck (India) Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ee6dea32b29fbb884642a3bc052990b9</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:20:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ind-Swift Laboratories Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ind-swift-laboratories-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3784845</link><description>Ind-Swift Laboratories Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>eee23838ac15ce36c0c099caa07f24e1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:20:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Doms Industries Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/doms-industries-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3784840</link><description>Doms Industries Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average, signalling a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum. This development marks a pivotal moment for the stock, suggesting a possible trend reversal and renewed investor confidence.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>8ba96aefb2e2fed40a1eede2cdd4e1d8</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:20:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Honasa Consumer Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/honasa-consumer-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3784837</link><description>Honasa Consumer Ltd, a prominent player in the FMCG sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, attracting renewed investor interest amid improving technical and fundamental metrics.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>a74b88ecc4a64e9dc1fbeb9ea1705fbe</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:20:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Procter &amp; Gamble Health Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/procter-gamble-health-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3784839</link><description>Procter &amp; Gamble Health Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s medium-term momentum and raising concerns about long-term weakness in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector player.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>987e8ce6f9fd3d035ad806a5c21a6155</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:20:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summit Securities Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/summit-securities-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3784838</link><description>Summit Securities Ltd, a Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC), has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's near-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>bfa4c5d1493aa7b6314f93492eb0b326</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:20:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Mixed Results Across 4,045 Stocks in Sep-2025 Quarter</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-mixed-results-across-4045-stocks-in-sep-2025-quarter-3784836</link><description>The September 2025 quarter earnings season has unfolded with a mixed yet cautiously optimistic tone as 4,045 companies declared results, revealing sectoral disparities and varied performance across market capitalisations. While mid-cap firms led with a 50.0% positive result ratio, large caps lagged at 39.0%, signalling nuanced investor sentiment amid evolving macroeconomic conditions.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>84644a2721e470ca55742198929c283d</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:20:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BIGBLOC Construction Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Indicating Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bigbloc-construction-ltd-forms-golden-cross-indicating-potential-bullish-breakout-3784844</link><description>BIGBLOC Construction Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) has crossed above the 200-day moving average. This development often heralds a bullish breakout and a potential long-term momentum shift, suggesting that the stock may be poised for an upward trend reversal despite its recent challenges.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>353c6e9a9b8872ab8c60a634bbef3d55</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:20:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>R M Drip &amp; Sprinklers Systems Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.88.87</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/r-m-drip-sprinklers-systems-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs8887-3784819</link><description>R M Drip &amp; Sprinklers Systems Ltd reached a fresh 52-week high of Rs.88.87 today, marking a significant milestone in its stock performance. The stock has demonstrated strong momentum, extending gains over the past nine trading sessions and outperforming its sector peers.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>9cba1d71a65b02d96273fdfe7c7adca5</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:20:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shriram Pistons &amp; Rings Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.3416.5</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shriram-pistons-rings-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs34165-3784814</link><description>Shriram Pistons &amp; Rings Ltd has surged to a fresh 52-week and all-time high of Rs.3416.5, marking a significant milestone in its stock performance. This new peak reflects sustained momentum supported by robust trading activity and favourable market conditions within the auto components sector.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>346d99dcc2c29b20d30813010e250458</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:20:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>R K Swamy Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/r-k-swamy-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-underperformance-3784813</link><description>Shares of R K Swamy Ltd have declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing near Rs 104.45, marking a significant downturn for the media and entertainment company amid persistent underperformance over the past year.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>c3cc2fd43a8cad5e5543a4e4802c9c77</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:20:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mukka Proteins Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mukka-proteins-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3784816</link><description>Mukka Proteins Ltd has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.23.59, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing concerns about the company’s financial metrics and market positioning.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>7a741fae9d6216649762ab313a756d26</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:20:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:20:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>