<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:54:24 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Utkarsh Small Finance Bank Ltd Hits Intraday High with 7.89% Surge on 24 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/utkarsh-small-finance-bank-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-789-surge-on-24-feb-2026-3853146</link><description>Utkarsh Small Finance Bank Ltd demonstrated a robust intraday performance on 24 Feb 2026, surging to a day’s high of Rs 15.09, marking an 8.17% increase from its previous close. This strong upward movement outpaced the broader sector and market indices, reflecting notable trading momentum despite a generally subdued market environment.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>d344289ea5873cc6e640a6667646d706</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sayaji Hotels (Pune) Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.663.8</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sayaji-hotels-pune-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs6638-3853144</link><description>Shares of Sayaji Hotels (Pune) Ltd declined sharply to a new 52-week low of Rs.663.8 on 24 Feb 2026, marking a significant drop of 19.04% on the day. This decline comes amid broader market weakness and reflects ongoing concerns about the company’s recent performance and valuation metrics.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>2d46f8ba1794bcd793c5d3a02c0428a5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Krsnaa Diagnostics Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/krsnaa-diagnostics-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3853135</link><description>Krsnaa Diagnostics Ltd’s share price declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.626.15 today, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing downward trajectory. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting a series of financial and market pressures that have weighed on investor sentiment over the past year.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>a463666b114a3a34a3f55f68fbea02e6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aartech Solonics Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low at Rs.43 Amid Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aartech-solonics-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-at-rs43-amid-prolonged-downtrend-3853138</link><description>Aartech Solonics Ltd, a player in the Heavy Electrical Equipment sector, has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.43 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downtrend. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing concerns about its financial performance and valuation metrics.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>3878f0d026567c67c9463d7d63b6c3b8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bhandari Hosiery Exports Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bhandari-hosiery-exports-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3853134</link><description>Shares of Bhandari Hosiery Exports Ltd have declined sharply to a new 52-week low of Rs.3.44 on 24 Feb 2026, marking a significant downturn amid broader market volatility and company-specific performance concerns.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>0aeede9ba1aba1bfebb2f01bdba56ea5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sterlite Technologies Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.171</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sterlite-technologies-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs171-3853137</link><description>Sterlite Technologies Ltd, a key player in the Telecom - Equipment &amp; Accessories sector, reached a significant milestone today by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.171. This achievement underscores the stock’s robust momentum amid a mixed market environment, reflecting sustained gains over recent sessions and outperforming its sector peers.
Time: 11 minutes ago</description><guid>a31c9d3dbd205544f07ee630d6779f19</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Marble City India Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.101 Amidst Market Downturn</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/marble-city-india-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs101-amidst-market-downturn-3853143</link><description>Marble City India Ltd has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.101 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid broader market volatility and sectoral underperformance. This fresh low reflects ongoing concerns surrounding the company’s financial metrics and valuation, despite recent positive earnings growth.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>1f9bf092e4cc578bb72bc3d8efe9a813</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kerala Ayurveda Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kerala-ayurveda-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3853136</link><description>Kerala Ayurveda Ltd’s shares have declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.215.15, marking a significant downturn for the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology company as it continues to underperform the broader market and its sector peers.
Time: 12 minutes ago</description><guid>2679ea83a4442a33bd39969546644efa</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blue Coast Hotels Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.24.06 Amid Market Downturn</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/blue-coast-hotels-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs2406-amid-market-downturn-3853142</link><description>Blue Coast Hotels Ltd’s shares declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.24.06 on 24 Feb 2026, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory. The stock’s performance has been notably weaker than its sector and broader market peers, reflecting persistent pressures on the company’s financial and market standing.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>13497e4a07d75c328c5ca2cd52b76f59</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shiva Cement Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shiva-cement-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3853139</link><description>Shiva Cement Ltd’s stock price declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.18.2 today, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing downward trajectory. The stock has underperformed its sector and benchmark indices, reflecting persistent pressures on the company’s valuation and financial metrics.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>78f18bd1fcde0bd9681ce1d283a9f558</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Relaxo Footwears Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.351.05</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/relaxo-footwears-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs35105-3853140</link><description>Relaxo Footwears Ltd’s shares declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.351.05 today, marking a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing downward trajectory. The stock has now recorded a four-day consecutive fall, shedding 5.72% over this period, reflecting persistent pressures within the footwear sector and company-specific performance concerns.
Time: 13 minutes ago</description><guid>b845dea1853e9f61ed58b70c345f6ad9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Multibase India Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/multibase-india-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3853141</link><description>Multibase India Ltd, a player in the Specialty Chemicals sector, recorded a fresh 52-week low of Rs.210.55 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has now fallen for three consecutive sessions, reflecting ongoing pressures in its performance metrics and valuation.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>73f135df7514e6745f51038f73e509a4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tarsons Products Ltd Hits All-Time Low Amid Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tarsons-products-ltd-hits-all-time-low-amid-prolonged-downtrend-3853130</link><description>Shares of Tarsons Products Ltd have plunged to an all-time low, closing just 0.45% above their 52-week nadir of ₹188.05 on 24 Feb 2026. The stock’s recent performance reflects a sustained period of decline, underperforming both its sector and broader market indices, signalling significant headwinds for the healthcare services company.
Time: 16 minutes ago</description><guid>19cb47cdaaafa86ed551c117129f840b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DCM Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dcm-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3853129</link><description>Shares of DCM Ltd, a company in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.81.01 on 24 Feb 2026, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing downward trajectory. This new low reflects a sustained period of price weakness amid broader market fluctuations and company-specific financial pressures.
Time: 19 minutes ago</description><guid>b9b91d7f424a151d6a821537b666b73c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ADF Foods Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 24 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/adf-foods-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-24-feb-2026-3853126</link><description>ADF Foods Ltd experienced a significant intraday decline on 24 Feb 2026, touching a low of Rs 209.2, down 8.17% from its previous close. The stock underperformed its FMCG sector peers and broader market indices amid sustained selling pressure and a broadly negative market environment.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>bb3bb5cd55b5ad63792ab76dde672120</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Premier Energies Ltd Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/premier-energies-ltd-sees-notable-surge-in-derivatives-open-interest-amid-mixed-market-signals-3853125</link><description>Premier Energies Ltd (NSE: PREMIERENE), a mid-cap player in the Other Electrical Equipment sector, has witnessed a significant 11.8% rise in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this surge, the stock underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting a complex interplay of bullish and bearish sentiments among traders.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>1e460d95accfd46bfb1f064295c4a220</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DJ Mediaprint &amp; Logistics Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dj-mediaprint-logistics-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3853124</link><description>Shares of DJ Mediaprint &amp; Logistics Ltd plunged to their lower circuit limit on 24 Feb 2026, reflecting intense selling pressure and panic among investors. The stock closed at ₹89.65, down 2.87% on the day, with intraday volatility reaching 5%, signalling heightened market nervousness in the transport services micro-cap.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>45cf51400cce91d4b603459032f081a3</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FSN E-Commerce Ventures Sees Notable Surge in Derivatives Open Interest Amid Mixed Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/fsn-e-commerce-ventures-sees-notable-surge-in-derivatives-open-interest-amid-mixed-price-action-3853123</link><description>FSN E-Commerce Ventures Ltd, the parent company of NYKAA, witnessed a notable 10.15% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock's underperformance and falling investor participation. This surge in open interest, coupled with volume patterns and price movements, offers critical insights into evolving market positioning and potential directional bets.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>94b2a6f51a623d8edde6b96c469837fb</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AKI India Ltd Plunges to Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aki-india-ltd-plunges-to-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3853121</link><description>Shares of AKI India Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Gems, Jewellery and Watches sector, plunged sharply on 24 Feb 2026, hitting the lower circuit limit as panic selling gripped the stock. The stock recorded its new 52-week and all-time low at ₹4.88, reflecting a maximum daily loss of 8.94%, significantly underperforming both its sector and the broader market indices.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>62211f6a13a99ab997dc905ae8a0d39a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JSW Energy Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jsw-energy-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-price-action-3853120</link><description>JSW Energy Ltd (JSWENERGY) has witnessed a notable 10.31% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this surge, the stock has underperformed its sector and the broader Sensex, reflecting a complex interplay of market forces and investor sentiment in the power sector.
Time: 24 minutes ago</description><guid>4a719077cc0f07aacd1bd719f2eff9c9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:54:24 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>