<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:15:59 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Are Shyam Metalics &amp; Energy Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-shyam-metalics-energy-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803807</link><description>Shyam Metalics &amp; Energy Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 17.71% year-on-year, but a concerning 24.65% decline in net profit and reduced operating margins indicate significant challenges in profitability and operational efficiency. Overall, while revenues are up, the decline in profitability raises concerns about the company's financial health.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>896f34c909ed940ec518985c472473a3</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:15:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Gandhar Oil Refinery (India) Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-gandhar-oil-refinery-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803806</link><description>Gandhar Oil Refinery (India) Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 16.09% year-on-year, reaching ₹1,167.06 crores, but profitability has declined, with a net profit drop of 10.15% from the previous quarter and decreasing margins, indicating operational challenges despite the revenue increase.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f056cd80920b73815fb2327697cc6426</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:15:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are SBFC Finance Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-sbfc-finance-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803805</link><description>SBFC Finance Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show an 8.15% quarter-on-quarter net profit increase to ₹118.04 crores and a 27.51% year-on-year growth, but concerns about capital efficiency and rising interest expenses suggest potential challenges ahead. Investors should monitor these trends closely.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4877babbe275e945979c665bbbd59d69</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:15:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Advik Capital Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-advik-capital-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803804</link><description>Advik Capital Ltd's latest results are concerning, showing a net loss of ₹20.87 crores and negative revenue of ₹-2.83 crores for the quarter ending December 2025, indicating severe operational and financial distress. The company's significant decline in sales and liquidity challenges suggest it is in a precarious position.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>89154f2c9fdc6465118be45a0a1900ce</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:15:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Cyber Media Research &amp; Services Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-cyber-media-research-services-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803803</link><description>Cyber Media Research &amp; Services Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 5.49% to ₹22.29 crores, but a concerning 33.73% drop in net profit to ₹0.55 crores, indicating challenges in profitability despite overall positive trends for the year. Investors should monitor future performance closely.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>85ccc291ae0fa34fc4d0b6b8965f8ed1</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:15:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-nuvama-wealth-management-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803802</link><description>Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd's latest results show a slight decline in net profit and revenue, indicating a deceleration in growth momentum, although operating margins improved due to cost management. Overall, the company faces challenges in sustaining growth amid competitive pressures and market volatility.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f3baed5e9c29b553bd1e118a143f64e0</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:15:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are 20 Microns Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-20-microns-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803801</link><description>20 Microns Ltd's latest results show a mixed performance, with a year-over-year net profit increase of 16.06% but a sequential decline in both profit and revenue, indicating operational challenges despite some improvements in efficiency. Overall, the company is facing stagnant revenue growth and inflationary pressures, leading to concerns about capital efficiency.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f5da824007ec70127ef88279b5a408ae</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:15:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are JSW Energy Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-jsw-energy-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803800</link><description>JSW Energy Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 59.91% to ₹5,177.42 crores, but net profit declined by 17.41% to ₹704.68 crores due to rising debt and interest expenses, raising concerns about financial stability and profitability. Investors should watch the company's ability to manage its debt and improve margins moving forward.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>192f9ec46517c594285d87edf44f2177</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:15:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Ashish Polyplast Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-ashish-polyplast-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803799</link><description>Ashish Polyplast Ltd's latest results show a return to profitability with a net profit of ₹0.15 crores, but revenue declined by 4.07% sequentially and 20.81% year-on-year, indicating ongoing operational challenges and negative returns on equity. Overall, the financial performance reflects mixed results with significant concerns about revenue generation and capital efficiency.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>610081528b361ef590868a78b55c919e</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:15:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Vakrangee Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-vakrangee-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803798</link><description>Vakrangee Ltd's latest results show a significant net profit increase of 168.07% to ₹3.19 crores, but revenue declined by 11.46% to ₹60.10 crores, marking the lowest in seven quarters. While operating margins improved due to cost control, ongoing revenue challenges and low return on equity indicate potential long-term issues.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>81aa9084bf07084e63ae073fd0182a9d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:15:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Anka India Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-anka-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803797</link><description>Anka India Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results show impressive revenue growth of 419.44% year-on-year, but profitability has declined significantly, with a net profit of only ₹0.10 crores and concerns over operational efficiency and cost management. Overall, the company is experiencing strong sales but struggling to convert that growth into sustainable profits.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>58c5bd5c71883e8692bc90c44e24558d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:15:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Bridge Securities Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-bridge-securities-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803796</link><description>Bridge Securities Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, showing a 44% year-on-year decline in net sales and a 54.79% drop in net profit, alongside significant margin compression and structural balance sheet weaknesses. Overall, the company is facing considerable operational challenges and may be overvalued given its deteriorating fundamentals.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e5dd4fa7dedd98b638c8d3f13eebf09f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:15:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Advani Hotels &amp; Resorts (India) Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-advani-hotels-resorts-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803795</link><description>Advani Hotels &amp; Resorts (India) Ltd reported strong Q3 FY26 results with a net profit of ₹11.33 crores and record revenue of ₹36.09 crores, reflecting significant operational improvements and seasonal demand. However, despite this positive performance, the company's long-term stock results have been mixed, with a one-year return of -2.78%.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d68b70fcdae644361bf7f6272031c9c9</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:15:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Sacheta Metals Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-sacheta-metals-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803794</link><description>Sacheta Metals Ltd's latest results show a mixed performance: while net profit increased by 54% and operating margins improved, revenue declined by 16.71%, raising concerns about demand and overall financial health due to weak return ratios. The company faces significant challenges that need to be addressed for sustainable growth.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>fd8fe8465dc69ffcb10beb44f101fed8</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:15:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Bansal Roofing Products Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-bansal-roofing-products-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803793</link><description>Bansal Roofing Products Ltd reported strong financial results for December 2025, with a net profit of ₹3.57 crores (up 57.96%) and revenue of ₹38.68 crores (up 46.29%). However, margin volatility raises concerns about the sustainability of this growth, despite robust capital efficiency and a healthy balance sheet.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5dce139499cfd57c8a72925f460abf26</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:15:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are DB (International) Stock Brokers Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-db-international-stock-brokers-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803792</link><description>DB (International) Stock Brokers Ltd's latest results are concerning, showing a significant decline in net sales and profit for the quarter ended December 2025, alongside challenges in generating returns on equity, despite maintaining some cost efficiency. The company is facing operational difficulties in a subdued trading environment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>38dcc4f9b2f14440b518ecef176c77de</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:15:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Bloom Dekor Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-bloom-dekor-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803791</link><description>Bloom Dekor Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are poor, showing a 46.43% decline in net sales to ₹0.60 crores and a net loss of ₹0.51 crores, alongside a negative operating margin of -98.33% and negative equity of ₹6.58 crores, indicating serious operational and financial challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>90d49db92800cb9b1e807375e0e7c3eb</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:15:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Multi Commodity Exchange of India Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-multi-commodity-exchange-of-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803790</link><description>The latest results for Multi Commodity Exchange of India Ltd (MCX) are generally positive, showing a 31.04% year-on-year growth in net sales and a 28.54% increase in net profit, though there was a slight sequential decline in profit. The company's strong operating margin and high return on equity reflect its market strength, but caution is warranted regarding valuation sustainability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>06affee0c8b9837de127b9a746bc3769</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:15:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Cella Space Ltd. latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-cella-space-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803789</link><description>Cella Space Ltd.'s latest Q3 FY26 results show a 10.34% revenue growth to ₹1.92 crores, but net profit fell 34.48% to ₹0.19 crores, indicating deteriorating profitability despite improved operating margins. The company faces significant challenges, including high interest costs and negative shareholder equity, raising concerns about its long-term financial health.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>fbdb16cd21e1d33c0369cb310903e694</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:15:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-kotak-mahindra-bank-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3803788</link><description>Kotak Mahindra Bank's latest results show a net profit decline to ₹3,253 crore due to increased provisions, despite stable revenue and improved asset quality. While the bank maintains a strong capital position, the outlook remains cautious amid margin compression and profitability challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>897e400d96a9cf09ce3a982363ef8d60</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:15:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:15:59 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>