<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:38:14 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Dec-2025 Quarterly Earnings Reveal Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/dec-2025-quarterly-earnings-reveal-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3827567</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has unfolded with a mixed bag of results as 1,744 companies declared their financials, revealing a modest improvement in positive earnings surprises compared to previous quarters. While mid-cap firms led the charge with a 52.0% positivity rate, large caps lagged behind at 38.0%, underscoring divergent sectoral and market cap trends amid evolving macroeconomic conditions.
Time: 8 minutes ago</description><guid>86d4647d93eb70fda36ccb6beb8b329f</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Loyal Equipments Ltd Gains 0.58%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/loyal-equipments-ltd-gains-058-2-key-factors-driving-the-week-3827565</link><description>Loyal Equipments Ltd experienced a mixed week from 2 to 6 February 2026, closing with a modest gain of 0.58% to Rs.173.00 despite a challenging start marked by a 6.22% drop to Rs.161.30 on 2 February. The stock underperformed the Sensex, which rose 1.51% over the same period, reflecting ongoing valuation recalibrations and financial pressures amid a broadly recovering market environment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ca26803d69b351bdece105206b70ae3b</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Galaxy Surfactants Gains 0.56%: 2 Key Events Shaping This Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/galaxy-surfactants-gains-056-2-key-events-shaping-this-weeks-volatility-3827564</link><description>Galaxy Surfactants Ltd experienced a volatile week from 2 to 6 February 2026, closing with a modest gain of 0.56% to Rs.1,828.85, slightly underperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise. The stock’s movement was marked by a fresh 52-week low early in the week, followed by a sharp gap up on 3 February, reflecting mixed investor sentiment amid ongoing challenges in financial performance and technical positioning.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>30ab2bf38686cdc19bd0cd3f61ebe60b</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AMJ Land Holdings Ltd Falls 3.85% Amid Sharp Profit Decline and 52-Week Low</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/amj-land-holdings-ltd-falls-385-amid-sharp-profit-decline-and-52-week-low-3827563</link><description>AMJ Land Holdings Ltd’s stock declined by 3.85% over the week ending 6 February 2026, closing at Rs.40.00 compared to Rs.41.60 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s 1.51% gain during the same period, reflecting investor concerns following the company’s sharp quarterly profit decline and a fresh 52-week low hit midweek.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a2fc90e2bfd74375f5ad5ee880320050</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bhageria Industries Falls 11.49%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bhageria-industries-falls-1149-2-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3827562</link><description>Bhageria Industries Ltd endured a challenging week, with its stock price declining 11.49% from Rs.181.00 on 30 Jan 2026 to Rs.160.20 on 6 Feb 2026, sharply underperforming the Sensex, which rose 1.51% over the same period. The week was marked by a notable shift in valuation metrics signalling changing market sentiment, followed by quarterly results that revealed revenue growth but raised concerns over margin compression. These developments contributed to heightened volatility and bearish pressure on the stock throughout the week.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>91a5eece0c743325ee498501e11e8dfa</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>eClerx Services Ltd Falls 10.25%: 4 Key Factors Behind the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eclerx-services-ltd-falls-1025-4-key-factors-behind-the-weekly-decline-3827560</link><description>eClerx Services Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its stock price declining by 10.25% from ₹4,653.25 to ₹4,176.45, sharply underperforming the Sensex which rose 1.51% over the same period. The week was marked by significant intraday volatility, technical downgrades, and sectoral pressures that collectively weighed on the stock’s performance despite its strong long-term fundamentals.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>653466e0ffb50dbb680272a96eeaa747</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ASM Technologies Ltd Falls 14.99%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/asm-technologies-ltd-falls-1499-2-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3827558</link><description>ASM Technologies Ltd experienced a challenging week from 2 to 6 February 2026, with its share price declining sharply by 14.99% to close at Rs.2,539.10, significantly underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.51% over the same period. The week was marked by a steep gap down opening on Monday amid market concerns and a subsequent valuation reassessment that reflected shifting investor sentiment. Despite some intraday recoveries, the stock remained under pressure throughout the week, highlighting ongoing caution among market participants.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>34eb432395be74596ae141ea82f94071</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bhagiradha Chemicals Gains 5.60%: 2 Key Factors Driving This Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bhagiradha-chemicals-gains-560-2-key-factors-driving-this-weeks-momentum-3827557</link><description>Bhagiradha Chemicals &amp; Industries Ltd recorded a notable weekly gain of 5.60%, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise during the week ending 6 February 2026. The stock’s performance was driven by a strong intraday surge on 3 February and a nuanced shift in technical momentum amid mixed market signals, reflecting both optimism and caution among investors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8fedf1564b37bc9150389c6615486974</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mangalore Refinery &amp; Petrochemicals Ltd Gains 4.84%: 7 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mangalore-refinery-petrochemicals-ltd-gains-484-7-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3827561</link><description>Mangalore Refinery &amp; Petrochemicals Ltd (MRPL) delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 4.84% from Rs.176.50 to Rs.185.05 between 2 and 6 February 2026, comfortably outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period. The stock demonstrated robust technical momentum, hitting a new 52-week high and registering exceptional volume surges amid positive sector dynamics and an upgraded mojo rating. This review analyses the key events shaping MRPL’s price action and market positioning throughout the week.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>cdd6bbcca2e8113a6afde4e118fd67b0</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JTL Industries Falls 5.76% Amid Valuation Concerns and Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jtl-industries-falls-576-amid-valuation-concerns-and-price-pressure-3827559</link><description>JTL Industries Ltd experienced a turbulent week ending 6 February 2026, with its share price declining by 5.76% from Rs.71.70 to Rs.67.57, underperforming the Sensex which rose 1.51% over the same period. The stock saw sharp intraday volatility, notably on 4 February when it hit an intraday low amid price pressure, and valuation metrics shifted to reflect challenges in price attractiveness. Despite a modest upgrade in its Mojo Grade to Sell, the week’s price action and fundamental signals suggest a cautious outlook for investors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>16ee5c95b9af7689c56640b021b591da</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Axis Bank Ltd. Dips 2.09% Despite 52-Week High; 4 Key Factors Shaping the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/axis-bank-ltd-dips-209-despite-52-week-high-4-key-factors-shaping-the-week-3827556</link><description>Axis Bank Ltd. experienced a volatile week from 2 to 6 February 2026, closing down 2.09% at Rs.1,341.55 despite hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.1,418.3 on 3 February. The stock’s performance contrasted with the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period, reflecting mixed investor sentiment amid strong intraday rallies, heavy put option activity, and notable institutional interest.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4812cfe3ce009644ff9ae20a5c0cfeed</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lexoraa Industries Gains 2.01%: Technical Momentum and 52-Week High Drive Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lexoraa-industries-gains-201-technical-momentum-and-52-week-high-drive-weekly-rally-3827554</link><description>Lexoraa Industries Ltd recorded a 2.01% gain over the week ending 6 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise. The stock showed resilience amid mixed market conditions, buoyed by a technical upgrade early in the week and a fresh 52-week high midweek. Despite persistent fundamental challenges, these developments underpinned investor interest and contributed to the stock’s relative strength.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3d4853d5481d2c5968ebd0fa091175ba</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Steelcast Ltd Gains 22.05%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/steelcast-ltd-gains-2205-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3827555</link><description>Steelcast Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 22.05% from Rs.184.80 to Rs.225.55 between 2 and 6 February 2026, significantly outpacing the Sensex’s modest 1.51% gain over the same period. The week was marked by a sharp rally early on, highlighted by a 16.15% surge on 2 February and a further 13.46% jump on 3 February, driven by technical momentum shifts and positive market sentiment. However, the latter part of the week saw a gradual correction with three consecutive days of declines, reflecting mixed technical signals and cautious investor positioning.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>012a1e90e5889aa7f44f2a54392bb716</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Karur Vysya Bank Gains 5.41%: Key Milestones and Market Dynamics This Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/karur-vysya-bank-gains-541-key-milestones-and-market-dynamics-this-week-3827553</link><description>Karur Vysya Bank Ltd. delivered a robust weekly performance, gaining 5.41% from Rs.301.40 to Rs.317.70 between 02 and 06 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise over the same period. The stock’s momentum was fuelled by a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs.322.65 on 03 February, supported by strong fundamentals and sustained institutional interest.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>aa9e6e4a1d0130d5e7226fd19551a0ab</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tarmat Ltd Gains 4.15%: Key Financial Trends and Market Moves This Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tarmat-ltd-gains-415-key-financial-trends-and-market-moves-this-week-3827552</link><description>Tarmat Ltd delivered a solid weekly performance, rising 4.15% from Rs.51.83 to Rs.53.98 between 2 and 6 February 2026, comfortably outpacing the Sensex’s 1.51% gain over the same period. The stock showed strong momentum early in the week, buoyed by positive quarterly financial results announced on 5 February, before retreating slightly on the final trading day amid mixed market signals. This review analyses the key events shaping Tarmat’s price action and financial outlook during the week.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>33014aace58a120a17dba476b2131d81</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Grindwell Norton Gains 5.82%: Mixed Technical Signals and Growth Reality Check</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/grindwell-norton-gains-582-mixed-technical-signals-and-growth-reality-check-3827551</link><description>Grindwell Norton Ltd. recorded a 5.82% gain over the week ending 6 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.51% rise. The stock showed notable volatility, surging 6.27% on 3 February following a sharp market rebound, before consolidating amid mixed technical signals and a cautious market response to its Q3 FY26 results. Despite the positive weekly performance, the stock closed slightly lower on the final trading day, reflecting investor caution amid premium valuation concerns.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>686905beaa252e22a2c14cebf0bc2d96</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rajratan Global Wire Ltd Gains 15.58%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rajratan-global-wire-ltd-gains-1558-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-rally-3827550</link><description>Rajratan Global Wire Ltd delivered a strong performance this week, surging 15.58% from Rs.406.65 to Rs.470.00, significantly outpacing the Sensex’s 1.51% gain. The stock’s rally was marked by robust intraday gains, a shift in technical momentum, and renewed buying interest amid mixed market signals. Despite some volatility and technical caution, the week closed on a positive note, reflecting investor optimism in the company’s near-term prospects.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>af75c1a11829a056a57befdc0b95e2aa</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Moschip Technologies Ltd Falls 5.55%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/moschip-technologies-ltd-falls-555-5-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3827549</link><description>Moschip Technologies Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its stock price declining by 5.55% from ₹209.75 to ₹198.10, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.51% over the same period. The week was marked by a series of technical shifts, a significant death cross formation, a downgrade to a Sell rating, and mixed financial signals that collectively weighed on investor sentiment and price momentum.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3ea0a7c076ab9b66160e3f5b74cbdc94</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Garware Hi Tech Films Ltd Gains 40.73%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/garware-hi-tech-films-ltd-gains-4073-5-key-factors-driving-the-surge-3827548</link><description>Garware Hi Tech Films Ltd delivered a remarkable weekly performance, surging 40.73% from Rs.3,014.70 to Rs.4,242.70 between 2 and 6 February 2026. This substantial gain vastly outpaced the Sensex’s modest 1.51% rise over the same period, reflecting strong investor interest amid a series of significant price rallies and mixed fundamental signals.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f9815624196a92fb8c48e48880e6bca6</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Colgate-Palmolive Gains 1.01%: 3 Key Factors Driving Mixed Technical Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/colgate-palmolive-gains-101-3-key-factors-driving-mixed-technical-momentum-3827547</link><description>Colgate-Palmolive (India) Ltd closed the week with a modest gain of 1.01%, rising from Rs.2,113.60 to Rs.2,134.90 between 2 and 6 February 2026. This performance, however, lagged behind the Sensex’s 1.51% advance over the same period, reflecting a week marked by mixed technical signals and a significant downgrade in the company’s rating. The stock experienced fluctuations amid cautious investor sentiment, technical momentum shifts, and deteriorating financial indicators, culminating in a nuanced weekly outcome.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>05c7e166a5fa55c08f90ee7b3f5cb2f3</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>