<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:45:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Popular Vehicles &amp; Services Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs 86</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/popular-vehicles-services-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs-86-3853322</link><description>Popular Vehicles &amp; Services Ltd has touched a new 52-week and all-time low of Rs.86 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downtrend. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing pressures on its financial and market performance.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>1170c45431c467a364539bbf874fd0a0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:45:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SIS Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.289.15 Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sis-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs28915-amidst-continued-underperformance-3853320</link><description>SIS Ltd, a key player in the Diversified Commercial Services sector, recorded a fresh 52-week low of Rs.289.15 today, marking a significant decline amid broader market fluctuations and persistent challenges in its financial performance. The stock’s fall to this level underscores ongoing concerns regarding its growth trajectory and relative market positioning.
Time: 9 minutes ago</description><guid>9b7c1b0b5f243f316a370d53c65726b9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:45:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ruchira Papers Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amid Continued Earnings Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ruchira-papers-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amid-continued-earnings-pressure-3853321</link><description>Ruchira Papers Ltd’s shares touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.103.15 today, marking a significant decline amid ongoing financial headwinds. The stock’s performance reflects persistent challenges in revenue and profitability, with the company’s recent quarterly results underscoring a continuation of subdued earnings trends.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>6c93b2bd6df512970d0682a330c8ac6a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:45:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jindal Steel Ltd. Hits New 52-Week High of Rs.1238 on 24 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jindal-steel-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-of-rs1238-on-24-feb-2026-3853324</link><description>Jindal Steel Ltd. has surged to a fresh 52-week and all-time high of Rs.1238, reflecting robust momentum in the ferrous metals sector despite broader market headwinds. The stock’s recent rally underscores its outperformance relative to both its sector and the benchmark Sensex over the past year.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>7c5bbedbe7028515eb2a415e8900ef5e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:45:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Last Mile Enterprises Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.5.83</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/last-mile-enterprises-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs583-3853323</link><description>Last Mile Enterprises Ltd, a Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC), touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.5.83 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained negative trend. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing pressures on its financial performance and valuation metrics.
Time: 10 minutes ago</description><guid>9f8536a9ec42df066df1ca30109b15d6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:45:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Endurance Technologies Ltd. Hits Intraday High with 5.06% Surge on 24 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/endurance-technologies-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-506-surge-on-24-feb-2026-3853315</link><description>Endurance Technologies Ltd. demonstrated robust intraday strength on 24 Feb 2026, surging 5.06% to touch a day’s high of Rs 2,700.45. This performance notably outpaced the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector and the broader market, underscoring the stock’s resilience amid a declining Sensex.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>f135ad93009471af0bc6546b2300fa00</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:45:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hexaware Technologies Ltd Hits Intraday Low Amid Price Pressure on 24 Feb 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hexaware-technologies-ltd-hits-intraday-low-amid-price-pressure-on-24-feb-2026-3853317</link><description>Hexaware Technologies Ltd experienced a significant intraday decline on 24 Feb 2026, touching a new 52-week low of Rs 477 as the stock faced notable price pressure amid broader market weakness and sector underperformance.
Time: 14 minutes ago</description><guid>c080e9a231ac413e1e2565da023f38f5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:45:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Swiggy Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amidst Bearish Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/swiggy-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amidst-bearish-price-action-3853314</link><description>Swiggy Ltd, a prominent player in the E-Retail and E-Commerce sector, has witnessed a notable surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, rising by 10.98% to 51,975 contracts. This increase comes amid a sustained downtrend in the stock price, which has declined over 6% in the past four trading sessions, signalling a complex interplay of market positioning and investor sentiment.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>11df56a2e49c6c90bdc47232e3375340</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:45:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>FSN E-Commerce Ventures Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/fsn-e-commerce-ventures-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3853316</link><description>FSN E-Commerce Ventures Ltd, the parent company of NYKAA, witnessed a notable 10.0% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment on 24 Feb 2026, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock underperforming its sector and broader indices. This surge in open interest, coupled with volume and price action, offers insights into evolving market positioning and potential directional bets among traders.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>734026df4f14a2f755c2d6f19c0845a7</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:45:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Premier Energies Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/premier-energies-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3853318</link><description>Premier Energies Ltd (NSE: PREMIERENE), a mid-cap player in the Other Electrical Equipment sector, has witnessed a notable 14.9% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this, the stock underperformed its sector and broader indices on 24 Feb 2026, reflecting a complex interplay of factors influencing its near-term outlook.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>5dcefd79f6118d2372020a52b2105f1b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:45:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Eternal Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eternal-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amidst-prolonged-downtrend-3853313</link><description>Eternal Ltd, a prominent player in the E-Retail and E-Commerce sector, has witnessed a significant 16.6% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock’s ongoing six-day losing streak and a 11.4% decline over the period. This development reflects evolving market positioning and potential directional bets as investors reassess the stock’s outlook amid broader sectoral and market pressures.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>f241af89be913cb5f03af8ebf3e40532</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:45:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KPIT Technologies Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kpit-technologies-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-prolonged-downtrend-3853312</link><description>KPIT Technologies Ltd has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, coinciding with a sustained decline in its share price. The stock’s open interest rose by nearly 12% on 24 Feb 2026, signalling heightened market activity and shifting positioning among traders amid a challenging market backdrop.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>9b15b00e69803694c7f8bfd919de0fa5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:45:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IDFC First Bank Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/idfc-first-bank-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-price-action-3853311</link><description>IDFC First Bank Ltd. has witnessed a notable 13.2% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this surge, the stock continues to trade below all major moving averages, reflecting a complex technical backdrop that investors must carefully analyse.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>15a5f2c1936f05fa92b46e3dc9ca758b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:45:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JSW Energy Ltd Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jsw-energy-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-market-signals-3853308</link><description>JSW Energy Ltd (JSWENERGY) has witnessed a notable 15.11% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this surge, the stock has underperformed its sector and broader indices, reflecting a complex interplay of market sentiment and technical factors.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>d1d4f210c128ead9287e881a5d621066</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:45:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sun-pharmaceutical-industries-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-market-positioning-3853307</link><description>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd (SUNPHARMA) has witnessed a notable surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling increased market participation and potential directional bets. The stock’s open interest rose by 13.46% to 1,49,669 contracts from the previous 1,31,919, accompanied by robust volume and rising investor interest, reflecting a bullish undertone in the pharmaceuticals sector.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>f0f66a156e100b3ee30daecd14654757</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:45:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Yes Bank Ltd. Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amidst Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/yes-bank-ltd-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amidst-mixed-market-signals-3853309</link><description>Yes Bank Ltd., a mid-cap player in the private sector banking space, has witnessed a notable 12.33% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this uptick, the stock continues to trade below key moving averages and has experienced a modest decline over recent sessions, reflecting a complex interplay of bullish and bearish sentiments among traders.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>6ee2a2534fd2ff4526535a9c12a707bb</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:45:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SRF Ltd. Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Downward Price Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/srf-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-downward-price-pressure-3853306</link><description>SRF Ltd., a key player in the specialty chemicals sector, has witnessed a notable 13.1% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity despite the stock hitting a fresh 52-week low. This development, coupled with declining price trends and increased delivery volumes, suggests a complex interplay of market positioning and investor sentiment that warrants close analysis.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>e36babd9bb58a5d53bdff876d9b7b1ec</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:45:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Steel Authority Of India Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bullish Market Positioning</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/steel-authority-of-india-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bullish-market-positioning-3853304</link><description>Steel Authority Of India Ltd. (SAIL) has witnessed a significant surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor sentiment. The stock’s open interest jumped by 32.67% to 66,235 contracts from 49,924, accompanied by robust volume and rising investor participation, suggesting a potential directional bet on the ferrous metals giant as it nears its 52-week high.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>6e0a530c5c15d3faa5d5f0520334be9e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:45:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Inox Wind Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/inox-wind-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-price-action-3853310</link><description>Inox Wind Ltd, a key player in the Heavy Electrical Equipment sector, has witnessed a significant 14.7% surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this spike, the stock continues to underperform, hitting a fresh 52-week low and trading below all major moving averages, reflecting persistent bearish sentiment.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>e74050d09338c585cb93c8aba19c3385</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:45:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TVS Motor Company Sees Significant Open Interest Surge Amidst Mixed Market Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tvs-motor-company-sees-significant-open-interest-surge-amidst-mixed-market-signals-3853305</link><description>TVS Motor Company Ltd has witnessed a notable 13.7% increase in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a modest decline in the stock price, the surge in open interest and volume suggests evolving directional bets among traders, warranting close attention from market participants.
Time: 15 minutes ago</description><guid>22e6951051c587e891f5449f80766583</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:45:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:45:46 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>