<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:18:56 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Gajanand International Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gajanand-international-ltd-fallingrising-3815185</link><description>On 01-Feb, Gajanand International Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, closing at ₹9.25, down ₹0.85 or 8.42% from the previous session. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s underperformance relative to broader market benchmarks and sector peers, driven by subdued investor participation and technical weaknesses.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>88f5e37ad74a61a689b9c38823ef3c93</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sahasra Electronic Solutions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sahasra-electronic-solutions-ltd-fallingrising-3815184</link><description>On 01-Feb, Sahasra Electronic Solutions Ltd witnessed a notable rise in its share price, climbing 6.18% to ₹264.40, driven by increased investor participation and outperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>506de0cdc8ae5a6af41fc7806a58a484</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Akums Drugs &amp; Pharmaceuticals Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-akums-drugs-pharmaceuticals-ltd-fallingrising-3815183</link><description>On 01-Feb, Akums Drugs &amp; Pharmaceuticals Ltd saw its share price rise by 1.01% to ₹444.65, continuing a positive momentum that has lasted for seven consecutive days. Despite this short-term gain, the stock’s longer-term performance remains subdued, reflecting a complex interplay of improving profits, institutional buying, and underlying fundamental challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>cd3df033d71278dbf1eacc2bdf9fcddd</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Rajputana Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-rajputana-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3815182</link><description>On 01-Feb, Rajputana Industries Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 5.62% to close at ₹75.50. This movement reflects a complex interplay of strong operational metrics overshadowed by recent underperformance and market sentiment challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ccd1c8c1966437b5ce1ecba79d1c451b</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Entero Healthcare Solutions Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-entero-healthcare-solutions-ltd-fallingrising-3815181</link><description>As of 01-Feb, Entero Healthcare Solutions Ltd’s stock price has risen by 1.85% to ₹1,123.00, marking a notable recovery after a five-day decline and outperforming its sector peers. This upward movement reflects a combination of robust financial performance, improving investor participation, and attractive valuation metrics despite mixed longer-term returns.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>bcdf14fcec62f909b7d7632244770ee5</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Muthoot Microfin Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-muthoot-microfin-ltd-fallingrising-3815180</link><description>On 01-Feb, Muthoot Microfin Ltd’s stock price fell by 1.94% to close at ₹174.30, continuing a four-day losing streak despite demonstrating resilience relative to its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>89b598e5052888e4cea29a50d07ac2af</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Italian Edibles Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-italian-edibles-ltd-fallingrising-3815179</link><description>On 01-Feb, Italian Edibles Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, falling by 9.55% to close at ₹24.15. This drop brings the stock perilously close to its 52-week low, reflecting ongoing challenges and underperformance relative to both its sector and broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>61ab480e3984185c1a4788bb62197f72</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-nuvama-wealth-management-ltd-fallingrising-3815178</link><description>On 01-Feb, Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, falling by 7.28% to close at ₹1,247.00. This drop comes after three consecutive days of gains and reflects a broader underperformance relative to its sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>21082ff2f1cd297bcd4477ac11d85a71</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vinyas Innovative Technologies Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vinyas-innovative-technologies-ltd-fallingrising-3815177</link><description>On 01-Feb, Vinyas Innovative Technologies Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 6.41% to close at ₹1,004.85. This drop reflects a broader short-term weakness in the stock’s performance relative to market benchmarks and sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d2b1507e4737008048f0aa3e3d2173ed</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Jio Financial Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-jio-financial-services-ltd-fallingrising-3815176</link><description>On 01-Feb, Jio Financial Services Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, falling by 4.66% to close at ₹242.60. This drop reflects a combination of disappointing quarterly financial results, broader sector weakness, and technical indicators signalling bearish momentum.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5ed99cb3ea6a02f63401ba06debd9823</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is BEML Land Assets Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-beml-land-assets-ltd-fallingrising-3815175</link><description>On 01-Feb, BEML Land Assets Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹186.30, down ₹4.45 or 2.33% from the previous session. This drop reflects a continuation of a downward trend amid persistent weak fundamentals and consistent underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>89537f50907d20fe65ddce1529dffa62</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Nuvoco Vistas Corporation Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-nuvoco-vistas-corporation-ltd-fallingrising-3815174</link><description>On 01-Feb, Nuvoco Vistas Corporation Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, closing at ₹331.45, down ₹16.20 or 4.66%. This drop reflects a continuation of recent underperformance amid broader sector weakness and disappointing company fundamentals.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b83b35d7e214fd62fc36a59e4e822d5c</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Gayatri Rubbers and Chemicals Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-gayatri-rubbers-and-chemicals-ltd-fallingrising-3815173</link><description>On 01-Feb, shares of Gayatri Rubbers and Chemicals Ltd rose sharply by 5.0%, closing at ₹389.55, reflecting a robust weekly performance that significantly outpaced the broader market and its sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ffdccb06060e1e56fde16ad716945156</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is AGS Transact Technologies Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ags-transact-technologies-ltd-fallingrising-3815172</link><description>On 01-Feb, AGS Transact Technologies Ltd recorded a 3.27% rise in its share price, closing at ₹4.11. This modest gain follows a four-day consecutive rally, during which the stock has appreciated by 9.02%, outperforming its sector by 2.48% on the day. Despite this short-term positive momentum, the company continues to grapple with significant long-term fundamental weaknesses and operational challenges that have severely impacted investor confidence and its market valuation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ed3649d424ea9c096926bcba3a2bd611</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is EKI Energy Services Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-eki-energy-services-ltd-fallingrising-3815171</link><description>On 01-Feb, EKI Energy Services Ltd witnessed a significant price increase of 14.3%, closing at ₹103.04, marking a notable rebound after two days of decline and outperforming its sector and benchmark indices despite ongoing fundamental challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ff0adb3edd711d0cd64925b15984ba94</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is United Van Der Horst Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-united-van-der-horst-ltd-fallingrising-3815170</link><description>On 01-Feb, United Van Der Horst Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 4.99% to close at ₹41.66. This drop comes after a sustained period of gains and strong fundamental performance, highlighting a short-term correction amid broader market dynamics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>75c89dc6a8aa08b1cedcd54c3e26833e</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ircon International Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ircon-international-ltd-fallingrising-3815169</link><description>As of 01-Feb, Ircon International Ltd’s stock price has fallen sharply by 6.28% to ₹153.60, reflecting mounting concerns over the company’s deteriorating financial health and sustained underperformance relative to market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c51c1b0e877633bb3846e8953223e42e</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Sikko Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-sikko-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3815167</link><description>On 01-Feb, Sikko Industries Ltd witnessed a significant price increase, rising by 8.87% to close at ₹4.54, outperforming both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>cec5db3bbb14d009733dca4037c398fd</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Aspira Pathlab &amp; Diagnostics Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-aspira-pathlab-diagnostics-ltd-fallingrising-3815168</link><description>On 01-Feb, Aspira Pathlab &amp; Diagnostics Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹61.80, down by ₹1.90 or 2.98%. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock's underperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>13daee99338db34a51021fa4c8b23dbd</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Omfurn India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-omfurn-india-ltd-fallingrising-3815166</link><description>On 01-Feb, Omfurn India Ltd witnessed a sharp decline in its share price, falling by 19.95% to close at ₹51.55, marking a significant underperformance relative to the broader market and its sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c533fa8b5cbde79de60c4180d6e2c93f</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:18:56 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>