<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:21:03 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Ortel Communications Ltd’s Volatile Week: 1.23% Decline Amid Circuit Hits and Trading Freezes</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ortel-communications-ltds-volatile-week-123-decline-amid-circuit-hits-and-trading-freezes-3862458</link><description>Ortel Communications Ltd experienced a turbulent week from 23 to 27 February 2026, marked by sharp intraday price swings including multiple circuit hits. The stock opened the week at Rs.1.65, briefly surged to an upper circuit on 23 February, then plunged to lower circuit limits on 24 and 25 February, before another upper circuit spike on 27 February. Despite these volatile moves, the stock closed the week marginally lower at Rs.1.61, down 1.23%, slightly underperforming the Sensex’s 0.96% decline over the same period.
Time: 44 minutes ago</description><guid>9418871673559f451a492be8eecd626f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:21:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Steel Authority Of India Ltd Gains 4.53%: 8 Key Factors Driving the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/steel-authority-of-india-ltd-gains-453-8-key-factors-driving-the-rally-3862457</link><description>Steel Authority Of India Ltd (SAIL) delivered a robust weekly performance, gaining 4.53% from Rs.158.80 to Rs.166.00 between 23 and 27 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex which declined by 0.96% over the same period. The stock demonstrated strong technical momentum, hitting multiple 52-week highs and attracting heightened trading volumes and open interest, signalling renewed investor confidence amid mixed broader market conditions.
Time: 44 minutes ago</description><guid>7de73751094b419e8ba7a9e6a0e118e3</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:21:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sasken Technologies Declines 6.02%: 5 Key Factors Behind the Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sasken-technologies-declines-602-5-key-factors-behind-the-prolonged-downtrend-3862456</link><description>Sasken Technologies Ltd experienced a challenging week from 23 to 27 February 2026, with its stock price declining by 6.02% to close at Rs.1,152.90, underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.96% over the same period. The week was marked by a series of technical setbacks, fresh 52-week lows, and persistent bearish momentum amid subdued financial performance and valuation concerns.
Time: 44 minutes ago</description><guid>627b09a42328dabff875492fa471dd84</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:21:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Power Finance Corporation Ltd Gains 0.66%: 4 Key Factors Driving Mixed Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/power-finance-corporation-ltd-gains-066-4-key-factors-driving-mixed-momentum-3862455</link><description>Power Finance Corporation Ltd (PFC) closed the week ending 27 February 2026 with a modest gain of 0.66%, rising from ₹410.05 to ₹412.75. This performance contrasted with the broader Sensex, which declined by 0.96% over the same period, signalling relative resilience amid mixed technical signals and valuation shifts. The week featured a series of valuation recalibrations, technical momentum changes, and a downgrade in rating, all influencing investor sentiment and price action.
Time: 44 minutes ago</description><guid>5045a62fdf7cbd7203a6cb9565e33e69</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:21:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Repco Home Finance Declines 2.88%: Mixed Technicals and Flat Fundamentals Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/repco-home-finance-declines-288-mixed-technicals-and-flat-fundamentals-shape-the-week-3862454</link><description>Repco Home Finance Ltd closed the week down 2.88% at Rs.378.85, underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.96% over the same period. The week was marked by a shift in technical momentum from sideways to mildly bearish, accompanied by a downgrade from MarketsMOJO to a Sell rating amid mixed fundamentals and subdued financial trends. Despite short-term weakness, the stock’s longer-term returns remain relatively strong, highlighting a complex investment landscape.
Time: 44 minutes ago</description><guid>e933f0c819d6733892f5dff191216fad</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:21:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reliance Communications Ltd Falls 13.86%: 7 Key Factors Driving the Sharp Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/reliance-communications-ltd-falls-1386-7-key-factors-driving-the-sharp-decline-3862453</link><description>Reliance Communications Ltd experienced a steep decline of 13.86% over the week ending 27 February 2026, closing at Rs.0.87 from Rs.1.01 the previous Friday. This underperformance was stark against the Sensex’s modest 0.96% fall, reflecting intense selling pressure amid deteriorating fundamentals, technical weakness, and sectoral challenges. The stock repeatedly hit lower circuit limits and new 52-week lows, signalling sustained bearish sentiment and investor caution.
Time: 44 minutes ago</description><guid>26faf21606c88d98b645417db6e305ac</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:21:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Finserv Declines 3.17%: 2 Key Factors Shaping This Week’s Movement</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bajaj-finserv-declines-317-2-key-factors-shaping-this-weeks-movement-3862452</link><description>Bajaj Finserv Ltd experienced a challenging week, closing at Rs.1,992.70 on 27 February 2026, down 3.17% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.2,057.95. This decline outpaced the broader Sensex’s 0.96% fall over the same period, reflecting a combination of heightened derivatives activity and a significant downgrade by MarketsMOJO amid technical and valuation concerns.
Time: 44 minutes ago</description><guid>84c41f3d46adfb3a52e8956c77761426</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:21:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SRF Ltd. Declines 4.65% Amid Bearish Momentum and Rising Derivatives Activity</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/srf-ltd-declines-465-amid-bearish-momentum-and-rising-derivatives-activity-3862451</link><description>SRF Ltd. closed the week down 4.65% at Rs.2,562.90, underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.96%. The stock faced sustained selling pressure, hitting a 52-week low on 24 February amid bearish technical signals and a sharp surge in derivatives open interest, reflecting heightened market activity and cautious sentiment.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>0a728e46d8d50c451d02b5ef657bd77b</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:21:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank Of Baroda Gains 4.18%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bank-of-baroda-gains-418-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3862448</link><description>Bank Of Baroda’s shares advanced 4.18% over the week ending 27 February 2026, closing at Rs.321.85 from Rs.308.95 the previous Friday. This performance notably outpaced the Sensex, which declined 0.96% during the same period, underscoring the stock’s resilience amid mixed market conditions. The week was marked by multiple new 52-week and all-time highs, strong institutional interest, and technical momentum shifts that collectively shaped the stock’s trajectory.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>d0d4515583fea1748a7cdafd7f1d6b9b</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:21:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Puravankara Ltd Falls 13.70%: 3 Key Factors Behind the Steep Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/puravankara-ltd-falls-1370-3-key-factors-behind-the-steep-weekly-decline-3862445</link><description>Puravankara Ltd’s shares declined sharply by 13.70% over the week ending 27 February 2026, closing at Rs.198.75 from Rs.230.30 the previous Friday. This underperformance was stark against the Sensex’s modest 0.96% fall, reflecting persistent bearish momentum amid technical downturns, fresh 52-week lows, and subdued fundamental metrics that weighed heavily on investor sentiment.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>ee150069bb2557fefff7a5b1a80c46f2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:21:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>63 Moons Technologies Ltd Falls 6.12%: Key Factors Behind the Steep Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/63-moons-technologies-ltd-falls-612-key-factors-behind-the-steep-weekly-decline-3862444</link><description>63 Moons Technologies Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its share price declining by 6.12% from Rs.641.85 to Rs.602.55, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.96% over the same period. The stock faced intense selling pressure early in the week, hitting an intraday low and a fresh 52-week low, before stabilising modestly in the latter sessions amid subdued volumes and persistent bearish momentum.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>6e79e57c50f26a1c41f939b27f8083cd</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:21:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sadhana Nitro Chem Ltd’s Volatile Week: 10% Surge Followed by Consecutive Lower Circuits</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sadhana-nitro-chem-ltds-volatile-week-10-surge-followed-by-consecutive-lower-circuits-3862449</link><description>Sadhana Nitro Chem Ltd experienced a turbulent week from 23 to 27 February 2026, opening at Rs.2.00 and closing slightly lower at Rs.1.98, marking a 1.00% decline. The stock initially surged 10.00% on 23 February amid exceptional volume and strong buying pressure, hitting its upper circuit. However, this momentum reversed sharply with the stock hitting lower circuit limits on three consecutive days, reflecting intense selling pressure and investor panic. Despite the broader Sensex declining 0.96% over the week, Sadhana Nitro Chem’s price volatility and volume spikes underscored a challenging trading environment for this micro-cap commodity chemicals player.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>171508c0074c50dfaf55deaaefef1991</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:21:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Synthiko Foils Ltd Falls 12.94%: Downgrade and Mixed Technical Signals Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/synthiko-foils-ltd-falls-1294-downgrade-and-mixed-technical-signals-shape-the-week-3862447</link><description>Synthiko Foils Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its stock price declining 12.94% from ₹2,048.75 to ₹1,783.60, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.96% over the same period. The week was marked by a downgrade to a Strong Sell rating amid deteriorating financial fundamentals and mixed technical signals, culminating in heightened caution among investors despite the stock’s impressive long-term returns.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>1bdb9b7fc6459cb187edea777c99e0af</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:21:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Greenply Industries Falls 0.97%: 3 Key Factors Behind the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/greenply-industries-falls-097-3-key-factors-behind-the-weekly-decline-3862446</link><description>Greenply Industries Ltd ended the week marginally lower by 0.97%, closing at Rs.220.60 on 27 February 2026, slightly underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.96% over the same period. The week was marked by a downgrade to a strong sell rating, a shift in valuation perception, and the stock hitting a fresh 52-week low, reflecting a challenging environment for the company amid weakening financials and bearish technical signals.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>9e23999d4eeacd4b5fa891ad52817486</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:21:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Larsen &amp; Toubro Ltd Declines 2.28%: 5 Key Factors Behind This Week’s Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/larsen-toubro-ltd-declines-228-5-key-factors-behind-this-weeks-volatility-3862450</link><description>Larsen &amp; Toubro Ltd (L&amp;T) experienced a volatile week ending 27 February 2026, with its share price declining 2.28% from Rs.4,380.25 to Rs.4,280.55. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s smaller 0.96% drop over the same period, reflecting mixed investor sentiment amid strong institutional interest and technical fluctuations. The stock hit new 52-week and all-time highs early in the week before facing profit-taking and consolidation in the latter sessions.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>21a18b6d8e95f608f254276247cb9302</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:21:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Stovec Industries Falls 5.10%: Valuation Risks and Margin Pressures Weigh</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/stovec-industries-falls-510-valuation-risks-and-margin-pressures-weigh-3862442</link><description>Stovec Industries Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its share price declining 5.10% from Rs.1,924.55 to Rs.1,826.45, underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.96%. The week was marked by a sharp margin collapse, persistent financial challenges, and heightened valuation concerns, all contributing to a cautious market sentiment despite a marginal improvement in the company’s financial trend score.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>6cf62c85df444a857e508ea4eb5f39f7</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:21:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Diligent Industries Ltd Declines 1.31%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/diligent-industries-ltd-declines-131-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-downtrend-3862443</link><description>Diligent Industries Ltd experienced a challenging week, closing at Rs.2.26 on 27 February 2026, down 1.31% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.2.29. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s decline of 0.96% over the same period, signalling a slightly weaker relative showing amid mixed valuation and technical developments. Key events including a valuation upgrade, a bearish technical formation, and a rating downgrade shaped the stock’s trajectory throughout the week.
Time: 45 minutes ago</description><guid>0dd1f13eb040e637d573ab47cf66da90</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:21:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mayur Uniquoters Declines 4.00%: Mixed Technical Signals and Valuation Shifts Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mayur-uniquoters-declines-400-mixed-technical-signals-and-valuation-shifts-shape-the-week-3862441</link><description>Mayur Uniquoters Ltd closed the week ending 27 Feb 2026 at Rs.531.65, marking a 4.00% decline from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.553.80. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s more modest 0.96% fall over the same period, reflecting a week of mixed technical signals and valuation shifts that influenced investor sentiment and price action.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>3019bc281247a66a7d9c9b9a9af0aaa4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:21:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Ltd’s Mixed Week: -0.38% Price Change Amid Technical Consolidation</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mahindra-mahindra-ltds-mixed-week--038-price-change-amid-technical-consolidation-3862440</link><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Ltd (M&amp;M) experienced a week of mixed signals, closing marginally lower by 0.38% at Rs.3,399.90 compared to the previous Friday’s close of Rs.3,413.00. This performance slightly outpaced the broader Sensex, which declined 0.96% over the same period. The week was marked by significant open interest activity, a downgrade in the company’s Mojo Grade to Hold, and a shift in technical momentum towards sideways consolidation, reflecting a cautious investor stance amid sectoral and market uncertainties.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>54c6a7f45045860c5aad90483c85be15</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:21:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SEPC Ltd Falls 7.30%: 5 Key Factors Behind the Steep Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sepc-ltd-falls-730-5-key-factors-behind-the-steep-weekly-decline-3862438</link><description>SEPC Ltd experienced a challenging week from 23 to 27 February 2026, with its stock price declining by 7.30% to close at Rs.7.49, significantly underperforming the Sensex which fell 0.96% over the same period. Despite sporadic volume surges and a brief technical upgrade in its Mojo Grade, the stock remained under pressure amid persistent sector weakness and bearish technical signals.
Time: 46 minutes ago</description><guid>7f689180eef962836ee8498341010bad</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:21:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:21:03 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>