<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:19:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Are Diffusion Engineers Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-diffusion-engineers-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3826992</link><description>Diffusion Engineers Ltd's latest results show strong year-on-year growth in net profit and sales, but sequential declines and challenges in operational efficiency and cash flow management raise concerns about sustainability. Overall, the performance is mixed, indicating a need for careful monitoring.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>eab85481b384c7872c00a648525fab8e</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:19:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are KRN Heat Exchanger and Refrigeration Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-krn-heat-exchanger-and-refrigeration-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3826991</link><description>KRN Heat Exchanger and Refrigeration Ltd's latest results show strong year-on-year growth, with a net profit increase of 46.39% and revenue up 66.93%. However, recent quarterly performance indicates a slowdown in growth, raising concerns about future sustainability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ec7ed828c33c90e5ebd01f1e2a9aeb8f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:19:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Baazar Style Retail Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-baazar-style-retail-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3826990</link><description>Baazar Style Retail Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show mixed performance: while revenue increased by 13.33% year-on-year, net profit fell by 63.18% from the previous quarter, raising concerns about profitability despite improved operational efficiency. The company's high debt-to-equity ratio and below-benchmark capital efficiency metrics suggest ongoing challenges ahead.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0a375681aa71060f2d990c9392cabb11</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:19:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Kalpataru Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-kalpataru-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3826989</link><description>Kalpataru Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, showing a net loss of ₹62.78 crores and a 36.39% drop in net sales, alongside a negative operating margin of -14.78% and high leverage, indicating significant operational challenges and sustainability issues.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c288fc53753f202e4ce72458a926c501</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:19:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Sanathan Textiles Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-sanathan-textiles-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3826988</link><description>Sanathan Textiles Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results show positive net sales growth of 9.75% sequentially and 10.22% year-on-year, but a concerning 50.23% decline in net profit, indicating significant operational challenges and rising costs that need to be addressed.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>fcb7a4e2fa0f31ebad34eb971747d6a8</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:19:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Akme Fintrade (India) Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-akme-fintrade-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3826987</link><description>Akme Fintrade (India) Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth with net sales up 44.81% year-on-year, but profitability concerns arise as net profit growth is modest and profit margins have contracted, indicating potential issues with operational efficiency and rising costs. Overall, while the company is expanding, the quality of that growth may be in question.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>08d36b39986b2cdd8097358767f9639d</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:19:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Max Estates Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-max-estates-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3826986</link><description>Max Estates Ltd's latest results are concerning, showing a slight increase in net sales but a significant decline in profitability, with a net loss of ₹1.21 crores and a sharp drop in operating profit margin. The company faces operational challenges and rising debt levels, indicating a critical phase of financial distress.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c6c38260034ec735dda30abf88aadf8f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:19:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Diensten Tech Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-diensten-tech-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3826985</link><description>Diensten Tech Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show strong revenue growth of 78.18% to ₹52.03 crores, but the company reported a net loss of ₹3.88 crores and faces significant operational challenges, including high employee costs and a concerning debt burden, indicating a complex financial situation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>119437f5255016107c0981c704332dcb</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:19:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Jana Small Finance Bank Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-jana-small-finance-bank-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3826984</link><description>Jana Small Finance Bank Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show a net profit decline to ₹9.69 crores due to increased provisions, despite record interest earnings and improved asset quality. Overall, the bank faces significant operational challenges and profitability concerns that warrant close monitoring.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d3e56c7d7a4bfec317200dbf2abdc24e</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:19:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Medi Assist Healthcare Services Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-medi-assist-healthcare-services-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3826983</link><description>Medi Assist Healthcare Services Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth of 28.88% year-on-year, with net sales of ₹239.68 crores; however, net profit plummeted by 85.88% to ₹4.17 crores, raising concerns about operational efficiency and cost management. The significant decline in profitability amidst rising costs suggests challenges for the company's financial stability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ff59d5b6e49012d6d68f12065f992354</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:19:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Shradha AI Technologies Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-shradha-ai-technologies-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3826982</link><description>Shradha AI Technologies Ltd's latest results show a significant sequential decline in net sales and profit, raising concerns about operational stability, despite year-on-year growth. The company's reliance on other income and inconsistent revenue growth suggest challenges in maintaining profitability and capital efficiency.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f2ab376b33627e28b810eb7d98479144</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:19:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Gateway Distriparks Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-gateway-distriparks-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3826981</link><description>Gateway Distriparks Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show strong year-on-year sales growth of 39.23% to ₹560.41 crores, but a significant year-on-year profit decline of 85.10% to ₹67.84 crores due to exceptional gains last year. While revenue growth is positive, rising costs and margin compression present challenges for future profitability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2dc4fab91d575ae71dba38c69fba610b</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:19:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Veranda Learning Solutions Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-veranda-learning-solutions-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3826980</link><description>Veranda Learning Solutions Ltd's latest results are concerning, showing a net profit decline of 89.13% and a 7.84% drop in revenue, with heavy reliance on non-operating income and negative returns on capital, indicating significant operational challenges and potential future viability issues.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>99a161735f72ee8680d1bfcadda9d32c</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:19:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Vasa Denticity Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-vasa-denticity-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3826979</link><description>Vasa Denticity Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results are concerning, showing a 71.28% decline in net profit and the lowest operating margin in seven quarters, despite stable revenue growth. The company faces significant operational challenges that could impact its future sustainability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b6ce9c219cae85145e51a94954b4b999</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:19:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Aveer Foods Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-aveer-foods-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3826978</link><description>Aveer Foods Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show strong net sales growth of 30.94% year-on-year, but a significant decline in net profit by 58.73% quarter-on-quarter raises concerns about profitability and cost management. Overall, while revenue performance is robust, margin compression and profitability challenges are notable.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>01ab1b4e94d2b3d54cd3d8ca1df7d3f9</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:19:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Sula Vineyards Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-sula-vineyards-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3826977</link><description>Sula Vineyards Ltd's latest results show significant challenges, with a 58.43% year-on-year decline in net profit and a drop in operating margin to 19.45%. While there was a sequential revenue improvement, overall profitability pressures and declining investor confidence indicate a tough outlook for the company.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1c90cfcf6ccfa4c130349d7ac33f72a2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:19:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Elin Electronics Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-elin-electronics-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3826976</link><description>Elin Electronics Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show a year-on-year revenue growth of 10.21%, but a significant sequential decline of 21.63% and a 64.47% drop in net profit, indicating operational challenges and margin compression. While year-on-year performance is positive, the recent declines raise concerns about the company's stability and efficiency.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>354b49ebf7f62325faa5d40839582ad6</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:19:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Pritika Engineering Components Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-pritika-engineering-components-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3826975</link><description>Pritika Engineering Components Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show mixed performance, with a net profit decline of 25.78% quarter-on-quarter but a year-on-year growth of 16.78%. While there is strong annual growth, the sequential drop in revenue and profit, along with a high debt-to-equity ratio, suggests potential challenges ahead.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d0a820832c13cd047816c704ae116f66</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:19:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Fusion Finance Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-fusion-finance-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3826974</link><description>Fusion Finance Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show a significant turnaround with a net profit of ₹14.05 crores, compared to a loss of ₹719.32 crores last year. However, revenue declined by 15.73%, raising concerns about the sustainability of this profitability amidst ongoing structural challenges.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>36545d82d5183cc5c5b6717e3ea7141f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:19:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Ethos Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-ethos-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3826973</link><description>Ethos Ltd's latest results show strong revenue growth with net sales up 22.20% sequentially and 26.65% year-on-year, but profitability is under pressure, with net profit growth at only 3.19% and declining operating margins. Overall, while sales are robust, the company faces challenges in maintaining profitability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7f0c82da6e8c1835d3ac15911f9d1185</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:19:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:19:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>