<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:21:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Are Lakhotia Polyesters (India) Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-lakhotia-polyesters-india-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3793533</link><description>Lakhotia Polyesters (India) Ltd's latest Q2 FY26 results show significant operational challenges, with net sales increasing 594.17% quarter-on-quarter but declining 70.36% year-on-year. The company reported a net profit of ₹0.60 crores, down 38.78% from the previous quarter, indicating revenue instability and concerns about sustainability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a4c7b7112fda399b81019b5beb27ff9c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:21:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are ISF Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-isf-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3793532</link><description>ISF Ltd's latest results show mixed performance, with a 4.65% increase in net sales and improved operating profit margins, but unchanged net profit and ongoing fundamental issues raise concerns about long-term sustainability. Overall, while there are signs of stabilization, financial health remains a concern.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9f394525728987d1ae88cd54f4d2e93c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:21:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Show Mixed Trends with Mid Caps Leading Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-with-mid-caps-leading-growth-3793596</link><description>The December 2025 quarterly earnings season has delivered a mixed bag of results across 186 stocks, with a notable improvement in positive outcomes compared to previous quarters. While mid-cap companies led the charge with a 69.0% positivity rate, large caps lagged behind at 30.0%, reflecting divergent sectoral and size-based performance trends.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>ad5cfcdaf1e58a327cf2806e4b425e7d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:21:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Equity Markets Slip as Small Caps Drag; Nifty Closes Below 26,000</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/indian-equity-markets-slip-as-small-caps-drag-nifty-closes-below-26000-3793591</link><description>Indian equity markets closed lower on 19 Jan 2026, with the Sensex and Nifty retreating amid broad-based selling pressure. Small caps bore the brunt of the decline, while FMCG stocks provided some respite. Foreign institutional investors remained net sellers, adding to the cautious sentiment ahead of key corporate earnings scheduled for tomorrow.
Time: 4 hours ago</description><guid>8289c1537703cb1c59682ea79197e524</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:21:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Top Small and Micro Cap Stocks Deliver Exceptional Half-Year Returns Amid Bullish Market Sentiment</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/top-small-and-micro-cap-stocks-deliver-exceptional-half-year-returns-amid-bullish-market-sentiment-3793590</link><description>A select group of small and micro cap stocks have outperformed the broader market significantly over the past six months, delivering returns well above benchmark indices. Driven by strong fundamentals, sector tailwinds and bullish technical signals, these stocks have attracted investor attention with gains ranging from over 100% to nearly 190% in half-year performance.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>9a7a0e3b2a19eab7186380876d1cf3b9</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:21:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Top-Performing Stocks Deliver Exceptional Returns Amid Market Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/top-performing-stocks-deliver-exceptional-returns-amid-market-rally-3793589</link><description>Bluegod Enterta., a micro-cap player in the fertilisers sector, has delivered an extraordinary return of 513.61% over the past year, significantly outperforming its peers and the broader market benchmarks. This remarkable surge highlights the stock’s strong fundamentals, bullish technical outlook, and investor confidence amid a challenging economic backdrop.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>9f0bba4224a010a126b4475f0238eb84</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:21:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec 2025 Results Show Mixed Trends with Mid Caps Leading Growth</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-with-mid-caps-leading-growth-3793587</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has unfolded with a notable improvement in positive results, particularly driven by mid-cap companies, while large caps continue to face challenges. With 174 stocks having declared results, the aggregate profit growth and sectoral performances reveal a nuanced market landscape as investors digest mixed outcomes across market capitalisation segments.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>ed09743c1be54dea5298f52a5b15066f</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:21:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sensex Dips 0.22% Amid Broad Market Weakness; Realty Sector Leads Losses</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-dips-022-amid-broad-market-weakness-realty-sector-leads-losses-3793588</link><description>The Indian equity market closed lower on 19 Jan 2026, with the Sensex retreating 186.07 points or 0.22% to 83,384.28 amid broad-based weakness. Market breadth was notably negative, reflecting cautious investor sentiment as key sectors diverged sharply in performance. Realty stocks led the declines while FMCG provided some respite, underscoring a mixed trading session influenced by global cues and domestic factors.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>7b8ec4ed48aa954271e3880e12f6e520</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:21:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sensex Dips 0.32% Amid Broad Market Weakness; Realty Sector Leads Losses</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-dips-032-amid-broad-market-weakness-realty-sector-leads-losses-3793586</link><description>Indian equity benchmarks closed lower on 19 Jan 2026, with the Sensex retreating 267.66 points or 0.32% to 83,302.69, weighed down by broad-based selling across sectors. Market breadth was weak as declines outpaced advances significantly, while FMCG stocks bucked the trend to emerge as sectoral leaders amid subdued global cues.
Time: 6 hours ago</description><guid>651860a97d83b93fc694ac8b91447a12</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:21:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sensex Dips 0.56% Amid Broad Market Weakness; Realty Sector Leads Losses</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-dips-056-amid-broad-market-weakness-realty-sector-leads-losses-3793585</link><description>Indian equity markets closed lower on 19 Jan 2026, with the Sensex falling 465.43 points or 0.56% to 83,104.92, reflecting broad-based selling pressure. Market breadth was weak as 32 of 38 sectors declined, led by the realty segment, while only six sectors managed gains. Mid and small caps underperformed, signalling cautious investor sentiment amid mixed global cues and subdued foreign institutional activity.
Time: 7 hours ago</description><guid>6034c27329bd2a965994792b08d99333</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:21:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sensex Dips 0.64% Amid Broad Market Weakness; Realty Sector Leads Declines</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-dips-064-amid-broad-market-weakness-realty-sector-leads-declines-3793584</link><description>Indian equity markets closed lower on 19 Jan 2026, with the Sensex retreating 533.77 points or 0.64% to settle at 83,036.58. Market breadth was weak as declines dominated advances across the BSE500, reflecting cautious investor sentiment amid mixed global cues and sectoral pressures.
Time: 8 hours ago</description><guid>41302f373215d6109e889b0f742f3847</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:21:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sensex Dips 0.63% as Realty Sector Slumps; Mid and Small Caps Also Under Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-dips-063-as-realty-sector-slumps-mid-and-small-caps-also-under-pressure-3793583</link><description>Indian equity markets closed lower on 19 Jan 2026, with the Sensex falling 530.31 points or 0.63% to 83,040.04, weighed down by broad-based sector declines and subdued investor sentiment. Midcap and small cap indices also ended in the red, reflecting cautious trading ahead of key corporate earnings.
Time: 9 hours ago</description><guid>ca043e950ee9ab20ec488d370d6d23a1</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:21:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Makers Laboratories Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/makers-laboratories-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3793965</link><description>Makers Laboratories Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 22 September 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 19 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 10 hours ago</description><guid>e6733d3aa9062c1538cc6870b6409c74</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:21:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prithvi Exchange (India) Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/prithvi-exchange-india-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3793966</link><description>Prithvi Exchange (India) Ltd is rated 'Strong Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 11 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 19 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 10 hours ago</description><guid>7ee2e7c3659de8d75679cd86d242c9f8</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:21:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Rajnish Retail Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/rajnish-retail-ltd-is-rated-sell-3793963</link><description>Rajnish Retail Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 26 September 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 19 January 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market performance.
Time: 10 hours ago</description><guid>1a81c15f857095e2388d88cbd3f6141f</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:21:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:21:28 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>