<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:27:49 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Chemfab Alkalis Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/chemfab-alkalis-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3767328</link><description>Chemfab Alkalis has reached a new 52-week low, closing near Rs 435.05, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing price decline. The stock’s recent performance reflects a challenging period for the company within the commodity chemicals sector, as it trades well below key moving averages and continues to lag behind broader market indices.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2930bb387a7ef9f917c7af8911e4eb0e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:27:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TTK Healthcare Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Prolonged Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ttk-healthcare-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-prolonged-underperformance-3767329</link><description>TTK Healthcare has reached a 52-week low, with its stock price touching Rs 1023.8 during intraday trading, marking a significant milestone in its recent market trajectory. This development reflects ongoing challenges in the company’s financial performance and market positioning over the past year.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>17b1a7e71bd554bccf5084e8a7e00802</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:27:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TCPL Packaging . Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Market Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tcpl-packaging-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-market-underperformance-3767330</link><description>TCPL Packaging . has reached a new 52-week low, with its share price touching ₹2,864.10, marking a significant point in its recent trading history. This development comes amid a broader market context where the stock has lagged behind key benchmarks and sector peers over the past year.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>064551141791def9b75c0d47d3f454ac</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:27:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sensex and Nifty Trade Flat Amid Mixed Sector Performance; Jupiter Wagons and Coforge Lead Market Moves</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-and-nifty-end-flat-amid-mixed-sectoral-trends-small-caps-outperform-3767327</link><description>The Indian equity markets exhibited a subdued session on 23 December 2025, with the Sensex and Nifty indices trading largely flat amid a mixed performance across sectors. While select large caps and small caps showed notable movements, overall market breadth remained modestly positive as investors weighed global cues and domestic factors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7f80ac6c216317c9b50ac2c195dde0d9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:27:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Samrat Forgings Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.242 Amid Market Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/samrat-forgings-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs242-amidst-weak-financial-metrics-3767326</link><description>Samrat Forgings has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.242, marking a significant decline in its share price amid broader market fluctuations and sectoral underperformance. The stock's recent movement reflects ongoing challenges within the Castings &amp; Forgings industry and highlights the company’s current financial position.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>2f2d67c5d9d9959966f3a39a6654ec0b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:27:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sundrop Brands Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.685 Amid Market Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sundrop-brands-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs685-amid-continued-underperformance-3767320</link><description>Sundrop Brands, a key player in the edible oil sector, touched a new 52-week low of Rs.685 today, marking a significant decline amid broader market fluctuations and sectoral underperformance. The stock’s fall comes after two days of gains, reversing recent momentum and trading below all major moving averages.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>863b78918051eea2ebd80df31e466960</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:27:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>DB (International) Stock Brokers Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.23.62</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/db-international-stock-brokers-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs2362-3767323</link><description>DB (International) Stock Brokers has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.23.62, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid a challenging market environment. This level reflects a substantial drop from its 52-week high of Rs.54.58, underscoring the stock's underperformance relative to broader market indices and sector peers.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>6c781914a9a687a9446ca5e7d012cb33</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:27:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanofi India Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.4050 Amidst Sector Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sanofi-india-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs4050-amidst-prolonged-underperformance-3767321</link><description>Sanofi India’s share price reached a new 52-week low of Rs.4050 today, reflecting a continued downward trend over the past year. The stock’s performance contrasts with broader market movements, as it underperformed its sector and key indices amid subdued sales growth and profit metrics.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>06a334cd8cf6b991a01c11bb8c6a4262</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:27:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Kesar Enterprises Stock Hits 52-Week Low at Rs.6.06 Amidst Prolonged Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kesar-enterprises-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-financial-struggles-3767325</link><description>Kesar Enterprises, a player in the sugar industry, recorded a fresh 52-week low of Rs.6.06 today, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing price decline. This new low reflects a continuation of the stock’s downward trajectory over the past year, contrasting sharply with broader market trends.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>817b603c5677fc44cddf7820226fd27c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:27:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Magnus Steel &amp; Infra Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.32.3</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/magnus-steel-infra-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs323-3767322</link><description>Magnus Steel &amp; Infra has reached a significant milestone by touching a new 52-week high of Rs.32.3, marking a notable phase of momentum for the stock within the Other Electrical Equipment sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>897b8eeeb764c7431e51642d6fa6f30f</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:27:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sreeleathers . Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.211 Amidst Market Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sreeleathers-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs211-amidst-continued-downtrend-3767324</link><description>Sreeleathers . has reached a new 52-week low of Rs.211, marking a significant price level for the footwear company. The stock has experienced a decline over the past two days, reflecting ongoing pressures within the sector and broader market fluctuations.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>089140ed03e7919716ccd2497b270d9b</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:27:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cupid Stock Surges Over 400% in Six Months, Outperforming Market Benchmarks</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/small-and-micro-cap-stocks-deliver-exceptional-half-year-returns-amidst-market-volatility-3767316</link><description>Cupid has delivered an extraordinary return of 413.9% over the past six months, significantly outpacing broader market indices and emerging as a standout performer among small-cap stocks in the FMCG sector. This remarkable surge reflects a combination of bullish technical signals and very positive financial indicators, despite the stock’s valuation remaining on the expensive side.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>9d779e6c52049cd64ce6e32704af0d45</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:27:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SMT Engineering Delivers Exceptional 1810% Return, Outshining Market Benchmarks</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/smt-engineering-leads-exceptional-stock-returns-with-1810-gain-in-one-year-3767315</link><description>SMT Engineering has emerged as a standout performer over the past year, generating a remarkable return of 1810.12%, vastly surpassing typical market benchmarks and drawing investor attention to its unique growth trajectory within the Trading &amp; Distributors sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>60a89e1cbe2ebab5c7466127b6f1e403</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:27:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Godawari Power &amp; Ispat Hits Intraday High with Robust Trading Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/godawari-power-ispat-hits-intraday-high-with-746-surge-on-23-dec-2025-3767317</link><description>Godawari Power &amp; Ispat demonstrated strong intraday performance on 23 Dec 2025, reaching a day’s high of Rs 260.1, reflecting a 7.75% rise. The stock outpaced its sector and broader market indices, supported by sustained buying interest and favourable technical positioning.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b3fcac20a0e1fa8cba917d4182d014af</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:27:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aarti Drugs Hits Intraday High with Strong 7.3% Surge Amid Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aarti-drugs-hits-intraday-high-with-73-surge-on-23-dec-2025-3767318</link><description>Aarti Drugs demonstrated robust intraday performance on 23 Dec 2025, touching a high of Rs 417, reflecting a 7.3% gain for the day. This surge stands out amid a broadly subdued market, with the Sensex retreating slightly after an initial positive start.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>d339d269dbaa627c6c1830f25fa64439</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:27:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Covance Softsol Hits All-Time High at Rs.92.26 Marking a Significant Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/covance-softsol-stock-reaches-all-time-high-of-rs9226-on-23-dec-2025-3767314</link><description>Covance Softsol, a key player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has reached a new all-time high of Rs.92.26, underscoring a remarkable phase in its market journey. This milestone reflects the company’s sustained performance amid a competitive industry landscape.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>1db4664da2914b70c20883c398ec2865</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:27:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ashok Leyland Hits All-Time High Amid Robust Market Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ashok-leyland-stock-hits-all-time-high-marking-a-significant-milestone-3767312</link><description>Ashok Leyland, a prominent player in the Indian automobile sector, has reached a new all-time high, reflecting a sustained period of strong market performance and investor confidence. The stock’s recent trajectory highlights its resilience and consistent gains across multiple time frames, setting a significant milestone in its trading history.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>03e32713c135182f94e22581b19df22a</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:27:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ashok Leyland Reaches New 52-Week High, Marking Significant Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/ashok-leyland-reaches-new-52-week-high-marking-strong-momentum-3767308</link><description>Ashok Leyland has achieved a notable milestone by reaching a new 52-week high of ₹177.95, reflecting sustained momentum in the automobile sector. The stock’s recent performance underscores a period of consistent gains, supported by favourable market dynamics and sectoral trends.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>e3a66a0dc74bad1cbef6344b262b7cfd</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:27:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 12:27:49 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>