<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 20:16:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Tanfac Industries Gains 4.67%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tanfac-industries-gains-467-2-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3780273</link><description>Tanfac Industries Ltd delivered a notable weekly gain of 4.67%, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.35% rise from 29 December 2025 to 2 January 2026. The stock rebounded strongly after early losses, driven by a sharp intraday surge on 31 December and a bullish momentum shift in early January, reflecting renewed investor confidence amid mixed technical signals.
Time: Jan 04 2026 05:58 PM IST</description><guid>dc10cf09a4e5831f56de4e65b9d2a1e9</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 20:16:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Everest Organics Surges 15.44%: 5 Key Factors Behind This Week’s Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/everest-organics-surges-1544-5-key-factors-behind-this-weeks-rally-3780272</link><description>Everest Organics Ltd delivered a robust weekly performance, surging 15.44% from Rs.458.25 to Rs.529.00 between 29 December 2025 and 2 January 2026, significantly outpacing the Sensex’s modest 1.35% gain over the same period. The stock hit multiple new 52-week and all-time highs during the week, reflecting strong momentum amid a mixed broader market environment. Key events including record intraday highs, technical strength, and upgraded ratings contributed to this notable rally.
Time: Jan 04 2026 05:56 PM IST</description><guid>b75673d9f6188e2034943b8b73a9ec5f</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 20:16:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indo Count Industries Gains 5.63%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indo-count-industries-gains-563-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3780271</link><description>Indo Count Industries Ltd closed the week with a 5.63% gain, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.35% rise from 29 December 2025 to 2 January 2026. The stock experienced significant volatility, including a sharp 14.61% surge on 30 December, reflecting a complex interplay of technical shifts, rating upgrades, and market dynamics within the garments and apparels sector.
Time: Jan 04 2026 05:54 PM IST</description><guid>15f8c9ef69d4a3c0fe66f6d7e97666a7</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 20:16:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharat Petroleum Gains 4.14%: 6 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharat-petroleum-gains-414-6-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3780270</link><description>Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd (BPCL) delivered a solid weekly gain of 4.14%, closing at Rs.381.30 on 2 January 2026, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.35% rise over the same period. The stock demonstrated strong resilience and momentum, hitting new 52-week and all-time highs during the week, supported by robust financial results, increased market participation, and favourable sector dynamics.
Time: Jan 04 2026 05:53 PM IST</description><guid>2eade96506d5b2b1201e0f41be1bb125</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 20:16:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prakash Industries Gains 7.85%: Technical Shift and Mixed Fundamentals Shape Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/prakash-industries-gains-785-technical-shift-and-mixed-fundamentals-shape-week-3780269</link><description>Prakash Industries Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 7.85% from Rs.136.90 to Rs.147.65 between 29 December 2025 and 2 January 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s 1.35% gain over the same period. The week was marked by a notable upgrade in the company’s investment rating from 'Strong Sell' to 'Sell' driven by improved technical indicators, despite ongoing fundamental challenges including subdued profitability and declining quarterly earnings. Mixed technical signals and sector headwinds shaped investor sentiment as the stock showed signs of stabilisation amid cautious optimism.
Time: Jan 04 2026 05:51 PM IST</description><guid>03fe30a5e25242d8b3557da140d63fc0</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 20:16:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>B.L.Kashyap &amp; Sons Gains 4.97%: 2 Key Factors Driving the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/blkashyap-sons-gains-497-2-key-factors-driving-the-week-3780268</link><description>B.L.Kashyap &amp; Sons Ltd recorded a mixed week ending 2 January 2026, closing at Rs.52.64, up 4.97% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.50.15. This performance notably outpaced the Sensex’s 1.35% gain over the same period, driven by a sharp rebound on 29 December followed by a technical downturn early in the new year. The stock’s volatility reflected shifting market sentiment amid broader sector challenges and technical signals.
Time: Jan 04 2026 05:49 PM IST</description><guid>e3e7147c61be7e241bb54ef9b145cbab</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 20:16:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tilak Ventures Ltd Gains 10.59%: 2 Key Technical Signals Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tilak-ventures-ltd-gains-1059-2-key-technical-signals-shape-the-week-3780267</link><description>Tilak Ventures Ltd recorded a notable weekly gain of 10.59%, closing at Rs.1.88 on 2 January 2026, outperforming the Sensex’s 1.35% rise over the same period. The week was marked by significant technical developments including a downgrade to a Sell rating and the formation of a Death Cross, signalling potential bearish momentum despite the stock’s strong price recovery.
Time: Jan 04 2026 05:48 PM IST</description><guid>5f571eb21a483a0d2f3de398a7a81dfc</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 20:16:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Brahmaputra Infrastructure Declines 2.65% Despite 52-Week High; Sensex Gains 1.35%</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/brahmaputra-infrastructure-declines-265-despite-52-week-high-sensex-gains-135-3780266</link><description>Brahmaputra Infrastructure Ltd experienced a challenging week ending 2 January 2026, with its stock price declining by 2.65% from Rs.132.20 to Rs.128.70, underperforming the Sensex which gained 1.35% over the same period. Despite hitting a new 52-week and all-time high of Rs.135.5 on 29 December 2025, the stock faced selling pressure in subsequent sessions, reflecting mixed investor sentiment amid broader market gains.
Time: Jan 04 2026 05:46 PM IST</description><guid>083678ce05405a8ce9fc35346c21c202</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 20:16:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>eClerx Services Ltd Gains 0.97%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eclerx-services-ltd-gains-097-4-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3780301</link><description>eClerx Services Ltd closed the week ending 2 January 2026 with a modest gain of 0.97%, rising from Rs.4,679.80 to Rs.4,725.00. This performance, while positive, lagged behind the Sensex’s 1.35% advance over the same period. The week was marked by a series of technical momentum shifts, a significant upgrade to a Strong Buy rating, and evolving valuation metrics that together shaped investor sentiment and price action.
Time: Jan 04 2026 05:42 PM IST</description><guid>87de835cc35044ddda0411d6534cbf45</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 20:16:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 20:16:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>