<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 21:18:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3863347</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has concluded with 4,095 companies reporting results, revealing a nuanced landscape of corporate performance across market capitalisations. While the proportion of companies delivering positive results has inched up to 46.0%, the data highlights divergent trends between large, mid, and small caps, alongside sector-specific standouts that are shaping investor sentiment as we move into the new fiscal year.
Time: Mar 01 2026 09:00 PM IST</description><guid>ce8d79769bf82bf2973f52801ebf7115</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 21:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dec-2025 Quarterly Earnings Reveal Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/dec-2025-quarterly-earnings-reveal-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3863325</link><description>The December 2025 quarterly earnings season has concluded with 4,095 companies reporting results, revealing a nuanced picture of corporate performance across market capitalisations. While the overall proportion of companies delivering positive results has improved marginally to 46.0%, mid-cap firms continue to lead the charge with a 53.0% positivity rate, outpacing large caps which lag at 43.0%. This article analyses the key trends, sectoral highlights, and standout performers shaping the current earnings landscape.
Time: Mar 01 2026 06:00 PM IST</description><guid>8329ba45709ebd816ef3f85c21837aee</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 21:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Loyal Equipments Falls 8.23%: Technical Stabilisation and Valuation Shift Mark the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/loyal-equipments-falls-823-technical-stabilisation-and-valuation-shift-mark-the-week-3863319</link><description>Loyal Equipments Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its stock price declining by 8.23% from Rs.178.00 to Rs.163.35 between 16 and 20 February 2026, underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The week was marked by a cautious upgrade in the company’s rating to 'Sell' amid persistent financial headwinds, alongside a shift in valuation metrics that rendered the stock more attractive despite ongoing market pressure.
Time: Mar 01 2026 05:01 PM IST</description><guid>30238bed7cce9280072dd39a41ecb567</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 21:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Galaxy Surfactants Gains 3.62%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Move</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/galaxy-surfactants-gains-362-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-move-3863320</link><description>Galaxy Surfactants Ltd recorded a 3.62% gain over the week ending 20 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% rise. The stock showed strong momentum early in the week, hitting an intraday high of Rs.2,048.50 on 17 February before retreating amid mixed technical signals and valuation concerns. This review analyses the key events shaping the stock’s performance and the implications for investors.
Time: Mar 01 2026 05:01 PM IST</description><guid>65b2170bd0867c4fa85893974583c220</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 21:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>W S Industries Falls 1.81%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/w-s-industries-falls-181-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3863317</link><description>W S Industries (India) Ltd closed the week at ₹73.76, down 1.81% from the previous Friday’s close of ₹75.12, underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The week was marked by a notable upgrade in the company’s quality parameters, a shift to bearish technical momentum, and a significant valuation reassessment, all contributing to a complex market sentiment around the stock.
Time: Mar 01 2026 05:01 PM IST</description><guid>e726920433079870b62f1a38f5772fc4</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 21:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indergiri Finance Surges 17.02% Amid Mixed Fundamentals and Technical Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indergiri-finance-surges-1702-amid-mixed-fundamentals-and-technical-shifts-3863316</link><description>Indergiri Finance Ltd delivered a robust weekly gain of 17.02%, closing at Rs.27.50 on 20 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% rise over the same period. The stock’s trajectory was marked by sharp daily advances, despite persistent fundamental challenges and mixed technical signals. This review analyses the key events and market dynamics that shaped the stock’s volatile week.
Time: Mar 01 2026 05:01 PM IST</description><guid>fe647b88a35f1512d208b0982d60345a</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 21:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Praj Industries Gains 0.70%: 4 Key Factors Driving This Week's Volatility</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/praj-industries-gains-070-4-key-factors-driving-this-weeks-volatility-3863318</link><description>Praj Industries Ltd closed the week with a modest gain of 0.70%, slightly outperforming the Sensex’s 0.39% rise. The stock experienced significant intraday volatility, driven by a downgrade in its quality and mojo grades, a sharp rebound on 17 February, and a marked shift in valuation metrics amid mixed market conditions. Despite the week ending near its opening price, the stock’s trading activity and fundamental reassessments highlight a complex outlook for investors navigating this industrial manufacturing player’s near-term prospects.
Time: Mar 01 2026 05:01 PM IST</description><guid>f0343f8734b13b2e48d088481f3dc69a</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 21:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Asian Hotels (East) Ltd Gains 6.17%: Downgrade and Mixed Signals Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/asian-hotels-east-ltd-gains-617-downgrade-and-mixed-signals-shape-the-week-3863321</link><description>Asian Hotels (East) Ltd delivered a notable weekly gain of 6.17%, closing at Rs.159.25 on 20 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex which rose a modest 0.39% over the same period. The week was marked by a significant downgrade in the company’s quality grade and rating to Strong Sell, reflecting deteriorating fundamentals and bearish technical signals. Despite these headwinds, the stock showed resilience with a sharp rally midweek, followed by mixed price movements aligned with sector and market trends.
Time: Mar 01 2026 05:01 PM IST</description><guid>fbc6c2b2fa979112f92b8989d3323d50</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 21:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>HMT Ltd Gains 10.32%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hmt-ltd-gains-1032-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-surge-3863315</link><description>HMT Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 10.32% from ₹43.50 to ₹47.99 between 16 and 20 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain. The stock’s rally was marked by two consecutive days hitting the upper circuit limit, reflecting intense buying momentum despite the company’s prevailing Strong Sell rating and mixed technical indicators.
Time: Mar 01 2026 05:00 PM IST</description><guid>c92b3b18700a58ee8ceb097741318532</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 21:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 21:18:37 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>