<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:47:57 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Haldyn Glass Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/haldyn-glass-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3857696</link><description>Haldyn Glass Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 13 February 2026. While the rating change occurred on that date, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market standing.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>bee75414b7a94645ce9f9ef627bb45f5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Savera Industries Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/savera-industries-ltd-is-rated-sell-3857694</link><description>Savera Industries Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 29 December 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 26 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date perspective on the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>66cd9461bba33e073510a0f1a9442148</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Donear Industries Ltd is Rated Hold by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/donear-industries-ltd-is-rated-hold-by-marketsmojo-3857695</link><description>Donear Industries Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 10 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>3d870d9bbdf91bf82eead6fccbe45fef</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Capital Small Finance Bank Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/capital-small-finance-bank-ltd-is-rated-sell-3857691</link><description>Capital Small Finance Bank Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 12 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>465a7173aae01444f47c4d500b60d16d</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>India Motor Parts &amp; Accessories Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/india-motor-parts-accessories-ltd-is-rated-sell-3857693</link><description>India Motor Parts &amp; Accessories Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 06 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>9db143b4b9f8f85d445a58010b002090</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ecos (India) Mobility &amp; Hospitality Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ecos-india-mobility-hospitality-ltd-is-rated-sell-3857692</link><description>Ecos (India) Mobility &amp; Hospitality Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 11 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>d35c38125bfdf522b17312a3c4e992be</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ganesh Benzoplast Ltd is Rated Sell by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/ganesh-benzoplast-ltd-is-rated-sell-by-marketsmojo-3857690</link><description>Ganesh Benzoplast Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 02 June 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company's performance and outlook.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>5e2aedea8dc2386448e249a9dd4793b2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chambal Fertilisers &amp; Chemicals Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/chambal-fertilisers-chemicals-ltd-is-rated-sell-3857688</link><description>Chambal Fertilisers &amp; Chemicals Ltd is rated Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 10 February 2026, reflecting a change from a previous Hold rating. However, the analysis and financial metrics presented here are based on the stock's current position as of 26 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>cfa1c36c4da3ed652d29be20a652c00b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Garware Technical Fibres Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/garware-technical-fibres-ltd-is-rated-sell-3857689</link><description>Garware Technical Fibres Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 03 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 February 2026, providing investors with the most up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market performance.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>f90b084c88072d24ba9064c44c530557</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CSL Finance Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/csl-finance-ltd-is-rated-sell-3857685</link><description>CSL Finance Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 14 Nov 2025. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date perspective on the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>46e4462c57ded7d14210c476d9f469e2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Electrosteel Castings Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/electrosteel-castings-ltd-is-rated-sell-3857684</link><description>Electrosteel Castings Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 03 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company's fundamentals, returns, and technical outlook.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>cbe0dd97fdfac1af09bdcc2ebdb15a17</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Orient Cement Ltd. is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/orient-cement-ltd-is-rated-hold-3857687</link><description>Orient Cement Ltd. is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 03 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>62cb9637f5586aa5d5bebeeeac81e3f0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tribhovandas Bhimji Zaveri Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/tribhovandas-bhimji-zaveri-ltd-is-rated-hold-3857683</link><description>Tribhovandas Bhimji Zaveri Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 20 January 2026. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 26 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the stock’s performance and outlook.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>9a2d4f9fc11d05a157191d716cdaea58</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sterling &amp; Wilson Renewable Energy Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sterling-wilson-renewable-energy-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3857686</link><description>Sterling &amp; Wilson Renewable Energy Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 12 January 2026, reflecting a reassessment of the stock’s outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here are current as of 26 February 2026, providing investors with the latest perspective on the company’s position.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>f7b40ceb2336d8d9c43232d05d848c44</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sicagen India Ltd is Rated Hold</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/sicagen-india-ltd-is-rated-hold-3857682</link><description>Sicagen India Ltd is rated 'Hold' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 01 February 2026. While the rating change occurred earlier this month, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the company’s current position as of 26 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>9bfc201af6f7501a94d15a2e90d9c62b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aeroflex Neu Ltd is Rated Sell by MarketsMOJO</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/aeroflex-neu-ltd-is-rated-sell-by-marketsmojo-3857681</link><description>Aeroflex Neu Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 23 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into the company’s performance and outlook.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>b0003cc6784a5c3e6acb9a6c0eb83884</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tara Chand Infralogistic Solutions Ltd is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/tara-chand-infralogistic-solutions-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3857680</link><description>Tara Chand Infralogistic Solutions Ltd is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO. This rating was last updated on 19 February 2026, reflecting a reassessment of the stock’s outlook. However, all fundamentals, returns, and financial metrics discussed here are current as of 26 February 2026, providing investors with the latest view of the company’s position.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>c6137929da46adb1511884e81455dc9f</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aarti Pharmalabs Ltd is Rated Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/aarti-pharmalabs-ltd-is-rated-sell-3857679</link><description>Aarti Pharmalabs Ltd is rated 'Sell' by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 12 January 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed below reflect the stock's current position as of 26 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, returns, and market performance.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>915a7bad849890a6d0ce862594bd6b13</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KCP Ltd. is Rated Strong Sell</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/kcp-ltd-is-rated-strong-sell-3857675</link><description>KCP Ltd. is rated Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 13 February 2026. However, the analysis and financial metrics discussed here reflect the stock’s current position as of 26 February 2026, providing investors with an up-to-date view of the company’s fundamentals, valuation, financial trends, and technical outlook.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>22e2a2563444256a7b4c096f62c64054</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mangalam Worldwide Ltd is Rated Buy</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-recommendation/mangalam-worldwide-ltd-is-rated-buy-3857677</link><description>Mangalam Worldwide Ltd is rated Buy by MarketsMOJO, with this rating last updated on 19 January 2026. While the rating change occurred then, the analysis and financial metrics presented here reflect the stock's current position as of 26 February 2026, providing investors with the latest insights into its performance and outlook.
Time: 6 minutes ago</description><guid>8f3dced30660a016a7f1348c4d794d3e</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>