<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:53:05 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3854390</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has unfolded with a nuanced picture across Indian equities, as 4,085 companies declared results reflecting a modest improvement in profitability and sales growth. While the overall proportion of companies reporting positive results rose slightly to 46.0%, sectoral and market capitalisation segments displayed divergent trends, underscoring the varied pace of recovery and operational performance across industries and company sizes.
Time: 22 minutes ago</description><guid>608d2d6ea6f1d568d99bb0d171fdb967</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:53:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Latent View Analytics Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/latent-view-analytics-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3853460</link><description>Latent View Analytics Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s long-term strength amid ongoing sector challenges.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>a7d93271a34e3943f2696d6baa0cb7e4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:53:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sellwin Traders Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sellwin-traders-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3853458</link><description>Sellwin Traders Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Diversified Commercial Services sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>9ba074b0e119aad987aee26975293e6d</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:53:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Authum Investment &amp; Infrastructure Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/authum-investment-infrastructure-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3853462</link><description>Authum Investment &amp; Infrastructure Ltd, a prominent player in the Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC) sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term momentum and investor sentiment.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>2827e11b0d3a9f150542f40710062f84</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:53:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Regency Ceramics Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/regency-ceramics-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3853461</link><description>Regency Ceramics Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>2e2ea2a73c745a1c6892b70f27b69acc</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:53:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Triveni Engineering and Industries Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/triveni-engineering-and-industries-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3853459</link><description>Triveni Engineering and Industries Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum for the sugar sector company, which has seen mixed performance against the broader market over the past year.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>58b620672ca9056fb693f695661c66a6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:53:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Quarterly Earnings Review: Dec-2025 Results Show Mixed Trends Across Market Caps</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/quarterly-earnings-review-dec-2025-results-show-mixed-trends-across-market-caps-3853422</link><description>The December 2025 quarter earnings season has concluded with 4,082 companies reporting results, revealing a nuanced picture of corporate performance across market capitalisations. While the proportion of companies delivering positive results has inched up slightly to 46.0%, sectoral and size-based disparities remain evident, underscoring the varied pace of recovery and growth across the Indian equity landscape.
Time: 3 hours ago</description><guid>e49c0341b3d5c8a43487677746d2f7ce</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:53:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Network People Services Technologies Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs 1082</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/network-people-services-technologies-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs-1082-3853367</link><description>Network People Services Technologies Ltd has reached a new 52-week low, closing at Rs.1082, marking a significant decline amid broader sectoral and market pressures. The stock’s recent performance reflects a combination of valuation concerns and subdued profit trends over the past year.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>3fec07f77512c5fc89ba21830f18b6e8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:53:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dev Information Technology Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dev-information-technology-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3853366</link><description>Dev Information Technology Ltd’s shares declined sharply to a new 52-week low of Rs.23.68 on 24 Feb 2026, marking a significant downturn amid a broader market correction and persistent company-specific headwinds.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>da765713a7d7ad1b4475c1dfe0908b77</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:53:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>D P Wires Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/d-p-wires-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3853365</link><description>D P Wires Ltd, a player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, recorded a fresh 52-week low of Rs.154 today, marking a significant decline amid ongoing downward momentum. The stock’s performance continues to lag behind sector peers and broader market indices, reflecting persistent challenges in financial metrics and market sentiment.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>4b45a37f6b4b39398d1278e0268f3287</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:53:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sanofi-consumer-healthcare-india-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-underperformance-3853364</link><description>Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd’s stock has recently touched a 52-week low, closing near Rs 3,967, marking a significant decline in its market valuation. This downturn reflects a combination of valuation concerns and underwhelming financial performance over the past year, positioning the stock distinctly below key moving averages and sector benchmarks.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>cac127ffe74497aa999f33cc5bd4e89c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:53:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RBZ Jewellers Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rbz-jewellers-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3853362</link><description>RBZ Jewellers Ltd has reached a 52-week low, with its stock price touching Rs 122.35, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has underperformed both its sector and broader market indices, reflecting ongoing concerns despite some positive quarterly financial results.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>ad0482fc2fd8153de6f84da000e2b7e8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:53:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Uma Exports Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/uma-exports-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3853363</link><description>Shares of Uma Exports Ltd have declined to a fresh 52-week low, reflecting a sustained period of underperformance. The stock’s latest low price marks a significant milestone in its downward trajectory, underscoring ongoing concerns about the company’s financial health and market position within the Trading &amp; Distributors sector.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>0ec96fb2a858633dd9d178992c32621e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:53:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fino Payments Bank Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/fino-payments-bank-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-underperformance-3853357</link><description>Fino Payments Bank Ltd has reached a fresh 52-week low, with its stock price touching an intraday low of Rs 199.55, marking a decline of 5.92% on the day. This significant drop reflects ongoing pressures on the company’s financial performance and market sentiment within the Financial Technology sector.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>8e15fcc9b7c70b4d7e20e3bd2eac7881</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:53:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Matrimony.com Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Earnings Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/matrimonycom-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-earnings-pressure-3853360</link><description>Matrimony.com Ltd’s shares have declined to a fresh 52-week low, reflecting ongoing challenges in both its near-term and long-term financial performance. The stock’s latest low price underscores a period of subdued growth and valuation pressures within the e-retail and e-commerce sector.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>b0bc60d2fc3d5691f767e32fe23e6935</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:53:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Khadim India Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/khadim-india-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3853361</link><description>Khadim India Ltd’s stock has declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing just 1% above its lowest price in the past year at ₹134.15. This marks a significant milestone in the company’s ongoing downward trajectory, reflecting persistent challenges in both its financial performance and market valuation.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>ab1f40dc26a25b05d8250e93ef54e87e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:53:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pudumjee Paper Products Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pudumjee-paper-products-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-downtrend-3853359</link><description>Pudumjee Paper Products Ltd has reached a fresh 52-week low, with its stock price touching an intraday low of Rs 80.9, just 2.12% above its lowest level of Rs 80.46 in the past year. This marks a significant milestone in the stock’s ongoing decline, reflecting a series of challenges that have weighed on its market performance.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>4584f5948a83b2d3a18c673a394aa067</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:53:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Electrotherm (India) Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/electrotherm-india-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3853358</link><description>Electrotherm (India) Ltd’s shares have declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing just 1.93% above the lowest price recorded in the past year at Rs 701. The stock’s recent performance reflects ongoing pressures within the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, with the share price retreating amid broader market weakness and company-specific financial trends.
Time: 5 hours ago</description><guid>d774b7c6c900327c7962ed8e60895a06</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:53:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:53:05 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>