<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:27:51 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Krishana Phoschem Q3 FY26: Stellar Growth Momentum Continues with 62% Profit Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/krishana-phoschem-q3-fy26-stellar-growth-momentum-continues-with-62-profit-surge-3790127</link><description>Krishana Phoschem Limited, a Rajasthan-based fertiliser and specialty chemicals manufacturer, has delivered an exceptional third quarter performance for FY2026, reporting a net profit of ₹33.32 crores—a remarkable 62.29% year-on-year surge from ₹20.53 crores in Q3 FY25. The company's stock, currently trading at ₹494.85 with a market capitalisation of ₹2,979 crores, has demonstrated extraordinary momentum over the past year with returns of 160.42%, significantly outperforming the Sensex's 8.21% gain by a staggering 152 percentage points.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9ba49461fd171a0a012cc7fcf08a5286</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Raj Rayon Industries Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/raj-rayon-industries-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3790200</link><description>Raj Rayon Industries Ltd, a small-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, witnessed a sharp decline on 12 Jan 2026 as it hit its lower circuit price limit, closing at ₹21.41. The stock faced intense selling pressure, resulting in a maximum daily loss of 1.97%, reflecting growing investor concerns amid deteriorating technical and fundamental indicators.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4d3f0bac48ebcd3ef89e0d1f8960d6f9</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blue Coast Hotels Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/blue-coast-hotels-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3790198</link><description>Blue Coast Hotels Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Hotels &amp; Resorts sector, witnessed intense selling pressure on 12 Jan 2026, hitting its lower circuit limit with a sharp 4.97% decline to close at ₹30.78. The stock’s performance starkly underperformed its sector and broader market benchmarks, reflecting mounting investor concerns and panic selling in a highly volatile trading session.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>12cbc9ec9000bed0eae3311fc8649819</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Winsome Yarns Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/winsome-yarns-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3790197</link><description>Shares of Winsome Yarns Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, plunged to their lower circuit limit on 12 Jan 2026, reflecting intense selling pressure and panic among investors. The stock closed at ₹1.85, down 1.07% on the day, marking its maximum permissible daily loss and signalling heightened market anxiety around the company’s near-term prospects.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>9e87523a15fb2b73cf25a0ede9c11f91</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>IDFC First Bank Sees Exceptional Volume Amid Mixed Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/idfc-first-bank-sees-exceptional-volume-amid-mixed-price-action-3790201</link><description>IDFC First Bank Ltd. emerged as one of the most actively traded stocks on 12 Jan 2026, registering a total traded volume exceeding 2.13 crore shares. Despite this surge in activity, the stock closed marginally lower at ₹84.84, down 0.96% from the previous close, reflecting a complex interplay of investor sentiment and market dynamics within the private sector banking space.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>da87ea77b7e592f52c4751a1934ecf9c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BF Utilities Ltd Hits Lower Circuit Amid Heavy Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bf-utilities-ltd-hits-lower-circuit-amid-heavy-selling-pressure-3790199</link><description>Shares of BF Utilities Ltd plunged to their lower circuit limit on 12 Jan 2026, succumbing to intense selling pressure that saw the stock lose 5.0% in a single session. The transport infrastructure company’s stock closed at ₹599.65, marking its lowest intraday price and triggering a trading halt due to the maximum permissible daily loss.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c1632f56bc55308e2c0b8bd3c349cf70</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Market Rebound</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indian-renewable-energy-development-agency-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-market-rebound-3790196</link><description>Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency Ltd (IREDA) witnessed a significant surge in open interest in its derivatives segment on 12 Jan 2026, signalling a potential shift in market positioning. The stock outperformed its sector peers and the broader Sensex, gaining 3.59% on the day, supported by a 10.46% rise in open interest and robust volume activity. This development has attracted investor attention amid a backdrop of mixed moving average signals and declining delivery volumes.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>97e9f546e5c82cb910f6c15e0eb82fb1</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Delhivery Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/delhivery-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-price-action-3790194</link><description>Delhivery Ltd, a key player in the transport services sector, has witnessed a notable surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, rising by 11.9% to 17,990 contracts. This increase comes amid a sustained decline in the stock price, which has fallen 7.7% over the past three trading sessions, signalling a complex interplay of market positioning and investor sentiment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8c4acdbfa3c6d22df5f63fefc9bd2ec0</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank of Maharashtra Sees Exceptional Volume Surge Amid Strong Buy Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bank-of-maharashtra-sees-exceptional-volume-surge-amid-strong-buy-momentum-3790195</link><description>Bank of Maharashtra (MAHABANK) has emerged as one of the most actively traded stocks on 12 Jan 2026, registering a remarkable surge in volume and price momentum. The public sector bank’s shares witnessed a total traded volume exceeding 2.04 crore shares, accompanied by a notable price appreciation, signalling strong accumulation interest among investors.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4f34f93364e19f0b2ec362c0e0991073</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Hitachi Energy India Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Bearish Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/hitachi-energy-india-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-bearish-price-action-3790193</link><description>Hitachi Energy India Ltd (POWERINDIA) has witnessed a significant 18.55% surge in open interest in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite this, the stock has underperformed its sector and the broader market, falling over 10% in the last three sessions, reflecting a complex interplay between rising speculative interest and bearish price momentum.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e37484d02c9e06465bfd9966943bf431</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Laurus Labs Ltd Sees Sharp Open Interest Surge Amid Mixed Price Action</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/laurus-labs-ltd-sees-sharp-open-interest-surge-amid-mixed-price-action-3790191</link><description>Laurus Labs Ltd, a key player in the Pharmaceuticals &amp; Biotechnology sector, has witnessed a notable surge in open interest (OI) in its derivatives segment, signalling heightened market activity and shifting investor positioning. Despite a recent price decline, the stock’s derivatives market reveals increased speculative interest, suggesting potential directional bets as investors recalibrate amid sectoral and broader market dynamics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3f5d9f91f38f3b6b43ba4d8b25457109</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bharti Airtel Ltd Sees High-Value Trading Amid Mixed Technical Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bharti-airtel-ltd-sees-high-value-trading-amid-mixed-technical-signals-3790192</link><description>Bharti Airtel Ltd, a heavyweight in the Telecom - Services sector, witnessed significant trading activity on 12 Jan 2026, with a total traded value exceeding ₹522 crores. Despite this robust turnover, the stock experienced a modest decline, reflecting a complex interplay of market forces and investor sentiment amid a four-day losing streak.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e705ed7164ec429f63253fd5f28fd745</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ITC Ltd Sees Surge in Call Option Activity Amid Bearish Technicals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/itc-ltd-sees-surge-in-call-option-activity-amid-bearish-technicals-3790189</link><description>ITC Ltd., a heavyweight in the FMCG sector, has witnessed a notable spike in call option trading activity despite its recent bearish price action and a downgrade in its mojo rating. The surge in call contracts, particularly at the ₹370 strike price expiring on 27 January 2026, signals a complex market sentiment as investors weigh the stock’s near-term prospects against its subdued fundamentals.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>329efacea7e35105571ea57fde38f289</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sensex Edges Higher Amid Mixed Sectoral Trends; Metal Sector Leads Gains</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-edges-higher-amid-mixed-sectoral-trends-metal-sector-leads-gains-3790036</link><description>The Indian equity market witnessed a cautious session on 12 Jan 2026, with the Sensex closing marginally higher by 0.09% at 83,647.99, recovering from an early dip. While metals emerged as the top-performing sector, media stocks faced significant pressure, reflecting a mixed sentiment among investors amid subdued breadth and cautious foreign institutional activity.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>06b304a641102366e640712bdf135dfe</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Bengal &amp; Assam Company Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs 6201.1</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/bengal-assam-company-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs-62011-3790202</link><description>Bengal &amp; Assam Company Ltd, a Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC), touched a new 52-week low of Rs 6201.1 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid broader market movements and company-specific performance trends.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>fcb4b0ddedc4d5b478c252e5772fcec2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aditya Birla Real Estate Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aditya-birla-real-estate-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3790190</link><description>Aditya Birla Real Estate Ltd’s stock declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.1559 on 12 Jan 2026, marking a significant downturn amid a sustained period of negative returns and underperformance relative to the broader market and its sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0352b3b04f7a70bcd2a019fa9fcca7da</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Valor Estate Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.107.7 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/valor-estate-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs1077-amidst-continued-downtrend-3790188</link><description>Valor Estate Ltd, a player in the Realty sector, touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs 107.7 today, marking a significant decline amid a sustained downward trend. The stock has now recorded losses for five consecutive sessions, reflecting ongoing pressures within the company’s performance metrics and market valuation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>5f222f222d7952444c85fb2d6e8a7c65</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jindal Poly Films Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jindal-poly-films-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3790187</link><description>Jindal Poly Films Ltd’s share price declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.430.65 today, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing downward trajectory. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting a series of financial setbacks and subdued performance metrics over the past year.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2fcaa7aaa54daf1e24069d9eac60a5ee</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>KCP Ltd. Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.163.45 Amidst Weak Financial Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/kcp-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs16345-amidst-weak-financial-performance-3790183</link><description>KCP Ltd., a player in the Cement &amp; Cement Products sector, touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.163.45 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid ongoing challenges reflected in its financial performance and market positioning.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c1f35c40a0772cdc859e075dde9a768b</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Banswara Syntex Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.101.5 Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/banswara-syntex-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs1015-amidst-continued-downtrend-3790186</link><description>Banswara Syntex Ltd, a player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.101.5 today, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing decline. The stock has underperformed its sector and broader market indices, reflecting persistent pressures on its financial and operational metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>daced4e2c9276c6865340c82a886f9c1</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:27:51 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>