<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:18:52 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Are Yuranus Infrastructure Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-yuranus-infrastructure-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3787440</link><description>Yuranus Infrastructure Ltd's latest results show a dramatic revenue increase of 5,766.67% to ₹1.76 crores, but the company still posted a net loss of ₹0.40 crores, indicating ongoing operational challenges and negative profitability metrics. Overall, while revenue growth year-on-year is positive, the company's financial health remains concerning.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>46078465ac189ad889751fb1a50ec495</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:18:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Globus Spirits Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-globus-spirits-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3787439</link><description>Globus Spirits Ltd's latest results are positive, showing a remarkable net profit growth of 1,456.74% year-on-year, despite a slight revenue decline. The company has improved its operating margin significantly, indicating strong operational efficiency and a focus on profitability.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ce43f1b7fa6a699b6cdb5e64de05ca6c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:18:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Are Elecon Engineering Company Ltd latest results good or bad?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/are-elecon-engineering-company-ltd-latest-results-good-or-bad-3787438</link><description>Elecon Engineering Company Ltd's latest Q3 FY26 results show a net profit decline of 33.06% year-on-year, with compressed operating margins at 19.79%, indicating significant profitability pressures despite a strong balance sheet. The company faces operational challenges that may require strategic intervention to improve future performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c981f18ade53461b711431b5c0120dd1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:18:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Coffee Day Enterprises Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/coffee-day-enterprises-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3787434</link><description>Coffee Day Enterprises Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>731e2201b7c119a530d05a43bfbb535f</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:18:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Campus Activewear Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/campus-activewear-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3787428</link><description>Campus Activewear Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>a6229c04d81c9a058346e97aa3c92185</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:18:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chemcon Speciality Chemicals Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/chemcon-speciality-chemicals-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3787427</link><description>Chemcon Speciality Chemicals Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average, signalling a potential shift towards a prolonged bearish trend. This development comes amid deteriorating price momentum and weak fundamentals, raising concerns about the stock’s near- and long-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>638c72f00d4ea20296952a279900e996</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:18:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Universus Photo Imagings Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/universus-photo-imagings-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3787432</link><description>Universus Photo Imagings Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a prolonged bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and long-term weakness in the stock’s price action.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>3b6460c8c4089abb5e5e790febbbeff4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:18:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Brand Concepts Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/brand-concepts-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3787431</link><description>Brand Concepts Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s long-term strength amid already challenging fundamentals.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>f5d8a6b807b931d3bd0dd5384384e2f2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:18:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sharda Motor Industries Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sharda-motor-industries-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3787430</link><description>Sharda Motor Industries Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raising concerns about its near to medium-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>f4aab45b8d46a4389fe2fb98a854eb4d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:18:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Terrain Fashions Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/indian-terrain-fashions-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3787426</link><description>Indian Terrain Fashions Ltd (NSE: 800227) has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average (DMA) crosses below the 200-DMA. This development signals a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about sustained bearish momentum in the near to medium term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>1e60624806e80780dc70a2deb05e5d98</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:18:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Orchasp Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/orchasp-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3787429</link><description>Orchasp Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential deterioration in the stock’s trend and raises concerns about sustained bearish momentum in the near to medium term.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>2794940c770795e9483a877581bf6835</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:18:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manali Petrochemicals Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend Ahead</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/manali-petrochemicals-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-ahead-3787422</link><description>Manali Petrochemicals Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock’s long-term strength amid a challenging market environment.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>2556b77499574c61cc6064ac58cbca6d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:18:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Simmonds Marshall Ltd Forms Death Cross Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/simmonds-marshall-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3787424</link><description>Simmonds Marshall Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>fb3d41f5aafe6ca56f775b3fe7ac2828</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:18:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Fineotex Chemical Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/fineotex-chemical-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3787418</link><description>Fineotex Chemical Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns over the stock’s near-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>663b53b402eca36e482c11598114e1ba</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:18:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Apollo Hospitals Enterprise Ltd. Forms Death Cross Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/apollo-hospitals-enterprise-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3787417</link><description>Apollo Hospitals Enterprise Ltd., a leading player in the hospital sector, has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, raising concerns about the stock's near-term momentum and long-term strength despite its strong fundamentals and large-cap status.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>15fd6cf48af3bd8a39ef9f207c80203a</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:18:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>CG Power &amp; Industrial Solutions Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cg-power-industrial-solutions-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-bearish-trend-3787425</link><description>CG Power &amp; Industrial Solutions Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average. This development signals a potential shift towards a bearish trend, reflecting deteriorating momentum and raising concerns about the stock's medium to long-term outlook.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b41a28799f754f72614abc1e3321a717</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:18:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Madhav Copper Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/madhav-copper-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3787419</link><description>Madhav Copper Ltd, a micro-cap player in the Non-Ferrous Metals sector, has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average. This development suggests a potential bullish breakout and a shift in long-term momentum, attracting renewed investor interest despite the company’s current Mojo Grade of Sell.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>7ac39ec040ac7d4e97b556cadf284bb4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:18:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Globus Spirits Q3 FY26: Strong Margin Expansion Drives Profitability Surge</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/result-analysis/globus-spirits-q3-fy26-strong-margin-expansion-drives-profitability-surge-3787433</link><description>Globus Spirits Ltd., one of North India's leading alcohol manufacturers, delivered an impressive operational performance in Q3 FY26, with consolidated net profit surging 1,456.74% year-on-year to ₹21.95 crores from a meagre ₹1.41 crores in Q3 FY25. The stellar performance was driven by substantial margin expansion, with operating margins (excluding other income) improving to 8.99% from 4.65% in the corresponding quarter last year. The stock, trading at ₹1,068.30, has retreated 1.64% following the results announcement, presenting what appears to be an attractive entry opportunity for long-term investors in this ₹3,137 crore market capitalisation company.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>7db0b2dfe2106f7541f40a3de76ba3ae</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:18:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Matrimony.com Ltd Forms Golden Cross, Signalling Potential Bullish Breakout</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/matrimonycom-ltd-forms-golden-cross-signalling-potential-bullish-breakout-3787423</link><description>Matrimony.com Ltd has recently formed a Golden Cross, a significant technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses above the 200-day moving average, suggesting a potential shift towards a bullish trend and long-term momentum improvement in the e-retail sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>fbd7bb5a454b28616eb822402822d4be</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:18:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>JM Financial Ltd Forms Death Cross, Signalling Potential Bearish Trend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/jm-financial-ltd-forms-death-cross-signalling-potential-bearish-trend-3787421</link><description>JM Financial Ltd has recently formed a Death Cross, a technical indicator where the 50-day moving average crosses below the 200-day moving average, signalling a potential shift towards a bearish trend. This development suggests a deterioration in the stock’s momentum and raises concerns about its near-term outlook amid broader market pressures.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>f8eefd78a7fa23315dd76a2c3ce96a3e</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:18:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:18:52 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>