<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:35:26 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>S Chand &amp; Company Ltd’s Mixed Week: +0.13% Price, Bearish Technical Signals Dominate</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/s-chand-company-ltds-mixed-week-013-price-bearish-technical-signals-dominate-3849537</link><description>S Chand &amp; Company Ltd closed the week with a modest gain of 0.13%, inching up to Rs.159.45 from Rs.159.25, while the Sensex outperformed slightly with a 0.39% rise to 36,674.32. The week was marked by a valuation upgrade, a significant downgrade to Strong Sell by MarketsMOJO, and a bearish technical momentum shift, all influencing the stock’s subdued price action amid mixed market conditions.
Time: 1 minute ago</description><guid>a5fab0965f64a9e6fe5e9e9c7969d7f1</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Variman Global Enterprises Ltd Declines 1.52%: Mixed Signals Amid Valuation Shift and Quarterly Gains</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/variman-global-enterprises-ltd-declines-152-mixed-signals-amid-valuation-shift-and-quarterly-gains-3849536</link><description>Variman Global Enterprises Ltd ended the week with a 1.52% decline to close at Rs.5.17 on 20 February 2026, underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The stock experienced notable volatility amid mixed quarterly financial results and a shift in valuation perception, reflecting ongoing operational challenges and market reassessment of its price attractiveness.
Time: 1 minute ago</description><guid>01cb84f91d1e20b697420c18f52b6287</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ERIS Lifesciences Declines 5.13%: Margin Pressures and Valuation Shift Weigh on Stock</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/eris-lifesciences-declines-513-margin-pressures-and-valuation-shift-weigh-on-stock-3849535</link><description>ERIS Lifesciences Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its share price declining 5.13% from ₹1,414.65 to ₹1,342.10, underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The week was marked by flat quarterly results amid margin pressures, a technical downgrade signalling bearish momentum, and a notable shift in valuation from expensive to fair, reflecting changing market sentiment and operational concerns.
Time: 1 minute ago</description><guid>d5c787570f689801b8317b879c20bf79</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AU Small Finance Bank Gains 3.40%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/au-small-finance-bank-gains-340-5-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-momentum-3849534</link><description>AU Small Finance Bank Ltd delivered a solid weekly gain of 3.40%, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% rise during the week ending 20 February 2026. The stock demonstrated resilience amid mixed market conditions, hitting new 52-week and all-time highs, supported by strong fundamentals, robust institutional interest, and a surge in derivatives market activity signalling bullish positioning.
Time: 1 minute ago</description><guid>af062529e0c92ae43b38d895c2406924</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GTPL Hathway Declines 9.06%: Valuation Shift and Sector Challenges Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/gtpl-hathway-declines-906-valuation-shift-and-sector-challenges-shape-the-week-3849533</link><description>GTPL Hathway Ltd. experienced a challenging week on the bourses, with its stock price declining 9.06% from Rs.77.85 to Rs.70.80, markedly underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The week was characterised by the stock hitting a fresh 52-week low, valuation recalibrations amid sector headwinds, and subdued trading volumes, reflecting cautious investor sentiment in a difficult media and entertainment environment.
Time: 1 minute ago</description><guid>a5fca535de2ae1c25ecb2747893f1773</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Riddhi Corporate Services Ltd Falls 3.69%: Downgrade and Flat Performance Weigh on Stock</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/riddhi-corporate-services-ltd-falls-369-downgrade-and-flat-performance-weigh-on-stock-3849532</link><description>Riddhi Corporate Services Ltd experienced a challenging week on the BSE, closing at Rs.67.27 on 20 Feb 2026, down 3.69% from the previous Friday’s close of Rs.69.85. This decline contrasted with the Sensex’s modest gain of 0.39% over the same period, highlighting the stock’s underperformance amid a flat quarterly financial performance and a recent downgrade to a Sell rating by MarketsMOJO. The week was marked by volatility and mixed technical signals, reflecting investor caution in the face of weak fundamentals and subdued growth prospects.
Time: 1 minute ago</description><guid>e32ea8c73a13ac9c187edad34b7c5d9a</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Salasar Techno Engineering Ltd Falls 4.60%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/salasar-techno-engineering-ltd-falls-460-4-key-factors-driving-the-decline-3849531</link><description>Salasar Techno Engineering Ltd’s stock declined by 4.60% over the week ending 20 February 2026, closing at Rs.8.08 compared to Rs.8.47 the previous Friday. This underperformance contrasted with the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain, reflecting a week marked by bearish technical signals, a downgrade to Strong Sell, deteriorating financial results, and valuation shifts amid market pressures.
Time: 1 minute ago</description><guid>d13fe1293cab8d252ee6b98b8f062a20</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shrenik Ltd’s Volatile Week: -2.33% Amid Circuit Hits and Strong Selling Pressure</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shrenik-ltds-volatile-week--233-amid-circuit-hits-and-strong-selling-pressure-3849530</link><description>Shrenik Ltd experienced a turbulent trading week from 16 to 20 February 2026, closing down 2.33% at Rs.0.42 despite early gains marked by multiple upper circuit hits. The stock’s performance contrasted with the Sensex’s modest 0.39% weekly rise, reflecting heightened volatility and investor uncertainty in this micro-cap stock. Intense buying pressure early in the week gave way to heavy selling and lower circuit hits in the latter sessions, underscoring a week of sharp swings and regulatory trading halts.
Time: 1 minute ago</description><guid>bb01925297213720da10a14cb3034f32</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cochin Shipyard Gains 2.96%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cochin-shipyard-gains-296-3-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-rally-3849529</link><description>Cochin Shipyard Ltd closed the week ending 20 February 2026 with a gain of 2.96%, outperforming the Sensex which rose 0.39% over the same period. The stock showed a notable rebound midweek, driven by strong intraday rallies and robust trading volumes, despite a recent downgrade to a Strong Sell rating by MarketsMOJO. This review analyses the key events and price movements that shaped the stock’s performance during the week.
Time: 1 minute ago</description><guid>7b87851bac918198f59e660ead029205</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Lexus Granito Gains 9.25%: Valuation Risks and Operational Challenges Shape the Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/lexus-granito-gains-925-valuation-risks-and-operational-challenges-shape-the-week-3849528</link><description>Lexus Granito (India) Ltd delivered a notable weekly gain of 9.25%, closing at Rs.37.44 on 20 Feb 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% rise over the same period. This surge followed a turbulent start to the week marked by operational challenges and valuation concerns, but was supported by a strong rebound in stock price midweek amid increased trading volumes and market volatility.
Time: 1 minute ago</description><guid>987f34bac5c661271d7a070c7ee82d09</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Aditya Birla Capital Gains 2.72%: 3 Key Factors Driving the Week’s Mixed Signals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aditya-birla-capital-gains-272-3-key-factors-driving-the-weeks-mixed-signals-3849527</link><description>Aditya Birla Capital Ltd recorded a 2.72% gain over the week ending 20 February 2026, outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% rise. The stock showed early strength with consecutive daily gains before a midweek pullback amid mixed technical signals and valuation concerns. Heightened derivatives activity and a recent downgrade to a Hold rating added complexity to the stock’s performance narrative, reflecting a cautious market stance despite solid long-term fundamentals.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>bf417dee1dbcd58cefc4e9daf25af0c6</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Dixon Technologies Falls 3.10%: 7 Key Factors Driving the Weekly Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/dixon-technologies-falls-310-7-key-factors-driving-the-weekly-decline-3849526</link><description>Dixon Technologies (India) Ltd experienced a challenging week from 16 to 20 February 2026, with its stock price declining by 3.10% to close at Rs.11,061.20, underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. Despite robust trading volumes and active options market participation, the stock faced sustained selling pressure amid mixed technical signals and sectoral headwinds, culminating in a cautious market stance.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>25cc94dd50a8690596d65b68a4637bbb</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pashupati Cotspin Ltd Gains 4.38%: 4 Key Factors Driving the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pashupati-cotspin-ltd-gains-438-4-key-factors-driving-the-rally-3849525</link><description>Pashupati Cotspin Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance from 16 to 20 February 2026, gaining 4.38% to close at Rs.939.20, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% rise. The stock marked multiple all-time and 52-week highs during the week, supported by sustained buying momentum and technical strength, despite some intraday volatility and cautious market sentiment reflected in its Mojo Grade of ‘Sell’.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>2f75e487712623af8da63d6d6f8194c9</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shish Industries Ltd Surges 27.51%: Key Drivers Behind the Weekly Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/shish-industries-ltd-surges-2751-key-drivers-behind-the-weekly-rally-3849523</link><description>Shish Industries Ltd delivered a remarkable weekly gain of 27.51%, vastly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% rise during 16 to 20 February 2026. The stock’s consistent daily advances, capped by a 5.00% jump on Friday, were supported by a series of fundamental upgrades, valuation shifts, and technical momentum improvements that collectively shaped investor sentiment and price action throughout the week.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>64d1238946595032dab977573dd9f9a5</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ICICI Lombard Gains 1.21%: 3 Key Factors Driving This Week’s Momentum</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/icici-lombard-gains-121-3-key-factors-driving-this-weeks-momentum-3849522</link><description>ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Ltd recorded a modest gain of 1.21% over the week ending 20 Feb 2026, outperforming the Sensex’s 0.39% rise. The stock showed resilience amid mixed technical signals and increased derivatives market activity, closing at Rs.1,934.60 on Friday. Key developments included shifts in technical momentum, a notable surge in open interest, and steady price appreciation supported by rising volumes.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>1c4215519fe87bc9886b637c04d88357</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>R M Drip &amp; Sprinklers Systems Ltd Gains 4.70%: 5 Key Factors Driving the Rally</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/r-m-drip-sprinklers-systems-ltd-gains-470-5-key-factors-driving-the-rally-3849520</link><description>R M Drip &amp; Sprinklers Systems Ltd delivered a strong weekly performance, rising 4.70% from Rs.114.90 to Rs.120.30 between 16 and 20 February 2026, significantly outperforming the Sensex’s modest 0.39% gain over the same period. The stock hit multiple all-time and 52-week highs during the week, supported by sustained buying momentum, technical strength, and an upgrade in its Mojo Grade to Hold. Despite broader market volatility, the company’s shares demonstrated resilience and consistent upward movement, marking a notable phase in its market journey.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>51f413a8790edfc22a7a27c354bbafa9</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Prataap Snacks Ltd’s Mixed Week: -0.16% Price Change Amid Technical Shifts</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/prataap-snacks-ltds-mixed-week--016-price-change-amid-technical-shifts-3849521</link><description>Prataap Snacks Ltd closed the week ending 20 February 2026 marginally lower by 0.16%, finishing at Rs.1,073.90 compared to Rs.1,075.60 the previous Friday. This performance contrasted with the Sensex’s 0.39% gain over the same period, reflecting a week of technical uncertainty and mixed signals for the FMCG stock amid evolving market pressures and a recent downgrade to a Sell rating.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>0fbc46d65cce89912a0e8b9cdcf31b39</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Trident Texofab Ltd Drops 22.51%: 6 Key Factors Behind the Steep Decline</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/trident-texofab-ltd-drops-2251-6-key-factors-behind-the-steep-decline-3849524</link><description>Trident Texofab Ltd endured a challenging week from 16 to 20 February 2026, with its share price plummeting 22.51% from Rs.125.05 to Rs.96.90, sharply underperforming the Sensex which gained 0.39% over the same period. The stock hit fresh 52-week lows each trading day amid persistent selling pressure, deteriorating fundamentals, and elevated leverage concerns, signalling sustained bearish momentum despite a resilient broader market.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>19792aa97b808f7fad9ebac902eef6f4</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mehai Technology Declines 5.66% Amid Sharp Revenue Drop and Margin Pressures</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/mehai-technology-declines-566-amid-sharp-revenue-drop-and-margin-pressures-3849518</link><description>Mehai Technology Ltd’s shares declined by 5.66% over the week ending 20 February 2026, closing at Rs.1.50 from Rs.1.59 the previous Friday. This contrasted with the Sensex’s modest gain of 0.39% during the same period, underscoring the stock’s underperformance amid disappointing quarterly results and heightened market challenges.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>9694c09db2e1a9b1595f356fa158d08f</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reliable Data Services Ltd Falls 6.35%: Key Events and Valuation Shifts This Week</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/reliable-data-services-ltd-falls-635-key-events-and-valuation-shifts-this-week-3849519</link><description>Reliable Data Services Ltd experienced a challenging week, with its share price declining by 6.35% from ₹161.40 to ₹151.15, significantly underperforming the Sensex, which rose 0.39% over the same period. The week was marked by a sharp sell-off triggered by disappointing quarterly results, a lower circuit hit amid heavy selling pressure, and a reassessment of the company’s valuation metrics amid market volatility.
Time: 2 minutes ago</description><guid>94bcacc4844898298b528b665a495152</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>