<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:33:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Happy Forgings Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.1160.85</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/happy-forgings-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs116085-3777771</link><description>Happy Forgings Ltd has reached a significant milestone by hitting a new 52-week high of Rs.1160.85, marking a notable surge in the Castings &amp; Forgings sector. This achievement reflects sustained momentum driven by strong financial performance and positive market dynamics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a5158d2c8dc7ef63615ed024a9cd73f7</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sansera Engineering Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.1796.3</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sansera-engineering-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs17963-3777768</link><description>Sansera Engineering Ltd, a key player in the Auto Components &amp; Equipments sector, achieved a significant milestone today by reaching a new 52-week high of Rs.1796.3. This marks the highest price level the stock has attained, reflecting sustained momentum and robust market performance over recent sessions.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7af5aa9a67e88976e496a4676374a0fd</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Samrat Forgings Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs 230 Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/samrat-forgings-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs-230-amidst-continued-underperformance-3777763</link><description>Samrat Forgings Ltd, a player in the Castings &amp; Forgings sector, has touched a new 52-week low of Rs.230 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid persistent underperformance relative to the broader market and its sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>3e36fe474bb9b6a352262a950b6f6419</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sarthak Metals Ltd Stock Hits 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Downtrend</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/sarthak-metals-ltd-stock-hits-52-week-low-amidst-continued-downtrend-3777767</link><description>Sarthak Metals Ltd, a player in the Iron &amp; Steel Products sector, recorded a fresh 52-week low of Rs.83.62 today, marking a significant milestone in its ongoing price decline. The stock underperformed its sector by 1.89% and closed with a day change of -1.26%, reflecting persistent downward pressure amid a volatile trading session.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f4aea13e399f822faa63cdf8e1a2adce</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>PBM Polytex Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/pbm-polytex-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3777770</link><description>PBM Polytex Ltd, a player in the Garments &amp; Apparels sector, has touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.46.85 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid persistent challenges and underwhelming financial metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8bf0f1a06d48eef8b393a4d3416d6ee6</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Remedium Lifecare Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Financial Struggles</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/remedium-lifecare-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-financial-struggles-3777766</link><description>Remedium Lifecare Ltd, a company operating in the Trading &amp; Distributors sector, has reached a new 52-week and all-time low of Rs.0.74 today, marking a significant decline in its stock price amid ongoing financial difficulties and subdued market performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>a32186c8a0d93af19857ac951ae78184</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Future Market Networks Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Weak Financial Metrics</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/future-market-networks-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-weak-financial-metrics-3777764</link><description>Future Market Networks Ltd has declined to a fresh 52-week low of Rs.8.61, marking a significant downturn in the stock’s performance amid ongoing financial pressures and subdued growth metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>4c86d042bd49f5449dcdb3499c4a8874</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>SMT Engineering Ltd Hits New 52-Week High at Rs.199.65</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/smt-engineering-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-at-rs19965-3777772</link><description>SMT Engineering Ltd, a key player in the Trading &amp; Distributors sector, achieved a significant milestone today by reaching a new 52-week and all-time high price of Rs.199.65. This marks a continuation of the stock’s impressive upward momentum, reflecting robust performance and sustained investor confidence.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>201fead3e3b3281c41556a4f896e50bd</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Orient Ceratech Ltd Hits New 52-Week High of Rs 55 Marking Significant Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/orient-ceratech-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-of-rs-55-marking-significant-milestone-3777769</link><description>Orient Ceratech Ltd, a key player in the Electrodes &amp; Refractories sector, surged to a fresh 52-week high of Rs.55 on 1 Jan 2026, reflecting robust momentum and a strong performance trajectory amid a broadly steady market environment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c0c7cd5a46b47d87a0c51e0fb0926868</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>TTI Enterprise Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tti-enterprise-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3777765</link><description>TTI Enterprise Ltd, a Non Banking Financial Company (NBFC), touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.6.51 today, marking a significant decline in its share price amid ongoing underperformance relative to its sector and broader market indices.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>e038990a33000c975294eeb90a79281d</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Tijaria Polypipes Ltd Falls to 52-Week Low Amidst Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/tijaria-polypipes-ltd-falls-to-52-week-low-amidst-continued-underperformance-3777758</link><description>Tijaria Polypipes Ltd has declined to a fresh 52-week low, closing near Rs 4.2, marking a significant downturn in the stock’s performance over the past year. This new low reflects ongoing pressures within the company’s financial and market metrics, as it continues to lag behind sector and benchmark indices.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>7a3ae1d5ece5a49f47b63641a1ffebfc</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AIA Engineering Ltd Hits New 52-Week High, Marking Significant Market Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/aia-engineering-ltd-hits-new-52-week-high-marking-significant-market-milestone-3777759</link><description>AIA Engineering Ltd has reached a new 52-week high, closing just 1.63% shy of its peak price of ₹4,081.15, underscoring a robust rally in the Castings &amp; Forgings sector. This milestone reflects sustained momentum supported by strong market positioning and favourable technical indicators.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>a5fc0c0c5cc4275bb0944a476f739cdd</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>VST Industries Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low Amid Continued Underperformance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/vst-industries-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-amid-continued-underperformance-3777760</link><description>VST Industries Ltd has declined to a fresh 52-week low, with the stock touching an intraday low of Rs 238.2, marking a significant drop of 7.21% on the day. This latest low reflects ongoing challenges in the company’s performance and market sentiment within the FMCG sector.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>4e32ede5ab91cc89827a06dc2c711e75</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sensex and Nifty Inch Higher Amid Mixed Sectoral Trends; Telecom Leads Gains</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/sensex-and-nifty-inch-higher-amid-mixed-sectoral-trends-telecom-leads-gains-3777756</link><description>Indian equity benchmarks closed the first trading day of 2026 with marginal gains as investors digested mixed sectoral performances and awaited key corporate earnings. The Sensex slipped slightly by 0.04%, while the Nifty managed a modest 0.06% rise, supported by strength in telecommunications and midcap stocks despite pressure on FMCG and select large caps.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>2b93386609663d4d548f135e4a61f0aa</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>REC Ltd Hits Intraday High with Strong 3.25% Surge on 1 Jan 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/rec-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-strong-325-surge-on-1-jan-2026-3777748</link><description>REC Ltd demonstrated robust intraday performance on 1 Jan 2026, surging to an intraday high of Rs 368.15, marking a 3.17% increase and outperforming its sector by 3.07% despite a broadly subdued market environment.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>30013682176bf585d92480d8c178b8a0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Small and Micro Cap Stocks Deliver Exceptional Half-Year Returns Amidst Varied Sector Performance</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/small-and-micro-cap-stocks-deliver-exceptional-half-year-returns-amidst-varied-sector-performance-3777746</link><description>A select group of small and micro cap stocks have outperformed the broader market significantly over the past six months, delivering extraordinary returns that have far exceeded benchmark indices. Led by Cupid from the FMCG sector, these stocks have been propelled by strong fundamentals, bullish technicals, and sector-specific catalysts, rewarding investors with gains well above 100% in many cases.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>a7a8221ec152897ee351fbf2dd5a8620</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Small Cap Stocks Deliver Exceptional Returns Amid Varied Sector Performances</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stock-market-news/small-cap-stocks-deliver-exceptional-returns-amid-varied-sector-performances-3777747</link><description>In a remarkable display of market outperformance, several small-cap stocks have delivered extraordinary returns over the past year, with Cupid from the FMCG sector emerging as the standout performer, surging by an impressive 586.32%. This surge far outpaces benchmark indices and highlights the potential rewards of targeted small-cap investments amid evolving sector dynamics.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>05adb59be2388e33d891b28210560171</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Silver Touch Technologies Ltd Hits All-Time High, Marking a Significant Milestone</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/silver-touch-technologies-ltd-hits-all-time-high-marking-a-significant-milestone-3777739</link><description>Silver Touch Technologies Ltd, a key player in the Computers - Software &amp; Consulting sector, has reached an all-time high, underscoring its robust performance and sustained growth trajectory. This milestone reflects the company’s strong market presence and consistent upward momentum over multiple time frames.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>f0db8df024d7ef3c30a0f41d6dd5476d</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>National Standard (India) Ltd Hits Intraday High with 8.0% Surge on 1 January 2026</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/national-standard-india-ltd-hits-intraday-high-with-80-surge-on-1-january-2026-3777737</link><description>National Standard (India) Ltd demonstrated a robust intraday performance on 1 Jan 2026, surging by 8.0% to touch an intraday high of Rs 1,327, outperforming its Realty sector peers and the broader market indices.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>c744ab41f03ffeb3a9726528e62804ab</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cityman Ltd Stock Falls to 52-Week Low of Rs.11.15 Amidst Weak Fundamentals</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/cityman-ltd-stock-falls-to-52-week-low-of-rs1115-amidst-weak-fundamentals-3777733</link><description>Cityman Ltd, a player in the Gems, Jewellery And Watches sector, has touched a fresh 52-week low of Rs.11.15 today, marking a significant decline in its share price amid ongoing concerns over its financial health and market performance.
Time: 2 hours ago</description><guid>b6937bf9f32f57446d07d1160281c7aa</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 12:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>