<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>MarketsMojo – News (homepage)</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</link><description>RSS scraped from https://www.marketsmojo.com/news</description><language>en-IN</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title>Why is Western Carriers (India) Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-western-carriers-india-ltd-fallingrising-3793246</link><description>As of 16-Jan, Western Carriers (India) Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling 3.16% to ₹110.35. This downward movement reflects a combination of weak financial performance, deteriorating investor confidence, and underwhelming market returns relative to benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d0366836f15b584dd7c272a9ee1e4a40</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Indegene Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-indegene-ltd-fallingrising-3793245</link><description>On 16-Jan, Indegene Ltd’s stock price fell by 1.78% to close at ₹497.05, continuing a downward trend amid disappointing quarterly earnings and sustained underperformance relative to market benchmarks and its sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>cf5a30bc90a0fb288e040250de583712</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Globale Tessile Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-globale-tessile-ltd-fallingrising-3793244</link><description>On 16-Jan, Globale Tessile Ltd’s stock price fell sharply to ₹11.43, down 4.75% for the day, continuing a downward trend driven by poor financial performance and sustained market underperformance relative to benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>83408007c4d8d830fb92c67dff08575b</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is ESAF Small Finance Bank Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-esaf-small-finance-bank-ltd-fallingrising-3793243</link><description>On 16-Jan, ESAF Small Finance Bank Ltd witnessed a significant price rise of 13.03%, closing at ₹29.41, marking a notable rebound despite persistent fundamental challenges and a history of underperformance relative to the broader market.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d41fcb1a7b719e872dc851a69be0b910</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Electro Force (India) Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-electro-force-india-ltd-fallingrising-3793242</link><description>On 16-Jan, Electro Force (India) Ltd recorded a notable rise in its share price, climbing 2.43% to ₹33.70. This increase reflects a short-term positive momentum despite the stock’s challenging longer-term performance relative to the broader market.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c894d833750c8780fa859b16e6d6108c</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is E Factor Experiences Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-e-factor-experiences-ltd-fallingrising-3793241</link><description>On 16-Jan, E Factor Experiences Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 5.0% to close at ₹299.25. This downturn reflects a combination of short-term underperformance relative to benchmarks and a marked drop in investor engagement.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>c84a6564a9d7f7a0d94efe25a586b750</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Marco Cables &amp; Conductors Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-marco-cables-conductors-ltd-fallingrising-3793240</link><description>As of 16-Jan, Marco Cables &amp; Conductors Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.91% to ₹35.00. This downturn reflects a broader pattern of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and waning investor interest.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>31087a8f08c4608e98b24e17d09995c6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Vinsys IT Services India Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-vinsys-it-services-india-ltd-fallingrising-3793239</link><description>On 16-Jan, Vinsys IT Services India Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling by 2.55% to close at ₹334.85. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s underwhelming performance relative to broader market benchmarks and its sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>b3fbb03ef7a20d09495ce400f0ee2ee4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Cyient DLM Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-cyient-dlm-ltd-fallingrising-3793238</link><description>As of 16-Jan, Cyient DLM Ltd’s stock price has been on a downward trajectory, closing at ₹390.10 with a decline of 1.76% on the day. This drop reflects a broader trend of underperformance relative to market benchmarks and sector peers, despite some positive financial indicators.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>2cced0971d1ba06e01b9e030103763a7</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Senco Gold Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-senco-gold-ltd-fallingrising-3793237</link><description>On 16-Jan, Senco Gold Ltd’s stock price fell by 3.05% to close at ₹322.75, continuing a downward trend that has seen the share price decline by over 8% in the past week despite underlying positive financial metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>ea188ef46f8da920bc81f26d8a26e59f</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ideaforge Technology Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ideaforge-technology-ltd-fallingrising-3793236</link><description>On 16-Jan, Ideaforge Technology Ltd’s stock price fell by 1.97% to close at ₹450.00, continuing a downward trend influenced by weak financial performance and subdued investor participation despite rising promoter confidence.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>1435f247a47ebccdecc2ce7a29447bc6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Urban Enviro Waste Management Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-urban-enviro-waste-management-ltd-fallingrising-3793235</link><description>On 16-Jan, Urban Enviro Waste Management Ltd witnessed a decline in its share price, closing at ₹142.50, down ₹2.35 or 1.62% from the previous session. This drop reflects a continuation of the stock’s underperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>eb4133c7efc851a7a236eefd7ff9d950</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shera Energy Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shera-energy-ltd-fallingrising-3793234</link><description>On 16-Jan, Shera Energy Ltd’s stock price declined by 2.15% to ₹125.25, reflecting a broader pattern of recent volatility despite the company’s strong operational performance and attractive valuation metrics.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>70b6a26dc43a967bac12609051e5fdb6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Archean Chemical Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-archean-chemical-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3793233</link><description>On 16-Jan, Archean Chemical Industries Ltd witnessed a significant rise in its share price, climbing 7.25% to close at ₹548.55. This sharp uptick comes despite the company’s challenging long-term financial performance and recent negative earnings reports, reflecting a complex interplay of market dynamics and investor sentiment.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>0b282a229740a4e1b6558c44b084397b</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Pace E-Commerce Ventures Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-pace-e-commerce-ventures-ltd-fallingrising-3793232</link><description>On 16-Jan, Pace E-Commerce Ventures Ltd witnessed a notable decline in its share price, closing at ₹17.99, down ₹0.45 or 2.44% from the previous session. This drop reflects a continuation of a downward trend that has persisted over recent weeks, signalling ongoing challenges for the company’s stock performance.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>fa767edb21599a5b8d19b8764f02a1b1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Shriram Properties Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-shriram-properties-ltd-fallingrising-3793231</link><description>As of 16-Jan, Shriram Properties Ltd’s stock price has fallen to ₹77.98, reflecting a 1.6% decline on the day and continuing a downward trend over recent weeks despite positive earnings growth and increased institutional interest.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f962a0d3a1412216a33f5a804ddb688f</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Padmanabh Alloys &amp; Polymers Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-padmanabh-alloys-polymers-ltd-fallingrising-3793230</link><description>On 16-Jan, Padmanabh Alloys &amp; Polymers Ltd witnessed a significant decline in its share price, closing at ₹15.50, down ₹1.40 or 8.28% from the previous session. This sharp fall reflects a continuation of the stock’s underperformance relative to both its sector and the broader market benchmarks.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>d2c6858ae93f774240a57b1b9a771102</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Prakash Pipes Ltd. falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-prakash-pipes-ltd-fallingrising-3793229</link><description>As of 16-Jan, Prakash Pipes Ltd. has witnessed a notable decline in its share price, falling 2.76% to ₹208.25 and hitting a fresh 52-week low of ₹206.25. This downturn reflects a broader pattern of underperformance driven by disappointing financial results and subdued investor interest.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>7d5f81e0fdae3891d6831d2fd9a55195</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Ashoka Metcast Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-ashoka-metcast-ltd-fallingrising-3793228</link><description>On 16-Jan, Ashoka Metcast Ltd’s stock price fell by 3.49% to close at ₹14.40, continuing a downward trend driven by disappointing financial results and subdued investor participation.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>f716b27dcb3f5e963f4c62586e72e31f</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why is Mihika Industries Ltd falling/rising?</title><link>https://www.marketsmojo.com/news/stocks-in-action/why-is-mihika-industries-ltd-fallingrising-3793227</link><description>On 16-Jan, Mihika Industries Ltd witnessed a further decline in its share price, closing at ₹12.70, down by ₹0.20 or 1.55%. This drop continues a sustained period of underperformance relative to the broader market and its sector peers.
Time: 1 hour ago</description><guid>8398c5a6322d4a579bab47f952b8d9fc</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>{{list.post_title}}</title><link>{{list.post_url}}</link><description>{{list.post_excerpt}}
Time: {{list.post_date_sep}}</description><guid>b464824a46030d214ddfe38c4d063449</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:16:47 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>