<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>SKI Capital – Stock Alert News</title>
    <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/stock-alert</link>
    <description>Stock alert news from SKI Capital Services - Indian stock market updates</description>
    <language>en-IN</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 06:27:37 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Bharat Forge, Power Grid, Titan Company, RITES</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-bharat-forge-power-grid-titan-company-rites/stock-alert/1662479/30</link>
      <description>Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Bharat Forge has received a contract worth Rs 1,661.9 crore from the Ministry of Defence for the supply of 255,128 CQB carbines (5.56 x 45 mm) to the Indian Army. The contract stipulates order execution within five years. Power Grid Corporation of India has been declared the successful bidder for the selection of battery energy storage developers for setting up a cumulative capacity of 2,000 MWh (1,000 MW x 2 hours) of standalone battery energy storage systems in Andhra Pradesh. The project comprises a 150 MW/300 MWh battery energy storage system at the 400/220 kV substation at Kalikiri in Chittoor district, Andhra Pradesh. RITES has received a Letter of Award for the supply of in-service Cape gauge diesel-electric locomotives from Berhard Development Corporation, Zimbabwe. The order is valued at $3.6 million. Dynacons Systems &amp; Solutions said that it has received orders worth Rs 249 crore from RBI for the implementation &amp; maintenance of enterprise applications platform software. Titan Company said that its board has approved the appointment of Sandhya Venugopal Sharma, IAS, as chairperson and additional director of the company, effective January 4, 2026. Arfin India announced that it has received an order worth Rs 321 crore from Diamond Power Infra for the supply of Aluminium sector conductors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-bharat-forge-power-grid-titan-company-rites/stock-alert/1662479/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:57:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Lupin, RVNL, BEL, Waaree Energies, GNFC, NTP...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-lupin-rvnl-bel-waaree-energies-gnfc-ntpc-green-energy/stock-alert/1662314/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on Tuesday, 30 December 2025. New Listing New Listing Gujarat Kidney &amp; Super Speciality is slated to make its market debut on the mainboard today. The IPO was subscribed 5.21 times. The issue opened for bidding on 22 December 2025 and it closed on 24 December 2025. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 108 and 114 per share. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Lupin said that it has entered into an exclusive License, Supply, and Distribution Agreement with China-based Gan &amp; Lee Pharmaceuticals for a novel fortnightly GLP-1 receptor agonist, Bofanglutide. Bofanglutide injection is indicated for the treatment of type 2 diabetes and for weight management in overweight or obese individuals. Rail Vikas Nigam (RVNL) said that it has emerged as the lowest bidder for an order worth Rs 201.23 crore from East Coast Railway. The project involves setting up a wagon Periodic Overhaul (POH) workshop with a capacity of 200 wagons at Kantabanji. Bharat Electronics (BEL) said that it has received additional orders worth Rs 569 crore since December 12. These orders include radars, tank overhauls, communication equipment, fire control systems, simulators, antenna stabilisation systems, security software, components, upgrades, and spares. Waaree Energies said that Amit Paithankar has resigned as whole-time director and chief executive officer of the company to pursue opportunities outside the organisation, effective May 15, 2026. The company further said that the Board has approved the appointment of Jignesh Rathod, currently Director'Operations, as chief executive officer-designate with immediate effect. The Board has also appointed Jignesh Rathod as chief executive officer and Key Managerial Personnel, effective May 16, 2026. Gujarat Narmada Valley Fertilizers &amp; Chemicals (GNFC) said that T Natarajan has resigned as managing director with effect from December 29 following an order from the Government of Gujarat. The Government of Gujarat has nominated Rajkumar Beniwal, IAS, as managing director with effect from December 29. NTPC Green Energy announced the commencement of commercial operations of the ninth part capacity of 13.98 MW of the 1,255 MW Khavda-I Solar PV project of NTPC Renewable Energy. With this addition, the current commercial capacity of NTPC Green Energy stands at 7,996.30 MW, while the total installed capacity of the NGEL Group has increased to 8,010.28 MW.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-lupin-rvnl-bel-waaree-energies-gnfc-ntpc-green-energy/stock-alert/1662314/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 07:58:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Coforge, Vedanta, Suzlon Energy, Solarworld ...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-coforge-vedanta-suzlon-energy-solarworld-energy-solutions/stock-alert/1662162/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on Monday, 29 December 2025. Key Events to Watch Key Events to Watch The government is slated to release the Index of Industrial Production (IIP) data for November, which will offer cues on industrial activity. The Supreme Court of India is scheduled to hear a matter related to the definition of the Aravalli Hills. S. Krishnan, Secretary, Ministry of Electronics &amp; IT, will brief the media on the upcoming India AI Impact Summit 2026. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Coforge announced that it has signed a definitive agreement to acquire a 100% stake in Encora from Advent International, Warburg Pincus, and other minority shareholders for Rs 17,032.6 crore. The enterprise value of the transaction stands at $2.35 billion. The board approved raising up to $550 million through a qualified institutional placement (QIP) to repay Encora's term loan. Vedanta said that it has been declared the successful bidder for the Depo Graphite'Vanadium block under the critical mineral auctions. The company said the development will strengthen its critical minerals portfolio. Suzlon Energy announced that Vivek Srivastava has resigned as Chief Executive Officer (CEO) of the WTG Division, effective December 26. Diamond Power Infrastructure said that it has received a letter of intent from Hild Projects, an EPC contractor, for the supply of power cables worth Rs 66.18 crore. Avantel informed that it has received a contract worth Rs 4.16 crore from the Ministry of Defence, Headquarters Naval Aviation, for CAMC of Satcom equipment. Solarworld Energy Solutions said that it has received a letter of award from NTPC Renewable Energy for an EPC package for the development of a 250 MWac grid-connected solar PV project valued at Rs 725.33 crore. Vikran Engineering announced that it has accepted letters of award from MP Urja Vikas Nigam for the implementation of grid-connected solar PV-based power plants with an aggregate capacity of 45.75 MW AC in Vidisha, Madhya Pradesh.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-coforge-vedanta-suzlon-energy-solarworld-energy-solutions/stock-alert/1662162/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:54:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: NBCC (India), Ola Electric, Lenskart Solutio...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-nbcc-india-ola-electric-lenskart-solutions-gujarat-gas/stock-alert/1661934/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Shares of Sammaan Capital banned from F&amp;O trading on 26 December 2025. Stocks To Watch: Stocks To Watch: NBCC (India) has signed memorandum of understanding (MoU) with Board of Mumbai Port Authority for the development of CGO Complex on 25 acres at Mumbai Port's land, as deposit work on turnkey basis. Ola Electric Mobility received a sanction order from the Ministry of Heavy Industries, Government of India, for the release of incentives amounting to Rs 366.78 crore under the Production Linked Incentive Scheme for Automobile and Auto Components (PLI-Auto Scheme) for claims pertaining to FY 2024-25. Lenskart Solutions' Singapore arm approved an investment of KRW 3 billon (approximately Rs 18.6 crore ) for the acquisition of 29.24% of the share capital of iiNeer Corp. Gujarat Gas' Milind Torawane, IAS has resigned as managing director with effect from 24 th December 2025, following his transfer and appoint as Principal Secretary to Government, Education Department (Primary &amp; Secondary Education). It has appointed Avantika Singh Aulakh, IAS as managing director. Strides Pharma Sciences' wholly owned subsidiary, Strides Pharma Inc. USA has received a Form 483 with four observations from US Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) following an inspection of its formulations facility at Chestnut Ridge, New York.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-nbcc-india-ola-electric-lenskart-solutions-gujarat-gas/stock-alert/1661934/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: GAIL (India), Vikran Engg, Adani Ports, Coal...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-gail-india-vikran-engg-adani-ports-coal-india-rvnl/stock-alert/1661747/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Shares of Sammaan Capital are banned from F&amp;O trading on 24 December 2025. Stocks To Watch: Stocks To Watch: GAIL (India) has signed memorandum of understanding (MoU) with Government of Chhattisgarh for development of a greenfield gas-based fertilizer project in Chhattisgarh. Vikran Engineering received a Rs 2035 crore order from Onix Renewables for EPC works for solar plant development. Adani Ports &amp; Special Economic Zone successfully completed the acquisition of 100% interest in North Queensland Export Terminal (NQXT), Australia pursuant to completion of all condition precedents, with the acquisition of NQXT, APSEZ is on track to achieve 1 Billion tonne of cargo volume by 2030. Emcure Pharmaceuticals has received establishment inspection report (EIR). The US FDA has classified the inspection of the facility as no action indicated (NAI). Inspection was conducted from 6 October to 10 October 2025. Coal India's board approved for listing of arm Mahanadi Coalfields in the upcoming financial year. Ajanta Pharma has entered into an in-licensing agreement with Biocon for marketing Semaglutide, a GLP-1 receptor agonist. Rail Vikas Nigam (RVNL) board approved the appointment of Saleem Ahmad as chairman &amp; managing director with effect from 23 December 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-gail-india-vikran-engg-adani-ports-coal-india-rvnl/stock-alert/1661747/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 08:01:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: HCL Tech, Sanghvi Movers, Prestige Estate Pr...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-hcl-tech-sanghvi-movers-prestige-estate-projects-saatvik-green-energy/stock-alert/1661587/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Shares of Sammaan Capital are banned from F&amp;O trading on 23 December 2025. New Listing: New Listing: KSH International shares will list on the stock exchanges. The IPO was subscribed 0.83 times. The issue opened for bidding on 16 December 2025 and it closed on 18 December 2025. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 365 and 384 per share. Stocks To Watch: Stocks To Watch: HCL Technologies' software business division, HCL Software will acquire Wobby, an early'stage startup providing AI Data Analyst 'Agents' for data warehouses, based in Antwerp, Belgium, for total consideration of Euro 4.5 million Meanwhile, HCL Software will also acquire Jaspersoft, a business unit of cloud software group and provider of a leading embedded analytics and pixel-perfect reporting platform, for a total consideration of $240 million Sanghvi Movers' material subsidiary, Sangreen Future Renewables has been awarded large work orders worth Rs 428.72 crore from prominent Independent Power Producers (IPP's). Prestige Estates Projects has announced the acquisition of a 25-acre land parcel in Medavakkam, Chennai with a development potential of approximately 5 million square feet. The project is estimated to generate top-line revenue of over Rs 5,000 crore. GPT Infraprojects said that its consortium with ISCPPL has been declared L1 (First Lowest) in order valued at Rs 670 crore for construction of four lane elevated road in Jodhpur city. Saatvik Green Energy's material subsidiary, Saatvik Solar Industries has received an order aggregating to Rs 486 crore from one renowned Independent Power producers/EPC Players for supply of solar PV modules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-hcl-tech-sanghvi-movers-prestige-estate-projects-saatvik-green-energy/stock-alert/1661587/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 08:02:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Reliance Inds, Lupin, TCS, HCL Tech</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-reliance-inds-lupin-tcs-hcl-tech/stock-alert/1661236/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on 19 December 2025. IPO Listing IPO Listing ICICI Prudential Asset Management Company's ICICI Prudential Asset Management Company's shares will list on the stock exchanges today. The issue price was set at Rs 2,165 per share. The issue was subscribed 39.17 times. It opened for bidding on 12 December 2025 and it closed on 16 December 2025. The price band was Rs 2,061-2,165. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Reliance Industries announced that its arm, Reliance Consumer, has acquired a majority stake in Udhaiyam Agro Foods. Lupin announced that its subsidiaries in the Philippines (Multicare Pharmaceuticals) and Brazil (MedQu'mica) have signed an agreement with Neopharmed Gentili to market the brand Plasil in Brazil and the Philippines. Tata Consultancy Services announced that its subsidiary, TCS Iberoamerica S.A., has incorporated a technology company, Sociedad An'nima, in Costa Rica. HCL Technologies announced that it has signed a definitive agreement to acquire the telecom solutions business of Hewlett Packard Enterprise for USD 160 million. Narayana Hrudayalaya announced that its board will meet shareholders and creditors on January 19 to seek approval for the merger scheme of Meridian Medical Research into the company. Hexaware Technologies announced that its Board has approved the merger of Softcrylic Tech Solutions and Mobiquity SoftTech with the company. Mishra Dhatu Nigam announced that it has secured orders worth Rs 121.75 crore. Its open order position as of date stands at approximately Rs 2,520 crore. Aeroflex Industries announced that its board has approved a capacity addition of 13,000 units per year for liquid cooling skids used in data centres. The plan includes installing robotic and automated welding lines for flexible stainless-steel hose assemblies and setting up an annealing plant for stainless-steel braided hoses for mission-critical applications, as per management requirements. Bharti Hexacom announced the appointment of Kathikeyan Velu as Chief Financial Officer, effective January 1, 2026. Akhil Garg has resigned as CFO due to organizational movement within the Bharti Group. Rossari Biotech announced that it has incorporated wholly owned subsidiary Rossari (Singapore) on 18 December 2025. Biocon announced that its New Jersey unit has received an Establishment Inspection Report (EIR) from the US FDA with a Voluntary Action Indicated (VAI) status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-reliance-inds-lupin-tcs-hcl-tech/stock-alert/1661236/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 08:08:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: KP Energy, Jio Financial Services, IndusInd ...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-kp-energy-jio-financial-services-indusind-bank-titagarh-rail-systems-astrazeneca-pharma/stock-alert/1661057/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Bandhan Bank shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on 18 December 2025. Key Events to Watch: Key Events to Watch: Prime Minister Narendra Modi in Oman on final leg of three-nation visit, India and Oman to sign a free trade agreement in Muscat. Renewable Energy Minister Pralhad Joshi to speak at ISMA AGM. IPO Offering IPO Offering KSH International KSH International : The public issue was subscribed to 0.26 times on day 2. There were no bids by Qualified institutional investors, while non-institutional investors subscribed (0.13 times) and retail investors (0.46 times). Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: KP Energy said that it has signed a memorandum of understanding (MoU) with the Republic of Botswana to collaborate on the development of renewable energy and power infrastructure projects in the country. Jio Financial Services said that its board has approved the appointment of Venkata Peri as group chief operating officer (COO), effective December 22. IndusInd Bank informed that Shiv Bhasin has resigned from his position as chief technology officer (CTO), with effect from 16 January 2026. Titagarh Rail Systems said it has received an order worth Rs 273 crore from the Ministry of Railways for the manufacture of Rail Borne Maintenance Vehicles. AstraZeneca Pharma India said the Central Drugs Standard Control Organisation (CDSCO) has granted permission to import, sell and distribute Datopotamab Deruxtecan powder in the country. Chalet Hotels said its board has approved the allotment of 2,000 commercial paper to raise funds worth Rs 100 crore. One MobiKwik Systems said its board has approved the appointment of Navdeep Singh Suri as chairman of the company. Denta Water and Infrastructure said it has received four orders worth Rs 106 crore from Karnataka Urban Infrastructure Development &amp; Finance Corporation for urban sanitisation &amp; water management projects across Karnataka.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-kp-energy-jio-financial-services-indusind-bank-titagarh-rail-systems-astrazeneca-pharma/stock-alert/1661057/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:14:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: RailTel Corp, Diamond Power Infra, Lupin, Ah...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-railtel-corp-diamond-power-infra-lupin-ahluwalia-contracts/stock-alert/1660884/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Bandhan Bank shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on 17 December 2025. Key Events to Watch: Key Events to Watch: Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman to speak at India Economic Conclave in New Delhi. Prime Minister Narendra Modi's second day in Ethiopia, travels to Oman later. SEBI Chairman Tuhin Kanta Pandey to address media in Mumbai. IPO Update: IPO Update: ICICI Prudential AMC ICICI Prudential AMC : The public issue was subscribed to 39.17 times on day 3. The bids were led by Qualified institutional investors with 123.87 times the subscription, non-institutional investors who subscribed 22.04 times, retail investors with 2.53 times the subscription and Shareholders who subscribed 9.75 times. KSH International KSH International : The public issue was subscribed to 0.15 times on day 1. There were no bids were led by Qualified institutional investors, non-institutional investors who subscribed 0.06 times and retail investors who subscribed 0.27 times. IPO Listings: IPO Listings: Park Medi World Park Medi World : The public issue was subscribed to 8.52 times on day 3. The bids were led by Qualified institutional investors (12.07 times), non-institutional investors (15.93x), retail investors (3.32x). Nephrocare Health Services Nephrocare Health Services : The public issue was subscribed to 14.08 times on day 3. The bids were led by Qualified institutional investors (26.82 times), non-institutional investors (24.77 times), retail investors (2.36 times), Employees (2.81 times). Stocks To Watch: Stocks To Watch: RailTel Corporation of India said that it has received a letter of acceptance (LoA) for a Rs 26.9 crore contract to implement advanced IT infrastructure at VO Chidambaranar Port. Diamond Power Infrastructure has received a letter of intent (LoI) for a Rs 57.6 crore order from Rajesh Power for supply of cables. Lupin said its injectable manufacturing facility at Nagpur has received the Establishment Inspection Report (EIR) from the US Food and Drug Administration (US FDA) with a Voluntary Action Indicated (VAI) classification. Ahluwalia Contracts (India) said that it has received an order worth Rs 888.38 crore from Bihar State Tourism Development Corporation Ltd for civil construction works. Niraj Cement Structurals said that it has secured an order worth Rs 131 crore from the Public Works Department (PWD) for road maintenance works. Glenmark Pharmaceuticals said that its subsidiary, Glenmark Specialty S.A. (GSSA) has entered into an agreement with Hansoh Pharma to jointly develop &amp; commercialise Aumolertinib, a drug indicated for the treatment of non-small cell lung cancer (NSCLC).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-railtel-corp-diamond-power-infra-lupin-ahluwalia-contracts/stock-alert/1660884/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 07:14:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Atlantaa, Hyundai Motor, Solex Energy, Zydus...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-atlantaa-hyundai-motor-solex-energy-zydus-lifesciences-arvind-smartspaces/stock-alert/1660718/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Bandhan Bank shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on 16 December 2025. IPO Update: IPO Update: ICICI Prudential AMC ICICI Prudential AMC : The public issue was subscribed to 2.11 times on day 2. The bids were led by Qualified institutional investors (2.91 times), non-institutional investors (3.79 times), retail investors (0.83 times). IPO Opening: IPO Opening: KSH International KSH International :The company is the third-largest manufacturer and the largest exporter of magnet winding wires, has opened its initial public offering. Operating under the 'KSH' brand, the company supplies to OEMs across sectors such as power, renewables, railways, automotive, and industrials. The IPO comprises a fresh issue worth Rs 420 crore and an offer for sale of Rs 290 crore. The price band has been fixed at Rs 365 to Rs 384 per share. Ahead of the issue, the company raised Rs 213 crore from anchor investors. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Atlantaa said that it has entered into a development agreement with Highway Milton Co-operative Housing Society for the redevelopment of a residential project in Borivali, Mumbai. The project is estimated to have a gross development value (GDV) of around Rs 500 crore. Hyundai Motor said its shareholders have approved the appointment of Tarun Garg as managing director (MD) and chief executive officer (CEO), effective 1 January 2026. Solex Energy said that it has partnered with Malaysia-based TT Vision to boost solar manufacturing and engineering capabilities in India. Zydus Lifesciences said the USFDA has accepted the resubmission of the new drug application for CUTX-101. The drug, a copper histidinate, is indicated for the treatment of Menkes disease in pediatric patients. Arvind SmartSpaces said that it has acquired a new residential high-rise project in Bengaluru, with an estimated revenue potential of nearly Rs 550 crore.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-atlantaa-hyundai-motor-solex-energy-zydus-lifesciences-arvind-smartspaces/stock-alert/1660718/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 07:29:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>