<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>SKI Capital – Stock Alert News</title>
    <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/stock-alert</link>
    <description>Stock alert news from SKI Capital Services - Indian stock market updates</description>
    <language>en-IN</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:29:48 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Lenskart Solutions, Capacite Infra, Patanjal...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-lenskart-solutions-capacite-infra-patanjali-foods-lg-electronics-godrej-industries/stock-alert/1675513/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Sammaan Capital and Steel Authority of India (SAIL) shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on 12 February 2026. Result Today: Result Today: Hindustan Unilever, Oil and Natural Gas Corporation, Coal India, Lupin, Hindalco Industries, Honasa Consumer, Abbott India, Bajaj Hindusthan Sugar, Bharat Forge, Biocon, CRISIL, Endurance Technologies, Engineers India, Entero Healthcare Solutions, Hindustan Aeronautics, Indraprastha Gas, Indian Hotels Company, Indian Railway Catering and Tourism Corporation, Muthoot Finance, Natco Pharma, Petronet LNG, Rashtriya Chemicals and Fertilizers, SpiceJet, TVS Electronics, Welspun Living, and Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services will release their quarterly earnings today. IPO Data: IPO Data: Fractal Analytics IPO: Subscribed 2.66x overall on Day 3, with QIBs leading at 4.18x subscription, followed by NII at 1.1x and retail at 1x. Aye Finance IPO: Subscribed 97% overall on Day 3, with QIBs leading at 1.5x subscription, while retail stands at 77% and NII at 5%. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Lenskart Solutions reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 131 crore in Q3 FY26, up from Rs 1.9 crore in Q3 FY25. Consolidated revenue from operations rose 38.3% year-on-year to Rs 2,308 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 1,669 crore in Q3 FY25. Capacite Infraprojects reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 50 crore in Q3 FY26, down 3.8% from Rs 52 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 14.4% year-on-year to Rs 675 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 590 crore in Q3 FY25. Jupiter Wagons reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 63 crore in Q3 FY26, down 35.3% from Rs 97.3 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations declined 13.6% year-on-year to Rs 890 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 1,030 crore in Q3 FY25. Elgi Equipments reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 95.2 crore in Q3 FY26, up 18.1% from Rs 80.6 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 18.4% year-on-year to Rs 1,003 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 848 crore in Q3 FY25. IRCON International reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 101 crore in Q3 FY26, up 16.2% from Rs 86.6 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations declined 18.9% year-on-year to Rs 2,119 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 2,613 crore in Q3 FY25. Godrej Industries reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 205 crore in Q3 FY26, up 8.7% from Rs 188 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 4.7% year-on-year to Rs 5,051 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 4,825 crore in Q3 FY25. LG Electronics reported a standalone net profit of Rs 89.6 crore in Q3 FY26, down 61.6% from Rs 233 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations declined 6.4% year-on-year to Rs 4,114 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 4,396 crore in Q3 FY25. Patanjali Foods reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 593 crore in Q3 FY26, up 60.0% from Rs 371 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 16.5% to Rs 10,484 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 8,997 crore in Q3 FY25.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-lenskart-solutions-capacite-infra-patanjali-foods-lg-electronics-godrej-industries/stock-alert/1675513/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 07:07:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Titan Company, Eicher Motors,  Apollo Hospit...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-titan-company-eicher-motors-apollo-hospitals-ent-grasim-industries-torrent-power/stock-alert/1674809/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Sammaan Capital and Steel Authority of India (SAIL) shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on 11 February 2026. Result Today: Result Today: Mahindra &amp; Mahindra, LG Electronics India, Lenskart Solutions, Ashok Leyland, Aarey Drugs &amp; Pharmaceuticals, Amagi Media Labs, Amara Raja Energy &amp; Mobility, AstraZeneca Pharma India, Avanti Feeds, CARE Ratings, Carraro India, Divis Laboratories, Godrej Industries, International Gemmological Institute (India), Max Financial Services, Patanjali Foods, TBO Tek, and Yatra Online will announce their quarterly earnings today. Key Events to Watch: Key Events to Watch: The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) will conduct Rs 34,000 crore in T-bill auctions. IPO Data: IPO Data: Fractal Analytics IPO: Subscribed 20% overall on Day 2, with retail investors leading with 60% subscription. Aye Finance IPO: Subscribed 16% overall on Day 2, with retail investors at 47%, and QIBs at 13%. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Titan Company reported a 60.84% year-on-year rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,684 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 1,047 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue increased 43.26% YoY to Rs 25,416 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 17,740 crore in Q3 FY25. Eicher Motors reported a 21.36% year-on-year increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,420.61 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 1,170.5 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue rose 22.94% YoY to Rs 6,114.04 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 4,973.12 crore in the year-ago period. ZF Commercial Vehicle Control Systems India reported an 11.72% year-on-year rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 140.17 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 125.46 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue increased 11.68% YoY to Rs 1,074.91 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 962.42 crore a year earlier. Jubilant FoodWorks reported a 65.22% year-on-year jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 70.9 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 42.91 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue rose 13.31% YoY to Rs 2,437.21 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 2,150.76 crore in the year-ago quarter Torrent Power reported a 35.19% year-on-year increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 643.08 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 475.66 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue rose 4.28% YoY to Rs 6,777.87 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 6,499.38 crore in the year-ago quarter. Gujarat Pipavav Port reported an 8.59% year-on-year increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 107.91 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 99.37 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue rose 11.16% YoY to Rs 292.25 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 262.89 crore in the corresponding quarter last year. Grasim Industries reported a 26.39% year-on-year rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 1,036.59 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 820.12 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue increased 25.25% YoY to Rs 44,311.97 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 35,378.34 crore in the year-ago quarter. Apollo Hospitals Enterprise reported a 34.91% year-on-year rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 502 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 372 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue increased 17.19% YoY to Rs 6,477 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 5,527 crore a year earlier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-titan-company-eicher-motors-apollo-hospitals-ent-grasim-industries-torrent-power/stock-alert/1674809/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 07:06:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Apollo Micro Systems, Neuland Laboratories, ...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-apollo-micro-systems-neuland-laboratories-pnc-infra-texmaco-rail-bata-india/stock-alert/1674214/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on 10 February 2026. Result Today: Result Today: Titan Company, Eicher Motors, Grasim Industries, Apollo Hospitals Enterprise, Britannia Industries, Oil India, Afcons Infrastructure, Balrampur Chini Mills, Dilip Buildcon, Edelweiss Financial Services, Escorts Kubota, Jubilant FoodWorks, Karnataka Bank, Samvardhana Motherson International, Torrent Power, TVS Supply Chain Solutions, United Breweries, Wakefit Innovations, and Wockhardt will release their quarterly earnings today. IPO Data: IPO Data: Aye Finance IPO Subscribed 12% on Day 1 The initial public offering (IPO) of Aye Finance saw an overall subscription of 12% on the first day of bidding. The issue was driven primarily by retail investors, whose portion was subscribed 26%. The qualified institutional buyers (QIBs) segment was subscribed 13%, while the non-institutional investors (NIIs) category saw a muted response with just 1% subscription as of Day 1. Fractal Analytics IPO Subscribed 9% on Day 1 The Fractal Analytics IPO garnered an overall subscription of 9% on the opening day of the issue. Retail investors led the demand, subscribing 35% of their allocated portion. The non-institutional investors (NIIs) segment was subscribed 7% on the first day of bidding, while other categories witnessed relatively subdued participation. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Apollo Micro Systems reported a 40.62% year-on-year increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 25.68 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 18.26 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue rose 69.96% to Rs 252.22 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 148.39 crore in the year-ago period. Neuland Laboratories reported a 60.06% year-on-year decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 40.57 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 101.59 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue increased 10.47% to Rs 439.71 crore from Rs 398.03 crore a year ago. PNC Infratech reported a 5.67% year-on-year decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 76.73 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 81.35 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue fell 18.33% to Rs 1,200.58 crore from Rs 1,470.01 crore a year ago. Texmaco Rail &amp; Engineering reported a 44.66% year-on-year decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 42.27 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 76.39 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue fell 21.46% to Rs 1,041.6 crore from Rs 1,326.14 crore a year ago. Bata India reported a 12.8% year-on-year increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 66.1 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 58.6 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue rose 2.8% to Rs 945 crore from Rs 919 crore a year ago. Gulf Oil Lubricants India reported a 21.9% year-on-year decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 76.4 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 97.9 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue increased 10.6% to Rs 1,018 crore from Rs 920 crore a year ago. Genus Power Infrastructures reported a 147.51% year-on-year jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 140.24 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 56.66 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue surged 85.75% to Rs 1,122.36 crore from Rs 604.2 crore a year ago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-apollo-micro-systems-neuland-laboratories-pnc-infra-texmaco-rail-bata-india/stock-alert/1674214/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:49:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: State Bank of India, Hi-Tech Pipes, Ram Ratn...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-state-bank-of-india-hi-tech-pipes-ram-ratna-wires-tata-steel-godawari-power/stock-alert/1673784/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on 9 February 2026. Result Today: Result Today: Zydus Lifesciences, Aurobindo Pharma, All Time Plastics, Amber Enterprises India, Bajaj Electricals, Bata India, Enviro Infra Engineers, PNGS Gargi Fashion Jewellery, GlaxoSmithKline Pharmaceuticals, Happiest Minds Technologies, Navin Fluorine International, P N Gadgil Jewellers, Ramco Cements, Sun Pharma Advanced Research Company, Trident, and Vadilal Industries will release quarterly earnings today. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: KRN Heat Exchanger and Refrigeration has reported 65.09% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 22.66 crore on a 33.29% increase in total income to Rs 155.09 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. State Bank of India has reported 24.49% jump in net profit to Rs 21,028 crore on a 9.69% increase in total income to Rs 1,40,915 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Hi-Tech Pipes has reported 14.2% fall in consolidated net profit to Rs 17.38 crore despite a 24.6% increase in net revenue from operations to Rs 1,069.58 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Ram Ratna Wires reported a 73.1% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 31.28 crore on 43.8% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 1,277.93 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Baazar Style Retail's consolidated net profit declined 37.65% to Rs 18.96 crore on 13.33% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 466.47 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Tata Steel reported a sharp 723.14% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 2688.70 crore on 6.4% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 56,646.05 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Sonata Software reported a 13.17% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 104.36 crore despite a 45.36% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 3,080.58 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q2 FY26. Godawari Power &amp; Ispat reported a 1.1% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 143 crore despite a 12.2% fall in revenue to Rs 1,139 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Sula Vineyards reported a sharp 67.6% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 9.1 crore on a 9.9% fall in revenue to Rs 180 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-state-bank-of-india-hi-tech-pipes-ram-ratna-wires-tata-steel-godawari-power/stock-alert/1673784/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:47:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Bharti Airtel, Nykaa, Tata Motors PV, LIC, B...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-bharti-airtel-nykaa-tata-motors-pv-lic-berger-paints/stock-alert/1672468/30</link>
      <description>Earnings Today Earnings Today Tata Steel, Baazar Style Retail, Shipping Corporation of India, Lemon Tree Hotels, Whirlpool of India, Sun TV Network, Shree Cement, Sonata Software, BEML, BLS International Services, Bosch, Centum Electronics, CESC, Crompton Greaves, JK Tyre &amp; Industries, Jana Small Finance Bank, Jubilant Pharmova, Kalpataru, Kalyan Jewellers India will declare their result later today. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Bharti Airtel reported a 55.14% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 6,630.5 crore, despite a 19.62% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 53,981.6 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Berger Paints reported 8.1% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 271.16 crore despite 0.3% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 2983.97 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q3 December 2024. FSN E-Commerce (Nykaa)'s consolidated net profit surged 142.4% to Rs 63.31 crore on 26.7% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 2973.26 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles reported consolidated net loss of Rs 3,486 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with net profit of Rs 5406 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations fell 25.81% YoY to Rs 69,605 crore during the quarter. Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC)'s consolidated net profit climbed 17.5% YoY to Rs 12,930.44 crore in Q3 FY26. Total income jumped 15.7% YoY to Rs 236,776.30 crore during the quarter. Bharti Hexacom recorded a 48.7% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 481.29 crore on 4.8% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 2,359.90 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Hero Motocorp's consolidated net profit climbed 19.6% to Rs 1438.88 crore on 20.7% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 12,328.38 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-bharti-airtel-nykaa-tata-motors-pv-lic-berger-paints/stock-alert/1672468/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 07:49:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Trent, Tata Power, JSW Cement, Cummins India...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-trent-tata-power-jsw-cement-cummins-india-marico/stock-alert/1671608/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Shares of Sammaan Capital are banned from F&amp;O trading on Thursday, 5 February 2026. Earnings to Watch: Earnings to Watch: Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles, Bharti Airtel, Bharti Hexacom, Hero MotoCorp, Hindustan Copper, Aditya Birla Fashion and Retail, Allcargo Logistics, Alembic Pharmaceuticals, PVR Inox, Berger Paints India, Godrej Properties, FSN E-Commerce, Page Industries, Power Finance Corporation, Borosil, Caplin Point Laboratories, Cemindia Projects, Dalmia Bharat Sugar and Industries, Data Patterns (India), Dhanuka Agritech, Dredging Corporation of India, Eveready Industries India, FDC, Gokul Agro Resources, Goodyear India, Harsha Engineers International, HealthCare Global Enterprises, Rail Vikas Nigam will declare their results later today. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Trent reported a 36.3% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 639.71 crore on 15.98% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 5259.46 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Tata Power Company reported 25.1% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 771.98 crore on 9.37% fall in revenue from operations to Rs 13,948.41 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. JSW Cement reported consolidated net profit of Rs 149.02 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with net loss of Rs 68.79 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 13.16% YoY to Rs 1621.22 crore in Q3 FY26. Cummins India reported a 12.96% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 486.06 crore on a 1.5% fall in revenue from operations to Rs 3006.24 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Metorpolis Healthcare's consolidated net profit jumped 31.97% to Rs 4138.56 crore on 25.76% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 40,590.97 crore in Q3 December 2025 over Q3 December 2024. Apollo Tyres reported 39.52% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 470.51 crore on 11.77% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 7743.07 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Marico has entered into definitive agreements to acquire a 60% stake in Cosmix Wellness, the company which owns the brand, Cosmix ' one of India's leading digital-first functional wellness brands, at an valuation of Rs 375 crore.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-trent-tata-power-jsw-cement-cummins-india-marico/stock-alert/1671608/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 07:40:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Mankind Pharma, Godrej Agrovet, Bajaj Financ...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-mankind-pharma-godrej-agrovet-bajaj-finance-rubicon-research/stock-alert/1671050/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on 04 February 2026. New SME Listing: New SME Listing: Accretion Nutraveda is set to list on the SME Platform today. The issue opened for bidding 28 January 2026 and it closed 30 January 2025. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 122 to Rs 129 per share. The issue was subscribed 1.77 times. Msafe Equipment set to debut on the SME platform today. The issue opened for bidding on 28 January 2026 and it closed on 30 January 2025. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 116 to Rs 123 per share. The issue was subscribed 153.98 times. Kanishk Aluminium India will list on SME platform today. The issue opened for bidding on 28 January 2026 and it closed 30 January 2026. The price band of the IPO was fixed at Rs 73 per share. The minimum order quantity is 1,600 equity shares. Result Today: Result Today: Archean Chemical Industries, Apollo Tyres, Aptus Value Housing Finance India, Aurionpro Solutions, Automotive Axles, Avalon Technologies, Bajaj Finserv, Bajaj Holdings &amp; Investment, Carysil, CCL Products (India), Century Plyboards (India), Cera Sanitaryware, Cummins India, Devyani International, Emami, Emcure Pharmaceuticals, Eureka Forbes, Force Motors, Gallantt Ispat, Greenply Industries, Hexaware Technologies, Inventurus Knowledge Solutions, Jain Irrigation Systems, Jaiprakash Power Ventures, JSW Cement, Jubilant Ingrevia, Kalpataru Projects International, Lloyds Engineering Works, Global Health, Metropolis Healthcare, NHPC, Parag Milk Foods, Apeejay Surrendra Park Hotels, Pokarna, Quality Power Electrical Equipments, Redington, RITES, Rane (Madras), Keystone Realtors, Saatvik Green Energy, Sammaan Capital, Shipping Corporation of India Land and Assets, Tata Power Company, Transport Corporation of India, TeamLease Services, Tube Investments of India, Timken India, Tamilnad Mercantile Bank, Trent, Welspun Enterprises, Westlife Foodworld, Wonderla Holidays and Xpro India will announce their quarterly earnings today. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Bajaj Finance reported 6.33% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,977.85 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 4,246.54 crore in Q3 FY25. Total revenue from operations jumped 17.63% YoY to Rs 21,213.89 crore in Q3 FY26. Mankind Pharma reported a 7.6% year-on-year increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 409 crore, driven by an 11.5% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 3,567 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Q3 FY25. Godrej Agrovet posted a 3% year-on-year growth in consolidated net profit to Rs 115 crore, while revenue increased 11% to Rs 2,718 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Rubucon Research reported 91.2% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 72.8 crore on 51.7% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 475.5 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Aditya Birla Capital's consolidated net profit jumped 33.48% to Rs 945.02 crore on 27.4% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 11952.09 crore in Q3 FY36 over Q2 FY25.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-mankind-pharma-godrej-agrovet-bajaj-finance-rubicon-research/stock-alert/1671050/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 08:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Ather Energy, Tata Chemicals, APSEZ,  Maruti...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-ather-energy-tata-chemicals-apsez-maruti-suzuki-india/stock-alert/1670488/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Shares of Sammaan Capital are banned from F&amp;O trading on Tuesday, 3 February 2026. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Export and import oriented stocks will be in focus after India and United States signed a trade deal under which tariffs will be reduced from 50% to 18% while the additional 25% duty linked to the purchases of Russian crude oil will be eliminated. Ather Energy's consolidated net loss narrowed to Rs 84.6 crore in Q3 Fy26 compared with net loss of Rs 197.8 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations jumped 50.2% YoY to Rs 953.6 crore in Q3 FY26. Tata Chemicals' consolidated net loss widened to Rs 93 crore compared with net loss of Rs 53 crore posted in corresponding period last year. Revenue from operations fell 1.11% YoY to Rs 3350 crore during the quarter. Bajaj Housing Finance reported a 21.33% jump in standalone net profit to Rs 664.89 crore on 17.85% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 2885.93 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. RailTel Corporation of India reported a 4.07% decline in consolidated net profit to Rs 62.40 crore despite a 19% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 913.45 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Adani Ports &amp; Special Economic Zone (APSEZ) handled total cargo of 44.8 MMT in January 2026, marking a 12% year-on-year increase. The growth was led by containers (up 16% YoY), liquids (up 21% YoY) and dry cargo (up 8% YoY). Maruti Suzuki India's production volume increased 9.33% to 226,146 units in January 2025, compared with 206,851 units produced in January 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-ather-energy-tata-chemicals-apsez-maruti-suzuki-india/stock-alert/1670488/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 08:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Studds Accessories, Hero Motocorp, TFCI</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-studds-accessories-hero-motocorp-tfci/stock-alert/1670135/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Shares of Sammaan Capital are ban from F&amp;O trading on Monday, 2 February 2026. Earnings to Watch: Earnings to Watch: Huyundai Motor India, PB Fintech, Utkarsh Small Finance Bank (SFB), Campus Activewear, Corona Remedies, Bajaj Housing Finance, Aether Energy, Aarti Industries, Akzo Nobel, Mahindra Lifespace Developers, Orectra Greentech, Railtel Corporation of India, Tata Chemicals Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Auto stocks will be in focus as companies will declare their auto sales numbers Hero Motocorp's total sales jumped 26% to 5,57,871 units in January 2026 compared with 442,873 units in January 2025. Latent View reported a 19.69% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 50.14 crore on 22.02% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 278 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Studds Accessories reported a 26.3% jump in consolidated net profit to Rs 20.7 crore on 9.4% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 163 crore in Q3 FY265 over Q3 FY25. Toursim Finance Corporation of India (TFCI) decided to invest upto 5% of corpus fund in Oxyzo Credit Funds I, a debt focused diversified sectors Category II Alternative Investment Fund registered with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-studds-accessories-hero-motocorp-tfci/stock-alert/1670135/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 08:02:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Sun Pharmaceutical Industries, Bajaj Auto, G...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-sun-pharmaceutical-industries-bajaj-auto-godfrey-phillips-india-power-grid/stock-alert/1669798/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on 1 February 2026. Key Events to Watch: Key Events to Watch: Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman is set to table and present the Union Budget in Parliament today, while January auto sales data will be keenly watched. Result Today: Result Today: Latent View Analytics will announce its quarterly earnings today. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Sun Pharmaceutical Industries has reported a 16.03% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 3,368.81 crore on a 13.49% increase in revenue to Rs 15,520.54 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Bajaj Auto's standalone net profit increased 18.68% to Rs 2,502.81 crore on an 18.84% jump in revenue from operations to Rs 15,220.33 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Godfrey Phillips India reported a steady performance in Q3 FY26, with consolidated net profit after tax rising 8.7% year-on-year to Rs 343 crore, compared with Rs 316 crore in Q3 FY25. Net revenue rose 15.1% YoY to Rs 1,829 crore, compared with Rs 1,589 crore a year ago. On a consolidated basis, Meesho's net loss widened to Rs 490.68 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with a loss of Rs 37.43 crore in Q3 FY25. Net sales rose 31.32% YoY to Rs 3,517.60 crore in Q3 FY26 from Rs 2,678.64 crore in the year-ago quarter Garware Hi-Tech Films (GHFL) reported a consolidated net profit of Rs 55.77 crore in Q3 FY26, down 8.3% year-on-year, on a 1.6% decline in revenue from operations to Rs 458.74 crore compared with Q3 FY25. NTPC reported an 8.27% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 5,597.05 crore on a 1.72% rise in net sales to Rs 45,845.68 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. Power Grid Corporation of India reported an 8.4% YoY rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 4,184.96 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 3,861.63 crore in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations rose 10.3% YoY to Rs 12,395.09 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Steel Authority of India reported a 163.6% surge in consolidated net profit to Rs 374 crore on an 11.8% rise in net sales to Rs 27,371.4 crore in Q3 FY26 over Q3 FY25. AstraZeneca Pharma India said it has received approval from the CDSCO to import, sell, and distribute Durvalumab (Imfinzi) solution for infusion in 120 mg/2.4 mL and 500 mg/10 mL strengths. Durvalumab, in combination with FLOT chemotherapy as neoadjuvant and adjuvant therapy, followed by single-agent durvalumab, is indicated for adult patients with resectable gastric or gastroesophageal junction adenocarcinoma (GC/GEJC).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-sun-pharmaceutical-industries-bajaj-auto-godfrey-phillips-india-power-grid/stock-alert/1669798/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 07:52:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>