<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>SKI Capital – Stock Alert News</title>
    <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/stock-alert</link>
    <description>Stock alert news from SKI Capital Services - Indian stock market updates</description>
    <language>en-IN</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 01:16:52 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: GAIL (India), Vikran Engg, Adani Ports, Coal...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-gail-india-vikran-engg-adani-ports-coal-india-rvnl/stock-alert/1661747/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Shares of Sammaan Capital are banned from F&amp;O trading on 24 December 2025. Stocks To Watch: Stocks To Watch: GAIL (India) has signed memorandum of understanding (MoU) with Government of Chhattisgarh for development of a greenfield gas-based fertilizer project in Chhattisgarh. Vikran Engineering received a Rs 2035 crore order from Onix Renewables for EPC works for solar plant development. Adani Ports &amp; Special Economic Zone successfully completed the acquisition of 100% interest in North Queensland Export Terminal (NQXT), Australia pursuant to completion of all condition precedents, with the acquisition of NQXT, APSEZ is on track to achieve 1 Billion tonne of cargo volume by 2030. Emcure Pharmaceuticals has received establishment inspection report (EIR). The US FDA has classified the inspection of the facility as no action indicated (NAI). Inspection was conducted from 6 October to 10 October 2025. Coal India's board approved for listing of arm Mahanadi Coalfields in the upcoming financial year. Ajanta Pharma has entered into an in-licensing agreement with Biocon for marketing Semaglutide, a GLP-1 receptor agonist. Rail Vikas Nigam (RVNL) board approved the appointment of Saleem Ahmad as chairman &amp; managing director with effect from 23 December 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-gail-india-vikran-engg-adani-ports-coal-india-rvnl/stock-alert/1661747/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 08:01:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: HCL Tech, Sanghvi Movers, Prestige Estate Pr...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-hcl-tech-sanghvi-movers-prestige-estate-projects-saatvik-green-energy/stock-alert/1661587/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Shares of Sammaan Capital are banned from F&amp;O trading on 23 December 2025. New Listing: New Listing: KSH International shares will list on the stock exchanges. The IPO was subscribed 0.83 times. The issue opened for bidding on 16 December 2025 and it closed on 18 December 2025. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 365 and 384 per share. Stocks To Watch: Stocks To Watch: HCL Technologies' software business division, HCL Software will acquire Wobby, an early'stage startup providing AI Data Analyst 'Agents' for data warehouses, based in Antwerp, Belgium, for total consideration of Euro 4.5 million Meanwhile, HCL Software will also acquire Jaspersoft, a business unit of cloud software group and provider of a leading embedded analytics and pixel-perfect reporting platform, for a total consideration of $240 million Sanghvi Movers' material subsidiary, Sangreen Future Renewables has been awarded large work orders worth Rs 428.72 crore from prominent Independent Power Producers (IPP's). Prestige Estates Projects has announced the acquisition of a 25-acre land parcel in Medavakkam, Chennai with a development potential of approximately 5 million square feet. The project is estimated to generate top-line revenue of over Rs 5,000 crore. GPT Infraprojects said that its consortium with ISCPPL has been declared L1 (First Lowest) in order valued at Rs 670 crore for construction of four lane elevated road in Jodhpur city. Saatvik Green Energy's material subsidiary, Saatvik Solar Industries has received an order aggregating to Rs 486 crore from one renowned Independent Power producers/EPC Players for supply of solar PV modules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-hcl-tech-sanghvi-movers-prestige-estate-projects-saatvik-green-energy/stock-alert/1661587/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 08:02:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Reliance Inds, Lupin, TCS, HCL Tech</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-reliance-inds-lupin-tcs-hcl-tech/stock-alert/1661236/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on 19 December 2025. IPO Listing IPO Listing ICICI Prudential Asset Management Company's ICICI Prudential Asset Management Company's shares will list on the stock exchanges today. The issue price was set at Rs 2,165 per share. The issue was subscribed 39.17 times. It opened for bidding on 12 December 2025 and it closed on 16 December 2025. The price band was Rs 2,061-2,165. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Reliance Industries announced that its arm, Reliance Consumer, has acquired a majority stake in Udhaiyam Agro Foods. Lupin announced that its subsidiaries in the Philippines (Multicare Pharmaceuticals) and Brazil (MedQu'mica) have signed an agreement with Neopharmed Gentili to market the brand Plasil in Brazil and the Philippines. Tata Consultancy Services announced that its subsidiary, TCS Iberoamerica S.A., has incorporated a technology company, Sociedad An'nima, in Costa Rica. HCL Technologies announced that it has signed a definitive agreement to acquire the telecom solutions business of Hewlett Packard Enterprise for USD 160 million. Narayana Hrudayalaya announced that its board will meet shareholders and creditors on January 19 to seek approval for the merger scheme of Meridian Medical Research into the company. Hexaware Technologies announced that its Board has approved the merger of Softcrylic Tech Solutions and Mobiquity SoftTech with the company. Mishra Dhatu Nigam announced that it has secured orders worth Rs 121.75 crore. Its open order position as of date stands at approximately Rs 2,520 crore. Aeroflex Industries announced that its board has approved a capacity addition of 13,000 units per year for liquid cooling skids used in data centres. The plan includes installing robotic and automated welding lines for flexible stainless-steel hose assemblies and setting up an annealing plant for stainless-steel braided hoses for mission-critical applications, as per management requirements. Bharti Hexacom announced the appointment of Kathikeyan Velu as Chief Financial Officer, effective January 1, 2026. Akhil Garg has resigned as CFO due to organizational movement within the Bharti Group. Rossari Biotech announced that it has incorporated wholly owned subsidiary Rossari (Singapore) on 18 December 2025. Biocon announced that its New Jersey unit has received an Establishment Inspection Report (EIR) from the US FDA with a Voluntary Action Indicated (VAI) status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-reliance-inds-lupin-tcs-hcl-tech/stock-alert/1661236/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 08:08:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: KP Energy, Jio Financial Services, IndusInd ...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-kp-energy-jio-financial-services-indusind-bank-titagarh-rail-systems-astrazeneca-pharma/stock-alert/1661057/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Bandhan Bank shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on 18 December 2025. Key Events to Watch: Key Events to Watch: Prime Minister Narendra Modi in Oman on final leg of three-nation visit, India and Oman to sign a free trade agreement in Muscat. Renewable Energy Minister Pralhad Joshi to speak at ISMA AGM. IPO Offering IPO Offering KSH International KSH International : The public issue was subscribed to 0.26 times on day 2. There were no bids by Qualified institutional investors, while non-institutional investors subscribed (0.13 times) and retail investors (0.46 times). Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: KP Energy said that it has signed a memorandum of understanding (MoU) with the Republic of Botswana to collaborate on the development of renewable energy and power infrastructure projects in the country. Jio Financial Services said that its board has approved the appointment of Venkata Peri as group chief operating officer (COO), effective December 22. IndusInd Bank informed that Shiv Bhasin has resigned from his position as chief technology officer (CTO), with effect from 16 January 2026. Titagarh Rail Systems said it has received an order worth Rs 273 crore from the Ministry of Railways for the manufacture of Rail Borne Maintenance Vehicles. AstraZeneca Pharma India said the Central Drugs Standard Control Organisation (CDSCO) has granted permission to import, sell and distribute Datopotamab Deruxtecan powder in the country. Chalet Hotels said its board has approved the allotment of 2,000 commercial paper to raise funds worth Rs 100 crore. One MobiKwik Systems said its board has approved the appointment of Navdeep Singh Suri as chairman of the company. Denta Water and Infrastructure said it has received four orders worth Rs 106 crore from Karnataka Urban Infrastructure Development &amp; Finance Corporation for urban sanitisation &amp; water management projects across Karnataka.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-kp-energy-jio-financial-services-indusind-bank-titagarh-rail-systems-astrazeneca-pharma/stock-alert/1661057/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 07:14:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: RailTel Corp, Diamond Power Infra, Lupin, Ah...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-railtel-corp-diamond-power-infra-lupin-ahluwalia-contracts/stock-alert/1660884/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Bandhan Bank shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on 17 December 2025. Key Events to Watch: Key Events to Watch: Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman to speak at India Economic Conclave in New Delhi. Prime Minister Narendra Modi's second day in Ethiopia, travels to Oman later. SEBI Chairman Tuhin Kanta Pandey to address media in Mumbai. IPO Update: IPO Update: ICICI Prudential AMC ICICI Prudential AMC : The public issue was subscribed to 39.17 times on day 3. The bids were led by Qualified institutional investors with 123.87 times the subscription, non-institutional investors who subscribed 22.04 times, retail investors with 2.53 times the subscription and Shareholders who subscribed 9.75 times. KSH International KSH International : The public issue was subscribed to 0.15 times on day 1. There were no bids were led by Qualified institutional investors, non-institutional investors who subscribed 0.06 times and retail investors who subscribed 0.27 times. IPO Listings: IPO Listings: Park Medi World Park Medi World : The public issue was subscribed to 8.52 times on day 3. The bids were led by Qualified institutional investors (12.07 times), non-institutional investors (15.93x), retail investors (3.32x). Nephrocare Health Services Nephrocare Health Services : The public issue was subscribed to 14.08 times on day 3. The bids were led by Qualified institutional investors (26.82 times), non-institutional investors (24.77 times), retail investors (2.36 times), Employees (2.81 times). Stocks To Watch: Stocks To Watch: RailTel Corporation of India said that it has received a letter of acceptance (LoA) for a Rs 26.9 crore contract to implement advanced IT infrastructure at VO Chidambaranar Port. Diamond Power Infrastructure has received a letter of intent (LoI) for a Rs 57.6 crore order from Rajesh Power for supply of cables. Lupin said its injectable manufacturing facility at Nagpur has received the Establishment Inspection Report (EIR) from the US Food and Drug Administration (US FDA) with a Voluntary Action Indicated (VAI) classification. Ahluwalia Contracts (India) said that it has received an order worth Rs 888.38 crore from Bihar State Tourism Development Corporation Ltd for civil construction works. Niraj Cement Structurals said that it has secured an order worth Rs 131 crore from the Public Works Department (PWD) for road maintenance works. Glenmark Pharmaceuticals said that its subsidiary, Glenmark Specialty S.A. (GSSA) has entered into an agreement with Hansoh Pharma to jointly develop &amp; commercialise Aumolertinib, a drug indicated for the treatment of non-small cell lung cancer (NSCLC).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-railtel-corp-diamond-power-infra-lupin-ahluwalia-contracts/stock-alert/1660884/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 07:14:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Atlantaa, Hyundai Motor, Solex Energy, Zydus...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-atlantaa-hyundai-motor-solex-energy-zydus-lifesciences-arvind-smartspaces/stock-alert/1660718/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Bandhan Bank shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on 16 December 2025. IPO Update: IPO Update: ICICI Prudential AMC ICICI Prudential AMC : The public issue was subscribed to 2.11 times on day 2. The bids were led by Qualified institutional investors (2.91 times), non-institutional investors (3.79 times), retail investors (0.83 times). IPO Opening: IPO Opening: KSH International KSH International :The company is the third-largest manufacturer and the largest exporter of magnet winding wires, has opened its initial public offering. Operating under the 'KSH' brand, the company supplies to OEMs across sectors such as power, renewables, railways, automotive, and industrials. The IPO comprises a fresh issue worth Rs 420 crore and an offer for sale of Rs 290 crore. The price band has been fixed at Rs 365 to Rs 384 per share. Ahead of the issue, the company raised Rs 213 crore from anchor investors. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Atlantaa said that it has entered into a development agreement with Highway Milton Co-operative Housing Society for the redevelopment of a residential project in Borivali, Mumbai. The project is estimated to have a gross development value (GDV) of around Rs 500 crore. Hyundai Motor said its shareholders have approved the appointment of Tarun Garg as managing director (MD) and chief executive officer (CEO), effective 1 January 2026. Solex Energy said that it has partnered with Malaysia-based TT Vision to boost solar manufacturing and engineering capabilities in India. Zydus Lifesciences said the USFDA has accepted the resubmission of the new drug application for CUTX-101. The drug, a copper histidinate, is indicated for the treatment of Menkes disease in pediatric patients. Arvind SmartSpaces said that it has acquired a new residential high-rise project in Bengaluru, with an estimated revenue potential of nearly Rs 550 crore.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-atlantaa-hyundai-motor-solex-energy-zydus-lifesciences-arvind-smartspaces/stock-alert/1660718/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 07:29:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Market snaps 2-days gaining streak; Nifty settles below 2...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/market-snaps-2-days-gaining-streak-nifty-settles-below-26050-mark/stock-alert/1660676/30</link>
      <description>Domestic equity benchmarks closed slightly lower, snapping a two-day winning streak, as sentiment stayed cautious amid persistent foreign fund outflows, uncertainty surrounding a potential U.S.'India trade deal and a sharp fall in the rupee to a record low. The Nifty ended below the 26,050 mark. The Indian rupee weakened further on Monday, sliding to a record low of 90.80 against the U.S. dollar. Auto, pharma and healthcare shares declined, while media, FMCG and counsumer durables shares advanced. As per provisional closing data, the barometer index, the S&amp;P BSE Sensex shed 54.30 points or 0.06% to 85,213.36. The Nifty 50 index lost 19.65 points or 0.08% to 26,027.30. In the past two consecutive trading sessions, the Sensex rose 1.03% while the Nifty added 1.12%. The broader market outperformed the frontline indices. the S&amp;P BSE Mid-Cap index rose 0.16% and the S&amp;P BSE Small-Cap index gained 0.41%. The market breadth was positive. On the BSE, 2,238 shares rose and 2,027 shares fell. A total of 179 shares were unchanged. The NSE's India VIX, a gauge of the market's expectation of volatility over the near term, added 1.40% to 10.25. Economy: Economy: India's foreign exchange reserves increased by $1.03 billion to $687.26 billion for the week ending on 12 December 2025, the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) said on Friday. Foreign currency assets, a major component of the reserves, decreased by $151 million to $556.88 billion, the data released showed. Value of the gold reserves increased by $1.188 billion to $106.984 billion during the week, the RBI said. The Special Drawing Rights (SDRs) were up by $93 million to $18.721 billion, the apex bank said. India's reserve position with the IMF was down by $97 million to $4.675 billion in the reporting week, according to the apex bank's data. Meanwhile, India's wholesale inflation remained in deflationary territory in November, with WPI falling 0.32% year-on-year, easing from a 1.21% drop in October. Food prices continued to weigh on the index, though the pace of decline moderated, with wholesale food inflation at -2.6% compared with -5.04% previously. Vegetable prices fell 20.23% after a much steeper 34.97% drop in October, signalling some stabilization. Manufactured product prices rose 1.33% year-on-year, while fuel and power prices declined 2.27%, keeping overall inflation pressures subdued. IPO Update: IPO Update: ICICI Prudential Asset Management Company ICICI Prudential Asset Management Company received bids for 5,82,17,286 shares as against 3,50,15,691 shares on offer, according to stock exchange data at 15:15 IST on Monday (15 December 2025). The issue was subscribed 1.66 times. The issue opened for bidding on 12 December 2025 and it will close on 16 December 2025. The price band of the IPO is fixed between Rs 2,061 and 2,165 per share. New Listings: New Listings: Shares of Corona Remedies Corona Remedies were at Rs 1437.20 on the BSE, representing a premium of 35.33% as compared with the issue price of Rs 1,062. The stock was listed at Rs 1,452, exhibiting a premium of 36.72% to the issue price. The stock has hit a high of 1499 and a low of 1412.65. On the BSE, over 238.28 lakh shares of the company were traded in the counter. Wakefit Innovations Wakefit Innovations were at Rs 192.30 on the BSE, representing a discount of 1.38% as compared with the issue price of Rs 195. The stock debuted at Rs 194.10 on the BSE, marking a marginal discount of 0.46% over the issue price. The stock has hit a high of 203.70 and a low of 177.25. Buzzing Index: Buzzing Index: The Nifty Auto index fell 0.95% to 27,557.90. The index rallied 1.69% in the past two consecutive trading sessions. Mahindra &amp; Mahindra (down 1.89%), Eicher Motors (down 1.52%), Bharat Forge (down 1.12%), Sona BLW Precision Forgings (down 1.12%), Samvardhana Motherson International (down 0.99%), Bajaj Auto (down 0.96%), Bosch (down 0.94%), Uno Minda (down 0.82%), Maruti Suzuki India (down 0.76%) and TVS Motor Company (down 0.41%) declined. Stocks in Spotlight: Stocks in Spotlight: Jayant Infratech hit an upper limit of 5% after securing a domestic contract worth approximately Rs 40.55 crore from Central Railway. The order involves the supply, erection, testing, and commissioning of conversion of existing unregulated 25 KV AC Overhead Equipment (OHE) to regulated OHE in the Kalyan'Karjat section (109 TKM) of Mumbai division. Wheels India jumped 5.58% after the company has signed a technical assistance agreement with Tokyo, Japan headquartered Topy Industries for the design, development and manufacture of aluminium alloy wheels. Matrimony.com declined 5.03%. The company said its board has approved a share buyback of up to Rs 58.5 crore through the tender offer route. The company plans to buy back 8,93,129 fully paid-up equity shares at a price of Rs 655 per share. As of 12 December 2025, promoters held a 54.61% stake in Matrimony.com, while public shareholders owned the remaining 45.39%. SEPC zoomed 12.09% after it has secured a domestic contract worth Rs 3,300 crore from South Eastern Coalfields (SECL) through the JARPL-AT Consortium, comprising Jai Ambey Roadlines (80%) &amp; Avinash Transport (20%). Ashoka Buildcon advanced 2.39% after it has received an EPC order from Brihanmumbai Municipal Corporation to construct a flyover connecting J.J. Bridge &amp; Sitaram Selam Bridge at J.J. Road'Saboo Siddik Polytechnic Road Junction in 'E' Ward. KEC International added 1.51% after the company announced that it has secured new orders worth Rs 1,150 crore across its transmission and distribution (T&amp;D) and civil businesses in India. SBC Exports added 1.15%. The company announced that it has secured an order worth Rs 10.76 crore from the Indian Institute of Technology (IIT) Jodhpur for the supply of manpower. Crest Ventures shed 0.83%. The company said that its wholly owned subsidiary Crest Urban Living has entered into joint development agreement with Vensco Projects LLP for development of a premium mixed-use project in Chembur. Excelsoft Technologies rose 0.81%. The company reported 19% rise in consolidated net profit to Rs 10.61 crore on a 20% increase in total income to Rs 68.63 crore in Q2 FY26 as compared with Q2 FY25. Mini Diamonds (India) declined 1.27%. The company has announced that it has received an order to supply lab-grown polished diamonds worth Rs 12 crore from SAHARSH EXPORTS. Oriental Rail Infrastructure added 0.53%. The company announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, Oriental Foundry, has secured an order worth Rs 1.10 crore from North Western Railway. Inox Wind (IWL) gained 1.04%. The company announced that it has secured a 102.3 MW order from ABREL EPC, a subsidiary of Aditya Birla Renewables, for the supply of its 3.3 MW wind turbine generators. Vascon Engineers rallied 3.42% after the company received an order from Navi Mumbai Municipal Corporation for the construction of a super speciatly hospital in CBD Belapur, Navi Mumbai. The said order is valued at Rs 260.09 crore and it is expected to be completed within 36 months. United Drilling Tools slipped 1.72%. The company announced that it has received an export order worth Rs 3.26 crore from Nigeria-based Weafri Well Services Company. WPIL surged 7.55% after the company's South African subsidiary, PCI Africa Consortium, has been awarded a contract for the upgradation and expansion of the Macassar Wastewater Treatment Works for the City of Cape Town. The said contract is valued at 2.50 billion Rand (Rs 1,340 crore). Elitecon International hit an upper limit of 5% after the company announced that it has secured a long term international supply contract valued at around Rs 875 crore. Global Markets: Global Markets: European markets advanced as investors turned their attention to the European Central Bank's final policy meeting of the year, scheduled for Thursday. Sentiment was also shaped by anticipation of a heavy slate of U.S. economic data due this week, including November nonfarm payrolls and October retail sales figures, both set to be released on Tuesday after delays caused by the U.S. government shutdown earlier in the fall. In addition, markets are awaiting the November consumer price index data, due on Thursday. Most Asian markets fell on Monday, pressured by steep losses in technology shares as weak guidance from U.S. firms left investors worried about stretched, artificial intelligence-driven valuations. Japan has announced its fourth-quarter Tankan numbers. The index for business optimism among large Japanese manufacturers increased to +15 for the fourth quarter, hitting the highest level in four years. The latest reading compared to the +14 increase in the previous quarter. The non-manufacturing index for the fourth quarter came in at +34. Meanwhile, retail sales in China rose 1.3% last month from a year earlier, slowing from the 2.9% rise in the prior month. Industrial production climbed 4.8% in November from a year ago, down from 4.9% in the prior month. On Friday in the U.S., the S&amp;P 500 fell 1.07%, retreating from a record, and the Nasdaq Composite declined 1.69%. The Dow Jones Industrial Average finished down 0.51% after scoring a new intraday all-time high earlier in the session. AI-related stocks faced pressure during the session, with stocks of Broadcom plunging more than 11%, and dragging the broad market index and tech-heavy Nasdaq. AMD, Palantir Technologies and Micron also declined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/market-snaps-2-days-gaining-streak-nifty-settles-below-26050-mark/stock-alert/1660676/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:54:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: GPT Infra, Oriental Rail Infra, Biocon, KEC ...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-gpt-infra-oriental-rail-infra-biocon-kec-international-united-drilling-tools/stock-alert/1660540/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Bandhan Bank shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on 15 December 2025. Key Events to Watch: Key Events to Watch: Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi will begin his two-day visit to Jordan, meet King Abdullah II bin Al Hussein. Government to release wholesale price inflation and trade data for November. IPO Update: IPO Update: Park Medi World Park Medi World : The public issue was subscribed 8.10 times on the final day of bidding, driven by strong demand from institutional investors. The QIB portion was subscribed 11.48 times, while the NII segment saw 15.15 times subscription. The retail category was subscribed 3.16 times. Nephrocare Health Services Nephrocare Health Services : The IPO garnered robust response, with the issue subscribed 13.96 times on Day 3. Bids were led by QIBs at 27.47 times, followed by NIIs at 24.27 times. The retail portion was subscribed 2.31 times. ICICI Prudential AMC ICICI Prudential AMC : The public issue was subscribed 72% on Day 1 of bidding. The QIB segment was subscribed 1.97 times, while the NII and retail portions were subscribed 37% and 21%, respectively. IPO Listings: IPO Listings: Corona Remedies Corona Remedies : The pharmaceutical company, with a presence in women's healthcare and cardiology, makes its market debut today. The IPO was priced at Rs 1,062 per share and witnessed an overwhelming response, with the issue subscribed 137 times. Wakefit Innovations Wakefit Innovations : The Indian direct-to-consumer home and sleep solutions company is also set to list today. The IPO was offered at Rs 195 per share and was subscribed 2.5 times. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: GPT Infraprojects announced that it has received a contract worth Rs 53.6 crore from PCMM, South Eastern Railway for the supply of concrete sleepers from its factory in Panagarh, West Bengal. Oriental Rail Infrastructure announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, Oriental Foundry, has secured an order worth Rs 1.10 crore from North Western Railway. Biocon announced that its subsidiary, Biocon Biologics, has entered into a new settlement and license agreement with Regeneron and Bayer for its biosimilar Aflibercept (40mg/ml), Yesafili, covering Europe and the rest of the world. KEC International announced that it has secured new orders worth Rs 1,150 crore across its transmission and distribution (T&amp;D) and civil businesses in India. United Drilling Tools announced that it has received an export order worth Rs 3 crore from Nigeria-based Weafri Well Services Company.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-gpt-infra-oriental-rail-infra-biocon-kec-international-united-drilling-tools/stock-alert/1660540/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 07:19:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Tata Power Co, Astra Microwave, Honasa Consu...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-tata-power-co-astra-microwave-honasa-consumer-vedanta/stock-alert/1660326/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Sammaan Capital and Bandhan Bank shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on 12 December 2025. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Tata Power Company announced that it has received an annual order worth Rs 155.78 crore per year for 35 years to commission a 400 kV transmission line, after securing a Letter of Intent (LoI) from REC's subsidiary for the Jejuri-Hinjewadi transmission project. Astra Microwave Products announced that it has received an order worth Rs 171.38 crore from the IMD for the procurement of six Polarimetric Doppler Weather Radars. Honasa Consumer announced that it will acquire a 95% stake in BTM Ventures for an enterprise value of Rs 195 crore, and plans to acquire the remaining 5% within 12 months of completing the initial acquisition. With this transaction, the company enters the men's personal care category through the acquisition of Reginald Men. Vedanta announced that it has emerged as the successful bidder for the Genjana block, which contains nickel, chromium, and PGE (Platinum Group Elements). NBCC (India) announced that it has received orders worth Rs 289.39 crore, including one from SAIL Bokaro for desilting of the cooling pond and another for civil, construction, and repair works at NALCO's office and township. Interarch Building Solutions announced that it has received a Letter of Intent worth Rs 70 crore for the design of a pre-engineered steel building system. Hitachi Energy India announced that it has received a tax demand of Rs 9.92 crore, including penalty, from the Lucknow tax authority. Tembo Global announced that it is in discussions with a large corporate group for potential projects worth Rs 700 crore, related to ports, data-centre development, and fuel-farm systems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-tata-power-co-astra-microwave-honasa-consumer-vedanta/stock-alert/1660326/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 07:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Mazagon Dock, Tata Steel, LIC, Petronet LNG</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-mazagon-dock-tata-steel-lic-petronet-lng/stock-alert/1660138/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Sammaan Capital and Bandhan Bank shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on 11 December 2025. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Mazagon Dock Shipbuilders stated that it has entered into an agreement with the Indian Navy and Brazilian Navy in association for information on maintenance of Scorp'ne-class submarines. Tata Steel announced that its board has approved the acquisition of a 50% stake in Thriveni Pellets for Rs 636 crore to secure a pellet-making facility for the supply of iron-ore pellets in India. Meanwhile Tata Steel and Lloyds Metals and Energy have entered into a non-binding Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) to examine potential areas of cooperation, including raw-material mining, logistics, pellet production, and steel making. Life Insurance Corporation (LIC) informed that it has received a GST demand order of Rs 2,370.34 crore from the Mumbai tax authorities. Petronet LNG announced that it has signed an agreement to borrow a secured rupee term loan of Rs 12,000 crore from a consortium led by SBI and Bank of Baroda. Ashoka Buildcon announced that its joint venture has received a Letter of Acceptance worth Rs 1,816 crore from the BMC for the Mithi River Development and Pollution Control Project. Lloyds Metals &amp; Energy announced that its subsidiary will acquire a 50% stake in Nexus Holdco FZCO for USD 55 million.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-mazagon-dock-tata-steel-lic-petronet-lng/stock-alert/1660138/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 07:58:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>