<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>SKI Capital – Stock Alert News</title>
    <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/stock-alert</link>
    <description>Stock alert news from SKI Capital Services - Indian stock market updates</description>
    <language>en-IN</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 04:00:42 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: IndusInd Bank, Axis Bank, Kotak Mahindra Ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-indusind-bank-axis-bank-kotak-mahindra-bank-tata-motors-pv/stock-alert/1663264/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Steel Authority of India (SAIL) and Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on 6 January 2026. Stocks in Spotlight: Stocks in Spotlight: IndusInd Bank's deposits fell 3.8% YoY to Rs 3,94,022 crore as of 31st December 2025. On a sequential basis however, deposits rose 1.1% from Rs 3,89,600 crore as of 30 September 2025. Net advances tumbled 13.1% YoY to Rs 3,66,889 crore as of 31st December 2025. Axis Bank's total deposits jumped 15% to Rs 12,60,800 crore as on 31st December 2025 compared with Rs 10,95,900 crore as on 31st December 2024. Tata Motors Passenger Vehicle's wholly owned subsidiary Jaguar land rover (JLR) wholesale volumes for the third quarter were 59,200 units (excluding the Chery Jaguar Land Rover China JV ('CJLR') ), down 43.3% YoY and down 10 .6% QoQ. Retail sales for the third quarter of 79,600 units (including CJLR ) were down 25.1 % YoY and down 6.7% QoQ. Production returned to normal levels only by mid -November post the cyber incident. Utkarsh Small Finance Bank (SFB) total deposits jumped 4.5% to Rs 21,087 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 20,172 crore in Q3 FY25. Gross loan portfolio fell 3.9% YoY to Rs 18,306 crore in Q3 FY26. Dabur India said that it expects consolidated revenue to grow in the mid-single digits with operating profit and Profit after Tax to grow ahead of revenuein Q3 FY26. During the quarter, early signs of demand recovery were witnessed, aided by GST rate revisions. Post trade stabilisation, consumer sentiment improved in urban and rural areas. Rural demand continued to outperform urban demand this quarter as well. Kotak Mahindra Bank's average total deposits climbed 14.7% to Rs 5,26,025 crore as of 31st December 2025 compared with Rs 5,10,138 crore as of 31st December 2024. Average advances jumped 16.2% YoY to Rs 465,879 crore as of 31st December 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-indusind-bank-axis-bank-kotak-mahindra-bank-tata-motors-pv/stock-alert/1663264/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 07:57:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Dmart, Mahindra &amp; Mahindra, Jammu &amp; Kashmir ...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-dmart-mahindra-and-mahindra-jammu-and-kashmir-bank-pnb-v2-retail/stock-alert/1663097/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Shares of Steel Authority of India (SAIL) are banned from F&amp;O trading on 5 January 2026. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Oil companies will be in focus following US attacks on Venezuela, as potential volatility in crude oil prices could impact the sector. Avenue Supermarts (Dmart)'s standalone revenue from operations jumped 13% to Rs 17,612.62 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 15,565.23 crore in Q3 FY25. Jammu &amp; Kashmir Bank's gross advances jumped 17.26% to Rs 1,16,247.92 crore as of 31 December 2025, compared with Rs 99,133.35 crore as of 31 December 2024. Punjab National Bank (PNB) domestic deposits increased 8.32% to Rs 15,97,487 crore as of 31 December 2025 compared with Rs 14,74,760 crore posted on 31 December 2024. Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Financial Services has reported overall disbursements of around Rs 17,600 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a 7% year-on-year growth. Union Bank of India has reported a 7.42% rise in domestic advances to Rs 9,80,643 crore as of 31 December 2025, as against Rs 9,42,273 crore posted as of 31 December 2025. Corona Remedies reported a 21.75% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 52.32 crore on 15.05% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 361.13 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. V2 Retail reported strong operational momentum in the December quarter, driven by aggressive network expansion and its continued transition from a regional player to a national retail footprint. Standalone revenue rose 57% year-on-year to Rs 927 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 591 crore in the year-ago period, Bank of India reported a 12.50% YoY increase in global business to Rs 16,27,098 crore as of 31 December 2025. Global deposits stood at Rs 8,87,287 crore, reflecting an 11.64% YoY increase. Domestic deposits rose 12.80% YoY to Rs 7,65,500 crore as of 31 December 2025 from Rs 6,78,626 crore a year earlier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-dmart-mahindra-and-mahindra-jammu-and-kashmir-bank-pnb-v2-retail/stock-alert/1663097/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 07:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: RailTel Corporation of India, Aurobindo Phar...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-railtel-corporation-of-india-aurobindo-pharma-olectra-greentech/stock-alert/1662872/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: SAIL shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on Tuesday, 30 December 2025. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: RailTel Corporation of India has received a Letter of Acceptance (LoA) from the Assam Health Infrastructure Development &amp; Management Society (AHIDMS) for procurement, implementation, and maintenance of a Hospital Management Information System (HMIS). The estimated order value is Rs 56.71 crore. Aurobindo Pharma announced that its subsidiary, Auro Pharma, has approved the acquisition of the non-oncology prescription formulations business of Khandelwal Laboratories on a going-concern basis through a Business Transfer Agreement for Rs 325 crore. Time Technoplast has received approvals from the Petroleum and Explosives Safety Organisation (PESO) and T'V Rheinland (India) for the manufacture and supply of high-pressure Type-3 fully wrapped fiber-reinforced composite cylinders of 2-liter capacity for compressed gas applications. Olectra Greentech declared the commercial operation date (COD) for its greenfield electric vehicle (EV) manufacturing facility in Hyderabad. The Phase-I per-shift annual production capacity stands at 2,500 electric buses, representing 50% of the planned per-shift capacity of 5,000 buses. Prataap Snacks said manufacturing operations at its Bengaluru unit ceased from 1 January 2026 as part of strategic consolidation. Production has been shifted to another facility in the region, ensuring continuity of supply. The company expects no adverse impact on its overall production capacity. Indegene announced the merger of its step-down arms'Indegene Aptilon Services and Trilogy Writing &amp; Consulting'to form Indegene Healthcare Canada Inc.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-railtel-corporation-of-india-aurobindo-pharma-olectra-greentech/stock-alert/1662872/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 07:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Canara Bank, NBCC (India), Titagarh Rail Sys...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-canara-bank-nbcc-india-titagarh-rail-systems-dr-reddys-laboratories-time-technoplast/stock-alert/1662723/30</link>
      <description>Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Canara Bank said Hardeep Singh Ahluwalia has been entrusted with the additional charge of managing director (MD) and chief executive officer (CEO), effective 1 January 2026, for a period of three months. NBCC (India) said it has secured multiple construction orders aggregating Rs 383 crore from Canara Bank and Navodaya Vidyalaya Samiti. Titagarh Rail Systems said its board has approved a business transfer agreement to transfer its Shipbuilding, Marine and Systems (SMS) business to its arm, Titagarh Naval Systems, in a transaction valued at Rs 114.9 crore, which will be executed in accordance with the terms of the pact. Dr Reddy's Laboratories said its Switzerland-based arm has received a complete response letter (CRL) from the US Food and Drug Administration for the biologics license application of its proposed biosimilar AVT03. Time Technoplast said it has received an order worth Rs 51 crore from Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd (HPCL) for the supply of goods. Hyundai Motor India said Unsoo Kim has resigned as managing director (MD) and director of the company, while shareholders have approved the appointment of Tarun Garg as the new managing director (MD) and chief executive officer (CEO), effective from 1 January 2026. Utkarsh Small Finance Bank said Pramod Kumar Dubey has resigned from his position as whole-time director (WTD) to pursue other career opportunities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-canara-bank-nbcc-india-titagarh-rail-systems-dr-reddys-laboratories-time-technoplast/stock-alert/1662723/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 07:16:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Bharat Forge, Power Grid, Titan Company, RITES</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-bharat-forge-power-grid-titan-company-rites/stock-alert/1662479/30</link>
      <description>Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Bharat Forge has received a contract worth Rs 1,661.9 crore from the Ministry of Defence for the supply of 255,128 CQB carbines (5.56 x 45 mm) to the Indian Army. The contract stipulates order execution within five years. Power Grid Corporation of India has been declared the successful bidder for the selection of battery energy storage developers for setting up a cumulative capacity of 2,000 MWh (1,000 MW x 2 hours) of standalone battery energy storage systems in Andhra Pradesh. The project comprises a 150 MW/300 MWh battery energy storage system at the 400/220 kV substation at Kalikiri in Chittoor district, Andhra Pradesh. RITES has received a Letter of Award for the supply of in-service Cape gauge diesel-electric locomotives from Berhard Development Corporation, Zimbabwe. The order is valued at $3.6 million. Dynacons Systems &amp; Solutions said that it has received orders worth Rs 249 crore from RBI for the implementation &amp; maintenance of enterprise applications platform software. Titan Company said that its board has approved the appointment of Sandhya Venugopal Sharma, IAS, as chairperson and additional director of the company, effective January 4, 2026. Arfin India announced that it has received an order worth Rs 321 crore from Diamond Power Infra for the supply of Aluminium sector conductors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-bharat-forge-power-grid-titan-company-rites/stock-alert/1662479/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:57:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Lupin, RVNL, BEL, Waaree Energies, GNFC, NTP...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-lupin-rvnl-bel-waaree-energies-gnfc-ntpc-green-energy/stock-alert/1662314/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on Tuesday, 30 December 2025. New Listing New Listing Gujarat Kidney &amp; Super Speciality is slated to make its market debut on the mainboard today. The IPO was subscribed 5.21 times. The issue opened for bidding on 22 December 2025 and it closed on 24 December 2025. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 108 and 114 per share. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Lupin said that it has entered into an exclusive License, Supply, and Distribution Agreement with China-based Gan &amp; Lee Pharmaceuticals for a novel fortnightly GLP-1 receptor agonist, Bofanglutide. Bofanglutide injection is indicated for the treatment of type 2 diabetes and for weight management in overweight or obese individuals. Rail Vikas Nigam (RVNL) said that it has emerged as the lowest bidder for an order worth Rs 201.23 crore from East Coast Railway. The project involves setting up a wagon Periodic Overhaul (POH) workshop with a capacity of 200 wagons at Kantabanji. Bharat Electronics (BEL) said that it has received additional orders worth Rs 569 crore since December 12. These orders include radars, tank overhauls, communication equipment, fire control systems, simulators, antenna stabilisation systems, security software, components, upgrades, and spares. Waaree Energies said that Amit Paithankar has resigned as whole-time director and chief executive officer of the company to pursue opportunities outside the organisation, effective May 15, 2026. The company further said that the Board has approved the appointment of Jignesh Rathod, currently Director'Operations, as chief executive officer-designate with immediate effect. The Board has also appointed Jignesh Rathod as chief executive officer and Key Managerial Personnel, effective May 16, 2026. Gujarat Narmada Valley Fertilizers &amp; Chemicals (GNFC) said that T Natarajan has resigned as managing director with effect from December 29 following an order from the Government of Gujarat. The Government of Gujarat has nominated Rajkumar Beniwal, IAS, as managing director with effect from December 29. NTPC Green Energy announced the commencement of commercial operations of the ninth part capacity of 13.98 MW of the 1,255 MW Khavda-I Solar PV project of NTPC Renewable Energy. With this addition, the current commercial capacity of NTPC Green Energy stands at 7,996.30 MW, while the total installed capacity of the NGEL Group has increased to 8,010.28 MW.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-lupin-rvnl-bel-waaree-energies-gnfc-ntpc-green-energy/stock-alert/1662314/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 07:58:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Coforge, Vedanta, Suzlon Energy, Solarworld ...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-coforge-vedanta-suzlon-energy-solarworld-energy-solutions/stock-alert/1662162/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on Monday, 29 December 2025. Key Events to Watch Key Events to Watch The government is slated to release the Index of Industrial Production (IIP) data for November, which will offer cues on industrial activity. The Supreme Court of India is scheduled to hear a matter related to the definition of the Aravalli Hills. S. Krishnan, Secretary, Ministry of Electronics &amp; IT, will brief the media on the upcoming India AI Impact Summit 2026. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Coforge announced that it has signed a definitive agreement to acquire a 100% stake in Encora from Advent International, Warburg Pincus, and other minority shareholders for Rs 17,032.6 crore. The enterprise value of the transaction stands at $2.35 billion. The board approved raising up to $550 million through a qualified institutional placement (QIP) to repay Encora's term loan. Vedanta said that it has been declared the successful bidder for the Depo Graphite'Vanadium block under the critical mineral auctions. The company said the development will strengthen its critical minerals portfolio. Suzlon Energy announced that Vivek Srivastava has resigned as Chief Executive Officer (CEO) of the WTG Division, effective December 26. Diamond Power Infrastructure said that it has received a letter of intent from Hild Projects, an EPC contractor, for the supply of power cables worth Rs 66.18 crore. Avantel informed that it has received a contract worth Rs 4.16 crore from the Ministry of Defence, Headquarters Naval Aviation, for CAMC of Satcom equipment. Solarworld Energy Solutions said that it has received a letter of award from NTPC Renewable Energy for an EPC package for the development of a 250 MWac grid-connected solar PV project valued at Rs 725.33 crore. Vikran Engineering announced that it has accepted letters of award from MP Urja Vikas Nigam for the implementation of grid-connected solar PV-based power plants with an aggregate capacity of 45.75 MW AC in Vidisha, Madhya Pradesh.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-coforge-vedanta-suzlon-energy-solarworld-energy-solutions/stock-alert/1662162/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:54:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: NBCC (India), Ola Electric, Lenskart Solutio...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-nbcc-india-ola-electric-lenskart-solutions-gujarat-gas/stock-alert/1661934/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Shares of Sammaan Capital banned from F&amp;O trading on 26 December 2025. Stocks To Watch: Stocks To Watch: NBCC (India) has signed memorandum of understanding (MoU) with Board of Mumbai Port Authority for the development of CGO Complex on 25 acres at Mumbai Port's land, as deposit work on turnkey basis. Ola Electric Mobility received a sanction order from the Ministry of Heavy Industries, Government of India, for the release of incentives amounting to Rs 366.78 crore under the Production Linked Incentive Scheme for Automobile and Auto Components (PLI-Auto Scheme) for claims pertaining to FY 2024-25. Lenskart Solutions' Singapore arm approved an investment of KRW 3 billon (approximately Rs 18.6 crore ) for the acquisition of 29.24% of the share capital of iiNeer Corp. Gujarat Gas' Milind Torawane, IAS has resigned as managing director with effect from 24 th December 2025, following his transfer and appoint as Principal Secretary to Government, Education Department (Primary &amp; Secondary Education). It has appointed Avantika Singh Aulakh, IAS as managing director. Strides Pharma Sciences' wholly owned subsidiary, Strides Pharma Inc. USA has received a Form 483 with four observations from US Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) following an inspection of its formulations facility at Chestnut Ridge, New York.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-nbcc-india-ola-electric-lenskart-solutions-gujarat-gas/stock-alert/1661934/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: GAIL (India), Vikran Engg, Adani Ports, Coal...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-gail-india-vikran-engg-adani-ports-coal-india-rvnl/stock-alert/1661747/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Shares of Sammaan Capital are banned from F&amp;O trading on 24 December 2025. Stocks To Watch: Stocks To Watch: GAIL (India) has signed memorandum of understanding (MoU) with Government of Chhattisgarh for development of a greenfield gas-based fertilizer project in Chhattisgarh. Vikran Engineering received a Rs 2035 crore order from Onix Renewables for EPC works for solar plant development. Adani Ports &amp; Special Economic Zone successfully completed the acquisition of 100% interest in North Queensland Export Terminal (NQXT), Australia pursuant to completion of all condition precedents, with the acquisition of NQXT, APSEZ is on track to achieve 1 Billion tonne of cargo volume by 2030. Emcure Pharmaceuticals has received establishment inspection report (EIR). The US FDA has classified the inspection of the facility as no action indicated (NAI). Inspection was conducted from 6 October to 10 October 2025. Coal India's board approved for listing of arm Mahanadi Coalfields in the upcoming financial year. Ajanta Pharma has entered into an in-licensing agreement with Biocon for marketing Semaglutide, a GLP-1 receptor agonist. Rail Vikas Nigam (RVNL) board approved the appointment of Saleem Ahmad as chairman &amp; managing director with effect from 23 December 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-gail-india-vikran-engg-adani-ports-coal-india-rvnl/stock-alert/1661747/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 08:01:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: HCL Tech, Sanghvi Movers, Prestige Estate Pr...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-hcl-tech-sanghvi-movers-prestige-estate-projects-saatvik-green-energy/stock-alert/1661587/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Shares of Sammaan Capital are banned from F&amp;O trading on 23 December 2025. New Listing: New Listing: KSH International shares will list on the stock exchanges. The IPO was subscribed 0.83 times. The issue opened for bidding on 16 December 2025 and it closed on 18 December 2025. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 365 and 384 per share. Stocks To Watch: Stocks To Watch: HCL Technologies' software business division, HCL Software will acquire Wobby, an early'stage startup providing AI Data Analyst 'Agents' for data warehouses, based in Antwerp, Belgium, for total consideration of Euro 4.5 million Meanwhile, HCL Software will also acquire Jaspersoft, a business unit of cloud software group and provider of a leading embedded analytics and pixel-perfect reporting platform, for a total consideration of $240 million Sanghvi Movers' material subsidiary, Sangreen Future Renewables has been awarded large work orders worth Rs 428.72 crore from prominent Independent Power Producers (IPP's). Prestige Estates Projects has announced the acquisition of a 25-acre land parcel in Medavakkam, Chennai with a development potential of approximately 5 million square feet. The project is estimated to generate top-line revenue of over Rs 5,000 crore. GPT Infraprojects said that its consortium with ISCPPL has been declared L1 (First Lowest) in order valued at Rs 670 crore for construction of four lane elevated road in Jodhpur city. Saatvik Green Energy's material subsidiary, Saatvik Solar Industries has received an order aggregating to Rs 486 crore from one renowned Independent Power producers/EPC Players for supply of solar PV modules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-hcl-tech-sanghvi-movers-prestige-estate-projects-saatvik-green-energy/stock-alert/1661587/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 08:02:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>