<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>SKI Capital – Stock Alert News</title>
    <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/stock-alert</link>
    <description>Stock alert news from SKI Capital Services - Indian stock market updates</description>
    <language>en-IN</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 01:22:22 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Powergrid, RVNL, Sagar Cements. Astra Micorw...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-powergrid-rvnl-sagar-cements-astra-micorwave-bharat-forge/stock-alert/1663894/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Shares of Steel Authority of India (SAIL) and Sammaan Capital are banned from F&amp;O trading on 9 January 2026. Initial Public Offer (IPO): Initial Public Offer (IPO): Bharat Coking Coal India IPO opens for subscription on 9 January 2026 to 13 January 2026. The IPO price band has been set between Rs 21 to Rs 23 per share with a lot size of 600 shares. Result Today: Result Today: Globus Spirits, Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency (IREDA) and Tejas Networks will declare their quarterly results later today. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Indian energy Exchange (IEX) will be in focus today as the Electricity Appellate Tribunal (APTEL) is scheduled to hear the market coupling case on Friday, January 9 at 10:30 AM. Power Grid Corporation of India has been declared as successful bidder under Tariff Based Competitive Bidding to establish 3GW transmission project situated in Davanagere, Karnataka. Rail Vikas Nigam (RVNL) has received a letter of award(LoA) from East Coast Railway for setting up of wagon POH workshop of 200 Nos. capacity at Kantabanji. Sagar Cements' board approved the offer for sale of up to 75,00,000 equity shares of face value of Rs 10 each equivalent to 8.14% of the total issued equity share capital of its subsidiary, Andhra Cements, through the stock exchange mechanism and in accordance with the OFS Guidelines. Astra Microwave Products' joint venture, Astra Rafael Comsys has received Rs 275.27 crore order from Indian Air Force for integration of software defined radio (SDR) and installation of network centric application (NCO) on MiG-29 aircraft. Bharat Forge has signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with Agile Robots S.E. to jointly explore the space of AI driven robotics and intelligent industrial automatiom. Venus Remedies has obtained marketing authorisation in Indonesia for its antibiotic combination Ceftazidime and Avibactam.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-powergrid-rvnl-sagar-cements-astra-micorwave-bharat-forge/stock-alert/1663894/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 07:48:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Gland Pharma, Angel One, Tata Steel, Meesho,...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-gland-pharma-angel-one-tata-steel-meesho-swaraj-engines/stock-alert/1663693/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Shares of Steel Authority of India(SAIL) and Sammaan Capital are banned from F&amp;O trading on 8 January 2026. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Gland Pharma has received an approval from the United States Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) for its abbreviated new drug application (ANDA) filed for Olopatadine Hydrochloride Ophthalmic Solution. The said drug is indicated for the treatment of ocular itching associated with allergic conjunctivitis. Angel One is scheduled to meet on Thursday, 15 January, 2026 to consider sub-division/split of existing equity shares having face value of Rs 10 each, fully paid up. Tata Steel's India crude steel production stood at 6.34 million tons in Q3 FY26, up 12% QoQ and YoY, primarily aided by higher output at Jamshedpur and Kalinganagar facilities. Meesho's general manager- business, Megha Agarwal has tendered her resignation with effect from 7 January 2026. Following her exit, Milan Partani, General Manager - User Growth and Content Commerce will now assume the role of General Manager ' Commerce Platform. Swaraj Engines received a warning letter from BSE and National Stock Exchange of India (NSE) for non-compliance with Regulation 21 (3A) of SEBI Listing Regulations, wherein only one meeting of the Risk Management Committee was held during the financial year 2024-25. Housing &amp; Urban Development Corporation (HUDCO) has signed a non-binding MoU with the Chhattisgarh government to provide financial assistance of up to Rs 1 lakh crore over five years for housing and infrastructure projects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-gland-pharma-angel-one-tata-steel-meesho-swaraj-engines/stock-alert/1663693/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 07:53:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Biocon, Senco Gold, Jubilant Foodworks, Tita...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-biocon-senco-gold-jubilant-foodworks-titan-company/stock-alert/1663469/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Shares of Steel Authority of India (SAIL) and Sammaan Capital are banned from F&amp;O trading on 7 January 2026. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Biocon's subsidiary, Biocon Biologics will introduce three new oncology biosimilars at a US event. Titan Company's consumer business registered a growth of 40% YoY in Q3FY26. A total of 56 stores (net) were added during the quarter expanding Titan's combined retail network presence to 3,433 stores. Lodha Developers' pre sales jumped 25% to Rs 56,200 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 45,100 crore in Q3 FY25. Collections declined 17% YoY to Rs 35,600 crore in Q3 FY26. Jubilant Foodworks' consolidated revenue stood at Rs 2,438.7 crore in Q3 FY26, up 13.4% YoY. Domino's recorded a Like-For-Like (LFL) growth of 5%. Senco Gold reported a 51% revenue growth in Q3 FY26, driven by robust performances across its businesses. The retail business reported around 49% growth while SSSG growth stood at 39%. Godrej Consumer Products said that its standalone business is well positioned to deliver double-digit revenue growth for the quarter, underpinned by close to double-digit underlying volume growth (UVG), albeit on a supportive comparator. Personal Care is expected to record mid-single-digit value growth, driven by a marked recovery in the soaps category.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-biocon-senco-gold-jubilant-foodworks-titan-company/stock-alert/1663469/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 07:58:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: IndusInd Bank, Axis Bank, Kotak Mahindra Ban...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-indusind-bank-axis-bank-kotak-mahindra-bank-tata-motors-pv/stock-alert/1663264/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Steel Authority of India (SAIL) and Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on 6 January 2026. Stocks in Spotlight: Stocks in Spotlight: IndusInd Bank's deposits fell 3.8% YoY to Rs 3,94,022 crore as of 31st December 2025. On a sequential basis however, deposits rose 1.1% from Rs 3,89,600 crore as of 30 September 2025. Net advances tumbled 13.1% YoY to Rs 3,66,889 crore as of 31st December 2025. Axis Bank's total deposits jumped 15% to Rs 12,60,800 crore as on 31st December 2025 compared with Rs 10,95,900 crore as on 31st December 2024. Tata Motors Passenger Vehicle's wholly owned subsidiary Jaguar land rover (JLR) wholesale volumes for the third quarter were 59,200 units (excluding the Chery Jaguar Land Rover China JV ('CJLR') ), down 43.3% YoY and down 10 .6% QoQ. Retail sales for the third quarter of 79,600 units (including CJLR ) were down 25.1 % YoY and down 6.7% QoQ. Production returned to normal levels only by mid -November post the cyber incident. Utkarsh Small Finance Bank (SFB) total deposits jumped 4.5% to Rs 21,087 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 20,172 crore in Q3 FY25. Gross loan portfolio fell 3.9% YoY to Rs 18,306 crore in Q3 FY26. Dabur India said that it expects consolidated revenue to grow in the mid-single digits with operating profit and Profit after Tax to grow ahead of revenuein Q3 FY26. During the quarter, early signs of demand recovery were witnessed, aided by GST rate revisions. Post trade stabilisation, consumer sentiment improved in urban and rural areas. Rural demand continued to outperform urban demand this quarter as well. Kotak Mahindra Bank's average total deposits climbed 14.7% to Rs 5,26,025 crore as of 31st December 2025 compared with Rs 5,10,138 crore as of 31st December 2024. Average advances jumped 16.2% YoY to Rs 465,879 crore as of 31st December 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-indusind-bank-axis-bank-kotak-mahindra-bank-tata-motors-pv/stock-alert/1663264/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 07:57:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Dmart, Mahindra &amp; Mahindra, Jammu &amp; Kashmir ...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-dmart-mahindra-and-mahindra-jammu-and-kashmir-bank-pnb-v2-retail/stock-alert/1663097/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Shares of Steel Authority of India (SAIL) are banned from F&amp;O trading on 5 January 2026. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Oil companies will be in focus following US attacks on Venezuela, as potential volatility in crude oil prices could impact the sector. Avenue Supermarts (Dmart)'s standalone revenue from operations jumped 13% to Rs 17,612.62 crore in Q3 FY26 compared with Rs 15,565.23 crore in Q3 FY25. Jammu &amp; Kashmir Bank's gross advances jumped 17.26% to Rs 1,16,247.92 crore as of 31 December 2025, compared with Rs 99,133.35 crore as of 31 December 2024. Punjab National Bank (PNB) domestic deposits increased 8.32% to Rs 15,97,487 crore as of 31 December 2025 compared with Rs 14,74,760 crore posted on 31 December 2024. Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Financial Services has reported overall disbursements of around Rs 17,600 crore in Q3 FY26, registering a 7% year-on-year growth. Union Bank of India has reported a 7.42% rise in domestic advances to Rs 9,80,643 crore as of 31 December 2025, as against Rs 9,42,273 crore posted as of 31 December 2025. Corona Remedies reported a 21.75% increase in consolidated net profit to Rs 52.32 crore on 15.05% rise in revenue from operations to Rs 361.13 crore in Q2 FY26 over Q2 FY25. V2 Retail reported strong operational momentum in the December quarter, driven by aggressive network expansion and its continued transition from a regional player to a national retail footprint. Standalone revenue rose 57% year-on-year to Rs 927 crore in Q3 FY26, compared with Rs 591 crore in the year-ago period, Bank of India reported a 12.50% YoY increase in global business to Rs 16,27,098 crore as of 31 December 2025. Global deposits stood at Rs 8,87,287 crore, reflecting an 11.64% YoY increase. Domestic deposits rose 12.80% YoY to Rs 7,65,500 crore as of 31 December 2025 from Rs 6,78,626 crore a year earlier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-dmart-mahindra-and-mahindra-jammu-and-kashmir-bank-pnb-v2-retail/stock-alert/1663097/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 07:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: RailTel Corporation of India, Aurobindo Phar...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-railtel-corporation-of-india-aurobindo-pharma-olectra-greentech/stock-alert/1662872/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: SAIL shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on Tuesday, 30 December 2025. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: RailTel Corporation of India has received a Letter of Acceptance (LoA) from the Assam Health Infrastructure Development &amp; Management Society (AHIDMS) for procurement, implementation, and maintenance of a Hospital Management Information System (HMIS). The estimated order value is Rs 56.71 crore. Aurobindo Pharma announced that its subsidiary, Auro Pharma, has approved the acquisition of the non-oncology prescription formulations business of Khandelwal Laboratories on a going-concern basis through a Business Transfer Agreement for Rs 325 crore. Time Technoplast has received approvals from the Petroleum and Explosives Safety Organisation (PESO) and T'V Rheinland (India) for the manufacture and supply of high-pressure Type-3 fully wrapped fiber-reinforced composite cylinders of 2-liter capacity for compressed gas applications. Olectra Greentech declared the commercial operation date (COD) for its greenfield electric vehicle (EV) manufacturing facility in Hyderabad. The Phase-I per-shift annual production capacity stands at 2,500 electric buses, representing 50% of the planned per-shift capacity of 5,000 buses. Prataap Snacks said manufacturing operations at its Bengaluru unit ceased from 1 January 2026 as part of strategic consolidation. Production has been shifted to another facility in the region, ensuring continuity of supply. The company expects no adverse impact on its overall production capacity. Indegene announced the merger of its step-down arms'Indegene Aptilon Services and Trilogy Writing &amp; Consulting'to form Indegene Healthcare Canada Inc.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-railtel-corporation-of-india-aurobindo-pharma-olectra-greentech/stock-alert/1662872/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 07:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Canara Bank, NBCC (India), Titagarh Rail Sys...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-canara-bank-nbcc-india-titagarh-rail-systems-dr-reddys-laboratories-time-technoplast/stock-alert/1662723/30</link>
      <description>Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Canara Bank said Hardeep Singh Ahluwalia has been entrusted with the additional charge of managing director (MD) and chief executive officer (CEO), effective 1 January 2026, for a period of three months. NBCC (India) said it has secured multiple construction orders aggregating Rs 383 crore from Canara Bank and Navodaya Vidyalaya Samiti. Titagarh Rail Systems said its board has approved a business transfer agreement to transfer its Shipbuilding, Marine and Systems (SMS) business to its arm, Titagarh Naval Systems, in a transaction valued at Rs 114.9 crore, which will be executed in accordance with the terms of the pact. Dr Reddy's Laboratories said its Switzerland-based arm has received a complete response letter (CRL) from the US Food and Drug Administration for the biologics license application of its proposed biosimilar AVT03. Time Technoplast said it has received an order worth Rs 51 crore from Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd (HPCL) for the supply of goods. Hyundai Motor India said Unsoo Kim has resigned as managing director (MD) and director of the company, while shareholders have approved the appointment of Tarun Garg as the new managing director (MD) and chief executive officer (CEO), effective from 1 January 2026. Utkarsh Small Finance Bank said Pramod Kumar Dubey has resigned from his position as whole-time director (WTD) to pursue other career opportunities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-canara-bank-nbcc-india-titagarh-rail-systems-dr-reddys-laboratories-time-technoplast/stock-alert/1662723/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 07:16:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Bharat Forge, Power Grid, Titan Company, RITES</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-bharat-forge-power-grid-titan-company-rites/stock-alert/1662479/30</link>
      <description>Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Bharat Forge has received a contract worth Rs 1,661.9 crore from the Ministry of Defence for the supply of 255,128 CQB carbines (5.56 x 45 mm) to the Indian Army. The contract stipulates order execution within five years. Power Grid Corporation of India has been declared the successful bidder for the selection of battery energy storage developers for setting up a cumulative capacity of 2,000 MWh (1,000 MW x 2 hours) of standalone battery energy storage systems in Andhra Pradesh. The project comprises a 150 MW/300 MWh battery energy storage system at the 400/220 kV substation at Kalikiri in Chittoor district, Andhra Pradesh. RITES has received a Letter of Award for the supply of in-service Cape gauge diesel-electric locomotives from Berhard Development Corporation, Zimbabwe. The order is valued at $3.6 million. Dynacons Systems &amp; Solutions said that it has received orders worth Rs 249 crore from RBI for the implementation &amp; maintenance of enterprise applications platform software. Titan Company said that its board has approved the appointment of Sandhya Venugopal Sharma, IAS, as chairperson and additional director of the company, effective January 4, 2026. Arfin India announced that it has received an order worth Rs 321 crore from Diamond Power Infra for the supply of Aluminium sector conductors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-bharat-forge-power-grid-titan-company-rites/stock-alert/1662479/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 07:57:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Lupin, RVNL, BEL, Waaree Energies, GNFC, NTP...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-lupin-rvnl-bel-waaree-energies-gnfc-ntpc-green-energy/stock-alert/1662314/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on Tuesday, 30 December 2025. New Listing New Listing Gujarat Kidney &amp; Super Speciality is slated to make its market debut on the mainboard today. The IPO was subscribed 5.21 times. The issue opened for bidding on 22 December 2025 and it closed on 24 December 2025. The price band of the IPO was fixed between Rs 108 and 114 per share. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Lupin said that it has entered into an exclusive License, Supply, and Distribution Agreement with China-based Gan &amp; Lee Pharmaceuticals for a novel fortnightly GLP-1 receptor agonist, Bofanglutide. Bofanglutide injection is indicated for the treatment of type 2 diabetes and for weight management in overweight or obese individuals. Rail Vikas Nigam (RVNL) said that it has emerged as the lowest bidder for an order worth Rs 201.23 crore from East Coast Railway. The project involves setting up a wagon Periodic Overhaul (POH) workshop with a capacity of 200 wagons at Kantabanji. Bharat Electronics (BEL) said that it has received additional orders worth Rs 569 crore since December 12. These orders include radars, tank overhauls, communication equipment, fire control systems, simulators, antenna stabilisation systems, security software, components, upgrades, and spares. Waaree Energies said that Amit Paithankar has resigned as whole-time director and chief executive officer of the company to pursue opportunities outside the organisation, effective May 15, 2026. The company further said that the Board has approved the appointment of Jignesh Rathod, currently Director'Operations, as chief executive officer-designate with immediate effect. The Board has also appointed Jignesh Rathod as chief executive officer and Key Managerial Personnel, effective May 16, 2026. Gujarat Narmada Valley Fertilizers &amp; Chemicals (GNFC) said that T Natarajan has resigned as managing director with effect from December 29 following an order from the Government of Gujarat. The Government of Gujarat has nominated Rajkumar Beniwal, IAS, as managing director with effect from December 29. NTPC Green Energy announced the commencement of commercial operations of the ninth part capacity of 13.98 MW of the 1,255 MW Khavda-I Solar PV project of NTPC Renewable Energy. With this addition, the current commercial capacity of NTPC Green Energy stands at 7,996.30 MW, while the total installed capacity of the NGEL Group has increased to 8,010.28 MW.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-lupin-rvnl-bel-waaree-energies-gnfc-ntpc-green-energy/stock-alert/1662314/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 07:58:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Coforge, Vedanta, Suzlon Energy, Solarworld ...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-coforge-vedanta-suzlon-energy-solarworld-energy-solutions/stock-alert/1662162/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on Monday, 29 December 2025. Key Events to Watch Key Events to Watch The government is slated to release the Index of Industrial Production (IIP) data for November, which will offer cues on industrial activity. The Supreme Court of India is scheduled to hear a matter related to the definition of the Aravalli Hills. S. Krishnan, Secretary, Ministry of Electronics &amp; IT, will brief the media on the upcoming India AI Impact Summit 2026. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Coforge announced that it has signed a definitive agreement to acquire a 100% stake in Encora from Advent International, Warburg Pincus, and other minority shareholders for Rs 17,032.6 crore. The enterprise value of the transaction stands at $2.35 billion. The board approved raising up to $550 million through a qualified institutional placement (QIP) to repay Encora's term loan. Vedanta said that it has been declared the successful bidder for the Depo Graphite'Vanadium block under the critical mineral auctions. The company said the development will strengthen its critical minerals portfolio. Suzlon Energy announced that Vivek Srivastava has resigned as Chief Executive Officer (CEO) of the WTG Division, effective December 26. Diamond Power Infrastructure said that it has received a letter of intent from Hild Projects, an EPC contractor, for the supply of power cables worth Rs 66.18 crore. Avantel informed that it has received a contract worth Rs 4.16 crore from the Ministry of Defence, Headquarters Naval Aviation, for CAMC of Satcom equipment. Solarworld Energy Solutions said that it has received a letter of award from NTPC Renewable Energy for an EPC package for the development of a 250 MWac grid-connected solar PV project valued at Rs 725.33 crore. Vikran Engineering announced that it has accepted letters of award from MP Urja Vikas Nigam for the implementation of grid-connected solar PV-based power plants with an aggregate capacity of 45.75 MW AC in Vidisha, Madhya Pradesh.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-coforge-vedanta-suzlon-energy-solarworld-energy-solutions/stock-alert/1662162/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 07:54:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>