<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>SKI Capital – Stock Alert News</title>
    <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/stock-alert</link>
    <description>Stock alert news from SKI Capital Services - Indian stock market updates</description>
    <language>en-IN</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 18:26:54 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: NBCC, Tata steel, Netweb Tech, Brigade Enter...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-nbcc-tata-steel-netweb-tech-brigade-enterprises-bpcl-hindalco/stock-alert/1679741/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on 27 February 2026. New listing: New listing: In the mainboard IPO segment, Gaudium IVF &amp; Women Health is set to debut on the stock exchanges today. The public issue witnessed a healthy response, getting subscribed 7.27 times. The IPO price band was fixed at Rs 75'79 per share. Meanwhile, in the SME segment, Manilam Industries India is also scheduled to list on the bourses today. Its IPO was subscribed 4.22 times, with the price band set at Rs 65'69 per share. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: NBCC said that it has secured a Rs 775 crore order from the Delhi Development Authority (DDA) for the redevelopment of staff quarters. Tata Steel said that it has acquired 262 crore shares in its arm, T Steel Holdings, for a total consideration of Rs 2,402 crore. Gujarat Mineral Development Corporation (GMDC) has entered into a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with NTPC to jointly explore opportunities in coal and lignite gasification and downstream utilization. The MoU establishes a collaborative framework to assess the feasibility of gasifying coal from GMDC's coal blocks in Odisha and lignite from its mining operations in Gujarat. Netweb Technologies announced that it has entered into a collaboration with Vertiv, a global critical digital infrastructure firm. Vishal Mega Mart declined 6.66% to Rs 119.10 after multiple block deals resulted in nearly 14% of the company's equity changing hands on the exchanges. According to media reports, the floor price for the transaction was set at Rs 115 per share, implying a discount of nearly 10% to the previous closing price of Rs 127.60. The total size of the block deal is estimated at around Rs 3,508 crore, with a 150-day lock-in applicable on the remaining stake. Jio Financial Services said that it has subscribed to 3,35,71,923 equity shares of Rs 10 each of Jio Credit (JCL), a wholly owned subsidiary, for cash at a premium of Rs 585.70 per equity share, aggregating to Rs 1,999.88 crore. MSTC has become the lowest bidder for a tender hosted by Coal India on the GeM portal for the appointment of an external service provider to conduct linkage auctions for the non-regulated sector (NRS) for three years. Brigade Enterprises announced that the Brigade Group has partnered with Primus Senior Living to launch three senior living communities across Bengaluru and other geographies in South India. The upcoming projects will have an expected gross development value (GDV) of approximately Rs 750 crore. Hindalco Industries has informed that due to the partial shutdown of the US federal government, the statutory timelines under the CFIUS review framework have been tolled, impacting the ongoing review process. At present, no definitive timeline is available for the conclusion of the shutdown. Accordingly, the CFIUS review and the related transaction remain temporarily halted. Bharat Petroleum Corporation (BPCL) has incorporated a wholly owned subsidiary in Singapore named Bharat Petroleum Global Energy Services to establish an international trading desk for crude oil and natural gas. Indian Railway Finance Corporation said that the board will meet on March 9 to consider the declaration of a second interim dividend for the current financial year 2025'26 and to consider approval of the market borrowing program for the financial year 2026'27. GRE Renew Enertech has received multiple orders worth Rs 19.27 crore from domestic entities for the execution of engineering, procurement, and construction (EPC) contracts on a turnkey basis in the ordinary course of its business operations. Greaves Cotton said that the company's subsidiary, Greaves Electric Mobility, has announced its international expansion into Nepal, in partnership with STC Auto Solution. As part of this expansion, the company is launching its flagship product, Ampere Nexus. Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services has entered into an agreement with Chennai Super Kings Cricket, Superking Ventures, and Saurashtra Cement. The company will offer its Zaggle Corporate Expense Cards to employees and associates of Chennai Super Kings Cricket and Superking Ventures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-nbcc-tata-steel-netweb-tech-brigade-enterprises-bpcl-hindalco/stock-alert/1679741/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 07:34:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Lupin, Zydus Life, Shaily Engineering, KSB, ...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-lupin-zydus-life-shaily-engineering-ksb-sanofi-india-kp-energy-rvnl/stock-alert/1679543/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on 26 February 2026. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Reliance Industries said that its step-down wholly owned subsidiary, Reliance Enterprise Intelligence (REIL), has allotted 59.66 crore equity shares worth Rs 596.6 crore to Reliance Intelligence, a wholly owned subsidiary of the company, and 25.65 crore equity shares worth Rs 256.6 crore to Facebook Overseas Inc., a wholly owned subsidiary of Meta Platforms, Inc. After the allotment, Reliance Intelligence holds a 70% stake in REIL, and the balance of 30% is held by Facebook. Consequently, REIL has ceased to be a wholly owned step-down subsidiary and has become a step-down subsidiary of the company. Indian Railway Finance Corporation (IRFC) said that the Government of India, the promoter, is not exercising the oversubscription option to the extent of 26.13 crore equity shares (2% of paid-up equity) since there is an under subscription of 1.18 crore equity shares of the company as of T Day (February 25). Hence, accordingly, the total offer size will be the base offer size of up to 26.13 crore shares (2 percent equity). Additionally, the company has signed a loan agreement with the consortium of Sumitomo Mitsui Banking Corporation and MUFG Bank (Gift City branches) in New Delhi for raising an External Commercial Borrowing loan of JPY equivalent to $400 million. Shaily Engineering Plastics has received an order worth Rs 423 crore from a domestic pharma company to supply pen injectors. Lupin said that the Goods &amp; Service Tax Department, Maharashtra on February 25, has initiated Inspection and Search proceedings at the registered office of the company, seeking documents related to payment of GST and claim of input tax credit, etc. Initiation of this inspection and search doesn't have any impact on the company's financials, operations, or other activities. KFin Technologies said that MFC Technologies, the joint venture between Computer Age Management Services (CAMS) and KFin Technologies, announced key leadership appointments as MF Central transitions into a professionally governed stand-alone entity serving India's mutual fund ecosystem. SBI Life Insurance Company said that the Board has declared an interim dividend on equity shares of the company of Rs 2.7 per share for FY26. Zydus Lifesciences said that the company plans to launch Semaglutide injection under the brand names SEMAGLYNTM, MASHEMATM, and ALTERMETM upon patent expiry in India. The Drug Controller General of India (DCGI) had earlier provided its approval for manufacturing and marketing Semaglutide injection for the treatment of Type 2 Diabetes Mellitus and Obesity. KP Energy said that it has received a Letter of Award (LoA) from Enerparc Energy for the development of a 40.8 MW wind-solar hybrid power project in Gujarat, comprising approximately 20.2 MW of wind capacity and 20.6 MWp of solar capacity. Rail Vikas Nigam announced that the company has received an LOA from the National Mineral Development Corporation (NMDC) for the development of a township in Kirandul, Chhattisgarh. The project cost is Rs 371.69 crore. ACME Solar Holdings said that the company, through its subsidiary ACME Suryodaya, has commissioned the first phase of 19 MW/38 MWh out of 285 MW/600 MWh capacity of the battery energy storage system (BESS) project at Jaisalmer, Rajasthan. This project will currently be deployed as a merchant capacity while ACME Solar Holdings retains flexibility to shift to a long-term PPA in the future. The commercial operation date for the said Phase I will be February 27. NTPC Green Energy announced that the first part capacity of 50 MW out of 200 MW of the Dayapar Wind Energy Project Phase II in Gujarat of the company's subsidiary NTPC Renewable Energy has been declared in commercial operation. The current commercial capacity of the NTPC Green Energy group stands at 9,151.08 MW. With the addition of this capacity, the total installed capacity of the NTPC Green Energy Group will increase to 9201.08 MW. Sanofi India reported a net profit of Rs 61.7 crore for Q4, down 32.4% from Rs 91.3 crore in the same period last year. Revenue for the quarter declined 18.5% to Rs 419.8 crore from Rs 514.9 crore a year ago. KSB reported a net profit of Rs 81 crore for the quarter, up 10.8% year-on-year from Rs 73.1 crore in the same period last year. Revenue grew 8% to Rs 784 crore, compared with Rs 726.4 crore a year ago, driven by steady demand across its key segments. Solarworld Energy's subsidiary has signed a non-binding memorandum of understanding (MoU) with Intelenergi Global for potential collaboration in solar photovoltaic (PV) module projects. The MoU outlines preliminary cooperation on technology, manufacturing, and deployment in the renewable energy segment. Emmvee Photovoltaic has stated that it remains insulated from the recently announced US solar import duties, as its manufacturing is primarily aligned with domestic demand.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-lupin-zydus-life-shaily-engineering-ksb-sanofi-india-kp-energy-rvnl/stock-alert/1679543/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 07:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: HG Infra, IRFC, RVNL, Schaeffler India, Dr R...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-hg-infra-irfc-rvnl-schaeffler-india-dr-reddys-lab-waaree-energies/stock-alert/1679365/30</link>
      <description>New listing: New listing: In the SME segment, Yashhtej Industries (India) is scheduled to debut on the bourses today. The company's IPO was subscribed 1.35 times. The issue price was fixed at Rs 110 per share. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: HG Infra Engineering has been declared the lowest bidder (L1) by NHAI for a project worth Rs 1,582 crore. The project involves the construction of a six-lane, access-controlled Capital Region Ring Road (Package-III) from Gobindpur (NH-55) to Tangi near Bandola Toll Plaza (NH-16) in Odisha under the Hybrid Annuity Mode (HAM). Indian Railway Finance Corporation (IRFC) said that the Government of India will sell up to 26.13 crore equity shares (2% stake) on 25'26 February, with an option to additionally sell up to 26.13 crore shares (2% stake) through the offer-for-sale (OFS) route on BSE and NSE. The floor price has been fixed at Rs 104 per share. Rail Vikas Nigam (RVNL) has received a Letter of Acceptance (LoA) worth Rs 270.22 crore from Central Railway. The order pertains to the design, supply, erection, testing, and commissioning of a 220/132/55 kV traction substation and associated works for the Daund'Solapur section. Waaree Energies announced that its subsidiary, Waaree Forever Energies, has received a Letter of Award from Solar Energy Corporation of India for the development of a 300 MW wind power project in Dwarka, Gujarat. Hindalco Industries said that Novelis has entered into a subscription agreement with AV Minerals, its sole shareholder and a wholly owned subsidiary of the company. AV Minerals will purchase 13.33 lakh Novelis common shares for $200 million at a price of $150 per share. Lupin has received approval from the US FDA for its Abbreviated New Drug Application (ANDA) for Brivaracetam Oral Solution 10 mg/mL. The product is bioequivalent to Briviact Oral Solution and is indicated for the treatment of partial-onset seizures. The reference-listed drug had estimated annual US sales of $135 million. Hexaware Technologies has expanded its collaboration with Amazon Web Services (AWS) to deliver AI-enabled software development lifecycle (SDLC) capabilities, building on its Strategic Collaboration Agreement (SCA) with AWS. Dr. Reddy's Laboratories has received a letter from the US Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) stating that it has concluded its investigation and does not intend to recommend enforcement action against the company at this time. The investigation related to allegations of improper payments to healthcare professionals in Ukraine and potential violations of US anti-corruption laws, including the Foreign Corrupt Practices Act (FCPA). Power Grid Corporation of India said that the Cabinet Committee on Economic Affairs has increased the permissible equity investment limit per subsidiary to Rs 7,500 crore from Rs 5,000 crore, while retaining the cap at 15% of the company's net worth. 5Paisa Capital said that its board has approved raising up to Rs 475 crore through a rights issue of equity shares. Schaeffler India reported a net profit of Rs 322.3 crore for Q4, up 35.9% from Rs 237.2 crore in the same period last year. Revenue for the quarter increased 27.5% to Rs 2,724 crore from Rs 2,136 crore a year ago. Biocon has received approval from the US Food and Drug Administration (FDA) for its drug-device combination, Liraglutide, indicated for weight management. Federal Bank has launched revamped current account variants named 'Fed Prime' and 'Shreni CA Premium.'</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-hg-infra-irfc-rvnl-schaeffler-india-dr-reddys-lab-waaree-energies/stock-alert/1679365/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 07:32:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Tata Tech, Torrent Power, MobiKwik, Bharti A...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-tata-tech-torrent-power-mobikwik-bharti-airtel-idfc-first-bank-bpcl-chalet-hotels/stock-alert/1679192/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: SAIL shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on 24 February 2026. New listing: New listing: In the SME segment, Fractal Industries is scheduled to debut on the bourses today. The company's IPO was subscribed 5.13 times. The price band for the issue was fixed at Rs 205'216 per share. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Bharti Airtel announced major plans for its non-banking financial company (NBFC), Airtel Money, underscoring its commitment to narrowing the credit gap in India. The NBFC subsidiary will be capitalized with Rs 20,000 crore, to be injected over the next few years. Airtel will contribute 70 percent, while the promoter group, through Bharti Enterprises, will bring in the remaining 30 percent. HUDCO, Piramal Pharma, Tata Technologies and Torrent Power to be excluded from F&amp;O The National Stock Exchange (NSE) has decided to exclude Housing &amp; Urban Development Corporation (HUDCO), Piramal Pharma, Tata Technologies, and Torrent Power from the Futures &amp; Options (F&amp;O) segment with effect from 29 April 2026. One Mobikwik Systems announced that its subsidiary, Mobikwik Securities Broking, has received approval from the Bombay Stock Exchange (BSE) to commence its stock broking business. IDFC First Bank said the recent volatility in its share price followed the detection of a Rs 590-crore fraud at its Chandigarh branch. The bank added that reports regarding government de-empanelment are part of the ordinary course of business. Container Corporation of India and Vizhinjam International Seaport, a Government of Kerala undertaking, have signed a non-binding and non-exclusive Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) at Thiruvananthapuram for the development of a Container Freight Station (CFS) near Vizhinjam International Seaport, Thiruvananthapuram, Kerala. Lupin said it has received approval from the European Commission for its biosimilar ranibizumab, Ranluspec (vials and pre-filled syringes), following a positive opinion from the Committee for Medicinal Products for Human Use (CHMP). Pace Digitek said that its subsidiary, Lineage Power, has secured a purchase order worth Rs 158.7 crore from Reliance Industries for the supply of Li-ion battery packs (48V 15S1P 314 AH). Blue Cloud Softech Solutions said its board has approved a definitive agreement framework to acquire a 100% stake in Global Impex Inc. from ConnectM Technology Solutions Inc, a US-based modern energy economy company. PC Jeweller said its arm has incorporated a wholly owned subsidiary, PCJ Mining SARL, in the Republic of Chad. Samvardhana Motherson International said it has inaugurated a manufacturing facility in Sanand, Gujarat, under its joint venture with Marelli. The advanced plant, set up as a strategic partnership with Marelli, will exclusively manufacture exterior lighting systems, strengthening the group's capabilities in automotive component manufacturing. Silver Touch Technologies said it has been selected by the Food Safety and Standards Authority of India (FSSAI) for a strategic digital transformation engagement. The company will act as the Managed Service Provider (MSP) for application development and enhancement, as well as for the operations and maintenance of FSSAI's portals and applications. Waaree Energies said its arm signed an agreement with ZFI to expand a 2.5-GW electrolyzer project in Uttar Pradesh and bagged a separate 500 MW solar module order from an unnamed producer. Signpost India has received an order worth Rs 450 crore from the Kolkata Municipal Corporation for exclusive outdoor advertising rights on key stretches, including Park Street (Mother Teresa Sarani), Jawaharlal Nehru Road, Camac Street (Abanindranath Sarani), and Theatre Road (Shakespeare Sarani), under the 'Kolkata Streetscape Renaissance' project on a PPP basis. Sigma Advanced Systems has secured fresh orders worth about Rs 100 crore from the Ministry of Defence and associated defence PSUs. The contracts relate to ongoing strategic programs across missile systems, naval platforms, and airborne applications, under which the company will supply built-to-spec systems, control electronics, and actuation solutions. Chalet Hotels said its board has approved the development of a proposed 330-room luxury hotel, along with commercial/retail space of 36,255 sq ft, at Madhapur in Hyderabad, with an investment of Rs 632.8 crore. Upon completion, this will be the company's third hotel in Hyderabad. Bharat Petroleum Corporation (BPCL) has received a tax demand order worth Rs 1,816.65 crore (duty of Rs 476.94 crore, interest up to date of Rs 1,339.70 crore, and a penalty of Rs 95,000) from the Central Tax &amp; Central Excise Department, Kochi, for the period from September 2004 to May 2010. The major portion of the demand pertains to the pre-merger period of Kochi Refineries (KRL), that is, September 2004 to August 2006, which was pending adjudication. BPCL said it will file an appeal against the order before the Customs, Excise and Service Tax Appellate Tribunal (CESTAT). RBL Bank said the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has approved the reappointment of Chandan Sinha as Non-Executive (Part-time) Chairman for a second term from 21 May 2026 to 20 May 2029. Cholamandalam Investment &amp; Finance said it has allotted 1 lakh non-convertible debentures (NCDs) aggregating to Rs 1,000 crore, including a greenshoe option.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-tata-tech-torrent-power-mobikwik-bharti-airtel-idfc-first-bank-bpcl-chalet-hotels/stock-alert/1679192/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 07:38:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Bharti Airtel, UPL, RailTel Corp, Cipla, Hig...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-bharti-airtel-upl-railtel-corp-cipla-highway-infrastructure/stock-alert/1679037/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Sammaan Capital shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on 23 February 2026. Initial Public Offer (IPO): Initial Public Offer (IPO): Shree Ram Twistex IPO opens for subscription today. The issue size is Rs 110.24 crore, comprising entirely a fresh issue. The price band has been fixed at Rs 95 to Rs 104 per share. Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions IPO opens for subscription today. The total issue size aggregates up to Rs 3,100 crore, comprising a fresh issue of Rs 1,200 crore and an offer for sale of up to Rs 1,900 crore. The price band has been set at Rs 1,000 to Rs 1,053 per share. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Bharti Airtel, in partnership with Zscaler Inc. (a leader in cloud security), announced the launch of the AI &amp; Cyber Threat Research Center'India, advancing national cyber resilience, protecting sectors, industries, and assets, and accelerating trusted AI adoption. UPL said its board has approved a group reorganization plan through a composite scheme of arrangement to unlock shareholder value by creating an independent, focused crop protection platform. Under the scheme, UPL Sustainable Agri Solutions will be amalgamated with UPL, while the India crop protection business will be demerged into UPL Global Sustainable Agri Solutions. UPL Crop Protection Holdings (UPL Cayman) will also be merged with UPL Global Sustainable Agri Solutions. Post-reorganization, the group will have two listed entities'UPL and UPL Global Sustainable Agri Solutions, which will be listed pursuant to the scheme. Suraj Estate Developers announced that it has entered into an agreement to acquire a 100% stake in Hally Pacific to undertake the development of a plot situated in Prabhadevi, Mumbai. Quality Power Electrical Equipments announced that its material subsidiary, Mehru Electrical and Mechanical Engineers, has received a letter of award (LoA) worth Rs 18 crore for the supply of instrument transformers from a domestic entity. Sathlokhar Synergys E&amp;C Global has secured new orders aggregating to Rs 37.57 crore for the execution of civil and pre-engineered building (PEB) works. WeWork India Management said that it has entered into a lease deed for capacity addition in Bengaluru, admeasuring 169,485 square feet, which will result in an increase in its operational capacity. Cipla announced that the United States Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) has classified the cGMP inspection at the Rodopi, Greece, facility of Pharmathen International S.A., which supplies lanreotide injection to Cipla USA Inc. (a wholly owned arm of Cipla), as Official Action Indicated (OAI). Meanwhile, Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC) raised its stake in Cipla to 9.091% from 7.055% between 27 November 2025 and 2 February 2026. RailTel Corporation of India, in consortium with Ashoka Buildcon, has received the Letter of Intent (LoI) from the Inspector General of Registration (IGR). The contract, worth Rs 1,136.18 crore, involves the selection of an MSP for the modernization of offices of the IGR and the Controller of Stamps under the Maharashtra Government. As per the letter of intent (LoI), the accepted rate is Rs 24.75 per page. The average number of pages scanned annually over the past five years, as per the Request for Proposal (RFP), stood at 9.18 crore pages. Based on this volume, the estimated financial impact over the five-year contract period is approximately Rs 1,136.18 crore. Highway Infrastructure has entered into a contract agreement for the operation and collection of user fees at Moti Naroli Fee Plaza in Gujarat, amounting to Rs 154.59 crore. Additionally, the company has entered into a contract agreement for the development of a road under Town Planning Scheme-08 from Kumedi to Lasudiya Mori (up to AB Road), Indore. The contract is worth Rs 69.68 crore.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-bharti-airtel-upl-railtel-corp-cipla-highway-infrastructure/stock-alert/1679037/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 07:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: RailTel Corp, Texmaco Rail &amp; Engineering, GH...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-railtel-corp-texmaco-rail-and-engineering-ghv-infra-projects-iifl-finance/stock-alert/1678802/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Sammaan Capital and Steel Authority of India shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on 20 February 2026. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: ABB India reported an 18.19% decline in consolidated net profit to 432.27 crore in Q4 CY25 compared to Rs 528.41 crore posted in same quarter last year. However, revenue from operations rose 5.7% YoY to Rs 3,557.01 crore reported in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. CIE Automotive India reported a 10.44% rise in consolidated net profit to 204.30 crore in Q4 CY25 compared to Rs 184.98 crore posted in same quarter last year. However, revenue from operations rose 13.41% YoY to Rs 2,392.99 crore reported in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. RailTel Corporation of India has announced that it has secured a Rs 36 crore railway signalling project from the Deputy Chief Signal and Telecommunication Engineer. Texmaco Rail &amp; Engineering has announced that it has executed a Strategic Joint Venture Shareholders' Agreement with RVNL to build a rolling stock powerhouse and expand its rail EPC footprint. GHV Infra Projects has announced that it has secured a Rs 123 crore work order from Enmas EPC Power Projects for the supply of rooftop solar plants. IIFL Finance has announced that its board will meet on February 24 to consider raising up to Rs 10,000 crore through non-convertible debentures (NCDs). 5paisa Capital has announced that its board will meet on February 24 to consider a fund-raising proposal. Avenue Supermarts has announced that it has opened a new store in Rangareddy, Telangana, bringing its total store count to 449. Zydus Lifesciences has announced that the US FDA has completed an inspection of the company's Ahmedabad unit with 'nil' observations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-railtel-corp-texmaco-rail-and-engineering-ghv-infra-projects-iifl-finance/stock-alert/1678802/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 08:07:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: B. L. Kashyap and Sons, Pace Digitek, DCX Sy...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-b-l-kashyap-and-sons-pace-digitek-dcx-systems-bharat-electronics/stock-alert/1678617/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Sammaan Capital and Steel Authority of India shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on 19 February 2026. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: B. L. Kashyap and Sons announced that it has secured a Rs 300 crore order from CRC Greens for the construction of civil works. Pace Digitek announced that its material subsidiary, Lineage Power, has secured a $1.35 million order from Yaqin Chem for the supply of mobile battery systems. DCX Systems announced that it and its wholly owned subsidiary, Raneal Advanced Systems, has secured combined orders worth Rs 45.4 crore for the supply of cable assemblies and printed circuit assemblies. Bharat Electronics (BEL) announced that its board will meet on February 27 to consider the declaration of an interim dividend for the financial year 2025'26. Nucleus Software Exports announced that it has expanded its global footprint by incorporating a new arm in Vietnam. Zydus Lifesciences announced that it has received USFDA approval for Bosentan tablets, used in the treatment of pulmonary arterial hypertension.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-b-l-kashyap-and-sons-pace-digitek-dcx-systems-bharat-electronics/stock-alert/1678617/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 07:58:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Bharti Airtel, Info Edge, Dilip Buildcon, In...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-bharti-airtel-info-edge-dilip-buildcon-infosys-bosch/stock-alert/1678334/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Sammaan Capital and Steel Authority of India shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on 18 February 2026. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Bharti Airtel announced that its subsidiary company, Airtel Money, has received RBI approval for registration as a Type-II NBFC. Info Edge (India) announced that it will invest Rs 30 crore in its arm, Startup Investments. Dilip Buildcon announced that it has been declared the L-1 bidder for a Gujarat government tender valued at Rs 702 crore. Infosys unveils its AI First Value Framework, aiming to capture a share of an estimated $300 billion AI services opportunity Bosch announced that Karin Gilges resigns as CFO effective May 31, and Tillmann Olsen is appointed as her successor effective June 1. Bharat Heavy Electricals announced that it has secured a Letter of Award worth between Rs 1,200'1,500 crore from SAIL for a Captive Power Plant (CPP) package. Chalet Hotels informed that the Bengaluru authority issued a notice to the company for non-payment of property tax worth Rs 40 crore.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-bharti-airtel-info-edge-dilip-buildcon-infosys-bosch/stock-alert/1678334/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: Lupin, NTPC, Cochin Shipyard, Texmaco Rail &amp;...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-lupin-ntpc-cochin-shipyard-texmaco-rail-and-engineering-bls-e-services/stock-alert/1678146/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Sammaan Capital and Steel Authority of India shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on 17 February 2026. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: Lupin announced that it has entered into a licensing and supply agreement with Spektus to commercialize its antidepressant formulation DeslaFlex in Canada. NTPC announced that its joint venture NTPC-SAIL Power Company has commenced operations of an additional 5 MW at its Bhilai Solar Project, taking the group's total commercial capacity to 86,729 MW. Cochin Shipyard has emerged as the L1 (lowest) bidder for a Rs 5,000 crore order from the Ministry of Defence to manufacture five survey vessels for the Indian Navy. Texmaco Rail &amp; Engineering has secured a Rs 219 crore contract from Mumbai Railway Vikas Corporation for construction work in the Mumbai suburban railway network. BLS E-Services announced that it has signed binding term sheet, to acquire a 100% stake in Atyati Technologies for Rs 154 crore. TVS Supply Chain Solutions has signed a memorandum of understanding (MoU) with Italy-based ALA Group to provide services to the Indian aerospace and defence market.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-lupin-ntpc-cochin-shipyard-texmaco-rail-and-engineering-bls-e-services/stock-alert/1678146/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 08:13:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock Alert: GK Energy, Vikran Engineering, Shakti Pumps,...</title>
      <link>https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-gk-energy-vikran-engineering-shakti-pumps-deep-industries-railtel-corp/stock-alert/1677913/30</link>
      <description>Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Securities in F&amp;O Ban: Sammaan Capital and Steel Authority of India shares are banned from F&amp;O trading on 16 February 2026. New listing: New listing: In the mainboard IPO space, Fractal Analytics and Aye Finance is set to make its market debut today. Stocks to Watch: Stocks to Watch: GK Energy reported a 57.74% rise in standalone net profit to Rs 58.83 crore on a 43.6% increase in revenue from operations to Rs 460.20 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Vikran Engineering reported a 37.9% decline in standalone net profit to Rs 20.91 crore on a 0.5% rise in net sales to Rs 266.46 crore in Q3 FY26 as compared with Q3 FY25. Shakti Pumps India's consolidated net profit declined 69.53% to Rs 31.70 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 104.05 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations decreased 15.07% to Rs 550.99 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 648.77 crore reported in Q3 FY25. Deep Industries said that it has secured a domestic contract from Oil India for the hiring of a 1000 HP mobile drilling rig package in Assam and Arunachal Pradesh. RailTel Corporation of India has secured a work order worth Rs 92.91 crore from the Directorate of Education, Government of National Capital Territory of Delhi (GNCTD). Titagarh Rail Systems' consolidated net profit tanked 23.48% to Rs 48.03 crore in Q3 FY26 as against Rs 62.77 crore posted in Q3 FY25. Revenue from operations decreased 7.8% year-on-year (YoY) to Rs 832.06 crore in the quarter ended 31 December 2025. Crisil's consolidated total income for Q4 2025, rose 17.5% to Rs 1,108.7 crore, compared with Rs 943.2 crore in Q4 2024. On a consolidated basis, the company's income from operations for Q4 2025 was up 18.5% to Rs 1,081.6 crore, compared with Rs 912.9 crore in Q4 2024. Profit after tax was up 7.5% to Rs 241.5 crore, compared with Rs 224.7 crore in Q4 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.skicapital.net/news/detailed-news/stock-alert-gk-energy-vikran-engineering-shakti-pumps-deep-industries-railtel-corp/stock-alert/1677913/30</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 07:56:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Alert</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>