<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:18:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[AVANTEL] Avantel Ltd. Approves Un-audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AVANTEL+LTD.&title=Avantel+Ltd.+Approves+Un-audited+Standalone+and+Consolidated+Financial+Results+for+Q3+2025&newsId=a7204990-8e70-4da9-8805-dc9860cdcfa7&token=YTcyMDQ5OTAtOGU3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a7204990-8e70-4da9-8805-dc9860cdcfa7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:02:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Avantel Ltd. approved the Un-audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the Third Quarter ended December 31, 2025. The results were reviewed by the Audit Committee and the Statutory Auditors. The company operates in a single segment and the results pertain to this segment. The financial results are available on the company&apos;s website and on the BSE and NSE websites.</p><ul><li>Avantel Ltd. approved the Un-audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 2025.</li><li>The results were reviewed by the Audit Committee and the Statutory Auditors.</li><li>The company operates in a single segment.</li><li>The financial results are available on the company&apos;s website and on the BSE and NSE websites.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/74cf51f8-a41b-4b43-8769-c4b33c7d52c7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AVANTEL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AVANTEL] Avantel Ltd. Announces Un-Audited Financial Results for Q3 2025, Revenue Up by 41.32%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AVANTEL+LTD.&title=Avantel+Ltd.+Announces+Un-Audited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+2025%2C+Revenue+Up+by+41.32%25&newsId=c14ef7da-2ce7-4eda-a7b2-2ba6d50bc7ae&token=YzE0ZWY3ZGEtMmNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c14ef7da-2ce7-4eda-a7b2-2ba6d50bc7ae</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Avantel Ltd. has announced its un-audited financial results for the third quarter ended December 31, 2025. The Board of Directors approved the un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results. The total revenue from operations has increased by 41.32% compared to the same period last year. The company operates in a single segment and the results pertain to this segment. The financial results are available on the company&apos;s website and the websites of BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange of India Limited.</p><ul><li>Un-Audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results approved for Q3 2025</li><li>Total Revenue from Operations increased by 41.32% compared to Q3 2024</li><li>Company operates in a single segment</li><li>Financial results available on company&apos;s website and stock exchange websites</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6413e3de-a3fe-4ab2-a8c3-82081168b874.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AVANTEL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JPPOWER] Jaiprakash Power Ventures Chairman Released on Interim Bail in ED Investigation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jaiprakash+Power+Ventures+Limited&title=Jaiprakash+Power+Ventures+Chairman+Released+on+Interim+Bail+in+ED+Investigation&newsId=02f6376c-fadd-4f07-98c8-4feb25bc0053&token=MDJmNjM3NmMtZmFk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02f6376c-fadd-4f07-98c8-4feb25bc0053</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jaiprakash Power Ventures Ltd. has released a disclosure stating that its Non-Executive Director and Chairman, Shri Manoj Gaur, has been granted interim bail by the Hon’ble Court of Additional Sessions Judge-7, Patiala House, New Delhi on 24th January 2026. This update comes in continuation with the previous disclosure dated 13th November, 2025 regarding the Enforcement Directorate (ED) action in connection with an ongoing investigation.</p><ul><li>Shri Manoj Gaur, Non-Executive Director and Chairman of Jaiprakash Power Ventures Ltd, has been released on interim bail</li><li>The bail was granted by the Hon’ble Court of Additional Sessions Judge-7, Patiala House, New Delhi</li><li>This update is in continuation with the previous disclosure dated 13th November, 2025 regarding ED action in an ongoing investigation</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/aa88dd2f-a370-45ff-98af-6439bfa9d24f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jaiprakash Power Ventures Limited | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CANBK] Canara Bank Branches and Offices May Be Affected by Proposed Strike on January 27, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CANARA+BANK&title=Canara+Bank+Branches+and+Offices+May+Be+Affected+by+Proposed+Strike+on+January+27%2C+2026&newsId=a1498d20-5bb3-443a-b877-e72ee687a3ee&token=YTE0OThkMjAtNWJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a1498d20-5bb3-443a-b877-e72ee687a3ee</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 08:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Strike Notice</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The United Forum of Bank Unions (U.F.B.U.) has announced a strike on Tuesday, January 27, 2026, due to various issues and demands. Canara Bank is preparing for the potential strike, but if it occurs, the bank&apos;s branches and offices may experience disruptions. This notice is to inform stock exchanges and stakeholders about the possible impact of the strike.</p><ul><li>The United Forum of Bank Unions (U.F.B.U.) has called for a strike on January 27, 2026, affecting Canara Bank branches and offices</li><li>Canara Bank is taking steps to ensure smooth functioning during the proposed strike</li><li>Potential disruptions may occur if the strike takes place</li><li>Stakeholders are informed about the possibility of branch and office disruptions</li><li>The notice is in compliance with SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4bed3b50-04d2-4a10-af63-4181a4abafbd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CANARA BANK | Category: Strike Notice</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RELTD] Ravindra Energy Revises General Business Update: Corrects Operating Swap Stations &amp; Provides Detailed Insight into Renewable Energy &amp; Electric Vehicle Business Activities</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ravindra+Energy+Ltd&title=Ravindra+Energy+Revises+General+Business+Update%3A+Corrects+Operating+Swap+Stations+%26+Provides+Detailed+Insight+into+Renewable+Energy+%26+Electric+Vehicle+Business+Activities&newsId=2843d18f-95c4-4871-911a-c7623b4ea8df&token=Mjg0M2QxOGYtOTVj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2843d18f-95c4-4871-911a-c7623b4ea8df</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 07:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Ravindra Energy Ltd. has submitted a revised business update regarding its renewable energy business and electric vehicle business activities. The company has corrected the number of operating swap stations in Q2 and Q3, which were inadvertently interchanged. The renewable energy business includes operating assets of 187 MW DC, with all 19 Mukhya Mantri Saurya Krishi Vahini Yojana (MSKVY) Phase 1 projects commissioned and generating income as per the target. MSKVY Phase 2 projects, with a capacity of 57 MW, are likely to be commissioned before 31st March 2026. The company also has a pipeline of 235 MW DC under development. In the electric vehicle business, the company has sold 125 vehicles in the nine-month period ending December 2025. Additionally, YES Bank Ltd. has sanctioned financial assistance of INR 296 Crore and a hedge facility of INR 32 Crore to Ravindra Energy Ltd.</p><ul><li>Ravindra Energy corrects the number of operating swap stations in Q2 and Q3</li><li>Company provides detailed insight into renewable energy business activities</li><li>MSKVY Phase 1 projects commissioned and generating income as per target</li><li>MSKVY Phase 2 projects with 57 MW capacity likely to be commissioned before 31st March 2026</li><li>YES Bank sanctions financial assistance of INR 296 Crore and a hedge facility of INR 32 Crore</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/17b3d109-1f5a-4cbc-baad-ef46a79f0352.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ravindra Energy Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UDS] Updater Services Ltd Receives Rs. 65,38,972 Order from Commercial Tax Officer, Chennai</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Updater+Services+Ltd&title=Updater+Services+Ltd+Receives+Rs.+65%2C38%2C972+Order+from+Commercial+Tax+Officer%2C+Chennai&newsId=f5d7b85f-838d-4152-b7b0-733ec47a764a&token=ZjVkN2I4NWYtODM4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f5d7b85f-838d-4152-b7b0-733ec47a764a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 07:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Updater Services Limited has received an order from the Office of the Commercial Tax Officer, Chennai, Tamil Nadu for an amount of Rs. 65,38,972/- under Sec 74 of the CGST Act, 2017. The order has been passed without considering the company&apos;s response to the notice. Updater Services Limited is exploring legal options and is hopeful that there will be no significant financial impact.</p><ul><li>Updater Services Limited has received an order from the Office of the Commercial Tax Officer, Chennai, Tamil Nadu for an amount of Rs. 65,38,972/- under Sec 74 of the CGST Act, 2017.</li><li>The order has been passed without considering the company&apos;s response to the notice.</li><li>Updater Services Limited is exploring legal options including filing writ / appeal before the Appellant authority.</li><li>The company is hopeful that there will be no significant financial impact.</li><li>The order is based on ITC Reversal of Exempted Supplies, Sundry Creditor, and Expenses payable under RCM.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9eb668db-2b34-4699-8c80-6c7c4bd21652.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Updater Services Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADANIGREEN] Adani Green Energy Ltd. Increases Operational Renewable Generation Capacity to 17,287.2 MW</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Adani+Green+Energy+Ltd&title=Adani+Green+Energy+Ltd.+Increases+Operational+Renewable+Generation+Capacity+to+17%2C287.2+MW&newsId=ff733dd6-84b7-444f-852d-e357a947bc28&token=ZmY3MzNkZDYtODRi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff733dd6-84b7-444f-852d-e357a947bc28</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 06:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Adani Green Energy Limited (AGEL) has operationalized a 50 MW solar power project at Khavda, Gujarat, through its wholly-owned stepdown subsidiary, Adani Green Energy Twenty Six A Limited (AGE26AL). This commissioning has increased AGEL&apos;s total operational renewable generation capacity to 17,287.2 MW. The decision to operationalize the plant and commence power generation was made at 10.49 a.m. on January 25, 2026.</p><ul><li>Adani Green Energy Limited has increased its total operational renewable generation capacity to 17,287.2 MW.</li><li>A 50 MW solar power project has been operationalized by Adani Green Energy Twenty Six A Limited in Khavda, Gujarat.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d3b57baf-5fd8-4d05-b1ac-d09adf867e86.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Adani Green Energy Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PARADEEP] Paradeep Phosphates Ltd Receives Seizure Memo from Customs Department for Exceeding Biuret Content Limit in Urea Import</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Paradeep+Phosphates+Ltd&title=Paradeep+Phosphates+Ltd+Receives+Seizure+Memo+from+Customs+Department+for+Exceeding+Biuret+Content+Limit+in+Urea+Import&newsId=41717879-6921-46f1-a857-4f21658be0da&token=NDE3MTc4NzktNjky</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41717879-6921-46f1-a857-4f21658be0da</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 06:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Paradeep Phosphates Ltd has received a Seizure Memo from the Customs Department for exceeding the Biuret content limit in 25,000 MTs of Technical Grade Urea imported for manufacturing NPK fertilisers. The assessable value of the seized urea is Rs. 103.30 crores. The Company has contested the testing methodology adopted by CRCL and is taking appropriate legal recourse for the Provisional Release of the seized goods for captive consumption as raw material in the manufacture of NPK fertilisers at their Goa plant.</p><ul><li>Paradeep Phosphates Ltd receives Seizure Memo from Customs Department for exceeding Biuret content limit in urea import.</li><li>The seized urea has an assessable value of Rs. 103.30 crores.</li><li>The Company contests the testing methodology adopted by CRCL.</li><li>Legal action is being taken for the Provisional Release of seized goods for captive consumption as raw material.</li><li>No material impact on financials, operations, or other activities of the listed entity.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1f56ba2a-57d7-43b7-866c-f12c76b86604.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Paradeep Phosphates Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BERYLSE] Beryl Securities Ltd to Approve Q4 Results on Feb 03, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BERYL+SECURITIES+LTD.&title=Beryl+Securities+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+Results+on+Feb+03%2C+2026&newsId=f429649d-2f65-4166-97cc-5468df691800&token=ZjQyOTY0OWQtMmY2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f429649d-2f65-4166-97cc-5468df691800</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 22:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Beryl Securities Ltd has scheduled a Board of Directors meeting on February 03, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited quarterly financial results for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025. The meeting will also discuss updates in RBI policies and consider resolutions passed at finance committee meetings.</p><ul><li>Beryl Securities Ltd to consider and approve unaudited Q4 financial results for the period ending December 31, 2025.</li><li>The company will discuss updates in RBI policies during the meeting.</li><li>Resolutions passed at finance committee meetings will be taken on record.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b91b31cc-5b4f-4e28-a4ff-ee3469132c8e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BERYL SECURITIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[OROSMITHS] Orosil Smiths India Ltd. to Approve Un-audited Financial Results for Q3 2025 on Feb 06, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=OROSIL+SMITHS+INDIA+LTD.-%24&title=Orosil+Smiths+India+Ltd.+to+Approve+Un-audited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+2025+on+Feb+06%2C+2026&newsId=1bef2c9b-2857-47ae-9f90-c5667329c84e&token=MWJlZjJjOWItMjg1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1bef2c9b-2857-47ae-9f90-c5667329c84e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 17:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Orosil Smiths India Ltd. has informed the BSE that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on February 06, 2026. The agenda includes the consideration and approval of the Un-audited Financial Results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, as per the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The Statutory Auditors&apos; Limited Review Report(s) will also be noted during the meeting.</p><ul><li>Orosil Smiths India Ltd. to consider and approve Un-audited Financial Results for Q3 2025</li><li>Meeting of the Board of Directors scheduled on February 06, 2026</li><li>Consideration of the Un-audited Financial Results in accordance with SEBI Regulations</li><li>Statutory Auditors&apos; Limited Review Report(s) to be noted</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/39920e21-ca6f-4ebc-9620-671eba44ecdc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: OROSIL SMITHS INDIA LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>