<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:32:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[GHUSHINE] Ghushine Fintrade Ocean Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Alter Memorandum and Articles of Association</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ghushine+Fintrrade+Ocean+Ltd&title=Ghushine+Fintrade+Ocean+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Alter+Memorandum+and+Articles+of+Association&newsId=002fc597-49c3-4b7d-9166-1811271518a4&token=MDAyZmM1OTctNDlj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">002fc597-49c3-4b7d-9166-1811271518a4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:31:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ghushine Fintrade Ocean Ltd has informed the BSE that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on 03/02/2026. The meeting will be held at the Registered Office of the Company in Surat, Gujarat, India. The agenda includes considering and approving alterations in the Main Object Clause of the Memorandum of Association and the Articles of Association of the Company. The Board will also transact any other incidental and ancillary matters as may be decided.</p><ul><li>Ghushine Fintrade Ocean Ltd scheduled a Board Meeting on 03/02/2026</li><li>The meeting will be held at the Registered Office in Surat, Gujarat, India</li><li>The agenda includes alterations in the Main Object Clause of the Memorandum of Association</li><li>The Articles of Association will also be altered and a new set will be adopted</li><li>The Board will transact any other incidental and ancillary matters as may be decided</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/61c8e0ef-3e2b-4cb9-9fc8-8e11a21689ad.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ghushine Fintrrade Ocean Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SKFINDIA] SKF India Ltd. to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on Feb 5, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SKF+India+Ltd&title=SKF+India+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+Feb+5%2C+2026&newsId=46d420ee-bcb1-497f-aaee-c5be11a7a069&token=NDZkNDIwZWUtYmNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">46d420ee-bcb1-497f-aaee-c5be11a7a069</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SKF India Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 5, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results (standalone and consolidated) for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in shares of the company by Directors, Promoters, Designated Persons, and Immediate Relatives of Directors, Promoters, Designated Persons is closed from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of financial results.</p><ul><li>SKF India Ltd. to consider and approve unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Trading window for dealing in shares of the company by insiders is closed from January 1, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ce1959fc-8313-4f6f-8fad-32e40e423407.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SKF India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FORCEMOT] Force Motors Ltd. Appoints Lt. Gen. Vinod Gulabrao Khandare (Retd.) as Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=FORCE+MOTORS+LTD.-%24&title=Force+Motors+Ltd.+Appoints+Lt.+Gen.+Vinod+Gulabrao+Khandare+%28Retd.%29+as+Independent+Director&newsId=b1a6a1fb-8ab6-4a85-87d1-0aad3aa554ae&token=YjFhNmExZmItOGFi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b1a6a1fb-8ab6-4a85-87d1-0aad3aa554ae</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Force Motors Ltd. has appointed Lt. Gen. Vinod Gulabrao Khandare (Retd.) as an Additional Director to be designated as an Independent Director, with effect from 29th January, 2026. His first term of appointment will be for a period of 5 years, subject to the approval of shareholders. Khandare is a retired Indian Army Officer with nearly four decades of experience in handling military affairs. He has held crucial positions in the Department of Ministry of Defence and has been awarded several prestigious medals for his distinguished service.</p><ul><li>Force Motors Ltd. appoints Lt. Gen. Vinod Gulabrao Khandare (Retd.) as Independent Director</li><li>Khandare&apos;s first term of appointment is for 5 years, subject to shareholders&apos; approval</li><li>Khandare is a retired Indian Army Officer with extensive experience in military affairs</li><li>He has held significant positions in the Department of Ministry of Defence</li><li>Khandare has been awarded several prestigious medals for his distinguished service</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d9f7d931-f4ac-417c-8190-a87b7cffba97.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: FORCE MOTORS LTD.-$ | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ROUTE] Route Mobile Ltd Announces De-registration of Step-down Subsidiary Route SMS Solutions Zambia Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Route+Mobile+Ltd&title=Route+Mobile+Ltd+Announces+De-registration+of+Step-down+Subsidiary+Route+SMS+Solutions+Zambia+Limited&newsId=bad6b0eb-cb60-4929-92a8-03fbef0b9f15&token=YmFkNmIwZWItY2I2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bad6b0eb-cb60-4929-92a8-03fbef0b9f15</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:24:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Route Mobile Ltd has announced the voluntary de-registration of its step-down wholly owned subsidiary, Route SMS Solutions Zambia Limited, with effect from January 06, 2026. The Company received the intimation of deregistration via email on January 29, 2026. Route SMS Solutions Zambia Limited had not commenced any business or conducted any operations, transactions or activities since its incorporation, and hence, there is no turnover, revenue, income, and net worth. The de-registration is not part of a related party transaction and is not done under a Scheme of Arrangement.</p><ul><li>Route Mobile Ltd announces de-registration of Route SMS Solutions Zambia Limited.</li><li>Route SMS Solutions Zambia Limited was a step-down wholly owned subsidiary of Route Mobile (UK) Limited and Route Mobile Limited.</li><li>The de-registration is effective from January 06, 2026.</li><li>Route SMS Solutions Zambia Limited had not commenced any business or conducted any operations, transactions or activities since its incorporation.</li><li>The de-registration is not part of a related party transaction and is not done under a Scheme of Arrangement.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0a6af053-742a-4e84-bd01-7d57e1d1beb5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Route Mobile Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FORCEMOT] Force Motors Ltd. Appoints Retd. Lt. Gen. Vinod Gulabrao Khandare as Additional Independent Director for 5 Years</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=FORCE+MOTORS+LTD.-%24&title=Force+Motors+Ltd.+Appoints+Retd.+Lt.+Gen.+Vinod+Gulabrao+Khandare+as+Additional+Independent+Director+for+5+Years&newsId=57a5ed7e-937f-49d6-a6ee-dab8a59a9c20&token=NTdhNWVkN2UtOTM3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57a5ed7e-937f-49d6-a6ee-dab8a59a9c20</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:24:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Force Motors Ltd. has appointed Retd. Lt. Gen. Vinod Gulabrao Khandare as an Additional Director who will be designated as an Independent Director for a first term of 5 years, effective from 29th January, 2026. This appointment is subject to the approval of shareholders. Khandare is a retired Indian Army Officer with extensive experience in military affairs and has held crucial positions in the Department of Ministry of Defence. He has been awarded several prestigious medals for his distinguished service.</p><ul><li>Force Motors Ltd. appoints Retd. Lt. Gen. Vinod Gulabrao Khandare as Additional Director</li><li>Khandare to be designated as Independent Director for a first term of 5 years</li><li>Appointment effective from 29th January, 2026</li><li>Khandare is a retired Indian Army Officer with vast experience in military affairs</li><li>Khandare has held crucial positions in the Department of Ministry of Defence and has been awarded several prestigious medals</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6c0e6750-b4e3-4837-bc6f-2cca7c6d194b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: FORCE MOTORS LTD.-$ | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DAAWAT] LT Foods Ltd Withdraws Proposed Acquisition of Global Green Group Due to Rejection by Hungarian Ministry</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LT+FOODS+LTD.&title=LT+Foods+Ltd+Withdraws+Proposed+Acquisition+of+Global+Green+Group+Due+to+Rejection+by+Hungarian+Ministry&newsId=ee63abb1-aba5-466e-9bc4-fab657c2117b&token=ZWU2M2FiYjEtYWJh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee63abb1-aba5-466e-9bc4-fab657c2117b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:24:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>LT Foods Ltd has announced the withdrawal of its proposed acquisition of the Global Green Group. The decision to withdraw the acquisition was made following the rejection of the proposed transaction by the Ministry of National Economy, Hungary. The rejection was based on identified national economic and sectoral risks. The Company had earlier proposed and approved the acquisition of the Global Green Group, which comprised Global Green Europe Kft., Greenhouse AGRAR Kft., and Global Green International (UK) Limited. The proposed transaction was to be taken forward, but with the rejection, the Company has decided to withdraw it.</p><ul><li>LT Foods Ltd withdraws proposed acquisition of Global Green Group</li><li>Withdrawal due to rejection by Hungarian Ministry</li><li>Rejection based on identified national economic and sectoral risks</li><li>Acquisition proposal included Global Green Europe Kft., Greenhouse AGRAR Kft., and Global Green International (UK) Limited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0928d00c-56d4-4632-b1b5-d5cb080d7125.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LT FOODS LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SANGHIIND] Sanghi Industries Appoints Rohit Soni as Additional Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SANGHI+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Sanghi+Industries+Appoints+Rohit+Soni+as+Additional+Director&newsId=77834295-b047-4d6f-9dd3-0a6afd1eac9d&token=Nzc4MzQyOTUtYjA0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77834295-b047-4d6f-9dd3-0a6afd1eac9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:21:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sanghi Industries Ltd has appointed Mr. Rohit Soni as an Additional Director (Non-Executive and Non-Independent) with effect from January 31, 2026. Mr. Soni is a distinguished finance leader, holding a Chartered Accountant degree and an alumnus of Harvard Business School’s General Management Program. He currently serves as Chief Financial Officer of Cement business. Previously, he served as Chief Financial Officer (CFO) at Adani New Industries Limited (ANIL) and Adani Energy Solutions Limited (AESL), where he led financial strategies and managed finances for numerous subsidiaries. He has also held several leadership positions with the Vedanta Group. His leadership excellence has been recognized with the ET Great Manager (Senior Leader) award by Economic Times and TAPMI in November 2019.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Rohit Soni as Additional Director</li><li>Mr. Soni is a distinguished finance leader and Chartered Accountant</li><li>Currently serves as Chief Financial Officer of Cement business</li><li>Previous experience includes CFO roles at Adani New Industries Limited and Adani Energy Solutions Limited</li><li>Has held several leadership positions with the Vedanta Group</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/03976b8e-3c5b-4cf5-9729-e62aebbabc06.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SANGHI INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SODHACAP] Sodhani Capital Ltd. Appointed as Sub-broker/Authorised Person of Prabhudas Lilladher Private Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sodhani+Capital+Ltd&title=Sodhani+Capital+Ltd.+Appointed+as+Sub-broker%2FAuthorised+Person+of+Prabhudas+Lilladher+Private+Limited&newsId=379c4c43-cc23-4b40-9b00-a0c041ea88c1&token=Mzc5YzRjNDMtY2My</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">379c4c43-cc23-4b40-9b00-a0c041ea88c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sodhani Capital Ltd. has been appointed as a Sub-broker/Authorised Person of Prabhudas Lilladher Private Limited, a SEBI registered stock broker. The company has received approval from the National Stock Exchange of India Limited (NSE) and has been authorized to commence operations in the securities market in the Capital Market (CM), Futures &amp; Options (FO), and Currency Derivatives (CD) segments. Approvals from other exchanges, including BSE Limited (BSE) and Multi Commodity Exchange of India Limited (MCX), are expected shortly. This appointment will enable the company to carry on its business operations in accordance with the approvals granted and the regulatory framework prescribed by the respective Stock Exchanges and SEBI.</p><ul><li>Sodhani Capital Ltd. appointed as a Sub-broker/Authorised Person of Prabhudas Lilladher Private Limited</li><li>Received approval from the National Stock Exchange of India Limited (NSE)</li><li>Authorized to commence operations in the Capital Market (CM), Futures &amp; Options (FO), and Currency Derivatives (CD) segments</li><li>Approvals from BSE Limited (BSE) and Multi Commodity Exchange of India Limited (MCX) expected shortly</li><li>Business operations to be carried out in accordance with the approvals granted and the regulatory framework prescribed by the respective Stock Exchanges and SEBI</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2c09e352-1c62-4c18-9275-dcdc9cacebdc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sodhani Capital Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHARDUL] Shardul Securities Ltd. Approves Q3 Results and Announces Independent Director&apos;s Tenure Completion</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHARDUL+SECURITIES+LTD.&title=Shardul+Securities+Ltd.+Approves+Q3+Results+and+Announces+Independent+Director%27s+Tenure+Completion&newsId=c5b8d418-d3cd-42e7-87aa-8de61b1d1397&token=YzViOGQ0MTgtZDNj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5b8d418-d3cd-42e7-87aa-8de61b1d1397</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shardul Securities Ltd. announced the approval of its un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at Rs. 1,981.18 crore for the quarter and Rs. 3,981.17 crore for the nine-month period. The profit before tax is Rs. (979.51) crore for the quarter. The Board also noted the completion of Mr. Devesh Vasavada&apos;s tenure as an Independent Director, who will cease to be a member of various committees and the chairman of the Audit committee, Nomination and Remuneration Committee, and Corporate Social Responsibility Committee.</p><ul><li>Shardul Securities Ltd. approves Q3 results with a revenue from operations of Rs. 1,981.18 crore.</li><li>The company reports a profit before tax of Rs. (979.51) crore for the quarter.</li><li>Independent Director, Mr. Devesh Vasavada, completes his tenure with the company.</li><li>Mr. Vasavada will cease to be a member of various committees and the chairman of the Audit committee, Nomination and Remuneration Committee, and Corporate Social Responsibility Committee.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bc07219f-7d50-4958-8cd0-3aabe48f6214.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHARDUL SECURITIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PAYTM*] One 97 Communications Ltd: Q4 2025 Monitoring Agency Report Submitted by Axis Bank Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=One+97+Communications+Ltd&title=One+97+Communications+Ltd%3A+Q4+2025+Monitoring+Agency+Report+Submitted+by+Axis+Bank+Limited&newsId=a9e2ca37-9a6d-4538-bc18-c4535f3277e6&token=YTllMmNhMzctOWE2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a9e2ca37-9a6d-4538-bc18-c4535f3277e6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 15:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Monitoring Agency Report for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, for One 97 Communications Ltd, has been submitted by Axis Bank Limited. The report indicates no deviation from the objects and no range of deviation. The company has utilized the funds as per the disclosure in the Offer Document and has obtained all necessary Government/Statutory approvals related to the object(s). The report also provides details of the objects to be monitored, including marketing and promotional expenses, expanding merchant base, strengthening technology powered payments platform, investing in new business initiatives, acquisitions and strategic partnerships, and general corporate purpose.</p><ul><li>No deviation from the objects</li><li>No range of deviation</li><li>Funds utilized as per the disclosure in the Offer Document</li><li>All necessary Government/Statutory approvals obtained</li><li>Detailed report on the utilization of funds</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0cc00bae-9296-46a4-815c-b373f658fcd2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: One 97 Communications Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>