<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:38:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SAATVIKGL] Saatvik Green Energy Invests ₹ 251.60 Crores in Wholly Owned Subsidiary Saatvik Solar Industries Private Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Saatvik+Green+Energy+Ltd&title=Saatvik+Green+Energy+Invests+%E2%82%B9+251.60+Crores+in+Wholly+Owned+Subsidiary+Saatvik+Solar+Industries+Private+Limited&newsId=9fa4a2a3-2ecd-41b9-9403-a20ffa55269c&token=OWZhNGEyYTMtMmVj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9fa4a2a3-2ecd-41b9-9403-a20ffa55269c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Saatvik Green Energy Ltd has made a further investment in its wholly owned subsidiary, Saatvik Solar Industries Private Limited (SSIPL), through a rights issue basis. The investment, amounting to ₹ 251.60 crores, is a part of the proceeds from the Initial Public Offer for setting up a 4 GW solar PV module manufacturing facility in Odisha. SSIPL, which had a turnover of ₹ 11,852.52 millions in FY 2025, is in the business of manufacture, trading, distribution, import, export, erection, installation, operation of solar plants, solar units in Indian or abroad. This investment will not change the percentage and/or number of shares acquired by Saatvik Green Energy in SSIPL, which will continue to remain a wholly owned subsidiary of the Company.</p><ul><li>Saatvik Green Energy invests ₹ 251.60 crores in its wholly owned subsidiary, Saatvik Solar Industries Private Limited.</li><li>The investment is a part of the proceeds from the Initial Public Offer for setting up a 4 GW solar PV module manufacturing facility in Odisha.</li><li>Saatvik Solar Industries Private Limited had a turnover of ₹ 11,852.52 millions in FY 2025.</li><li>The investment will not change the percentage and/or number of shares acquired by Saatvik Green Energy in SSIPL.</li><li>SSIPL is in the business of manufacture, trading, distribution, import, export, erection, installation, operation of solar plants, solar units in Indian or abroad.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/02f8d0b5-380c-4687-9cde-febc1b0aa6c1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Saatvik Green Energy Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SARLAPOLY] Sarla Performance Fibers Ltd. Acquires Commercial Premises in Suraj One Business Bay for Rs. 27.89 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SARLA+PERFORMANCE+FIBERS+LTD.-%24&title=Sarla+Performance+Fibers+Ltd.+Acquires+Commercial+Premises+in+Suraj+One+Business+Bay+for+Rs.+27.89+Crores&newsId=a17b7433-b798-4f3d-9765-378ba1fd0647&token=YTE3Yjc0MzMtYjc5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a17b7433-b798-4f3d-9765-378ba1fd0647</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:27:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Sarla Performance Fibers Ltd. has approved and ratified the investment made towards the acquisition of commercial premises in the project &apos;Suraj One Business Bay&apos;. The company has acquired four commercial units with a total RERA carpet area of 5,432 sq. ft. for a total consideration of Rs. 27,88,65,748. The acquisition is expected to be completed by December 31, 2031.</p><ul><li>Acquisition of commercial premises in Suraj One Business Bay for Rs. 27.89 Crores</li><li>Four commercial units with a total RERA carpet area of 5,432 sq. ft.</li><li>Acquisition from a third-party developer, not a related party transaction</li><li>Expected completion by December 31, 2031</li><li>Additional office space for expansion of business operations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/734e6fe3-b01b-45ee-ae3f-4387384fef31.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SARLA PERFORMANCE FIBERS LTD.-$ | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IKS] Inventurus Knowledge Solutions Ltd Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Inventurus+Knowledge+Solutions+Ltd&title=Inventurus+Knowledge+Solutions+Ltd+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025&newsId=f08e5a9b-3283-4233-874b-12e5290e770d&token=ZjA4ZTVhOWItMzI4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f08e5a9b-3283-4233-874b-12e5290e770d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Inventurus Knowledge Solutions Ltd has announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The Board of Directors approved the financial results in a meeting held on February 4, 2026. The review report by Price Waterhouse Chartered Accountants LLP, the statutory auditors, is also enclosed.</p><ul><li>Unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025 approved by the Board of Directors.</li><li>Review report submitted by Price Waterhouse Chartered Accountants LLP, the statutory auditors.</li><li>The Board Meeting commenced at 06:45 P.M. IST and concluded at 07:43 P.M. IST.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c807763b-8355-45a8-aa98-9b663ca09a6d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Inventurus Knowledge Solutions Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JSWCEMENT] JSW Cement Ltd: Board Approves Issuance of Corporate Guarantee, Unaudited Q3 Results, and Re-appointment of Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JSW+Cement+Ltd&title=JSW+Cement+Ltd%3A+Board+Approves+Issuance+of+Corporate+Guarantee%2C+Unaudited+Q3+Results%2C+and+Re-appointment+of+Directors&newsId=0c21223b-2216-42e0-9a3c-98dcbfa55d0a&token=MGMyMTIyM2ItMjIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c21223b-2216-42e0-9a3c-98dcbfa55d0a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:24:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>JSW Cement Ltd&apos;s board of directors approved the issuance of a corporate guarantee, considered and approved unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025, and re-appointed Mr. Parth Jindal as Managing Director and Mr. Pankaj Kulkarni as an Independent Director. The company also proposed to incorporate a wholly-owned subsidiary in Fujairah, UAE, to set up a cement grinding unit. The capital expenditure for the unit is approximately USD 39.00 Million, which will be funded through a mix of debt and equity. A corporate guarantee of up to USD 29.25 million will be given in favor of a bank or financial institution for sanction of a foreign currency term loan to the proposed subsidiary.</p><ul><li>Issuance of Corporate Guarantee up to USD 29.25 million</li><li>Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 2025</li><li>Re-appointment of Mr. Parth Jindal as Managing Director</li><li>Re-appointment of Mr. Pankaj Kulkarni as Independent Director</li><li>Proposed Incorporation of Wholly Owned Subsidiary in Fujairah, UAE</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6b790762-57d0-4954-9eb1-97861fbb195e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JSW Cement Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JSWCEMENT] JSW Cement Ltd. Announces Q4 Results, Re-Appoints MD &amp; Director, and Plans Wholly Owned Subsidiary in Fujairah, UAE</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JSW+Cement+Ltd&title=JSW+Cement+Ltd.+Announces+Q4+Results%2C+Re-Appoints+MD+%26+Director%2C+and+Plans+Wholly+Owned+Subsidiary+in+Fujairah%2C+UAE&newsId=81ba6068-00de-42f2-8b5c-5f1291368fb7&token=ODFiYTYwNjgtMDBk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">81ba6068-00de-42f2-8b5c-5f1291368fb7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>JSW Cement Ltd. announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s Board of Directors has re-appointed Mr. Parth Jindal as the Managing Director and Mr. Pankaj Kulkarni as an Independent Director for another term. Additionally, the Board has approved the incorporation of a wholly owned subsidiary in Fujairah, UAE, to set up a Cement Grinding Unit with a capacity of 1.65 million tonnes per annum. The capital expenditure for this project is approximately USD 39.00 Million, which will be funded through a mix of debt and equity. The company will also issue a corporate guarantee of up to USD 29.25 million for the subsidiary&apos;s foreign currency term loan.</p><ul><li>JSW Cement announced Q4 results for the period ending 31st December 2025</li><li>Re-appointment of Mr. Parth Jindal as Managing Director and Mr. Pankaj Kulkarni as an Independent Director</li><li>Plans to incorporate a wholly owned subsidiary in Fujairah, UAE for a Cement Grinding Unit</li><li>Capital expenditure of approximately USD 39.00 Million for the project</li><li>Corporate guarantee of up to USD 29.25 million for the subsidiary&apos;s foreign currency term loan</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b8888026-aa51-4640-8037-2b1972ff24b8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JSW Cement Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FORCEMOT] Force Motors Explores Acquiring Veera Tanneries Private Limited for Chrome Free Organic Leather Production</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=FORCE+MOTORS+LTD.-%24&title=Force+Motors+Explores+Acquiring+Veera+Tanneries+Private+Limited+for+Chrome+Free+Organic+Leather+Production&newsId=2f95f898-25bb-4029-9f68-78f5cef4795e&token=MmY5NWY4OTgtMjVi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2f95f898-25bb-4029-9f68-78f5cef4795e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:22:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Force Motors Ltd. has announced its intention to explore the possibility of acquiring 100% shares in Veera Tanneries Private Limited (VTPL), a private limited company involved in the tannery business of manufacturing Chrome Free Organic Leather. The Board of Directors held a meeting on 4th February 2026 and gave initial approval, subject to mutually agreeable terms and conditions. The acquisition is expected to be completed before 31st March 2026, with the proposed consideration to be paid in cash. VTPL, incorporated on 19th August 1978, has a history of increasing turnovers for the last three financial years. The acquisition is aimed at expanding Force Motors&apos; current business and obtaining VTPL&apos;s land bank.</p><ul><li>Force Motors to explore acquiring 100% shares in Veera Tanneries Private Limited</li><li>VTPL is involved in the tannery business of manufacturing Chrome Free Organic Leather</li><li>The acquisition is expected to be completed before 31st March 2026</li><li>Proposed consideration to be paid in cash</li><li>VTPL has a history of increasing turnovers for the last three financial years</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/208d2e09-d07e-4aa3-92f8-5d061b961905.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: FORCE MOTORS LTD.-$ | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LUPIN] Lupin Launches Topiramate Extended-Release Capsules in the United States</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LUPIN+LTD.&title=Lupin+Launches+Topiramate+Extended-Release+Capsules+in+the+United+States&newsId=6a9a9997-9a3a-4911-b729-4577b06c35b6&token=NmE5YTk5OTctOWEz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a9a9997-9a3a-4911-b729-4577b06c35b6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Global pharma major Lupin Limited has announced the launch of Topiramate Extended-Release Capsules in the United States. The product is bioequivalent to the reference listed drug Trokendi XR® Extended-Release Capsules of Supernus Pharmaceuticals, Inc. The capsules are indicated for the treatment of partial-onset or primary generalized tonic-clonic seizures in patients 6 years of age and older, as adjunctive therapy for the treatment of partial-onset seizures, primary generalized tonic-clonic seizures, and seizures associated with Lennox-Gastaut syndrome in patients 6 years of age and older, and for the preventive treatment of migraine in patients 12 years of age and older. The estimated annual sale of this product in the U.S. is USD 164 million.</p><ul><li>Lupin Limited launches Topiramate Extended-Release Capsules in the United States.</li><li>The product is bioequivalent to Supernus Pharmaceuticals, Inc.&apos;s Trokendi XR® Extended-Release Capsules.</li><li>Indicated for the treatment of various types of seizures and migraine prevention in different age groups.</li><li>Estimated annual sale of USD 164 million in the U.S.</li><li>Lupin Limited is a global pharmaceutical leader with products in over 100 markets.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/073347d8-af42-48ec-9b1c-02ae7208b592.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LUPIN LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CUMMINSIND] Cummins India Declares Interim Dividend of Rs. 20/- per Share for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CUMMINS+INDIA+LTD.&title=Cummins+India+Declares+Interim+Dividend+of+Rs.+20%2F-+per+Share+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=71261e52-f574-42fc-8bb7-f5e364755717&token=NzEyNjFlNTItZjU3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71261e52-f574-42fc-8bb7-f5e364755717</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:21:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cummins India Ltd. announced its decision to distribute an interim dividend of Rs. 20/- per equity share for the Financial Year 2025-26. The record date for determining entitlement of members for the dividend is February 11, 2026. The company&apos;s Board of Directors also approved and declared the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</p><ul><li>Interim dividend of Rs. 20/- per equity share for FY 2025-26</li><li>Record date for dividend entitlement is February 11, 2026</li><li>Approval of unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9226d45d-4521-44cc-bec7-b630c9f60494.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CUMMINS INDIA LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JSWCEMENT] JSW Cement: No Deviation in Utilization of IPO Proceeds as per Crisil Ratings Monitoring Agency Report</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JSW+Cement+Ltd&title=JSW+Cement%3A+No+Deviation+in+Utilization+of+IPO+Proceeds+as+per+Crisil+Ratings+Monitoring+Agency+Report&newsId=cc7294a3-0cc7-4433-b765-a4241e65ef10&token=Y2M3Mjk0YTMtMGNj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cc7294a3-0cc7-4433-b765-a4241e65ef10</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>JSW Cement Ltd has utilized the proceeds of its Initial Public Offer (IPO) as per the objects stated in the Prospectus, according to the Monitoring Agency Report issued by Crisil Ratings Limited for the quarter ended 31st December, 2025. The report was reviewed and taken on record by the Board of Directors and the Audit Committee of the Company on 4th February, 2026.</p><ul><li>JSW Cement Ltd has utilized the IPO proceeds as per the objects stated in the Prospectus.</li><li>The Monitoring Agency Report was issued by Crisil Ratings Limited for the quarter ended 31st December, 2025.</li><li>The report was reviewed and taken on record by the Board of Directors and the Audit Committee of the Company on 4th February, 2026.</li><li>Crisil Ratings Limited did not find any deviation in the utilization of the issue proceeds.</li><li>The report is in line with the format prescribed by SEBI.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8f8f8167-c764-4be3-b7c7-4795a79ab8de.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JSW Cement Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HEXT] Hexaware Technologies Ltd Announces Q4 &amp; FY2025 Audited Financial Results with Unmodified Opinion</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Hexaware+Technologies+Ltd&title=Hexaware+Technologies+Ltd+Announces+Q4+%26+FY2025+Audited+Financial+Results+with+Unmodified+Opinion&newsId=3931c44a-d116-4d36-af6f-6496cd83255e&token=MzkzMWM0NGEtZDEx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3931c44a-d116-4d36-af6f-6496cd83255e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:11:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hexaware Technologies Ltd has announced its audited financial results for the quarter and year ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s standalone and consolidated financial results have been approved by the Board of Directors. The audited financial results show a true and fair view in conformity with the recognition and measurement principles laid down in the applicable Indian Accounting Standards. The company has also approved amendments in Securities Dealing Code under SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2025.</p><ul><li>Hexaware Technologies Ltd announced its Q4 &amp; FY2025 audited financial results with unmodified opinion.</li><li>The company&apos;s standalone and consolidated financial results have been approved by the Board of Directors.</li><li>The audited financial results show a true and fair view in conformity with the applicable Indian Accounting Standards.</li><li>The company has also approved amendments in Securities Dealing Code under SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3b109b70-d9c1-4acd-964c-335c8187776a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Hexaware Technologies Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>