<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:24:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[BIRLACORPN] Birla Corporation Ltd Extends Services of Two Senior Management Personnels</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BIRLA+CORPORATION+LTD.&title=Birla+Corporation+Ltd+Extends+Services+of+Two+Senior+Management+Personnels&newsId=534e45f7-b927-4d0c-b349-b9a921feb1b7&token=NTM0ZTQ1ZjctYjky</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">534e45f7-b927-4d0c-b349-b9a921feb1b7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:23:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Birla Corporation Ltd has extended the term of services of Shri Kalidas Pramanik and Shri Rajesh Kakkar, both senior management personnels, for a further period of two years and one year respectively. The board of directors approved the extension in their meeting held on 31st January, 2026. The company also approved and released the Standalone and Consolidated Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025.</p><ul><li>Birla Corporation Ltd extends the term of services of Shri Kalidas Pramanik and Shri Rajesh Kakkar</li><li>Shri Kalidas Pramanik&apos;s term extended for two years, Shri Rajesh Kakkar&apos;s term extended for one year</li><li>The board of directors approved the extensions in their meeting held on 31st January, 2026</li><li>Company released the Standalone and Consolidated Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e8187cdf-4836-4a3d-a822-3d09d9cb0790.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BIRLA CORPORATION LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BDL] Bharat Dynamics Ltd Announces Unaudited Financial Results for Quarter &amp; Nine Months Ended 31 Dec 2025 &amp; Declares Interim Dividend</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Bharat+Dynamics+Ltd&title=Bharat+Dynamics+Ltd+Announces+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Quarter+%26+Nine+Months+Ended+31+Dec+2025+%26+Declares+Interim+Dividend&newsId=7c56c34c-a60a-4ad4-a503-2789cf139dec&token=N2M1NmMzNGMtYTYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c56c34c-a60a-4ad4-a503-2789cf139dec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:22:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bharat Dynamics Ltd has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31 Dec 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 56,663.04 lakh for the quarter and 1,14,702.80 lakh for the nine months ended 31 Dec 2025. The total income for the quarter is 66,380.29 lakh and 1,26,759.81 lakh for the nine months ended 31 Dec 2025. The company has declared an interim dividend of Rs 4.5 per share of the face value of Rs. 5/- each for the Financial Year 2025-26. The record date for the purpose of payment of interim dividend is 9 February, 2026.</p><ul><li>Unaudited financial results for quarter &amp; nine months ended 31 Dec 2025 announced</li><li>Revenue from operations stands at 56,663.04 lakh for the quarter</li><li>Total income for the quarter is 66,380.29 lakh</li><li>Interim dividend of Rs 4.5 per share declared for the Financial Year 2025-26</li><li>Record date for the purpose of payment of interim dividend is 9 February, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b2e87a77-8ad4-46e9-a919-390af3401333.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Bharat Dynamics Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SESHAPAPER] Seshasayee Paper and Boards Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SESHASAYEE+PAPER+%26+BOARDS+LTD.&title=Seshasayee+Paper+and+Boards+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025&newsId=8c79e44b-25cf-4cc6-924f-06364fab2b35&token=OGM3OWU0NGItMjVj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c79e44b-25cf-4cc6-924f-06364fab2b35</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Seshasayee Paper and Boards Ltd has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 386.81 crores for the quarter and 1118.39 crores for the nine months period. The net profit after tax for the quarter is 15.53 crores and 50.39 crores for the nine months period.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter is 386.81 crores</li><li>Revenue from operations for the nine months period is 1118.39 crores</li><li>Net profit after tax for the quarter is 15.53 crores</li><li>Net profit after tax for the nine months period is 50.39 crores</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/99a31755-4b7f-4fbb-8cfa-b2e59472bb9f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SESHASAYEE PAPER & BOARDS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NITINSPIN] Nitin Spinners Ltd. Approves Q3 and 9 Months Results for FY2025, Announces Solar Power Plant Agreement</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NITIN+SPINNERS+LTD.&title=Nitin+Spinners+Ltd.+Approves+Q3+and+9+Months+Results+for+FY2025%2C+Announces+Solar+Power+Plant+Agreement&newsId=ca55d7fa-c7f6-4139-b38d-887bc0f57025&token=Y2E1NWQ3ZmEtYzdm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ca55d7fa-c7f6-4139-b38d-887bc0f57025</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Nitin Spinners Ltd. has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 235,754.06 Lacs and 33,0925.00 Lacs respectively. The company also announced the execution of an agreement with LNB Renewable Energy Limited for setting up a 33 MW (AC)/49.50 MW (DC) Solar Power Plant at Village Chamu, District Jodhpur, Rajasthan. The project will be financed partly from internal accruals and partly from term loans.</p><ul><li>Nitin Spinners Ltd. announces Q3 and 9 months results for FY2025</li><li>Revenue from operations stands at 235,754.06 Lacs and 33,0925.00 Lacs respectively</li><li>Agreement with LNB Renewable Energy Limited for setting up a 33 MW (AC)/49.50 MW (DC) Solar Power Plant</li><li>Project to be financed partly from internal accruals and partly from term loans</li><li>Trading window to open from February 03, 2026 for Directors, Designated &amp; Connected Persons of the Company and their immediate relatives</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ceb666eb-0eda-48d5-9b35-fed95e639b99.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NITIN SPINNERS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JUSTO] Promoter Puspamitra Das Acquires 3,000 Shares of Justo Realfintech Ltd via Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Justo+Realfintech+Ltd&title=Promoter+Puspamitra+Das+Acquires+3%2C000+Shares+of+Justo+Realfintech+Ltd+via+Open+Market&newsId=df39883d-3be4-4358-b7cb-f11509b93bfa&token=ZGYzOTg4M2QtM2Jl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df39883d-3be4-4358-b7cb-f11509b93bfa</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:21:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Promoter Puspamitra Das has acquired 3,000 equity shares of Justo Realfintech Ltd through the open market. This acquisition increases his holding to 38.45% of the total voting rights. The shares were acquired on 30th January 2026. This acquisition is in line with the SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011 and has been disclosed to the stock exchange.</p><ul><li>Promoter Puspamitra Das acquires 3,000 shares of Justo Realfintech Ltd</li><li>Shares acquired through open market</li><li>Acquisition increases holding to 38.45% of total voting rights</li><li>Acquisition date: 30th January 2026</li><li>In line with SEBI regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7640BAEE_9B6A_4F11_A134_E20BFA5273AA_144109.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Justo Realfintech Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PDMJEPAPER] Pudumjee Paper Products Ltd Reports Total Income of Rs.630 Crores for Nine Months Ended 31st December, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Pudumjee+Paper+Products+Ltd&title=Pudumjee+Paper+Products+Ltd+Reports+Total+Income+of+Rs.630+Crores+for+Nine+Months+Ended+31st+December%2C+2025&newsId=feaf88ee-a02f-409a-ac0d-32367af12dbf&token=ZmVhZjg4ZWUtYTAy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">feaf88ee-a02f-409a-ac0d-32367af12dbf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Pudumjee Paper Products Ltd, on Saturday, reported Total Income at Rs.630 Crores for the nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The EBIDTA stood at 18% at Rs.112 Crores. The Company has successfully commissioned a 15.4 MWac Solar Power Plant in Solapur District, Maharashtra. The new Boiler commissioning is awaiting statutory approval. The Company is focusing on manufacturing various Biodegradable and Compostable Specialty Papers for sustainable packaging solutions.</p><ul><li>Total Income of Rs.630 Crores for the nine months ended 31st December, 2025</li><li>EBIDTA at 18% at Rs.112 Crores</li><li>Commissioned a 15.4 MWac Solar Power Plant</li><li>Awaiting statutory approval for new Boiler commissioning</li><li>Focusing on manufacturing Biodegradable and Compostable Specialty Papers</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8b143c60-6662-4f9d-885a-555ac3a57667.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Pudumjee Paper Products Ltd | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KALPATARU] Kalpataru Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025 and Consider Fund Raising</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kalpataru+Ltd&title=Kalpataru+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025+and+Consider+Fund+Raising&newsId=d1f92261-0e62-4208-a4e9-af1dc9c00609&token=ZDFmOTIyNjEtMGU2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d1f92261-0e62-4208-a4e9-af1dc9c00609</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kalpataru Ltd has announced a Board of Directors meeting on February 06, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company also plans to consider raising funds through the issuance of Non-Convertible Debentures on a private placement basis. The trading window for dealing in securities of the company has been closed from January 01, 2026, and will remain closed for 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results.</p><ul><li>Kalpataru Ltd to approve Q3 and nine months results for 2025</li><li>Company to consider fund raising through Non-Convertible Debentures</li><li>Trading window closed from January 01, 2026, to 48 hours after result declaration</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0688153a-2091-475b-b4bc-28480fd4b837.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kalpataru Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NGIL] Nakoda Group of Industries Ltd to Approve Q4 2025 Financial Results on Feb 9, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Nakoda+Group+of+Industries+Ltd&title=Nakoda+Group+of+Industries+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+2025+Financial+Results+on+Feb+9%2C+2026&newsId=79f639fc-8d94-4c44-9350-d7470bc136e6&token=NzlmNjM5ZmMtOGQ5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79f639fc-8d94-4c44-9350-d7470bc136e6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Nakoda Group Of Industries Ltd has informed BSE that the meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on 09/02/2026 to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended on 31st December, 2025. The meeting will also discuss the late submission of the standalone limited review report identified by the Stock Exchange and the action taken by the Exchange. The &apos;Trading Window&apos; of the Company will remain closed till 48 hours after the declaration of Un-Audited Financial Results of the company for the Quarter Ended on 31st December, 2025.</p><ul><li>Nakoda Group of Industries Ltd to approve Q4 2025 financial results on Feb 9, 2026</li><li>Meeting scheduled to discuss unaudited financial results for the quarter ended on 31st December, 2025</li><li>Discussion on late submission of standalone limited review report identified by the Stock Exchange</li><li>Consideration of comments of the Board on the late submission of the report</li><li>Trading Window of the Company to remain closed till 48 hours after the declaration of Un-Audited Financial Results of the company for the Quarter Ended on 31st December, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9eac7e20-c1fa-47f0-a925-dede73adb3df.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Nakoda Group of Industries Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADVENZYMES] Advanced Enzyme Technologies Ltd Reverses $159.64 Million Provision in Lawsuit Case</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Advanced+Enzyme+Technologies+Ltd&title=Advanced+Enzyme+Technologies+Ltd+Reverses+%24159.64+Million+Provision+in+Lawsuit+Case&newsId=47fa602a-02b4-4c95-aa23-c7776483600d&token=NDdmYTYwMmEtMDJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47fa602a-02b4-4c95-aa23-c7776483600d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Advanced Enzyme Technologies Ltd has reversed a provision of $159.64 million in respect of a lawsuit filed by World Nutrition Inc. against its step-down wholly owned subsidiary, Advanced Supplementary Technologies Corporation, USA. This decision comes after the United States Court of Appeals for the Ninth Circuit&apos;s decision on the appeal and a recent confirmation from the legal attorney. The reversal was noted in the Audit Committee&apos;s meeting and the un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025 were approved by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Advanced Enzyme Technologies Ltd reverses $159.64 million provision in lawsuit case</li><li>The lawsuit was filed by World Nutrition Inc. against Advanced Supplementary Technologies Corporation, USA</li><li>The decision is based on the United States Court of Appeals for the Ninth Circuit&apos;s decision on the appeal</li><li>The reversal was noted in the Audit Committee&apos;s meeting</li><li>The un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025 were approved by the Board of Directors</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5e177715-38ba-40f8-9618-95359ebde96b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Advanced Enzyme Technologies Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MADHUVEER] Madhuveer Com 18 Network Ltd Receives Approval for Name Change to JOJO LIMITED</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Madhuveer+Com+18+Network+Ltd&title=Madhuveer+Com+18+Network+Ltd+Receives+Approval+for+Name+Change+to+JOJO+LIMITED&newsId=fdc78344-14b6-426d-b3d3-affd8b08bdc9&token=ZmRjNzgzNDQtMTRi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fdc78344-14b6-426d-b3d3-affd8b08bdc9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 09:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Madhuveer Com 18 Network Ltd has received approval from the Ministry of Corporate Affairs (MCA) for the proposed change of its name to JOJO LIMITED. The new name was approved on 31st January 2026 and is valid for 60 days from the date of approval. The company plans to obtain shareholder approval via postal ballot and complete the necessary steps to effect the name change, including approvals from stock exchanges and other regulatory authorities.</p><ul><li>Madhuveer Com 18 Network Ltd has received approval from MCA to change its name to JOJO LIMITED</li><li>The new name is approved for a period of 60 days from the date of approval</li><li>The company plans to obtain shareholder approval via postal ballot</li><li>The name change process includes obtaining approvals from stock exchanges and other regulatory authorities</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cd449abb-4007-4569-84d3-ca90e41d4a45.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Madhuveer Com 18 Network Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>