<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:37:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[MAHEPC] Mahindra EPC Irrigation Ltd Re-Appoints Mr. K N Vaidyanathan as Internal Auditor, Reports Q3 and Nine Months Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Mahindra+EPC+Irrigation+Ltd&title=Mahindra+EPC+Irrigation+Ltd+Re-Appoints+Mr.+K+N+Vaidyanathan+as+Internal+Auditor%2C+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results&newsId=56b673e3-b3b8-42a0-bbfb-e2587434fa0c&token=NTZiNjczZTMtYjNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56b673e3-b3b8-42a0-bbfb-e2587434fa0c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:34:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mahindra EPC Irrigation Ltd has announced the re-appointment of Mr. K N Vaidyanathan as an Internal Auditor up to 5th May, 2026. The company also released its un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December, 2025. The Board of Directors approved these results in a meeting held on 16th January, 2026. The company has estimated an incremental impact of Rs 2 crore on retiral benefits due to the new Labour Codes notified by the Government of India.</p><ul><li>Re-appointment of Mr. K N Vaidyanathan as Internal Auditor</li><li>Release of un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 and nine months of FY2025-2026</li><li>Approval of financial results by the Board of Directors</li><li>Estimated impact of Rs 2 crore on retiral benefits due to new Labour Codes</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/226da693-13cc-4ca9-9382-a6830b99a193.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Mahindra EPC Irrigation Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PAGEIND] Page Industries Ltd May Declare 3rd Interim Dividend for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PAGE+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Page+Industries+Ltd+May+Declare+3rd+Interim+Dividend+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=5908151a-1e87-4038-a153-20594aff0b74&token=NTkwODE1MWEtMWU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5908151a-1e87-4038-a153-20594aff0b74</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:27:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Page Industries Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 5 February 2026 to consider the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended 31 December 2025 and to consider the declaration of the 3rd interim dividend for the current financial year 2025-26. The record date for the payment of the interim dividend, if declared, will be 11 February 2026. The company will also hold investors/analyst calls on 5 February 2026 at 4.00 PM IST to discuss the financial results for the Quarter ending 31 December 2025.</p><ul><li>Page Industries Ltd Board to meet on 5 February 2026 to consider unaudited financial results for Q3 FY 2025-26</li><li>Board to consider declaration of 3rd interim dividend for FY 2025-26</li><li>If declared, the record date for the payment of the interim dividend will be 11 February 2026</li><li>Company to hold investors/analyst calls on 5 February 2026 at 4.00 PM IST to discuss the financial results for Q3 FY 2025-26</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a748cadd-a98b-4724-9865-8ae3158a53ac.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PAGE INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BLUEDART] Blue Dart Express Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025 on Jan 30, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BLUE+DART+EXPRESS+LTD.&title=Blue+Dart+Express+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025+on+Jan+30%2C+2026&newsId=4241d7d7-ca9e-437b-bfbd-eeea8b9487ae&token=NDI0MWQ3ZDctY2E5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4241d7d7-ca9e-437b-bfbd-eeea8b9487ae</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:26:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Blue Dart Express Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 30, 2026, to consider and approve the Un-Audited Financial Results (Standalone &amp; Consolidated) for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting is in accordance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations &amp; Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, as amended. The Trading Window would remain closed from January 01, 2026, to February 2, 2026, as per the Code of Conduct for Prevention of Insider Trading in Securities of Blue Dart Express Limited.</p><ul><li>Blue Dart Express Ltd to consider and approve Un-Audited Financial Results for quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The meeting is scheduled on January 30, 2026, in accordance with Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations &amp; Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, as amended.</li><li>Trading Window to remain closed from January 01, 2026, to February 2, 2026, as per the Code of Conduct for Prevention of Insider Trading in Securities of Blue Dart Express Limited.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b00ee80c-b296-4c7a-a059-85be79b03dca.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BLUE DART EXPRESS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ABHICAP] Abhinav Capital Services Ltd Re-Appoints Mr. Nasir Shaikh as Independent Director for Second Term</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ABHINAV+CAPITAL+SERVICES+LTD.&title=Abhinav+Capital+Services+Ltd+Re-Appoints+Mr.+Nasir+Shaikh+as+Independent+Director+for+Second+Term&newsId=5a735325-5523-45e7-bc56-c178cda6ce9c&token=NWE3MzUzMjUtNTUy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a735325-5523-45e7-bc56-c178cda6ce9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:24:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Abhinav Capital Services Ltd has announced the re-appointment of Mr. Nasir Shaikh as an Independent Director (Non-Executive) for a second term of 5 consecutive years. The re-appointment is subject to the approval of the members of the Company by way of a Special Resolution at the ensuing General Meeting. Mr. Shaikh is a Chartered Accountant with 9 years of experience in Direct Taxation, Audit, Accounting, Planning &amp; executing Financial statements &amp; Compliance related to various statutory regulations.</p><ul><li>Re-Appointment of Mr. Nasir Shaikh as Independent Director for a second term of 5 consecutive years</li><li>Re-Appointment is subject to the approval of the members of the Company by way of a Special Resolution at the ensuing General Meeting</li><li>Mr. Shaikh is a Chartered Accountant with 9 years of experience in Direct Taxation, Audit, Accounting, Planning &amp; executing Financial statements &amp; Compliance related to various statutory regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7926b84e-5ee3-4822-aafd-7618f1db1079.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ABHINAV CAPITAL SERVICES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CONTCHM] Continental Chemicals Ltd: December 2025 Special Window Transfer Status</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CONTINENTAL+CHEMICALS+LTD.&title=Continental+Chemicals+Ltd%3A+December+2025+Special+Window+Transfer+Status&newsId=3ac001bd-8774-4f0c-ad90-cb85c534e0a4&token=M2FjMDAxYmQtODc3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ac001bd-8774-4f0c-ad90-cb85c534e0a4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Continental Chemicals Ltd has released the status of re-lodgement requests for the transfer of physical shares under a special window during December 2025. The report was prepared by the company&apos;s Registrar and Transfer Agent, Beetal Financial and Computer Services (P) Ltd, and approved by the Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) as per their circular no SEBI/HO/MIRSDPoD/P/CIR/2025/97 dated 02/07/2025. The report includes the number of transfer requests received, processed, approved, and rejected during the month, with an average time taken for processing.</p><ul><li>Continental Chemicals Ltd releases special window transfer status for December 2025</li><li>Report prepared by Beetal Financial and Computer Services (P) Ltd</li><li>SEBI approved the report as per their circular no SEBI/HO/MIRSDPoD/P/CIR/2025/97 dated 02/07/2025</li><li>Number of transfer requests received, processed, approved, and rejected during the month</li><li>Average time taken for processing the transfer requests</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/da216715-ffa7-48c5-9323-85b3fe361ed3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CONTINENTAL CHEMICALS LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VFL] Viji Finance Ltd. Submits Un-audited Financial Results for Q3 &amp; Nine Months Ended on 31st December, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Viji+Finance+Ltd&title=Viji+Finance+Ltd.+Submits+Un-audited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Ended+on+31st+December%2C+2025&newsId=6423c43d-d6ea-4aca-94f1-a8b17a9a3427&token=NjQyM2M0M2QtZDZl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6423c43d-d6ea-4aca-94f1-a8b17a9a3427</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:22:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Viji Finance Ltd. has submitted its un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December, 2025. The results were approved in a Board of Directors meeting on 16th January, 2026. The company&apos;s total income stands at INR 29,292 Lakhs, with a net loss of INR 9.69 Lakhs for the continuing operations. The company does not have any subsidiary, associate, or joint venture companies as of 31st December, 2025.</p><ul><li>Viji Finance Ltd. submitted un-audited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended on 31st December, 2025.</li><li>The results were approved in a Board of Directors meeting on 16th January, 2026.</li><li>The company&apos;s total income stands at INR 29,292 Lakhs.</li><li>The net loss for the continuing operations is INR 9.69 Lakhs.</li><li>Viji Finance Ltd. does not have any subsidiary, associate, or joint venture companies as of 31st December, 2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c648ed8c-87f9-4ea9-b5fa-af4e64549202.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Viji Finance Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FILATEX] Filatex India Acquires 1,50,00,000 Shares in Wholly Owned Subsidiary Texfil Private Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=FILATEX+INDIA+LTD.-%24&title=Filatex+India+Acquires+1%2C50%2C00%2C000+Shares+in+Wholly+Owned+Subsidiary+Texfil+Private+Limited&newsId=958afba5-4d1f-4a7e-b605-5f65bcf6c6a5&token=OTU4YWZiYTUtNGQx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">958afba5-4d1f-4a7e-b605-5f65bcf6c6a5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Filatex India Ltd. has acquired 1,50,00,000 Equity Shares of Texfil Private Limited, a wholly owned subsidiary, for an aggregate amount of Rs. 15.00 crore. The investment will be used to finance the ongoing Polyester Textiles Recycling Project, repayment of existing loan taken from Filatex, and working capital requirements. The transaction is between the company and its wholly owned subsidiary, making it a related party transaction. It is conducted on an arm’s length basis with no interest from the company’s promoter / promoter group / other group companies. No governmental or regulatory approval was required for the acquisition.</p><ul><li>Filatex India acquires 1,50,00,000 Equity Shares in Texfil Private Limited</li><li>Transaction amount is Rs. 15.00 crore</li><li>Investment to finance Polyester Textiles Recycling Project, repayment of existing loan, and working capital requirements</li><li>Related party transaction conducted on arm’s length basis</li><li>No interest from promoter / promoter group / other group companies</li><li>No governmental or regulatory approval required</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e8ec2081-c879-4f41-85aa-a87ef0986ca6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: FILATEX INDIA LTD.-$ | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SOBHA] Sobha Ltd. Reports Deviations in Rights Issue Utilization as of December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sobha+Limited&title=Sobha+Ltd.+Reports+Deviations+in+Rights+Issue+Utilization+as+of+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=28b4f1bb-a0eb-4e37-afc9-c0ddee2c9373&token=MjhiNGYxYmItYTBl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">28b4f1bb-a0eb-4e37-afc9-c0ddee2c9373</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sobha Limited has informed the stock exchange about deviations in the use of proceeds from the Rights Issue that ended on December 31, 2025. The deviations are detailed in a Statement of Deviation reviewed by the Audit Committee. The company raised INR 1,999.03 crore, of which INR 1,744.55 crore has been utilized towards the objects stated in the Letter of Offer dated June 12, 2024. INR 254.48 crore remains unutilized, which includes INR 0.32 crore of unutilized issue-related expenses. The deviation or variation could mean a deviation in the objects or purposes for which the funds have been raised, a deviation in the amount of funds actually utilized as against what was originally disclosed, or a change in terms of a contract referred to in the fund-raising document.</p><ul><li>Sobha Limited reports deviations in Rights Issue utilization as of December 31, 2025.</li><li>The company raised INR 1,999.03 crore, of which INR 1,744.55 crore has been utilized.</li><li>INR 254.48 crore remains unutilized, including INR 0.32 crore of unutilized issue-related expenses.</li><li>The deviations are detailed in a Statement of Deviation reviewed by the Audit Committee.</li><li>The deviation or variation could mean a deviation in the objects, purposes, or amount of funds utilized as against what was originally disclosed.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ad3f41b9-1186-404d-afd3-e4db74f64941.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sobha Limited | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TFSL] Typhoon Financial Services Ltd Elevates Rishab Chhajer as Managing Director for Five Years</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Typhoon+Financial+Services+Ltd&title=Typhoon+Financial+Services+Ltd+Elevates+Rishab+Chhajer+as+Managing+Director+for+Five+Years&newsId=e4d5d83b-ddde-411f-8ce9-e93a89f047e1&token=ZTRkNWQ4M2ItZGRk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e4d5d83b-ddde-411f-8ce9-e93a89f047e1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:21:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Typhoon Financial Services Ltd, based on the recommendation of the Nomination and Remuneration Committee, has elevated Mr. Rishab Chhajer as Managing Director for a period of five years with effect from 16th January, 2026. Mr. Chhajer is an industrialist with experience in engineering, business administration, sales, marketing, and administration. He holds a Bachelor of Industrial Engineering degree. His appointment is subject to approval by the shareholders as per the provisions of the Companies Act, 2013. Neither Mr. Chhajer nor any other director is debarred from holding the office of director by virtue of any SEBI order or any other such authority.</p><ul><li>Rishab Chhajer elevated as Managing Director of Typhoon Financial Services Ltd</li><li>Chhajer&apos;s appointment is for a period of five years, effective from 16th January, 2026</li><li>Chhajer is an industrialist with experience in engineering, business administration, sales, marketing, and administration</li><li>His appointment is subject to approval by the shareholders as per the Companies Act, 2013</li><li>Neither Chhajer nor any other director is debarred from holding the office of director by virtue of any SEBI order or any other such authority</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/59c7f299-a60c-422a-b8d4-97dbeb47cb52.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Typhoon Financial Services Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GESHIP] GE Shipping Takes Delivery of 2015 Built Very Large Gas Carrier &apos;Jag Vijay&apos;</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GREAT+EASTERN+SHIPPING+CO.LTD.&title=GE+Shipping+Takes+Delivery+of+2015+Built+Very+Large+Gas+Carrier+%27Jag+Vijay%27&newsId=74fa1836-db9b-432d-ac1f-2cf75fb1c40d&token=NzRmYTE4MzYtZGI5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74fa1836-db9b-432d-ac1f-2cf75fb1c40d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 12:20:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>The Great Eastern Shipping Company Limited (GE Shipping) took delivery of the 2015 South Korean built Very Large Gas Carrier &apos;Jag Vijay&apos; of about 84,048 cbm on January 16, 2026. The company had contracted to buy the vessel in Q3 FY26, and this transaction was financed entirely from internal accruals. The company&apos;s current owned fleet stands at 40 vessels, comprising 26 Tankers and 14 Dry Bulk Carriers, with a total capacity of 3.22 mn dwt. The company&apos;s current capacity utilization is close to 100%. Additionally, the company has contracted to buy one secondhand Ultramax Dry Bulk Carrier, buy one secondhand Medium Range Tanker, sell one Kamsarmax Dry Bulk Carrier &apos;Jag Aarati&apos;, and sell one Very Large Gas Carrier &apos;Jag Vishnu&apos;. These purchase and sale transactions are expected to be completed in Q4 FY26.</p><ul><li>GE Shipping takes delivery of a 2015 built Very Large Gas Carrier &apos;Jag Vijay&apos;</li><li>The vessel is financed entirely from internal accruals</li><li>GE Shipping&apos;s current owned fleet stands at 40 vessels, including 26 Tankers and 14 Dry Bulk Carriers</li><li>The company&apos;s current capacity utilization is close to 100%</li><li>GE Shipping has contracted to buy one secondhand Ultramax Dry Bulk Carrier, buy one secondhand Medium Range Tanker, sell one Kamsarmax Dry Bulk Carrier &apos;Jag Aarati&apos;, and sell one Very Large Gas Carrier &apos;Jag Vishnu&apos;</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ce889edb-d1ed-47d5-892d-78b40de02369.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GREAT EASTERN SHIPPING CO.LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>