<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 04:05:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ZUARI] Zuari Agro Chemicals Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ZUARI+AGRO+CHEMICALS+LTD.&title=Zuari+Agro+Chemicals+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025&newsId=bca110b4-0c8a-47dd-89ef-e9cdce0297b5&token=YmNhMTEwYjQtMGM4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bca110b4-0c8a-47dd-89ef-e9cdce0297b5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 04:01:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Zuari Agro Chemicals Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 4th February 2026 to consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The trading window will remain closed until 6th February 2026, 48 hours after the declaration of the results.</p><ul><li>Zuari Agro Chemicals Ltd scheduled a Board Meeting on 4th February 2026</li><li>The meeting aims to consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025</li><li>The trading window will be closed till 6th February 2026, 48 hours after the declaration of the results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/61ad9528-4301-4cda-9f33-eefd6276d971.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ZUARI AGRO CHEMICALS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TRIDENT] Trident Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results on Feb 09, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TRIDENT+LTD.&title=Trident+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+on+Feb+09%2C+2026&newsId=d3a75304-48f2-4e9f-99b7-65af2b4af3d2&token=ZDNhNzUzMDQtNDhm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3a75304-48f2-4e9f-99b7-65af2b4af3d2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 03:55:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Trident Ltd, a renowned company, has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 09, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results (Standalone and Consolidated) for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window will open at 9:00 AM IST on Thursday, February 12, 2026, in accordance with the Code of Conduct for Regulating, Monitoring and Reporting of Trades by Designated Persons of the Company as adopted by the Company in compliance of SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Trident Ltd to consider and approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Board Meeting scheduled on February 09, 2026</li><li>Trading window to open at 9:00 AM IST on Thursday, February 12, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9c90d42b-a36a-4dba-b389-0a970decfb27.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TRIDENT LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LT] L&amp;T Secures Ultra-Mega Contract for Heavy Civil Infrastructure in Saudi Arabia</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LARSEN+%26+TOUBRO+LTD.&title=L%26T+Secures+Ultra-Mega+Contract+for+Heavy+Civil+Infrastructure+in+Saudi+Arabia&newsId=4fc8c0b1-6df5-486e-bf33-c76cd45305b4&token=NGZjOGMwYjEtNmRm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4fc8c0b1-6df5-486e-bf33-c76cd45305b4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 03:54:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Larsen &amp; Toubro Limited (L&amp;T) has won a contract from the Royal Commission of Riyadh City in Saudi Arabia for works pertaining to the extension of the Riyadh Metro. The order is a part of an ultra-mega project won by a consortium of Webuild S.p.A, L&amp;T, Nesma &amp; Partners Contracting, Alstom and IDOM. The scope of work includes design and turnkey construction of 8.4 km long metro line comprising both elevated and underground sections, and five stations.</p><ul><li>L&amp;T has won a contract from the Royal Commission of Riyadh City in Saudi Arabia for works pertaining to the extension of the Riyadh Metro.</li><li>The order is a part of an ultra-mega project won by a consortium of Webuild S.p.A, L&amp;T, Nesma &amp; Partners Contracting, Alstom and IDOM.</li><li>The scope of work includes design and turnkey construction of 8.4 km long metro line comprising both elevated and underground sections, and five stations.</li><li>L&amp;T has a proven capability in constructing fast and reliable mass transit systems across the globe.</li><li>This latest order stands as a testament to the trust customers place in the company.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/622b3010-af95-4fc2-929a-4341fd85ae3b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LARSEN & TOUBRO LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUZLON] Suzlon Secures 248.5 MW Wind Order from ArcelorMittal for Green Steel Production</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SUZLON+ENERGY+LTD.&title=Suzlon+Secures+248.5+MW+Wind+Order+from+ArcelorMittal+for+Green+Steel+Production&newsId=6e87625b-cc79-4662-92e8-ecdba9956e10&token=NmU4NzYyNWItY2M3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6e87625b-cc79-4662-92e8-ecdba9956e10</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 03:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Suzlon Energy Ltd has secured a 248.85 MW wind energy order from ArcelorMittal Group through its Renewable Energy entity in India. This order is part of the 550 MW hybrid project in Gujarat for captive use for ArcelorMittal Nippon steel facilities in India. Suzlon is now powering about 1,156 MW for green steel in India. This is Suzlon&apos;s fourth major wind order for decarbonizing steel production. The partnership reflects a shared vision to accelerate green steel production and build a sustainable future for India.</p><ul><li>Suzlon secures 248.5 MW wind order from ArcelorMittal</li><li>Order is part of the 550 MW hybrid project in Gujarat</li><li>Wind order for captive use for ArcelorMittal Nippon steel facilities in India</li><li>Suzlon&apos;s fourth major wind order for decarbonizing steel production</li><li>Partnership reflects a shared vision to accelerate green steel production</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3485a364-f164-4527-a717-eab440dadc19.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SUZLON ENERGY LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SKMEGGPROD] SKM Egg Products Export (India) Ltd&apos;s Chairman Awarded &apos;Padma Bhushan&apos;</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SKM+EGG+PRODUCTS+EXPORT+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=SKM+Egg+Products+Export+%28India%29+Ltd%27s+Chairman+Awarded+%27Padma+Bhushan%27&newsId=0520893e-ba55-4979-a545-e14546e87d46&token=MDUyMDg5M2UtYmE1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0520893e-ba55-4979-a545-e14546e87d46</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 03:23:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Award</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SKM Egg Products Export (India) Ltd&apos;s Chairman, Shri KM Maeilanandhan, has been conferred with India&apos;s prestigious award, the &apos;Padma Bhushan&apos;. This recognition is for his contributions to rural development, education, and healthcare.</p><ul><li>SKM Egg Products Export (India) Ltd&apos;s Chairman, Shri KM Maeilanandhan, has been honored with the &apos;Padma Bhushan&apos; award</li><li>The &apos;Padma Bhushan&apos; is one of India&apos;s highest civilian awards</li><li>Shri KM Maeilanandhan has been recognized for his contributions to rural development, education, and healthcare</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e8375ae9-c565-429a-b699-b7d6f04ea626.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SKM EGG PRODUCTS EXPORT (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Award</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BIOCON] S&amp;P Global Upgrades Biocon Biologics Credit Rating To ‘BB+’; Revises Outlook to “Stable”</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BIOCON+LTD.&title=S%26P+Global+Upgrades+Biocon+Biologics+Credit+Rating+To+%E2%80%98BB%2B%E2%80%99%3B+Revises+Outlook+to+%E2%80%9CStable%E2%80%9D&newsId=24299000-dd0f-49f1-904c-c36e82a87804&token=MjQyOTkwMDAtZGQw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24299000-dd0f-49f1-904c-c36e82a87804</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 03:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>S&amp;P Global Ratings has upgraded Biocon Biologics’ long-term issuer credit rating to ‘BB+’ from ‘BB’, and revised the outlook to “Stable”. This follows Biocon’s recent equity issuance to settle compulsorily convertible preference shares (CCPS) issued to Viatris Inc. S&amp;P Global provided the following Rating Action Rationale: Biocon has simplified its capital structure, reduced its outstanding structured debt liabilities, and removed a US$1 billion CCPS issued to Viatris through a mix of equity share swaps and cash consideration. Biocon funded the cash payout through fresh equity of about US$460 million that it raised earlier this month. New product launches and favorable industry trends will support Biocon&apos;s earnings. Biocon&apos;s financial policy underpins its credit strength, with a commitment to reverting its balance sheet position to levels before its acquisition of Viatris&apos; biosimilars portfolio.</p><ul><li>S&amp;P Global upgrades Biocon Biologics credit rating to ‘BB+’ from ‘BB’</li><li>Outlook revised to “Stable”</li><li>Biocon simplifies capital structure and reduces debt liabilities</li><li>New product launches and industry trends support Biocon&apos;s earnings</li><li>Biocon remains committed to reverting balance sheet position to pre-acquisition levels</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2b46dce1-c5e2-4516-a3cb-72b2b31f69d0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BIOCON LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[POONAWALLA] Poonawalla Fincorp Deepens AI-First Transformation with Five New Enterprise AI Solutions</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Poonawalla+Fincorp+Ltd&title=Poonawalla+Fincorp+Deepens+AI-First+Transformation+with+Five+New+Enterprise+AI+Solutions&newsId=3ccd7c16-169a-4d3d-8d1e-65a07a47a5f9&token=M2NjZDdjMTYtMTY5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ccd7c16-169a-4d3d-8d1e-65a07a47a5f9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 02:46:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>AI, Technology, Finance</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Poonawalla Fincorp Limited has announced the rollout of five new AI-powered enterprise solutions. These initiatives reflect PFL’s long-term vision to become a digitally fluent, data-driven, and highly scalable financial organization. The new solutions include an AI-powered Competition Benchmarking Engine, a Central KYC (CKYC) AI Platform, Agentic Data Quality Intelligence (DQI), AI-led Voice of Customer (VOC) Categorisation, and Build Buddy for Accelerated Application Development. These solutions aim to strengthen decision-making and execution across strategic decision-making, customer onboarding, data quality management, customer experience analytics, and application development.</p><ul><li>Poonawalla Fincorp has introduced five new AI-powered solutions to strengthen decision-making and execution.</li><li>The new solutions include an AI-powered Competition Benchmarking Engine, a Central KYC (CKYC) AI Platform, Agentic Data Quality Intelligence (DQI), AI-led Voice of Customer (VOC) Categorisation, and Build Buddy for Accelerated Application Development.</li><li>These initiatives reflect PFL’s long-term vision to become a digitally fluent, data-driven, and highly scalable financial organization.</li><li>PFL has already initiated 57 AI projects, of which 30 have been successfully completed.</li><li>Poonawalla Fincorp continues to deepen its commitment to its AI-first approach, driving intelligent automation, accuracy, and future-ready innovation.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/99b3b4ac-6d96-4cbc-ac5d-285ddf509c48.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Poonawalla Fincorp Ltd | Category: AI, Technology, Finance</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VAIBHAVGBL] Vaibhav Global Ltd Declares 3% Interim Dividend, Grants ESOPs and RSUs, and Reports Q3 and YTD Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vaibhav+Global+Ltd&title=Vaibhav+Global+Ltd+Declares+3%25+Interim+Dividend%2C+Grants+ESOPs+and+RSUs%2C+and+Reports+Q3+and+YTD+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=3cdb195e-fd29-4046-b783-32e977bd859f&token=M2NkYjE5NWUtZmQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3cdb195e-fd29-4046-b783-32e977bd859f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vaibhav Global Ltd has declared a 3% interim dividend of Rs. 1.50 per equity share for the financial year 2025-26. The company has also granted 63,789 stock options (ESOPs) and 5,862 restricted stock units (RSUs) to eligible employees. The Board approved the unaudited financial results for Q3 and YTD ended 31st December 2025. The company reported a revenue of Rs. 1,06,602.51 lakhs for Q3 and Rs. 2,75,707.83 lakhs for YTD 2025.</p><ul><li>Declared 3% interim dividend of Rs. 1.50 per equity share</li><li>Granted 63,789 stock options (ESOPs) and 5,862 restricted stock units (RSUs) to eligible employees</li><li>Approved unaudited financial results for Q3 and YTD ended 31st December 2025</li><li>Revenue of Rs. 1,06,602.51 lakhs for Q3 and Rs. 2,75,707.83 lakhs for YTD 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1127f9ba-eb40-44fd-8231-f3d5e9370f7e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vaibhav Global Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VAIBHAVGBL] Vaibhav Global Ltd. Declares Interim Dividend, Approves Grant of ESOPs and RSUs, and Reports Q3 Results for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vaibhav+Global+Ltd&title=Vaibhav+Global+Ltd.+Declares+Interim+Dividend%2C+Approves+Grant+of+ESOPs+and+RSUs%2C+and+Reports+Q3+Results+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=ae9021e8-5699-40d9-abc2-ffa4f919831a&token=YWU5MDIxZTgtNTY5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae9021e8-5699-40d9-abc2-ffa4f919831a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In a recent board meeting, Vaibhav Global Ltd. approved the unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31 December 2025. The company declared an interim dividend of Rs. 1.50 per equity share for FY 2025-26, with a record date set for 03 February 2026. Additionally, the board granted 63,789 stock options and 5,862 restricted stock units under the VGL ESOP Plan — 2021 and VGL RSU Plan — 2019, respectively. The company also provided updates on various legal proceedings and assessed the incremental impact of the new Labour Codes.</p><ul><li>Declared interim dividend of Rs. 1.50 per equity share for FY 2025-26</li><li>Granted 63,789 stock options and 5,862 restricted stock units</li><li>Approved unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31 December 2025</li><li>Provided updates on various legal proceedings</li><li>Assessed the incremental impact of new Labour Codes</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8244db23-70b3-406d-aa67-25e8fb142b97.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vaibhav Global Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ALLSEC] Alldigi Tech Q3 FY26 Revenue up by 10%; EBITDA up by 42%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ALLSEC+TECHNOLOGIES+LTD.&title=Alldigi+Tech+Q3+FY26+Revenue+up+by+10%25%3B+EBITDA+up+by+42%25&newsId=1194e81e-190b-4c3b-b350-215e7c63fad6&token=MTE5NGU4MWUtMTkw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1194e81e-190b-4c3b-b350-215e7c63fad6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Alldigi Tech Limited, a global leader in Tech &amp; Digital (T&amp;D) &amp; BPM solutions, announced its financial results for Q3 FY26. The company&apos;s Q3 FY 26 YoY revenue from Operations is up by 9.5% and EBIDTA up by 41.7%. The Board has declared an interim dividend of Rs.30/- per equity share. The BPM vertical&apos;s revenue is up by 7.4% YoY and 3.2% QoQ, with international revenue up by 13.8% YoY and 7.9% QoQ. The Tech &amp; Digital vertical&apos;s revenue is up by 16.2% YoY and 4.9% QoQ.</p><ul><li>Q3 FY26 YoY revenue up by 9.5% and EBIDTA up by 41.7%</li><li>International revenue in BPM up by 13.8% YoY and 7.9% QoQ</li><li>Tech &amp; Digital revenue up by 16.2% YoY and 4.9% QoQ</li><li>Interim dividend of Rs.30/- per equity share declared</li><li>48.5 lacs employee records processed in Tech &amp; Digital, up by 10.0% YoY</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a5cc78f8-f236-4068-85ee-3abc812675ea.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ALLSEC TECHNOLOGIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>