<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:49:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[FINKURVE] Finkurve Financial Services Reschedules Board Meeting to Consider Funds Raising via Private Placement</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Finkurve+Financial+Services+Ltd&title=Finkurve+Financial+Services+Reschedules+Board+Meeting+to+Consider+Funds+Raising+via+Private+Placement&newsId=48b95ae7-c302-43e0-b9eb-997701624b4d&token=NDhiOTVhZTctYzMw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48b95ae7-c302-43e0-b9eb-997701624b4d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:49:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Finkurve Financial Services Ltd. has informed the BSE that the meeting of the Board of Directors, originally scheduled for February 09, 2026, to consider and approve the raising of funds through the issuance of Non-Convertible Debentures, has been rescheduled to February 11, 2026, due to certain technical issues. The debentures will have a face value and issue price of Rs. 10,000 (Indian Rupees Ten Thousand only) each, and will be issued via the Electronic Bidding Platform (EBP) through private placement.</p><ul><li>Finkurve Financial Services Ltd. reschedules Board meeting to February 11, 2026</li><li>Meeting originally scheduled for February 09, 2026, to consider and approve funds raising through Non-Convertible Debentures issuance</li><li>Debentures to have a face value and issue price of Rs. 10,000 (Indian Rupees Ten Thousand only) each</li><li>Issuance to be carried out via Electronic Bidding Platform (EBP) through private placement</li><li>Rescheduling due to technical issues</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e9f099eb-9a87-4f97-bec6-edc45aea0220.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Finkurve Financial Services Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HPAL] HP Adhesives Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HP+Adhesives+Ltd&title=HP+Adhesives+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025&newsId=5be48e64-880f-4ae8-971c-4aaaffa26c91&token=NWJlNDhlNjQtODgw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5be48e64-880f-4ae8-971c-4aaaffa26c91</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:47:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>HP Adhesives Ltd has informed BSE that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on 12th February 2026. The meeting will consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results (Standalone and Consolidated) for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The trading window for Designated/Connected Persons and their immediate relatives will be closed till 48 hours after the announcement of financial results.</p><ul><li>HP Adhesives Ltd board meeting scheduled on 12th February 2026</li><li>Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months of 2025 to be considered and approved</li><li>Trading window for Designated/Connected Persons and their immediate relatives to be closed till 48 hours after the announcement of financial results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a701e5b2-8946-4363-b199-b020b4641edf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HP Adhesives Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AIRAN] Airan Ltd to Approve Q3 &amp; Nine Months Financial Results on Feb 14, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Airan+Ltd&title=Airan+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+Feb+14%2C+2026&newsId=0ebf9143-f921-4f5a-bd73-be4b2702c274&token=MGViZjkxNDMtZjky</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ebf9143-f921-4f5a-bd73-be4b2702c274</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:46:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Airan Ltd has announced a Board meeting on February 14, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the company is closed for the insiders from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of financial results.</p><ul><li>Airan Ltd to consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the securities of the company is closed for the insiders from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of financial results.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b850ffdb-b76b-4abd-8ab2-0bb6a4b8f877.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Airan Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HERITGFOOD] Heritage Foods Ltd Vice President Marketing, Puneet Kusumbia, Resigns</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Heritage+Foods+Limited&title=Heritage+Foods+Ltd+Vice+President+Marketing%2C+Puneet+Kusumbia%2C+Resigns&newsId=355e26b9-350a-4d2e-8539-2fb67e92194c&token=MzU1ZTI2YjktMzUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">355e26b9-350a-4d2e-8539-2fb67e92194c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:46:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Heritage Foods Ltd has informed about the resignation of Mr. Puneet Kusumbia, Vice President (Marketing) and Senior Management Personnel (SMP), due to personal reasons. The resignation is accepted and he will be relieved from his duties on or before May 5, 2026. The decision details are provided in accordance with Regulation 30 read with Schedule III - Para A(7C) of Part A of the SEBI Listing Regulations.</p><ul><li>Heritage Foods Ltd Vice President (Marketing) Mr. Puneet Kusumbia has resigned.</li><li>The resignation is due to personal reasons.</li><li>The resignation is accepted and he will be relieved from his duties on or before May 5, 2026.</li><li>The decision is in compliance with Regulation 30 read with Schedule III - Para A(7C) of Part A of the SEBI Listing Regulations.</li><li>Heritage Foods Ltd is an ISO 22000 certified company.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7dc3d7b4-86b1-477e-9974-819bd7968783.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Heritage Foods Limited | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SURYAAMBA] Suryaamba Spinning Mills Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on February 14, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SURYAAMBA+SPINNING+MILLS+LTD.&title=Suryaamba+Spinning+Mills+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+February+14%2C+2026&newsId=34434403-ec40-4702-a53a-60c39dd54b7a&token=MzQ0MzQ0MDMtZWM0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">34434403-ec40-4702-a53a-60c39dd54b7a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:44:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Suryaamba Spinning Mills Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 14, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The meeting will also take note of the Limited Review Report of the Statutory Auditor on the unaudited financial results. The company&apos;s trading window will remain closed until 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results.</p><ul><li>Suryaamba Spinning Mills Ltd to approve Q3 and nine months financial results on February 14, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the period ended on December 31, 2025</li><li>The company&apos;s trading window will be closed until 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f97c43be-f8b7-4cdf-b00e-71e61802f5a5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SURYAAMBA SPINNING MILLS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BAJEL] Bajel Projects Secures a Large Order for 765kV Mandsaur Substation Extension</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Bajel+Projects+Ltd&title=Bajel+Projects+Secures+a+Large+Order+for+765kV+Mandsaur+Substation+Extension&newsId=221bd3fb-3cab-43ee-ad63-96bd47d0bb22&token=MjIxYmQzZmItM2Nh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">221bd3fb-3cab-43ee-ad63-96bd47d0bb22</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:44:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Bajel Projects Limited, a leading player in the Power Transmission and Distribution (T&amp;D) EPC sector and a Bajaj Group company, has been awarded a ‘Large’ order for the extension of the Mandsaur Pooling Station (PS). This project is a critical component of India’s strategy to augment transformation capacity for Renewable Energy (RE) interconnection. The contract, designated as 765kV AIS Extn. Substation Package SS 108T, involves the extension of the existing 765/400/220kV Mandsaur Pooling Station (PS) under the &apos;Augmentation of Transformation Capacity and Implementation of line bays at Mandsaur for RE interconnection&apos; and is being executed through the Tariff Based Competitive Bidding (TBCB) route. The Company is already executing the transmission line of 260 route kms from Beawar to Mandsaur Pooling station traversing through Madhya Pradesh and Rajasthan.</p><ul><li>Bajel Projects Limited has secured a ‘Large’ order for the extension of the Mandsaur Pooling Station (PS).</li><li>The project is a critical component of India’s strategy to augment transformation capacity for Renewable Energy (RE) interconnection.</li><li>The contract, designated as 765kV AIS Extn. Substation Package SS 108T, involves the extension of the existing 765/400/220kV Mandsaur Pooling Station (PS).</li><li>The project falls under the &apos;Augmentation of Transformation Capacity and Implementation of line bays at Mandsaur for RE interconnection&apos; and is being executed through the Tariff Based Competitive Bidding (TBCB) route.</li><li>Bajel Projects is already executing the transmission line of 260 route kms from Beawar to Mandsaur Pooling station traversing through Madhya Pradesh and Rajasthan.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/89e2a00e-f205-4f1c-8a55-4a9533d40b89.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Bajel Projects Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VEERHEALTH] Veerhealth Care Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results on Feb 14, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Veerhealth+Care+Limited&title=Veerhealth+Care+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+on+Feb+14%2C+2026&newsId=a38f414b-4721-4d3d-85db-be6d57a30308&token=YTM4ZjQxNGItNDcy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a38f414b-4721-4d3d-85db-be6d57a30308</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:43:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Veerhealth Care Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 14, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will be held at the company&apos;s registered office in Mumbai. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the company, which was closed from January 1, 2026, will be reopened on February 17, 2026, in accordance with the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading Regulations), 2015.</p><ul><li>Veerhealth Care Ltd to approve Q3 and nine months results on Feb 14, 2026</li><li>The meeting will be held at the company&apos;s registered office in Mumbai</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the securities of the company to be reopened on Feb 17, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/244b555b-0992-4906-8876-18df8dea266f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Veerhealth Care Limited | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DIVSHKT] Divyashakti Ltd. Approves Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Divyashakti+Ltd&title=Divyashakti+Ltd.+Approves+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+2025&newsId=d5b2c8bc-2277-425e-bf74-4b095f1dc82c&token=ZDViMmM4YmMtMjI3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5b2c8bc-2277-425e-bf74-4b095f1dc82c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:43:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Divyashakti Ltd. held a Board Meeting on 06th February 2026 to approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The meeting was conducted in accordance with the SEBI LODR Regulations. The Board approved the unaudited financial results as reviewed by the Audit Committee and recommended by the Statutory Auditors M/s Pavuluri &amp; Co Chartered Accountants, Hyderabad.</p><ul><li>Approval of unaudited financial results for Q3 2025</li><li>Review and approval by the Audit Committee and the Board of Directors</li><li>Approval of Limited Review Reports by the Statutory Auditors</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/eced8d62-b1d4-412a-ad07-ecbf1b37a79d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Divyashakti Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ENERGYINF] Energy Infrastructure Trust Approves Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Energy+Infrastructure+Trust&title=Energy+Infrastructure+Trust+Approves+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=5a541992-cc86-4983-abeb-d7e800a03895&token=NWE1NDE5OTItY2M4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a541992-cc86-4983-abeb-d7e800a03895</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:41:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Energy Infrastructure Trust, managed by EnCap Investment Manager Private Limited, has approved the un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The results were reviewed by Deloitte Haskins &amp; Sells LLP. The Trust&apos;s total income stands at INR 848.61 crore, with a net profit of INR 650.19 crore. The Trust&apos;s net distributable cash flows (NDCF) for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, is INR 2.28 crore.</p><ul><li>Energy Infrastructure Trust approves Q3 and nine months financial results for 2025</li><li>Total income stands at INR 848.61 crore</li><li>Net profit for the period is INR 650.19 crore</li><li>Net distributable cash flows (NDCF) for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, is INR 2.28 crore</li><li>Reviewed by Deloitte Haskins &amp; Sells LLP</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/72119fbe-a611-4497-8782-25f32c3f2572.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Energy Infrastructure Trust | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[POLYLINK] Polylink Polymers India Ltd Approves Quarterly Financial Results for Q4 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=POLYLINK+POLYMERS+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Polylink+Polymers+India+Ltd+Approves+Quarterly+Financial+Results+for+Q4+2025&newsId=067f12e7-2c35-4984-9a40-fc1da1ec28d3&token=MDY3ZjEyZTctMmMz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">067f12e7-2c35-4984-9a40-fc1da1ec28d3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Polylink Polymers India Ltd has approved the Quarterly Financial Results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The un-audited financial results and the limited review report for the quarter ended 31st December 2025 were issued by M/s. K. N. Gutgutia &amp; Co. Chartered Accountants, Statutory Auditors of the Company.</p><ul><li>Polylink Polymers India Ltd has approved the Quarterly Financial Results for Q4 2025.</li><li>The un-audited financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025 were reviewed by M/s. K. N. Gutgutia &amp; Co. Chartered Accountants.</li><li>The financial results are in compliance with Regulation 33 of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c00816d2-a1bb-4044-aedd-87ef704c4187.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: POLYLINK POLYMERS (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>