<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:53:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[MUKATPIP] Mukat Pipes Ltd. to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on February 12, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MUKAT+PIPES+LTD.-%24&title=Mukat+Pipes+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+February+12%2C+2026&newsId=4b897781-05e1-4392-b1d8-62782dc982f9&token=NGI4OTc3ODEtMDVl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4b897781-05e1-4392-b1d8-62782dc982f9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:53:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mukat Pipes Ltd. has informed the BSE that a Board of Directors meeting is scheduled on February 12, 2026. The meeting will inter alia consider and approve the unaudited financial results of the company for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. In accordance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, the trading window for designated persons will remain closed for 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results.</p><ul><li>Mukat Pipes Ltd. to consider and approve unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December, 2025</li><li>Trading window for designated persons to remain closed for 48 hours after the declaration of financial results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/49c59c19-cfaa-4832-bda8-5c94f9970ea6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MUKAT PIPES LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ULTRACEMCO] UltraTech Cement Limited: A Force for Good with Strong Operational and Financial Performance</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ULTRATECH+CEMENT+LTD.&title=UltraTech+Cement+Limited%3A+A+Force+for+Good+with+Strong+Operational+and+Financial+Performance&newsId=8d61869e-aa28-4dfe-93ff-e70fbdb1f4cf&token=OGQ2MTg2OWUtYWEy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d61869e-aa28-4dfe-93ff-e70fbdb1f4cf</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:53:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>UltraTech Cement Limited, a part of the Aditya Birla Group, is a leading global cement player by sales volume and the second largest by capacity, excluding China. The company is known for its premium western brands, sustainable practices, and strong financial performance. It operates in 6 continents and 40+ countries, with a significant presence in the Indian cement sector. The company is committed to responsible business practices, innovation, and growth, with a focus on improving profitability and expanding its scale over the next five years.</p><ul><li>UltraTech Cement Limited is the largest cement player globally by sales volume and the second largest by capacity, excluding China.</li><li>The company is part of the Aditya Birla Group, a premium global conglomerate with a strong presence in various sectors including aluminum rolling, cellulosic fibers, and specialty chemicals.</li><li>UltraTech Cement Limited operates in 6 continents and 40+ countries, with a significant presence in the Indian cement sector.</li><li>The company is committed to responsible business practices, innovation, and growth, with a focus on improving profitability and expanding its scale over the next five years.</li><li>UltraTech Cement Limited has been recognized as a &apos;Top Employer&apos; in India by the Top Employers Institute for its exceptional employee conditions.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/911c1fb6-bd22-42e3-b316-a8b903037c9a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ULTRATECH CEMENT LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MODMA] Modern Malleables Ltd. to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results on February 12, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Modern+Malleables+Ltd&title=Modern+Malleables+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+on+February+12%2C+2026&newsId=70b8529c-b41d-459b-9db9-b30b598d38a1&token=NzBiODUyOWMtYjQx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70b8529c-b41d-459b-9db9-b30b598d38a1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:50:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Modern Malleables Ltd. has announced a Board of Directors meeting on February 12, 2026, at 3.30 p.m., at the company&apos;s registered office in Kolkata. The meeting aims to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s trading window for dealing in securities will be closed from January 1, 2026, and will reopen 48 hours after the announcement of the results.</p><ul><li>Modern Malleables Ltd. to hold a Board Meeting on February 12, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities to be closed from January 1, 2026</li><li>Trading window to reopen 48 hours after the announcement of the results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ca75ae2f-0107-46f8-a1d0-e04eb49f6e5d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Modern Malleables Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MFML] Mahalaxmi Fabric Mills Ltd to Approve Q3 Financial Results on Feb 13, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Mahalaxmi+Fabric+Mills+Ltd&title=Mahalaxmi+Fabric+Mills+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+Financial+Results+on+Feb+13%2C+2026&newsId=c29a65e0-7105-41bc-a169-be94b02f5f15&token=YzI5YTY1ZTAtNzEw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c29a65e0-7105-41bc-a169-be94b02f5f15</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mahalaxmi Fabric Mills Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 13, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025. The meeting is scheduled in accordance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The trading window for dealing in securities of the company for the designated persons has been closed from January 1, 2026, and will reopen 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results.</p><ul><li>Mahalaxmi Fabric Mills Ltd to consider and approve Q3 financial results for the year 2025-26.</li><li>The meeting is scheduled for February 13, 2026.</li><li>The trading window for dealing in securities of the company for the designated persons is closed from January 1, 2026.</li><li>The trading window will reopen 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results.</li><li>The announcement is in accordance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/123289d2-1d52-4b4c-9ce5-6ce20bd71e6f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Mahalaxmi Fabric Mills Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BALGOPAL] Balgopal Commercial Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on February 12, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Balgopal+Commercial+Ltd&title=Balgopal+Commercial+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+February+12%2C+2026&newsId=d7ec4a03-1255-40c8-96ad-950d072bb02e&token=ZDdlYzRhMDMtMTI1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7ec4a03-1255-40c8-96ad-950d072bb02e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:46:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Balgopal Commercial Ltd has announced a meeting of the Board of Directors on February 12, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company is closed for the Insiders from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of the Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Balgopal Commercial Ltd to approve Q3 and nine months financial results on February 12, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company is closed for Insiders from January 1, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/15915f0f-ec54-4e7e-b6ab-3dc04a8f5d7a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Balgopal Commercial Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AINFRA] Kanoria Energy &amp; Infrastructure Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q3 and Nine Month Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=A+Infrastructure+Ltd&title=Kanoria+Energy+%26+Infrastructure+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Month+Results+for+2025&newsId=bd65ab2f-6ed0-4a7b-aa85-8db1ea60c981&token=YmQ2NWFiMmYtNmVk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd65ab2f-6ed0-4a7b-aa85-8db1ea60c981</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:46:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kanoria Energy &amp; Infrastructure Ltd has informed the BSE that its Board of Directors will meet on 14th February 2026 to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The meeting will also discuss dividend on preference shares and other business as per the agenda. The trading window for dealing in the equity shares of the company was closed for designated persons from 1st January 2026 till the expiry of 48 hours after the declaration of un-audited financial results.</p><ul><li>Kanoria Energy &amp; Infrastructure Ltd to consider and approve un-audited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December 2025</li><li>The meeting will discuss dividend on preference shares</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the equity shares of the company was closed for designated persons from 1st January 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/51323f00-d000-452f-b8c4-bd71d966a6e8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: A Infrastructure Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GEMSI] Gemstone Investments Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results of FY2025-2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GEMSTONE+INVESTMENTS+LTD.&title=Gemstone+Investments+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+of+FY2025-2026&newsId=bba4478a-946d-4015-858d-792b6c58140b&token=YmJhNDQ3OGEtOTQ2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bba4478a-946d-4015-858d-792b6c58140b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:46:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gemstone Investments Ltd has informed the BSE that its Board of Directors will meet on 13th February 2026 to consider and approve the un-audited standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months period ended on 31st December 2025. The meeting will also approve the limited review report to be issued by M/s. Rishi Sekhri and Associates, Chartered Accountants for the quarter ended on 31st December 2025. The trading window for dealing in securities of the company, which was closed from 01st January 2026, will re-open 48 hours after the financial results become generally available information.</p><ul><li>Gemstone Investments Ltd to consider and approve un-audited standalone financial results for Q3 and nine months period ended on 31st December 2025</li><li>The Board will approve the limited review report issued by M/s. Rishi Sekhri and Associates, Chartered Accountants for Q4 2025</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities of the company to re-open 48 hours after financial results become publicly available</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/45902fff-5217-46e1-8291-d531962356ac.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GEMSTONE INVESTMENTS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AKSHAR] Akshar Spintex Ltd Schedules Board Meeting on 13th February, 2026 to Approve Q4 Results of 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Akshar+Spintex+Ltd&title=Akshar+Spintex+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+on+13th+February%2C+2026+to+Approve+Q4+Results+of+2025&newsId=5432f654-d563-4766-aae8-fad24cf12ba6&token=NTQzMmY2NTQtZDU2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5432f654-d563-4766-aae8-fad24cf12ba6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:46:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Akshar Spintex Ltd has informed BSE that the meeting of the Board of Directors of the Company is scheduled on 13th February, 2026. The meeting will be held at the registered office of the company in Jamnagar, Gujarat. The Board will consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone Financial Results for the Quarter ended on 31st December, 2025 along with the Limited Review Report by the Auditor. Any other business(s) with permission of Chair will also be discussed if necessary.</p><ul><li>Akshar Spintex Ltd scheduled a Board Meeting on 13th February, 2026</li><li>The meeting will be held at the registered office in Jamnagar, Gujarat</li><li>The Board will consider and approve the Q4 results of 2025</li><li>The Unaudited Standalone Financial Results for the quarter ended on 31st December, 2025 will be discussed</li><li>Any other business(s) with permission of Chair will be discussed if necessary</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/92fec2d7-facf-461f-a155-33307b9b951f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Akshar Spintex Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SANHP] Sangam Health Care Products Ltd to Consider Unaudited Financial Results for Q4 2025 in February Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sangam+Health+Care+Products+Ltd&title=Sangam+Health+Care+Products+Ltd+to+Consider+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q4+2025+in+February+Board+Meeting&newsId=bd7e84ef-1d6c-46a7-acb5-ac66b06b73bc&token=YmQ3ZTg0ZWYtMWQ2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd7e84ef-1d6c-46a7-acb5-ac66b06b73bc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sangam Health Care Products Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 13th February 2026 to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended 31.12.2025. The meeting will also consider the Limited Review Report for the same quarter. Any other business with the permission of the Chair will also be discussed.</p><ul><li>Sangam Health Care Products Ltd to consider unaudited financial results for Q4 2025</li><li>Board meeting scheduled on 13th February 2026</li><li>Limited Review Report for Q4 2025 will also be considered</li><li>Any other business with the permission of the Chair will be discussed</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7ce3762a-7749-4b5b-9317-d5b555d53f32.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sangam Health Care Products Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GLOBALE] Globale Tessile Ltd to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 FY2025-26 on Feb 11, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Globale+Tessile+Ltd&title=Globale+Tessile+Ltd+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+FY2025-26+on+Feb+11%2C+2026&newsId=3053eaca-38cf-4729-b7f6-5adf15c1a33f&token=MzA1M2VhY2EtMzhj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3053eaca-38cf-4729-b7f6-5adf15c1a33f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Globale Tessile Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 11, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. This meeting is in accordance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The trading window for dealing in securities of the company for designated persons has been closed from January 1, 2026, and will reopen 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results.</p><ul><li>Globale Tessile Ltd to consider and approve unaudited financial results for Q3 FY2025-26</li><li>Meeting of the Board of Directors scheduled on February 11, 2026</li><li>Trading window for designated persons closed from January 1, 2026</li><li>Trading window to reopen 48 hours after the declaration of financial results</li><li>Announcement in accordance with Securities and Exchange Board of India regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/17e0f264-19de-4473-baac-8694bb83e0b1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Globale Tessile Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>