<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 21:32:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[BBOX] Black Box Ltd Allots 8,179 Equity Shares After Conversion of Warrants</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Black+Box+Ltd&title=Black+Box+Ltd+Allots+8%2C179+Equity+Shares+After+Conversion+of+Warrants&newsId=a63a8134-b0d5-4302-b140-b7d15277eba2&token=YTYzYTgxMzQtYjBk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a63a8134-b0d5-4302-b140-b7d15277eba2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Black Box Ltd has allotted 8,179 equity shares to Manish Agarwal, a non-promoter, following the conversion of warrants. The allotment was made at a premium of Rs. 415/- per share, with 25% of the total consideration already received at the time of allotment of warrants. The balance consideration was received at the time of current conversion. This allotment has increased the issued, subscribed, and paid-up capital of the company to Rs. 34,09,81,444/-. As of the current date, 70,04,533 warrants are still outstanding for conversion.</p><ul><li>Black Box Ltd has allotted 8,179 equity shares to Manish Agarwal.</li><li>The allotment was made following the conversion of warrants.</li><li>The allotment was made at a premium of Rs. 415/- per share.</li><li>This allotment has increased the issued, subscribed, and paid-up capital of the company.</li><li>70,04,533 warrants are still outstanding for conversion.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ebd3fcc5-a668-459f-9e3a-751bf81e30c5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Black Box Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VIKRAMSOLR] Vikram Solar Ltd Renews and Enhances Working Capital Facilities, Releases Promoter&apos;s Pledge</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vikram+Solar+Ltd&title=Vikram+Solar+Ltd+Renews+and+Enhances+Working+Capital+Facilities%2C+Releases+Promoter%27s+Pledge&newsId=41333268-3bf1-4f5e-bfb7-62cfd21972b3&token=NDEzMzMyNjgtM2Jm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41333268-3bf1-4f5e-bfb7-62cfd21972b3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vikram Solar Limited has entered into a working capital consortium agreement led by Indian Bank for renewal and enhancement of its existing working capital facilities. The agreement, which allows for up to Rs. 3,200 crores in fund-based and non-fund-based working capital facilities, will result in the release of 9,49,60,893 equity shares of the Company, equivalent to 26.21% of the total equity share capital, which were earlier pledged by the promoters for securing earlier working capital facilities.</p><ul><li>Vikram Solar Ltd has renewed and enhanced its working capital facilities up to Rs. 3,200 crores</li><li>The renewal cum enhancement of working capital facilities is led by Indian Bank</li><li>Existing pledge of 9,49,60,893 equity shares by promoters will be released</li><li>The facilities are secured by a first pari-passu charge over the Company’s current assets and other specified securities</li><li>The facilities are governed by individual sanction letters carrying interest linked to the applicable MCLR/EBLR rates</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f07bf877-16cd-4e53-ae12-1f3f278b7d07.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vikram Solar Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BAFNAPHARM] Bafna Pharmaceuticals Ltd. Reports Q3 and Nine-Months Unaudited Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BAFNA+PHARMACEUTICALS+LTD.&title=Bafna+Pharmaceuticals+Ltd.+Reports+Q3+and+Nine-Months+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=b99505dc-74e0-457a-b773-abc6b64b13ae&token=Yjk5NTA1ZGMtNzRl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b99505dc-74e0-457a-b773-abc6b64b13ae</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 18:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bafna Pharmaceuticals Ltd. announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at INR 3,828.58 crores for the nine-month period. The total income, including other income, amounts to INR 4,008.62 crores. The company reported a profit before tax of INR 3,664.79 crores and earnings per equity share of INR 1.76. The financial results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for Q3 and nine-months ended December 31, 2025: INR 1,485.99 crores and INR 3,828.58 crores respectively.</li><li>Total income for Q3 and nine-months ended December 31, 2025: INR 1,637.27 crores and INR 4,008.62 crores respectively.</li><li>Profit before tax for Q3 and nine-months ended December 31, 2025: INR 273.13 crores and INR 3,664.79 crores respectively.</li><li>Earnings per equity share for Q3 and nine-months ended December 31, 2025: INR 0.88 and INR 1.76 respectively.</li><li>The financial results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/161123a6-3901-4a28-9f9a-194a42a07872.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BAFNA PHARMACEUTICALS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VALIANTLAB] Valiant Laboratories Utilizes Rights Issue Proceeds Appropriately, According to India Ratings and Research Report</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Valiant+Laboratories+Ltd&title=Valiant+Laboratories+Utilizes+Rights+Issue+Proceeds+Appropriately%2C+According+to+India+Ratings+and+Research+Report&newsId=63e25592-c83c-493c-8695-f8870833a41c&token=NjNlMjU1OTItYzgz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63e25592-c83c-493c-8695-f8870833a41c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 18:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Valiant Laboratories Ltd has utilized the proceeds from its Rights Issue, which was made through the Letter of Offer dated July 15, 2025, appropriately for the objects mentioned in the offer document. This is according to the Monitoring Agency Report issued by India Ratings and Research Private Limited for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The report has been reviewed by the Audit Committee and Board of Directors at their meeting(s) held on February 11, 2026.</p><ul><li>Valiant Laboratories has utilized the proceeds from its Rights Issue appropriately for the objects mentioned in the offer document</li><li>The Monitoring Agency Report has been reviewed by the Audit Committee and Board of Directors</li><li>The report was issued by India Ratings and Research Private Limited</li><li>The report is in line with the format prescribed by SEBI</li><li>There is no conflict of interest in the relationship between the Monitoring Agency and the issuer</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d820867d-0cea-4c0c-ba61-c35918d6a0b5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Valiant Laboratories Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RAPICUT] Rapicut Carbides Ltd. Announces Q3 Results with Revenue of INR 4,198.64 Lakhs and Basic Earnings Per Share of INR 4.33</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RAPICUT+CARBIDES+LTD.&title=Rapicut+Carbides+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+Results+with+Revenue+of+INR+4%2C198.64+Lakhs+and+Basic+Earnings+Per+Share+of+INR+4.33&newsId=3e1baa83-5d64-4089-8aaf-1d3fb5757cc0&token=M2UxYmFhODMtNWQ2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e1baa83-5d64-4089-8aaf-1d3fb5757cc0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 18:02:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rapicut Carbides Ltd. has announced the financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at INR 2,077.73 Lakhs for the quarter and INR 4,697.28 Lakhs for the nine months period. The cost of materials consumed is INR 2,978.73 Lakhs, employee benefits expense is INR 36.02 Lakhs, and finance costs are INR 29.56 Lakhs. The company&apos;s basic earnings per share is INR 4.33 and diluted earnings per share is also INR 4.33. The financial results have been reviewed and recommended by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter is INR 2,077.73 Lakhs</li><li>Revenue from operations for the nine months period is INR 4,697.28 Lakhs</li><li>Cost of materials consumed is INR 2,978.73 Lakhs</li><li>Basic earnings per share is INR 4.33</li><li>Diluted earnings per share is also INR 4.33</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/574ed7dc-a692-4052-80fa-45facc061cca.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RAPICUT CARBIDES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MARUTISE] Maruti Securities Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025, With Net Profit of Rs. 1.90 Lakhs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MARUTI+SECURITIES+LTD.&title=Maruti+Securities+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025%2C+With+Net+Profit+of+Rs.+1.90+Lakhs&newsId=8c019efe-4167-42cf-8ad9-763c175fe63e&token=OGMwMTllZmUtNDE2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c019efe-4167-42cf-8ad9-763c175fe63e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 18:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Maruti Securities Ltd, now known as Maruti Global Industries Limited, has reported its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The board of directors considered and approved the standalone financial results, which were reviewed by the audit committee and approved in a meeting on 11.02.2026. The results were prepared in accordance with Ind AS 34 - Interim Financial Reporting and Section 133 of the Companies Act, 2013. The company reported a net profit of Rs. 1.90 Lakhs for the quarter, but the accumulated losses of Rs. 2644.38 Lakhs have eroded the company’s net worth. Despite this, the management believes that the company’s going concern status remains unaffected due to the change in management and induction of new promoters with a strong background in the infrastructure sector. The company has resumed its operations in alignment with the promoters’ core business expertise and prepared the financials on a going-concern basis.</p><ul><li>Unaudited Standalone Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025 approved</li><li>Net profit of Rs. 1.90 Lakhs for the quarter</li><li>Accumulated losses of Rs. 2644.38 Lakhs, eroding the company’s net worth</li><li>Going concern status remains unaffected due to change in management and new promoters</li><li>Company has resumed operations in alignment with promoters’ core business expertise</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/572a550c-9699-451e-a3b5-f03f319563b0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MARUTI SECURITIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GODREJIND] Godrej Industries Approves Unaudited Financial Results for Quarter and Nine Months Ended December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GODREJ+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Godrej+Industries+Approves+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Quarter+and+Nine+Months+Ended+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=960a3aea-1305-435e-8d30-d57c16f0f5f9&token=OTYwYTNhZWEtMTMw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">960a3aea-1305-435e-8d30-d57c16f0f5f9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 18:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Godrej Industries Limited held a Board Meeting on February 11, 2026, where they approved the unaudited financial results (standalone and consolidated) for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The Statutory Auditors, Kalyaniwalla &amp; Mistry LLP, have issued an unmodified conclusion with respect to these results. The Company&apos;s revenue and net profit for the nine months ended December 31, 2025, are Rs. 11,421.66 crore and Rs. 1,788.65 crore, respectively. The consolidated financial results include the results of 55 subsidiaries, one associate, and 24 joint ventures, whose interim financial results have been reviewed by other auditors. The results of three subsidiaries and three joint ventures have not been reviewed by their auditors, but they are not considered material to the Group.</p><ul><li>Godrej Industries approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The Statutory Auditors, Kalyaniwalla &amp; Mistry LLP, issued an unmodified conclusion on the results.</li><li>The Company&apos;s revenue for the nine months ended December 31, 2025, is Rs. 11,421.66 crore.</li><li>The consolidated financial results include the results of 55 subsidiaries, one associate, and 24 joint ventures.</li><li>The results of three subsidiaries and three joint ventures have not been reviewed by their auditors.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8f35626c-3de7-43fa-9d12-e90317586701.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GODREJ INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MEGRISOFT] Megri Soft Ltd Subsidiary Allots Equity Shares to Director, Diluting Company&apos;s Stake to 62.50%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Megri+Soft+Ltd&title=Megri+Soft+Ltd+Subsidiary+Allots+Equity+Shares+to+Director%2C+Diluting+Company%27s+Stake+to+62.50%25&newsId=874bacef-7cea-4fad-b9f8-b044c2c0faa2&token=ODc0YmFjZWYtN2Nl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">874bacef-7cea-4fad-b9f8-b044c2c0faa2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:59:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Subsidiary Allotment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Megri Soft Ltd announced that its subsidiary, Megrisoft Limited, has allotted 60 equity shares of GBP 1 each at par to Aprajita Kohli, Director of Megri Soft Limited and Megrisoft Limited, who is also a related party. The allotment increased Megrisoft Limited&apos;s total paid-up equity share capital from 100 to 160 equity shares of GBP 1 each, diluting the Company&apos;s stake from 100% to 62.50%. The transaction does not have a material impact on the financial position or operations of the Company.</p><ul><li>Megrisoft Limited allotted 60 equity shares to Aprajita Kohli, diluting Megri Soft Ltd&apos;s stake to 62.50%</li><li>The transaction does not have a material impact on the Company&apos;s financial position or operations</li><li>Megrisoft Limited is a UK-based subsidiary of Megri Soft Ltd</li><li>Aprajita Kohli is a Director in both Megri Soft Limited and Megrisoft Limited</li><li>The allotment was approved by the Audit Committee and Board of Directors of Megri Soft Ltd</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cdb8e53a-365f-438c-9f0b-74882ac9414d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Megri Soft Ltd | Category: Subsidiary Allotment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TALBROAUTO] Talbros Automotive Components Ltd. Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025, Reshuffles Top Management</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TALBROS+AUTOMOTIVE+COMPONENTS+LTD.&title=Talbros+Automotive+Components+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Reshuffles+Top+Management&newsId=2ec94f93-b89b-4686-8eb4-2ee9e732c6cc&token=MmVjOTRmOTMtYjg5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ec94f93-b89b-4686-8eb4-2ee9e732c6cc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:58:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Talbros Automotive Components Ltd. announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s Board of Directors, in a meeting held on 11th February 2026, approved these results. The Board also approved several key management changes, including the resignation of Naresh Talwar as Chairman, the elevation of Umesh Talwar as Executive Chairman, the appointment of Anuj Talwar as Managing Director, and the appointment of Varun Talwar as Vice Chairman and Managing Director. These changes will be effective from 1st April 2026. The company has also fixed Monday, 23rd February 2026, as the cut-off date to determine the eligible shareholders for the Postal Ballot process.</p><ul><li>Talbros Automotive Components Ltd. announced its unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December 2025.</li><li>Naresh Talwar will step down as Chairman on 31st March 2026 and continue as Non-Executive Director.</li><li>Umesh Talwar will be elevated as Executive Chairman-Whole Time Director for a period of three years from 1st April 2026.</li><li>Anuj Talwar will be appointed as Managing Director for a period of three years from 1st April 2026.</li><li>Varun Talwar will be appointed as Vice Chairman and Managing Director for a period of three years from 1st April 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9a08fa46-a7aa-4c6d-8276-cf6e7b75fc91.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TALBROS AUTOMOTIVE COMPONENTS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DHUNINV] Dhunseri Investments Ltd: Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended 31st December 2025 Approved</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DHUNSERI+INVESTMENTS+LTD.&title=Dhunseri+Investments+Ltd%3A+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+31st+December+2025+Approved&newsId=26a2475e-2687-4c79-ac9d-f3cedb040941&token=MjZhMjQ3NWUtMjY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26a2475e-2687-4c79-ac9d-f3cedb040941</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 17:58:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dhunseri Investments Ltd announced the outcome of its Board Meeting held on 11th February, 2026. The Board approved and took on record the unaudited financial results (standalone and consolidated) for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The company has also appointed Ms. Payal Kumari Shaw as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer. The review report for the unaudited standalone quarterly financial results was conducted by U S Agarwal &amp; Associates India Chartered Accountants.</p><ul><li>Unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December, 2025 approved</li><li>Ms. Payal Kumari Shaw appointed as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer</li><li>Review report conducted by U S Agarwal &amp; Associates India Chartered Accountants</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/86e2b7c0-4d17-4207-a7b2-775c19c20f88.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DHUNSERI INVESTMENTS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>