<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:44:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SWATIPRO] Swati Projects Ltd Announces Resignation of Managing Director Shreegopal Daga</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Swati+Projects+Ltd&title=Swati+Projects+Ltd+Announces+Resignation+of+Managing+Director+Shreegopal+Daga&newsId=91650f1f-1c01-4f05-bc7a-33fdf8ef0e43&token=OTE2NTBmMWYtMWMw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">91650f1f-1c01-4f05-bc7a-33fdf8ef0e43</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Swati Projects Ltd has announced the resignation of its Managing Director, Mr. Shreegopal Daga, due to his age (86 years old) and personal health issues. The resignation will take effect from the closure of business hours on February 24, 2026. The company&apos;s Board of Directors took note of this resignation in a meeting held on February 24, 2026. Mr. Ravi Todi, Whole Time Director, has been authorized to sign and file necessary forms with the Registrar of Companies regarding the resignation.</p><ul><li>Swati Projects Ltd announces resignation of Managing Director Shreegopal Daga</li><li>Resignation due to age (86 years old) and health issues</li><li>Resignation to take effect from February 24, 2026</li><li>Board of Directors took note of the resignation in a meeting held on February 24, 2026</li><li>Ravi Todi authorized to sign and file necessary forms with the Registrar of Companies</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/edf5d72c-d1b8-446a-8517-7f57c1a5a4c8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Swati Projects Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RIDDHICORP] Riddhi Corporate Services Ltd. Board Approves Object Clause Deviation in IPO, Appoints Secretarial Auditor, and Sets Postal Ballot</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Riddhi+Corporate+Services+Ltd&title=Riddhi+Corporate+Services+Ltd.+Board+Approves+Object+Clause+Deviation+in+IPO%2C+Appoints+Secretarial+Auditor%2C+and+Sets+Postal+Ballot&newsId=97bfa91b-eb85-4772-ac15-febf61de2b6e&token=OTdiZmE5MWItZWI4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97bfa91b-eb85-4772-ac15-febf61de2b6e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:38:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Riddhi Corporate Services Ltd. announced that its board has approved deviations in the object clause of its initial public offering (IPO). The board also appointed M/s Amrish Gandhi &amp; Associates as the secretarial auditor for five years starting from the financial year 2025-2026 to 2029-2030. Additionally, the board considered and approved the Postal Ballot Notice &amp; Calendar of Events for seeking approval of the members in respect of the agenda items and appointed M/s. Samsad Alam Khan, Practicing Company Secretary as Scrutinizer for E-Voting Process for Postal Ballot. National Securities Depository Limited (NSDL) was appointed as the Remote E-Voting Agency for resolutions proposed to be passed via Postal Ballot.</p><ul><li>Board approved deviations in the object clause of the IPO</li><li>M/s Amrish Gandhi &amp; Associates appointed as secretarial auditor for 5 years</li><li>Postal Ballot Notice &amp; Calendar of Events approved</li><li>M/s. Samsad Alam Khan appointed as Scrutinizer for E-Voting Process</li><li>National Securities Depository Limited (NSDL) appointed as Remote E-Voting Agency</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f9599121-7812-4fee-ac09-667a3ad5c767.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Riddhi Corporate Services Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HEMORGANIC] Hemo Organic Ltd. Approves Allotment of 34 Lakh Convertible Warrants at Rs. 12.50 Each to Non-Promoter Entities</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Hemo+Organic+Limited&title=Hemo+Organic+Ltd.+Approves+Allotment+of+34+Lakh+Convertible+Warrants+at+Rs.+12.50+Each+to+Non-Promoter+Entities&newsId=cec4fd59-21a3-4aff-a9ee-dd55f8678a8d&token=Y2VjNGZkNTktMjFh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cec4fd59-21a3-4aff-a9ee-dd55f8678a8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:35:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Hemo Organic Ltd. announced the outcome of its Board Meeting held on Thursday, 26th February, 2026. The Board approved the allotment of 34,00,000 (Thirty-Four Lakhs) Convertible Warrants to entities belonging to the &apos;Non-Promoter Category&apos; on a preferential basis. Each warrant is priced at Rs. 12.50 (Rupees Twelve and Fifty Paisa Only), which includes a premium of Rs. 02.50 (Rupees Two and Fifty Paisa Only). The warrants can be converted into one fully paid-up Equity share of the Company having a face value of Rs. 10.00/- (Rupees Ten Only) each within 18 (Eighteen) months from the date of allotment. Post-conversion, the Paid-up Equity Share Capital of the Company will increase from Rs. 3,46,59,000/- divided into 34,65,900 Equity shares to Rs. 6,86,59,000/- divided into 68,65,900 Equity shares. The Company also announced the shifting of its Registered Office within the same city.</p><ul><li>Hemo Organic Ltd. approved the allotment of 34 Lakh Convertible Warrants to non-promoter entities.</li><li>Each warrant is priced at Rs. 12.50 with a premium of Rs. 02.50.</li><li>Warrants can be converted into Equity shares within 18 months from the date of allotment.</li><li>Post-conversion, the Paid-up Equity Share Capital will increase to Rs. 6,86,59,000 divided into 68,65,900 Equity shares.</li><li>The Company&apos;s Registered Office will be shifted within the same city.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ee04be0a-732f-4130-96ee-530c2b7ae5ee.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Hemo Organic Limited | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[QPOWER] Quality Power Electrical Equipments Ltd Receives Multiple Orders for 800 KV Coil Products Worth INR 146 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Quality+Power+Electrical+Equipments+Ltd&title=Quality+Power+Electrical+Equipments+Ltd+Receives+Multiple+Orders+for+800+KV+Coil+Products+Worth+INR+146+Crores&newsId=ee575a1f-470c-46f0-b217-0a583d7b80a5&token=ZWU1NzVhMWYtNDcw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee575a1f-470c-46f0-b217-0a583d7b80a5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Quality Power Electrical Equipments Limited has received multiple purchase orders for the supply of 800 KV Coil Products, with a gross value of approximately INR 146 Crores (Including Taxes). The orders are expected to be executed within approximately 18 months. The name of the entity awarding the order has not been disclosed due to a Non-Disclosure agreement. The orders do not fall under related party transactions and are done at &apos;arm’s length&apos;.</p><ul><li>Received multiple purchase orders for 800 KV Coil Products</li><li>Gross value of approximately INR 146 Crores (Including Taxes)</li><li>Expected execution period of approximately 18 months</li><li>Non-Disclosure agreement with the entity awarding the order</li><li>Not a related party transaction</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c6da97e9-0716-44a0-aceb-fbbb34be4a11.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Quality Power Electrical Equipments Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BMWVENTLTD] BMW Ventures Secures Largest Order Worth 36 Crore for Structural Steel Supply</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BMW+Ventures+Ltd&title=BMW+Ventures+Secures+Largest+Order+Worth+36+Crore+for+Structural+Steel+Supply&newsId=c94624a6-921c-4427-9c00-c90abd4d68c9&token=Yzk0NjI0YTYtOTIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c94624a6-921c-4427-9c00-c90abd4d68c9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>BMW Ventures Ltd has received the largest order of worth 36 Crore for the supply of Structural Steel for Bharat Heavy Electricals Limited (BHEL) Project in the Fabricated Steel Manufacturing Division. The payment will be done on delivery, and the supply is to be completed within 10 months from the date of the Purchase Order. The customer&apos;s name cannot be disclosed due to confidentiality. This order is a domestic one and does not involve any related party transactions.</p><ul><li>BMW Ventures secures largest order worth 36 Crore</li><li>Order for supply of Structural Steel for Bharat Heavy Electricals Limited (BHEL) Project</li><li>Payment to be done on delivery</li><li>Supply to be completed within 10 months from the date of Purchase Order</li><li>Domestic order; no related party transactions involved</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/072cc797-7d07-4bca-9dd5-4c86c3af677d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BMW Ventures Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RIDDHICORP] Riddhi Corporate Services Ltd: Board Approves Object Clause Deviation in IPO, Appoints Secretarial Auditor, and More</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Riddhi+Corporate+Services+Ltd&title=Riddhi+Corporate+Services+Ltd%3A+Board+Approves+Object+Clause+Deviation+in+IPO%2C+Appoints+Secretarial+Auditor%2C+and+More&newsId=44a5ca30-fa8f-4091-a8b3-afc909e78ac8&token=NDRhNWNhMzAtZmE4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">44a5ca30-fa8f-4091-a8b3-afc909e78ac8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Riddhi Corporate Services Ltd, in a meeting held on February 26, 2026, approved several key decisions. These include the deviation in the object clause of the initial public issue, appointment of M/s Amrish Gandhi &amp; Associates as Secretarial Auditor for five years, approval of the Postal Ballot Notice &amp; Calendar of Events, appointment of M/s. Samsad Alam Khan as Scrutinizer for E-Voting Process, and appointment of National Securities Depository Limited as Remote E-Voting Agency. All these decisions are subject to the approval of the shareholders of the Company.</p><ul><li>Board approves deviation in object clause of initial public issue</li><li>M/s Amrish Gandhi &amp; Associates appointed as Secretarial Auditor for 5 years</li><li>Postal Ballot Notice &amp; Calendar of Events approved</li><li>M/s. Samsad Alam Khan appointed as Scrutinizer for E-Voting Process</li><li>National Securities Depository Limited appointed as Remote E-Voting Agency</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/719a3560-e50d-4687-901b-f22b7783c666.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Riddhi Corporate Services Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RVNL] Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd Secures LOA from NMDC for Construction of Residential Towers Worth Rs. 796.80 Crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Rail+Vikas+Nigam+Ltd&title=Rail+Vikas+Nigam+Ltd+Secures+LOA+from+NMDC+for+Construction+of+Residential+Towers+Worth+Rs.+796.80+Crore&newsId=5b64b577-2f0f-4313-8757-967f9cda87d4&token=NWI2NGI1NzctMmYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b64b577-2f0f-4313-8757-967f9cda87d4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd has announced that it has received a Letter of Award (LOA) from National Mineral Development Corporation (NMDC) Limited for the construction of residential towers at Iron Ore Deposit-5, Bacheli, Chhattisgarh. The project cost is Rs. 796.80 Crore and it is expected to be completed in 34 months. This is a domestic order and does not involve any related party transactions.</p><ul><li>Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd has received a LOA from NMDC Limited for a construction project worth Rs. 796.80 Crore.</li><li>The project involves the construction of residential towers at Iron Ore Deposit-5, Bacheli, Chhattisgarh.</li><li>The project is expected to be completed in 34 months.</li><li>This is a domestic order and does not involve any related party transactions.</li><li>The announcement was made in accordance with Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a68aff92-470e-4c1d-85b1-50970fb9057e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MOTILALOFS] Motilal Oswal Alternates Achieves First Close of Maiden Private Credit Fund at INR 1,700 Crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MOTILAL+OSWAL+FINANCIAL+SERVICES+LTD.&title=Motilal+Oswal+Alternates+Achieves+First+Close+of+Maiden+Private+Credit+Fund+at+INR+1%2C700+Crore&newsId=e2e902e8-3688-462d-94d4-aa4cc1570ef8&token=ZTJlOTAyZTgtMzY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e2e902e8-3688-462d-94d4-aa4cc1570ef8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Motilal Oswal Alternates, a leading full-spectrum alternatives platform, has announced the first close of its maiden private credit fund, India Credit Excellence Fund, at INR 1,700 crore. The Fund, launched in January 2026, targets a total corpus of INR 3,000 crore including a green shoe option of INR 1,500 Crore. The final close is envisaged in the near term and the Fund has a strong pipeline of investment opportunities. This milestone marks a significant step in Motilal Oswal Alternates’ evolution towards becoming a multi-asset alternatives platform, coinciding with its 20-year journey in the alternatives space.</p><ul><li>Motilal Oswal Alternates achieves first close of maiden private credit fund at INR 1,700 Crore</li><li>Targets a total corpus of INR 3,000 Crore including a green shoe option of INR 1,500 Crore</li><li>Strong pipeline of investment opportunities</li><li>Significant step in Motilal Oswal Alternates’ evolution towards becoming a multi-asset alternatives platform</li><li>20-year journey in the alternatives space</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/18d65dec-565f-4f32-8682-77f40fc12962.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MOTILAL OSWAL FINANCIAL SERVICES LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MOTISONS] Motisons Jewellers Ltd. Approves Allotment of Equity Shares Upon Conversion of Warrants</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Motisons+Jewellers+Ltd&title=Motisons+Jewellers+Ltd.+Approves+Allotment+of+Equity+Shares+Upon+Conversion+of+Warrants&newsId=70107592-51c9-4d9b-83b7-dd2f24a31c89&token=NzAxMDc1OTItNTFj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70107592-51c9-4d9b-83b7-dd2f24a31c89</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:23:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Motisons Jewellers Ltd. has approved the allotment of 54,00,000 equity shares at an issue price of Rs. 17/- each, including a premium of Rs. 16/- each, to Nexpact Limited. This allotment is pursuant to the conversion of 5,40,000 warrants out of the outstanding 26,00,000 warrants issued at an issue price of Rs. 170/- each. The warrants were allotted to Nexpact Limited, a non-promoter public category, on a preferential basis. The new equity shares will rank pari-passu with the existing equity shares of the Company.</p><ul><li>Motisons Jewellers Ltd. approves allotment of 54,00,000 equity shares</li><li>Allotment is pursuant to the conversion of 5,40,000 warrants</li><li>Warrants were allotted to Nexpact Limited, a non-promoter public category</li><li>New equity shares will rank pari-passu with existing shares</li><li>82,70,000 total warrants are still outstanding for conversion</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/71088a22-ba1a-491f-a564-969456d36048.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Motisons Jewellers Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RVNL] Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd Receives LOA from NMDC for Construction of Residential Towers in Chhattisgarh</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Rail+Vikas+Nigam+Ltd&title=Rail+Vikas+Nigam+Ltd+Receives+LOA+from+NMDC+for+Construction+of+Residential+Towers+in+Chhattisgarh&newsId=c7162c86-6c47-475b-a735-0279e0226d05&token=YzcxNjJjODYtNmM0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7162c86-6c47-475b-a735-0279e0226d05</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 09:22:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd has announced the receipt of a Letter of Award (LOA) from National Mineral Development Corporation (NMDC) Limited for the construction of residential towers at Iron Ore Deposit-10/11A at Bacheli, Chhattisgarh. The project cost is Rs. 536.40 Crore (Rubéég Five Hundred Thirty Six Crores Forty Lakhs Only) and is expected to be completed in 34 months. This is a domestic order and does not involve any related party transactions.</p><ul><li>Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd receives LOA from NMDC Limited</li><li>Construction of Residential Towers at Iron Ore Deposit-10/11A at Bacheli, Chhattisgarh</li><li>Project cost is Rs. 536.40 Crore</li><li>Expected to be completed in 34 months</li><li>Domestic order, not a related party transaction</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9afdc11d-0e3e-4aa5-9e78-6baf07d3d45a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>