<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:31:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[LLOYDSTEEL] Lloyds Engineering Works Ltd Approves First and Final Call on Rights Issue Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Lloyds+Steels+Industries+Ltd&title=Lloyds+Engineering+Works+Ltd+Approves+First+and+Final+Call+on+Rights+Issue+Equity+Shares&newsId=f03d7ddc-af42-4284-ad76-7fcb9a25ebe6&token=ZjAzZDdkZGMtYWY0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f03d7ddc-af42-4284-ad76-7fcb9a25ebe6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Rights Issue</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Lloyds Engineering Works Ltd has approved the making of First and Final Call on partly paid-up equity shares of Rs. 32/- per Equity share i.e. at Rs. 16/- per Equity share. The Record Date for the purpose of determining the holders of partly paid-up equity shares to whom the First and Final Call notice will be sent for payment of remaining 50% of the call is fixed as January 28, 2026. The call money payment period opens on February 17, 2026 and closes on March 4, 2026. The trading for partly paid-up equity shares of the Company on the Stock Exchanges will be suspended after the closure of trading hours of Tuesday, January 27, 2026.</p><ul><li>Lloyds Engineering Works Ltd approves First and Final Call on partly paid-up equity shares of Rs. 32/- per Equity share i.e. at Rs. 16/- per Equity share.</li><li>Record Date for the purpose of determining the holders of partly paid-up equity shares is fixed as January 28, 2026.</li><li>Call money payment period opens on February 17, 2026 and closes on March 4, 2026.</li><li>Trading for partly paid-up equity shares of the Company on the Stock Exchanges will be suspended after the closure of trading hours of Tuesday, January 27, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3a3b299a-ed1b-40c0-99e9-a24bfb4f2e3c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Lloyds Steels Industries Ltd | Category: Rights Issue</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DPL] Dipna Pharmachem Ltd Denies Price Sensitive Info Behind Stock Price Movement</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Dipna+Pharmachem+Ltd&title=Dipna+Pharmachem+Ltd+Denies+Price+Sensitive+Info+Behind+Stock+Price+Movement&newsId=de3bb031-39af-4754-9116-f4f8019a2ddf&token=ZGUzYmIwMzEtMzlh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de3bb031-39af-4754-9116-f4f8019a2ddf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dipna Pharmachem Ltd has clarified that there is no price sensitive or material information that has resulted in the significant movement of their stock price. The company has made all required disclosures under the SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. There is currently no event or information that needs to be reported to the Stock Exchange. The volatility in the price of the company’s script on the Stock Exchange is natural and market-driven.</p><ul><li>Dipna Pharmachem Ltd has no price sensitive information leading to stock price movement</li><li>All required disclosures under SEBI regulations have been made</li><li>No event or information needs to be reported to the Stock Exchange</li><li>Stock price volatility is natural and market-driven</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e5c47b54-27b7-4ab5-910c-e8818b4297ba.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Dipna Pharmachem Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHINEFASH] Shine Fashions (India) Ltd Approves Release of 4,55,000 Bonus Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shine+Fashions+%28India%29+Ltd&title=Shine+Fashions+%28India%29+Ltd+Approves+Release+of+4%2C55%2C000+Bonus+Equity+Shares&newsId=196eb56d-d6ea-4604-b8ba-0f01190dda6d&token=MTk2ZWI1NmQtZDZl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">196eb56d-d6ea-4604-b8ba-0f01190dda6d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Bonus</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shine Fashions (India) Ltd has approved the release of 4,55,000 fully paid-up Bonus Equity Shares of Rs. 5/- each in the proportion of 7:1. The shares were previously reserved for holding outstanding convertible warrants as on the record date fixed for this purpose. The paid-up share capital of the Company has increased from Rs. 12,42,85,000/- divided into 2,48,57,000 Fully Paid-up Equity Shares of Rs. 5/- each to Rs. 12,65,60,000/- divided into 25312000 Fully Paid-up Equity Shares of Rs. 5/- each. The Bonus Equity Shares allotted shall rank pari-passu in all respect and carry the same rights as the exiting equity shares of the Company. The meeting of the Board of Directors commenced at 11.00 a.m. and concluded at 11.40 p.m.</p><ul><li>Shine Fashions (India) Ltd has approved the release of 4,55,000 Bonus Equity Shares</li><li>The shares were previously reserved for holding outstanding convertible warrants</li><li>The paid-up share capital of the Company has increased from Rs. 12,42,85,000/- to Rs. 12,65,60,000/-</li><li>The Bonus Equity Shares allotted shall rank pari-passu in all respect</li><li>The meeting of the Board of Directors commenced at 11.00 a.m. and concluded at 11.40 p.m.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7c38fd00-d267-4b6c-bc1a-ddb3d450578c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shine Fashions (India) Ltd | Category: Bonus</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HERITGFOOD] Heritage Foods to Receive GST Refund of Rs. 77.95 Lakhs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Heritage+Foods+Limited&title=Heritage+Foods+to+Receive+GST+Refund+of+Rs.+77.95+Lakhs&newsId=6704aa63-9275-40a6-881d-1b7762f01d2a&token=NjcwNGFhNjMtOTI3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6704aa63-9275-40a6-881d-1b7762f01d2a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:26:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>GST Refund</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Heritage Foods Ltd. is set to receive a GST refund of Rs. 77.95 Lakhs pursuant to the refund sanction/release orders issued by the Office of the Assistant Commissioner, Central Tax. The refund is in relation to a GST refund application dated 27-11-2025 filed by the Company for the GST refund amounting to the same amount. The refund covers CGST, SGST, and IGST components.</p><ul><li>Heritage Foods Ltd. to receive a GST refund of Rs. 77.95 Lakhs</li><li>Refund sanction/release orders have been passed through form RFD-06</li><li>Refund is in relation to a GST refund application dated 27-11-2025</li><li>The refund covers CGST, SGST, and IGST components</li><li>The refund is pursuant to the favorable orders passed by the Additional Commissioner, Appeals, Central Tax, dated 25-11-2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c07d4c08-0b7c-43dd-9541-abca327cc711.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Heritage Foods Limited | Category: GST Refund</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BUILDPRO] Shankara Buildpro Ltd to Approve Q3 &amp; HY 2025 Unaudited Financial Results on Jan 29, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shankara+Buildpro+Ltd&title=Shankara+Buildpro+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+%26+HY+2025+Unaudited+Financial+Results+on+Jan+29%2C+2026&newsId=289aa85f-638e-4a1e-8eb7-4912a45e6ec2&token=Mjg5YWE4NWYtNjM4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">289aa85f-638e-4a1e-8eb7-4912a45e6ec2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:23:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shankara Buildpro Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 29, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and half year ended 30 September, 2025. The meeting is in accordance with the SEBI Listing Regulations and the approval of Listing and Trading has been granted, effective January 9, 2026. The trading window for dealing in securities of the Company for Directors, Promoters, Designated Employees and the Connected Person has been closed from January 9, 2026 till 48 hours after the results are made public. The notice of the Board Meeting is available on the Company&apos;s website as per regulation 46(2) of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Shankara Buildpro Ltd to approve Q3 &amp; HY 2025 Unaudited Financial Results on Jan 29, 2026</li><li>The meeting is in accordance with the SEBI Listing Regulations</li><li>Approval of Listing and Trading granted effective January 9, 2026</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities closed from Jan 9, 2026 till 48 hours after results are made public</li><li>Notice of the Board Meeting available on the Company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c86d70a4-565b-4f9a-9502-0f77ed15669c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shankara Buildpro Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TTL] T T Ltd. to Approve Un-Audited Financial Results for Q3 2025 in Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=T+T+LTD.-%24&title=T+T+Ltd.+to+Approve+Un-Audited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+2025+in+Board+Meeting&newsId=7ccb4af0-2397-40c9-a3a8-9ed503676276&token=N2NjYjRhZjAtMjM5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ccb4af0-2397-40c9-a3a8-9ed503676276</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>T T Ltd. has informed the BSE that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on 28th January 2026 to consider and approve the Un-Audited Financial Results for the third quarter ended 31st December 2025. The trading window, as per the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015 and the Company&apos;s code for Prevention of Insider Trading, is closed from 1st January 2026 and will reopen after 48 hours from the date of announcement/declaration of the Un-Audited Financial Results.</p><ul><li>T T Ltd. to consider and approve Un-Audited Financial Results for Q3 2025</li><li>Board Meeting scheduled on 28th January 2026</li><li>Trading window closed from 1st January 2026</li><li>Trading window to reopen after 48 hours from the date of announcement/declaration of Un-Audited Financial Results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/eb6bbecf-6c68-4294-b396-24c05642c73d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: T T LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAINDUS] Sai Industries Ltd to Approve Q3 2026 Financial Results on Jan 24</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SAI+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Sai+Industries+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+2026+Financial+Results+on+Jan+24&newsId=780d3f41-bced-4245-af74-07add594e81a&token=NzgwZDNmNDEtYmNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">780d3f41-bced-4245-af74-07add594e81a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:18:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sai Industries Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 24, 2026, at 5:00 PM to consider and approve the unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2026. This is in accordance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Sai Industries Ltd to hold a Board Meeting on January 24, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the unaudited standalone financial results for Q3 2026</li><li>The meeting is in accordance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (LODR) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6013f039-6731-4914-bc5c-6a3c2ecb6106.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SAI INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ECORECO] Eco Recycling Ltd: Special Resolution for QIP Now Time-Barred by Law</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ECO+RECYCLING+LTD.&title=Eco+Recycling+Ltd%3A+Special+Resolution+for+QIP+Now+Time-Barred+by+Law&newsId=019aeb3e-9aac-408f-ab73-d58abdce47c4&token=MDE5YWViM2UtOWFh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">019aeb3e-9aac-408f-ab73-d58abdce47c4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Eco Recycling Ltd&apos;s Special Resolution for Qualified Institutional Placement (QIP), approved on January 22, 2025, was valid for 365 days. However, as the resolution has now been time-barred by law, all ancillary QIP offer proposals, agreements entered into with parties are deemed null and void.</p><ul><li>Eco Recycling Ltd&apos;s Special Resolution for QIP is now time-barred by law</li><li>The resolution was approved on January 22, 2025, and was valid for 365 days</li><li>All ancillary QIP offer proposals and agreements entered into with parties are null and void</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/35a9ccce-d203-46b7-8c23-99931f1075e8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ECO RECYCLING LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CHOWGULSTM] Ashok Chowgule Acquires 1,14,210 Shares of Chowgule Steamships Ltd via Off-Market Gift</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CHOWGULE+STEAMSHIPS+LTD.&title=Ashok+Chowgule+Acquires+1%2C14%2C210+Shares+of+Chowgule+Steamships+Ltd+via+Off-Market+Gift&newsId=1724952a-216c-41d2-840f-ec571461598a&token=MTcyNDk1MmEtMjE2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1724952a-216c-41d2-840f-ec571461598a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ashok Chowgule has acquired 1,14,210 equity shares of Chowgule Steamships Limited by way of off-market gift from Ms. Padma Vishwasrao Chowgule. This disclosure is being filed within the stipulated timeline. Pre-shareholding was 2,93,761 and post-shareholding is 4,07,971.</p><ul><li>Ashok Chowgule acquires 1,14,210 shares of Chowgule Steamships Ltd via off-market gift.</li><li>Pre-shareholding was 2,93,761 and post-shareholding is 4,07,971.</li><li>The acquisition was made from Ms. Padma Vishwasrao Chowgule.</li><li>The disclosure is being filed within the stipulated timeline.</li><li>This is in compliance with the SEBI guidelines.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/C0B31AEA_58D4_4C01_B5B2_C188C5E92FA2_113639.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CHOWGULE STEAMSHIPS LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TCS] TCS and Rajarambapu Sahakari Bank Deepen Partnership; Integrate TCS BaNCS for Treasury to Enhance Operations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TATA+CONSULTANCY+SERVICES+LTD.&title=TCS+and+Rajarambapu+Sahakari+Bank+Deepen+Partnership%3B+Integrate+TCS+BaNCS+for+Treasury+to+Enhance+Operations&newsId=7055be55-4c47-46db-af74-fbd51b64defb&token=NzA1NWJlNTUtNGM0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7055be55-4c47-46db-af74-fbd51b64defb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:12:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Partnership</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) has announced that Rajarambapu Sahakari Bank (RSB) has selected TCS BaNCS™ for Treasury to automate its treasury operations. The integration will strengthen RSB’s digital ecosystem and enable efficient management of investments, money markets, repo, and reverse repo transactions. The transformation will make the bank more agile and responsive to its customers’ evolving needs, enhancing its competitive edge in the financial sector. TCS has been a growth partner to RSB for over 5 years, and the Bank has fully implemented the advanced TCS BaNCS Global Banking Platform across its 50 branches.</p><ul><li>RSB has selected TCS BaNCS™ for Treasury to automate its treasury operations.</li><li>The integration will strengthen RSB’s digital ecosystem and enable efficient management of various transactions.</li><li>The transformation will make the bank more agile and responsive to its customers’ evolving needs.</li><li>TCS has been a growth partner to RSB for over 5 years, and the Bank has fully implemented the advanced TCS BaNCS Global Banking Platform across its 50 branches.</li><li>The new partnership aims to enhance RSB’s competitive edge in the financial sector.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b7d23b7a-cde8-46f5-8ac5-40b9274d5788.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TATA CONSULTANCY SERVICES LTD. | Category: Partnership</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>