<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 18:29:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[TCIEXP*] TCI Express Completes Acquisition of TCI Global (Singapore) Pte. Ltd. for SGD 18,000</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TCI+Express+Ltd&title=TCI+Express+Completes+Acquisition+of+TCI+Global+%28Singapore%29+Pte.+Ltd.+for+SGD+18%2C000&newsId=f5001aa0-15f7-4855-9e4f-1a809f0e09be&token=ZjUwMDFhYTAtMTVm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f5001aa0-15f7-4855-9e4f-1a809f0e09be</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>TCI Express Ltd has completed the acquisition of 100% equity shares of TCI Global (Singapore) Pte. Ltd. from TCI Holdings Asia Pacific Pte. Ltd. The transaction, valued at SGD 18,000, was completed in cash and TCI Global (Singapore) Pte. Ltd. has become a step-down wholly owned subsidiary of TCI Express Limited. TCI Global (Singapore) Pte. Ltd., incorporated in 2006, is engaged in the business of transport, logistics, and related services.</p><ul><li>TCI Express Ltd completes acquisition of TCI Global (Singapore) Pte. Ltd.</li><li>Transaction valued at SGD 18,000</li><li>TCI Global (Singapore) Pte. Ltd. becomes a step-down wholly owned subsidiary of TCI Express Limited</li><li>TCI Global (Singapore) Pte. Ltd. incorporated in 2006 and engaged in transport, logistics, and related services</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f457a3fd-5af1-4dde-b390-9fe9316ab81e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TCI Express Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[COFORGE] Coforge and Innovaccer Partner to Accelerate AI Transformation in Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Coforge+Ltd&title=Coforge+and+Innovaccer+Partner+to+Accelerate+AI+Transformation+in+Healthcare&newsId=0ef19da7-1f42-4c5c-9723-44860e961aed&token=MGVmMTlkYTctMWY0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ef19da7-1f42-4c5c-9723-44860e961aed</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Partnership</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Coforge, a global digital services and solutions provider, and Innovaccer, a leading healthcare AI company, have announced a strategic partnership to improve care delivery and patient outcomes. The partnership combines Coforge&apos;s domain expertise in driving organizational transformation with Innovaccer’s AI infrastructure and data platform, aiming to drive measurable improvements in clinical, financial and administrative results for healthcare organizations. The two firms have launched G-Forge, a joint initiative to help healthcare organizations scale AI, integrate siloed data, and improve enterprise decision-making.</p><ul><li>Strategic partnership between Coforge and Innovaccer to improve care delivery and patient outcomes in the healthcare ecosystem.</li><li>Combination of Coforge&apos;s domain expertise and Innovaccer’s AI infrastructure and data platform to drive measurable improvements in clinical, financial and administrative results for healthcare organizations.</li><li>Launch of G-Forge, a joint initiative to help healthcare organizations scale AI, integrate siloed data, and improve enterprise decision-making.</li><li>Coforge as the preferred platinum implementation partner for Innovaccer’s Gravity AI platform, establishing a Healthcare AI Center of Excellence.</li><li>Development of industry-specific accelerators and solutions in the areas of member and provider experience, care management, and revenue cycle management.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b136a5f0-8783-422e-b2c0-e92d9a791a18.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Coforge Ltd | Category: Partnership</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IFGLEXPOR] IFGL Refractories&apos; UK Subsidiary Appoints New Statutory Auditors, Hebblethwaites</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IFGL+Refractories+Ltd&title=IFGL+Refractories%27+UK+Subsidiary+Appoints+New+Statutory+Auditors%2C+Hebblethwaites&newsId=f38453bc-3f0e-4615-8773-a59cc52ef9ab&token=ZjM4NDUzYmMtM2Yw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f38453bc-3f0e-4615-8773-a59cc52ef9ab</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Further to a previous announcement, IFGL Refractories Ltd&apos;s material subsidiary, M/s Sheffield Refractories Ltd, UK, has appointed Hebblethwaites, Chartered Accountants and Registered Auditors as their Statutory Auditors. Hebblethwaites is a well-established firm based in Sheffield, South Yorkshire, offering a range of professional services including audit, accounting, tax, and business advisory. This disclosure is in accordance with applicable laws, rules, and regulations of the United Kingdom and is also available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>IFGL Refractories&apos; UK subsidiary appoints new Statutory Auditors</li><li>New auditors, Hebblethwaites, are a well-established firm of Chartered Accountants and Registered Auditors based in Sheffield, South Yorkshire</li><li>Hebblethwaites provide a range of professional services including audit, accounting, tax, and business advisory</li><li>Appointment is in accordance with applicable laws, rules, and regulations of the United Kingdom</li><li>Disclosure is available on the company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e40a7428-dd67-452e-9445-92357d1a2afe.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IFGL Refractories Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STALLION] Stallion India Fluorochemicals Ltd to Consider and Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months of FY2025-2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Stallion+India+Fluorochemicals+Ltd&title=Stallion+India+Fluorochemicals+Ltd+to+Consider+and+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+nine+months+of+FY2025-2026&newsId=8c6f18b6-344b-4bf9-bcbe-360311c8a674&token=OGM2ZjE4YjYtMzQ0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c6f18b6-344b-4bf9-bcbe-360311c8a674</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Stallion India Fluorochemicals Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 29th January 2026 to consider and approve the unaudited financial results (standalone and consolidated) for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December 2025. This is in accordance with the Regulation 29 of SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, as amended from time to time.</p><ul><li>Stallion India Fluorochemicals Ltd to consider and approve unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months of FY2025-2026</li><li>The meeting is scheduled on 29th January 2026</li><li>The financial results are for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December 2025</li><li>The consideration and approval is in accordance with the Regulation 29 of SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, as amended from time to time</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2b95d91b-b609-4968-a2de-e4e5cbf176cc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Stallion India Fluorochemicals Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RCL] Radhagobind Commercial LTD Receives Provisional List of Expressions of Interest</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Radhagobind+Commercial+Ltd&title=Radhagobind+Commercial+LTD+Receives+Provisional+List+of+Expressions+of+Interest&newsId=c04d32f3-2d76-4990-8f92-d9181a3aed95&token=YzA0ZDMyZjMtMmQ3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c04d32f3-2d76-4990-8f92-d9181a3aed95</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:51:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Radhagobind Commercial Ltd has submitted a provisional list of Expressions of Interest (EOIs) for Section 25(2)(h) of the IBC in compliance with SEBI regulations. The list includes Anuj Jalan, Bhawarlal Camellia Tradex Private Limited, Madhusudhana Reddy, M Dynamic Services and Security Limited, and several other applicants. This compilation is provisional, subject to further verification and updates, and has been filed in good faith to ensure transparency and adherence to regulatory timelines.</p><ul><li>Radhagobind Commercial LTD submits provisional EOIs for Section 25(2)(h) of the IBC.</li><li>List includes Anuj Jalan, Bhawarlal Camellia Tradex Private Limited, Madhusudhana Reddy, and M Dynamic Services and Security Limited among others.</li><li>Compilation is provisional and subject to further verification and updates.</li><li>Filed in good faith to ensure transparency and adherence to regulatory timelines.</li><li>Includes various individual applicants, consortiums, and joint ventures.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2d9a1fc3-ef43-405f-90e9-32f95b060db4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Radhagobind Commercial Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MARCLOIRE] Marc Loire Fashions Ltd Opens New Store, Total Count Now 4</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Marc+Loire+Fashions+Ltd&title=Marc+Loire+Fashions+Ltd+Opens+New+Store%2C+Total+Count+Now+4&newsId=59cb6aed-429d-4c69-9851-16cfa3e38157&token=NTljYjZhZWQtNDI5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59cb6aed-429d-4c69-9851-16cfa3e38157</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:11:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pursuant to Regulation 30 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, Marc Loire Fashions Ltd has announced the opening of a new store in Delhi- 110033. This brings the total number of stores to 4.</p><ul><li>Marc Loire Fashions Ltd has opened a new store</li><li>The new store is located at B-12/B, Majlis Park, Adarsh Nagar, Delhi- 110033</li><li>This brings the total number of stores to 4</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0bc909d2-afe4-431c-a9fa-ca7722153f0a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Marc Loire Fashions Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BANSTEA] Bansisons Tea Industries Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BANSISONS+TEA+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Bansisons+Tea+Industries+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025&newsId=331e448f-8984-4ea7-8f16-a9f5e4625622&token=MzMxZTQ0OGYtODk4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">331e448f-8984-4ea7-8f16-a9f5e4625622</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:42:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bansisons Tea Industries Ltd has announced its unaudited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue, expenses, and net profit are reported in the statement. The Board of Directors reviewed the business and approved the financial results in the meeting held on January 26, 2026. The independent auditor, Hiren J. Maru, has also issued a review report on the quarterly unaudited standalone financial results.</p><ul><li>Bansisons Tea Industries Ltd has released its unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue, expenses, and net profit are reported in the statement.</li><li>The Board of Directors reviewed the business and approved the financial results in the meeting held on January 26, 2026.</li><li>Hiren J. Maru, the independent auditor, has issued a review report on the quarterly unaudited standalone financial results.</li><li>The financial results are prepared in accordance with Indian Accounting Standards 34 and other accounting principles generally accepted in India.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4127e67d-8561-4713-8660-4ee8b5f3cdeb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BANSISONS TEA INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BANSTEA] Bansisons Tea Industries Ltd Approves Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BANSISONS+TEA+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Bansisons+Tea+Industries+Ltd+Approves+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=7ac6048d-bb18-467f-aee9-cffe68d0ce0d&token=N2FjNjA0OGQtYmIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ac6048d-bb18-467f-aee9-cffe68d0ce0d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:41:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bansisons Tea Industries Ltd, formerly known as Novyra Pharmachem Limited, held a Board Meeting on January 26, 2026, where they approved the un-audited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting was conducted in accordance with Regulation 30 and 33 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations 2015. The company&apos;s management and Board of Directors have prepared the statement in accordance with Indian Accounting Standards 34 and other accounting principles generally accepted in India.</p><ul><li>Bansisons Tea Industries Ltd approved the un-audited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The approval was given in accordance with Regulation 30 and 33 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations 2015.</li><li>The financial results were prepared in accordance with Indian Accounting Standards 34 and other accounting principles generally accepted in India.</li><li>The Board Meeting was held on January 26, 2026.</li><li>The company&apos;s name was changed from Novyra Pharmachem Limited to Bansisons Tea Industries Ltd.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/643c9bb6-0127-4467-b24b-543d4d508405.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BANSISONS TEA INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IBREALEST] Embassy Developments Ltd. to Raise Funds via NCDs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDIABULLS+REAL+ESTATE+LTD.&title=Embassy+Developments+Ltd.+to+Raise+Funds+via+NCDs&newsId=518b1363-4c7c-4b69-aeb1-622cc5ebd7d6&token=NTE4YjEzNjMtNGM3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">518b1363-4c7c-4b69-aeb1-622cc5ebd7d6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:21:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Embassy Developments Ltd. has announced a meeting of the Board of Directors on 29/01/2026 to consider and approve the raising of funds by way of issuance of non-convertible debentures. The meeting will be held in accordance with Regulation 29(1)(d) and Regulation 29(2) of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The fundraising is subject to applicable regulatory and/or statutory approvals.</p><ul><li>Embassy Developments Ltd. to raise funds through non-convertible debentures</li><li>The fundraising is subject to applicable regulatory and/or statutory approvals</li><li>The decision will be made in a Board of Directors meeting scheduled on 29/01/2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0cba2dd7-df13-45b7-9561-cf8eec45d529.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDIABULLS REAL ESTATE LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CPL] Captain Polyplast Ltd. Announces Board Meeting to Approve Q3 Results for FY2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Captain+Polyplast+Ltd&title=Captain+Polyplast+Ltd.+Announces+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+Results+for+FY2025-26&newsId=7cbe531d-5e6d-440a-a8b9-91fd90676426&token=N2NiZTUzMWQtNWU2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7cbe531d-5e6d-440a-a8b9-91fd90676426</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Captain Polyplast Ltd. has announced a board meeting scheduled for Saturday, 7th February, 2026, to consider and approve the standalone &amp; consolidated unaudited financial results for the quarter ended on 31st December, 2025. The trading window for directors, promoters, designated employees, and connected persons of the company will be closed from 1st January, 2026, and will end 48 hours after the results are made public.</p><ul><li>Captain Polyplast Ltd. to hold a board meeting on 7th February, 2026</li><li>The meeting aims to consider and approve the Q3 FY2025-26 financial results</li><li>The trading window for insiders will be closed from 1st January, 2026</li><li>The window will reopen 48 hours after the results are made public</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3aa748b1-3de5-4688-b16d-eb2e798dfb82.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Captain Polyplast Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>