<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:55:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[KHOOBSURAT] Khoobsurat Ltd to Start Commercial Production of Beer by April 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Khoobsurat+Ltd&title=Khoobsurat+Ltd+to+Start+Commercial+Production+of+Beer+by+April+2026&newsId=8ef51868-3d54-4543-95aa-0a4afbf77265&token=OGVmNTE4NjgtM2Q1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ef51868-3d54-4543-95aa-0a4afbf77265</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Khoobsurat Ltd has provided an update on its Brewery Plant. The installation of the Brew-house and Fermentation tanks is underway and expected to be completed by 15th March 2026. The delivery of the Bottling Plant is expected by the end of March 2026. Once the tanks and the packaging plant are integrated, the company plans to brew the first test batch of beer between mid to end of April 2026. The technical team from Germany will visit the plant in March 2026 to make the bottling plant operational and connected to the brewery production. Commercial production is expected to start by mid of April 2026.</p><ul><li>Installation of Brew-house and Fermentation tanks to be completed by 15th March 2026</li><li>Delivery of Bottling Plant expected by end of March 2026</li><li>First test batch of beer to be brewed between mid to end of April 2026</li><li>Technical team from Germany to visit the plant in March 2026</li><li>Commercial production expected to start by mid of April 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/91b25f5d-2cec-490a-b827-bae459d8afef.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Khoobsurat Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TATACOMM] Tata Communications, RailTel Collaborate to Strengthen India’s Digital Infrastructure Backbone for AI</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TATA+COMMUNICATIONS+LTD.&title=Tata+Communications%2C+RailTel+Collaborate+to+Strengthen+India%E2%80%99s+Digital+Infrastructure+Backbone+for+AI&newsId=bbc62397-19b8-4a9e-a69a-86667c1146c0&token=YmJjNjIzOTctMTli</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bbc62397-19b8-4a9e-a69a-86667c1146c0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:33:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Tata Communications and RailTel Corporation of India Ltd. have entered into a strategic association to jointly advance next-generation digital infrastructure globally. The collaboration aims to modernise network infrastructure, strengthen cyber protection, enhance customer experiences, enable secure and sovereign cloud adoption for sensitive workloads, and leverage advanced AI-enabled platforms. This partnership is expected to benefit ministries, state governments, PSUs, and enterprises that rely on RailTel’s network, as well as citizen-facing services such as railway Wi-Fi, public broadband, surveillance systems, and digital governance platforms.</p><ul><li>Tata Communications and RailTel Corporation of India Ltd. enter into a strategic association to strengthen digital infrastructure</li><li>Collaboration aims to modernise network infrastructure, strengthen cyber protection, and enhance customer experiences</li><li>Partnership to enable secure and sovereign cloud adoption for sensitive workloads and leverage advanced AI-enabled platforms</li><li>Expected to benefit ministries, state governments, PSUs, and enterprises relying on RailTel’s network</li><li>Citizen-facing services such as railway Wi-Fi, public broadband, surveillance systems, and digital governance platforms to improve</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7d4b6816-d83f-4709-8baa-843b6d738758.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TATA COMMUNICATIONS LTD. | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AETHER] Aether Industries Ltd Commences Commercial Operations at Manufacturing Site 3++</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Aether+Industries+Ltd&title=Aether+Industries+Ltd+Commences+Commercial+Operations+at+Manufacturing+Site+3%2B%2B&newsId=6bca1d21-5782-4a85-acce-2c0004b85876&token=NmJjYTFkMjEtNTc4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6bca1d21-5782-4a85-acce-2c0004b85876</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Aether Industries Ltd has announced the commencement of commercial operations at its Manufacturing Site 3++ (Plot No. 8202/2/A-B) as of February 22, 2026. This new site is expected to significantly contribute to the company&apos;s production capacities and revenue growth in the future.</p><ul><li>Aether Industries Ltd has started commercial operations at Manufacturing Site 3++.</li><li>The new site, Plot No. 8202/2/A-B, is expected to contribute to the company&apos;s production capacities and revenue growth.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e2ffc416-8c88-4f46-b9e3-dbf96e32fb9b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Aether Industries Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GARMNTMNTR] Garment Mantra Lifestyle Ltd Develops Recycled Fabric Men’s T-Shirts for African &amp; U.A.E. Markets</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Garment+Mantra+Lifestyle+Ltd&title=Garment+Mantra+Lifestyle+Ltd+Develops+Recycled+Fabric+Men%E2%80%99s+T-Shirts+for+African+%26+U.A.E.+Markets&newsId=8cb09169-d2e1-4f2e-9002-8be370e81419&token=OGNiMDkxNjktZDJl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8cb09169-d2e1-4f2e-9002-8be370e81419</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:09:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Garment Mantra Lifestyle Limited has developed a new range of men’s T-shirts manufactured using recycled fabrics, specifically designed for export into select African and U.A.E. markets. The new collection integrates high-quality recycled fibers, combining sustainability with durability, comfort, and climate suitability tailored to diverse African and U.A.E. geographies. The product has been engineered to meet international export standards while maintaining competitive pricing for bulk distribution channels. The Company is optimistic about receiving encouraging feedback based on preliminary interactions and growing demand for sustainable apparel solutions. Subject to favourable buyer response and order confirmations, the Company expects this initiative to translate into commercial export orders in the forthcoming quarters.</p><ul><li>Use of recycled yarns derived from post-consumer and post-industrial textile waste</li><li>Compliance with international quality benchmarks</li><li>Customizable specifications as per buyer requirements</li><li>Focus on affordability for emerging market retail networks</li><li>Initiation of sampling for the recycled fabric men’s T-shirt range marks an important milestone in the Company’s export growth strategy</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/28f5045f-aa46-44bc-ac27-9e048fa7e8ff.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Garment Mantra Lifestyle Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STALLION] Stallion India Fluorochemicals Receives Land Allotment Approval for Proposed HFO Manufacturing Plant in Rajasthan</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Stallion+India+Fluorochemicals+Ltd&title=Stallion+India+Fluorochemicals+Receives+Land+Allotment+Approval+for+Proposed+HFO+Manufacturing+Plant+in+Rajasthan&newsId=22cb648b-4c96-4cbd-a0c5-1e19284030f1&token=MjJjYjY0OGItNGM5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">22cb648b-4c96-4cbd-a0c5-1e19284030f1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Stallion India Fluorochemicals Limited (SIFL) has received approval from RIICO for allotment of land for its proposed Hydrofluoroolefin (HFO) manufacturing plant at the RIICO Industrial Area, Ukhalliya, District Bhilwara, Rajasthan. The company now holds three adjoining plots totaling approximately 122,543 sq. mtrs, which will allow shared infrastructure, utilities, security, administration, and common factory management, creating strong operational synergies, improving efficiencies, and supporting cost optimization. The R-32 project is targeted for commissioning by October 2026, followed by the proposed HFO manufacturing facility, for which an investment of approximately INR 200 crore is outlined with start of work planned in 2027. The Rajasthan project will also be eligible for incentives under RIPS-2024, significantly enhancing project viability and long-term returns.</p><ul><li>Stallion India Fluorochemicals Limited receives approval for land allotment for proposed HFO manufacturing plant in Rajasthan.</li><li>The company now holds three adjoining plots totaling approximately 122,543 sq. mtrs, enabling a fully integrated manufacturing layout.</li><li>The proposed HFO manufacturing facility is targeted for commissioning in 2027 with an investment of approximately INR 200 crore.</li><li>The Rajasthan project is eligible for incentives under RIPS-2024, enhancing project viability and long-term returns.</li><li>SIFL aims to achieve a 30-35% revenue CAGR over the next three years, building a strong domestic manufacturing base.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b4c1864c-dd37-47bf-8576-892c0dcc48e8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Stallion India Fluorochemicals Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DELPHIFX] Delphi World Money Reports Strong Q3 &amp; 9M FY26 Performance Driven by Travel Recovery and Operational Efficiencies</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Delphi+World+Money+Ltd&title=Delphi+World+Money+Reports+Strong+Q3+%26+9M+FY26+Performance+Driven+by+Travel+Recovery+and+Operational+Efficiencies&newsId=23e9839b-68fe-4c23-bdd5-bd60097bd772&token=MjNlOTgzOWItNjhm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23e9839b-68fe-4c23-bdd5-bd60097bd772</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 03:55:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Delphi World Money, a leading travel and foreign exchange solutions provider, reported its financial results for Q3 and 9M FY26. The company&apos;s adjusted revenue grew by 24% QoQ to INR 547 Mn in Q3-FY26, while its adjusted EBITDA turned around from INR (60.46) Mn in Q2-FY26 to INR 52.54 Mn in Q3-FY26. The strategic integration of travel services into the broader financial services platform and strengthening of its leadership team contributed to the strong performance. The company is planning to scale growth and strengthen profitability through AI-driven customer and platform optimization, technology upgrades and automation, fintech partnerships &amp; embedded solutions, international expansion &amp; new product introductions, and leadership position in experiential travel. The company expects to process transactions totaling approximately INR 68 Bn in GMV and deliver full-year Adjusted EBITDA of ~INR 240 Mn in FY26.</p><ul><li>Adjusted revenue grew by 24% QoQ to INR 547 Mn in Q3-FY26</li><li>Adjusted EBITDA turned around from INR (60.46) Mn in Q2-FY26 to INR 52.54 Mn in Q3-FY26</li><li>Strategic integration of travel services into the broader financial services platform</li><li>Plans to scale growth and strengthen profitability through various initiatives</li><li>Expects to process transactions totaling approximately INR 68 Bn in GMV and deliver full-year Adjusted EBITDA of ~INR 240 Mn in FY26</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4aca8c47-053d-4f13-97e0-fe0700a27899.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Delphi World Money Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RMDRIP] R M Drip And Sprinklers Systems Ltd Announces Board Meeting to Consider Bonus Shares Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=R+M+Drip+and+Sprinklers+Systems+Ltd&title=R+M+Drip+And+Sprinklers+Systems+Ltd+Announces+Board+Meeting+to+Consider+Bonus+Shares+Issue&newsId=30f8f231-fe71-4091-9956-30cd30f5d1a3&token=MzBmOGYyMzEtZmU3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">30f8f231-fe71-4091-9956-30cd30f5d1a3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 03:39:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Bonus</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>R M Drip And Sprinklers Systems Ltd has informed the Bombay Stock Exchange (BSE) that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on 28/02/2026. The agenda includes considering and approving a proposal for a bonus share issue, subject to shareholder and regulatory approvals. The board will also consider related matters concerning the proposed bonus issue.</p><ul><li>R M Drip And Sprinklers Systems Ltd has scheduled a Board Meeting on 28/02/2026</li><li>The agenda includes considering a proposal for a bonus share issue</li><li>The bonus share issue is subject to shareholder and regulatory approvals</li><li>The board will consider related matters concerning the proposed bonus issue</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/01eb8193-ee04-41ea-8026-07b9c26936db.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: R M Drip and Sprinklers Systems Ltd | Category: Bonus</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MOREPENLAB] Morepen Secures $91M Global CDMO Mandate, Expands Manufacturing Footprint</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MOREPEN+LABORATORIES+LTD.&title=Morepen+Secures+%2491M+Global+CDMO+Mandate%2C+Expands+Manufacturing+Footprint&newsId=141d844f-f542-42ab-83ca-93eb92dff2d6&token=MTQxZDg0NGYtZjU0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">141d844f-f542-42ab-83ca-93eb92dff2d6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 03:32:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Morepen Laboratories Limited has secured a multi-year Contract Development and Manufacturing Organization (CDMO) mandate valued at approximately INR 825 crore (USD 91 million) from a leading global pharma major. The supplies under the mandate are expected to commence within the next 4-5 months. This engagement marks one of the most significant single CDMO mandates in the Company’s history, as it scales its global manufacturing footprint. The mandate reflects the Company’s growing capabilities in regulated markets, supported by internationally accredited facilities including USFDA, WHO-GMP, and EU approvals.</p><ul><li>Morepen has secured a $91M CDMO mandate from a leading global pharma major.</li><li>The mandate is expected to commence within the next 4-5 months and continue through Q1 of the following financial year.</li><li>This is one of the most significant single CDMO mandates in Morepen&apos;s history, signifying its growing capabilities in regulated markets.</li><li>Morepen&apos;s CDMO platform is built on over four decades of API manufacturing expertise and regulatory credibility.</li><li>The Company is evaluating capacity enhancement and technology investments aligned with its expanding CDMO opportunity pipeline.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a3f8aa0c-4cd5-4c03-9141-8edf1bb366cd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MOREPEN LABORATORIES LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MINID] Mini Diamonds India Secures Rs. 12 Crore Domestic Order for Lab-Grown Polished Diamonds</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MINI+DIAMONDS+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Mini+Diamonds+India+Secures+Rs.+12+Crore+Domestic+Order+for+Lab-Grown+Polished+Diamonds&newsId=27048d90-82b2-4a67-838d-901c0b58aa13&token=MjcwNDhkOTAtODJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27048d90-82b2-4a67-838d-901c0b58aa13</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 03:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Mini Diamonds India Ltd has received a significant domestic order of INR 12.00 Crores from a Mumbai-based client for the supply of lab-grown polished diamonds. This order is expected to strengthen the company&apos;s domestic market position, improve customer relationships, and contribute to a more predictable demand pipeline in the Indian market.</p><ul><li>Mini Diamonds India Ltd has secured a domestic order of INR 12.00 Crores from a Mumbai-based client.</li><li>The order is for the supply of lab-grown polished diamonds.</li><li>This order is expected to support the company&apos;s credibility in the domestic lab-grown diamond market.</li><li>It is also expected to strengthen domestic channel relationships and improve customer retention.</li><li>This order marks a new customer addition in the domestic segment.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/54e07bc8-8fd1-465d-a1e5-1af43de2f8a6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MINI DIAMONDS (INDIA) LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DEEDEV] Dee Development Engineers Secures INR 173 Crores Contracts Across Domestic and International Markets</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Dee+Development+Engineers+Ltd&title=Dee+Development+Engineers+Secures+INR+173+Crores+Contracts+Across+Domestic+and+International+Markets&newsId=7b48ba1a-a11d-4840-877c-cde3ef9db2e6&token=N2I0OGJhMWEtYTEx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b48ba1a-a11d-4840-877c-cde3ef9db2e6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 02:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Dee Development Engineers Ltd and its material subsidiary have secured contracts amounting to approximately INR 173 Crores. The Company has been awarded domestic contracts worth INR 88 Crores on a job work basis. The material subsidiary, DEE Piping Systems (Thailand) Co., Ltd., has secured international contracts of US$ 8 million on a job work basis and US$ 1.5 million with material basis. The contracts are expected to be executed within specified time periods.</p><ul><li>Dee Development Engineers Ltd secures contracts worth approximately INR 173 Crores</li><li>The Company has been awarded domestic contracts of INR 88 Crores</li><li>DEE Piping Systems (Thailand) Co., Ltd. secures international contracts of US$ 8 million and US$ 1.5 million</li><li>Contracts are awarded on a job work basis and with material basis</li><li>The contracts are expected to be executed within specified time periods</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b53c0a6c-4f78-4a3f-b5b0-623e86f1edc4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Dee Development Engineers Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>