<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:38:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[STDSFAC] Standard Surfactants Board Meeting Deferred on Potential Fund Raising Proposal</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=STANDARD+SURFACTANTS+LTD.&title=Standard+Surfactants+Board+Meeting+Deferred+on+Potential+Fund+Raising+Proposal&newsId=76178c25-389b-4033-bf1c-9b8f8a7413e3&token=NzYxNzhjMjUtMzg5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76178c25-389b-4033-bf1c-9b8f8a7413e3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:37:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board Meeting of Standard Surfactants Ltd, held on 14.01.2026 at 8/15 Arya Nagar, Kanpur-208002, was convened to discuss a potential fund raising through issuance of securities or any other mode. However, due to lack of necessary details and information, the Board decided to defer further consideration of the matter. The proposal will be revisited at a subsequent meeting. The Company will duly inform the Stock Exchange of the next Board Meeting and make necessary disclosures as required by the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, if and when the proposal is approved.</p><ul><li>Standard Surfactants Board Meeting held on 14.01.2026 to discuss potential fund raising through issuance of securities or any other mode.</li><li>Board decided to defer further consideration due to lack of necessary details and information.</li><li>Proposal to be revisited at a subsequent meeting.</li><li>Company to inform Stock Exchange of the next Board Meeting as required by SEBI regulations.</li><li>Necessary disclosures to be made if the proposal is approved.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d5656a8d-daa2-4d97-a181-d9eb95b7d81f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: STANDARD SURFACTANTS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZMILGFIN] Milgrey Finance &amp; Investments Ltd Appoints Mr. Samadhan Suresh Patil as Additional Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Milgrey+Finance+%26+Investments+Ltd&title=Milgrey+Finance+%26+Investments+Ltd+Appoints+Mr.+Samadhan+Suresh+Patil+as+Additional+Independent+Director&newsId=0eaf3407-6365-4067-ae59-3b3a4e89be9b&token=MGVhZjM0MDctNjM2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0eaf3407-6365-4067-ae59-3b3a4e89be9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:37:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Milgrey Finance &amp; Investments Ltd has appointed Mr. Samadhan Suresh Patil as an Additional Independent Director. The appointment was approved at a Board of Directors meeting held on 14.01.2026 and is subject to shareholder approval. Mr. Patil has five years of experience in share broking and is not related to any of the company&apos;s directors. He is also not debarred from holding the office of Director by any order of SEBI or any other statutory authority.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Samadhan Suresh Patil as Additional Independent Director</li><li>Appointment is subject to shareholder approval</li><li>Mr. Patil has five years of experience in share broking</li><li>Mr. Patil is not related to any of the company&apos;s directors</li><li>Mr. Patil is not debarred from holding the office of Director by any order of SEBI or any other statutory authority</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d0d3aef7-ee67-46fe-b72a-284fb645cfd9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Milgrey Finance & Investments Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CHORDIA] Chordia Food Products Ltd: Mrs. Sharvari Sandesh Kadam Resigns as CFO, Mr. Rushikesh Popat Veer Appointed as New CFO</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CHORDIA+FOOD+PRODUCTS+LTD.&title=Chordia+Food+Products+Ltd%3A+Mrs.+Sharvari+Sandesh+Kadam+Resigns+as+CFO%2C+Mr.+Rushikesh+Popat+Veer+Appointed+as+New+CFO&newsId=2bd0f4c2-066c-4a51-b73f-cd430d60a15a&token=MmJkMGY0YzItMDY2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2bd0f4c2-066c-4a51-b73f-cd430d60a15a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:34:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Chordia Food Products Ltd has announced that Mrs. Sharvari Sandesh Kadam has resigned as the Chief Financial Officer (CFO) with immediate effect due to her other commitments. The company has appointed Mr. Rushikesh Popat Veer as the new CFO with effect from 14th January, 2026. Mr. Veer has given his consent to act as CFO and has certified that he is not disqualified under any provisions of the Companies Act, 2013 or the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Mrs. Sharvari Sandesh Kadam has resigned as the CFO of Chordia Food Products Ltd.</li><li>Mr. Rushikesh Popat Veer has been appointed as the new CFO of the company.</li><li>Mr. Veer&apos;s appointment is effective from 14th January, 2026.</li><li>Mr. Veer has given his consent to act as CFO.</li><li>Mr. Veer is not disqualified under any provisions of the Companies Act, 2013 or the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cee731b2-b82a-44eb-aedd-f89777261086.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CHORDIA FOOD PRODUCTS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CHCL] Cian Healthcare Ltd. Reports Half-Yearly Financial Results for September 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Cian+Healthcare+Ltd&title=Cian+Healthcare+Ltd.+Reports+Half-Yearly+Financial+Results+for+September+2025&newsId=5498f96e-78fc-47bb-8233-c48f24ed9007&token=NTQ5OGY5NmUtNzhm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5498f96e-78fc-47bb-8233-c48f24ed9007</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cian Healthcare Ltd. has released its consolidated financial results for the half-year ended on September 30, 2025. The company&apos;s Statement of Assets &amp; Liabilities and Statement of Cash Flows are included in the report. The results were reviewed by M/s, SSRC A &amp; Co., Chartered Accountants, the company&apos;s statutory auditors. The un-audited consolidated financial results are also submitted in XBRL mode.</p><ul><li>Cian Healthcare Ltd. has released its half-yearly financial results for the period ending on September 30, 2025.</li><li>The results were reviewed by M/s, SSRC A &amp; Co., Chartered Accountants, the company&apos;s statutory auditors.</li><li>The un-audited consolidated financial results are submitted in XBRL mode.</li><li>The Statement of Assets &amp; Liabilities and Statement of Cash Flows are included in the report.</li><li>The report highlights the company&apos;s financial position and performance for the half-year ended on September 30, 2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b2a5bd98-0472-47c7-aff3-0bbf9df30a82.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Cian Healthcare Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ICICIAMC] ICICI Prudential Asset Management Company Ltd Declares Interim Dividend, Approves Re-appointment of Directors, and Reports Q3 &amp; Nine Months Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ICICI+Prudential+Asset+Management+Company+Ltd&title=ICICI+Prudential+Asset+Management+Company+Ltd+Declares+Interim+Dividend%2C+Approves+Re-appointment+of+Directors%2C+and+Reports+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025&newsId=9226cf64-8835-48ae-bd98-1fc0f66740dc&token=OTIyNmNmNjQtODgz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9226cf64-8835-48ae-bd98-1fc0f66740dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>ICICI Prudential Asset Management Company Ltd announced the approval of the interim dividend of ~ 14.85 per equity share, the re-appointment of Mr. Antony Jacob as an Independent Director for a second term and Mr. Sankaran Naren as the Executive Director for two years. The company&apos;s unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ending December 31, 2025, were also approved, showing revenue from operations at 15,146.7 million INR, other income at 1,089.1 million INR, and a profit before tax of 12,188.0 million INR.</p><ul><li>ICICI Prudential Asset Management Company Ltd declares an interim dividend of ~ 14.85 per equity share.</li><li>Re-appointment of Mr. Antony Jacob as an Independent Director for a second term and Mr. Sankaran Naren as the Executive Director for two years.</li><li>Unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ending December 31, 2025, approved.</li><li>Revenue from operations at 15,146.7 million INR, other income at 1,089.1 million INR, and a profit before tax of 12,188.0 million INR.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b66ead36-2034-4670-81e7-4037351da7f4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ICICI Prudential Asset Management Company Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SFL] Sheela Foam Ltd&apos;s Statutory Auditor MS KA &amp; Associates Converts to LLP</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sheela+Foam+Ltd&title=Sheela+Foam+Ltd%27s+Statutory+Auditor+MS+KA+%26+Associates+Converts+to+LLP&newsId=8d2cfdb3-5c91-4eeb-8f53-7f91df4eaa9b&token=OGQyY2ZkYjMtNWM5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d2cfdb3-5c91-4eeb-8f53-7f91df4eaa9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sheela Foam Ltd announced that its statutory auditor, MS KA &amp; Associates, has converted into a Limited Liability Partnership (LLP) under the Limited Liability Partnership Act, 2008. The new name of the auditor is MS KA &amp; Associates LLP, Chartered Accountants. The auditor will continue to fulfill its obligations for the remaining period of its tenure.</p><ul><li>Sheela Foam Ltd&apos;s statutory auditor, MS KA &amp; Associates, has converted into an LLP.</li><li>The new name of the auditor is MS KA &amp; Associates LLP, Chartered Accountants.</li><li>The auditor will continue to perform its duties for the remaining tenure.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/316ad0a8-8026-4858-bab8-a596c0dfa62f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sheela Foam Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ANDHRAPAP] Statutory Auditors of Andhra Paper Ltd, M S K A &amp; Associates, Converted to Limited Liability Partnership</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Andhra+Paper+Ltd&title=Statutory+Auditors+of+Andhra+Paper+Ltd%2C+M+S+K+A+%26+Associates%2C+Converted+to+Limited+Liability+Partnership&newsId=8e41433d-400b-477a-85bf-121cf643e520&token=OGU0MTQzM2QtNDAw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8e41433d-400b-477a-85bf-121cf643e520</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:27:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Andhra Paper Ltd has announced that their Statutory Auditors, M S K A &amp; Associates, have converted from a Partnership Firm into a Limited Liability Partnership (LLP) under the name M S K A &amp; Associates LLP. This change in constitution of the audit firm took effect on 13th January, 2026. Despite this change, M S K A &amp; Associates LLP will continue to function and discharge their obligations as Statutory Auditors for the remaining period of their tenure. The ICAI Firm Registration No for the new LLP is 105047W/W101187.</p><ul><li>M S K A &amp; Associates has converted into a Limited Liability Partnership (LLP) under the Limited Liability Partnership Act, 2008.</li><li>The new name of the auditor firm is M S K A &amp; Associates LLP.</li><li>The change in constitution of the audit firm took effect on 13th January, 2026.</li><li>M S K A &amp; Associates LLP will continue to serve as Statutory Auditors for the remaining period of their tenure.</li><li>The ICAI Firm Registration No for the new LLP is 105047W/W101187.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/51bb342f-de9a-4707-ad9d-080daa21693e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Andhra Paper Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CHORDIA] Chordia Food Products Ltd: Mrs. Sharvari Sandesh Kadam Resigns as CFO, Mr. Rushikesh Popat Veer Appointed as New CFO</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CHORDIA+FOOD+PRODUCTS+LTD.&title=Chordia+Food+Products+Ltd%3A+Mrs.+Sharvari+Sandesh+Kadam+Resigns+as+CFO%2C+Mr.+Rushikesh+Popat+Veer+Appointed+as+New+CFO&newsId=6a612adf-8214-4370-8635-3666fa8c2b4f&token=NmE2MTJhZGYtODIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a612adf-8214-4370-8635-3666fa8c2b4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Chordia Food Products Ltd has announced that Mrs. Sharvari Sandesh Kadam has resigned as the Chief Financial Officer (CFO) with immediate effect due to her other commitments. The company has appointed Mr. Rushikesh Popat Veer as the new CFO with effect from 14th January, 2026. Mr. Veer has given his consent to act as CFO and has certified that he is not disqualified under any provisions of the Companies Act, 2013 or the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Mrs. Sharvari Sandesh Kadam has resigned as the CFO of Chordia Food Products Ltd.</li><li>Mr. Rushikesh Popat Veer has been appointed as the new CFO of the company.</li><li>Mr. Veer&apos;s appointment is effective from 14th January, 2026.</li><li>Mr. Veer has given his consent to act as CFO.</li><li>Mr. Veer is not disqualified under any provisions of the Companies Act, 2013 or the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c97fdcb9-a9e2-4ab5-ae08-15c20ba5dc23.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CHORDIA FOOD PRODUCTS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CHEVIOT] Cheviot Company Acquires Shares of Hindalco Industries Limited for Long-Term Investment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CHEVIOT+CO.LTD.-%24&title=Cheviot+Company+Acquires+Shares+of+Hindalco+Industries+Limited+for+Long-Term+Investment&newsId=fba8f239-9777-4858-aa83-8aa49e6e2071&token=ZmJhOGYyMzktOTc3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fba8f239-9777-4858-aa83-8aa49e6e2071</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:24:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cheviot Company Ltd. has acquired equity shares of Hindalco Industries Limited (HIL) through the stock exchange mechanism. The acquisition is a long-term investment and does not aim to acquire control. The value or expected impact of the shares exceeds the threshold specified in Regulation 30(4)(i)(c) of the Listing Regulations, necessitating disclosure. HIL, incorporated in 1958, is engaged in manufacturing metal and metal products. It reported a Total Equity of INR 70,206 crores as of 31.3.2025, revenue from operations of INR 93,309 crores, and Profit for the year of INR 6,387 crores for the year ended 31.3.2025 (on a standalone basis). The acquisition was made without any interest from the promoter/promoter group/group companies. The shares were purchased at INR 954.3767 per share, and Cheviot Company Ltd. holds 0.01% of HIL&apos;s share capital.</p><ul><li>Cheviot Company Ltd. acquires shares of Hindalco Industries Limited (HIL) for long-term investment</li><li>The acquisition does not aim to acquire control of HIL</li><li>HIL is a company incorporated in 1958, engaged in manufacturing metal and metal products</li><li>The value or expected impact of the shares exceeds the threshold specified in Regulation 30(4)(i)(c) of the Listing Regulations</li><li>Cheviot Company Ltd. holds 0.01% of HIL&apos;s share capital</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a8b8d4c1-d20a-4b48-adb4-4b2f003c9489.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CHEVIOT CO.LTD.-$ | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CHORDIA] Chordia Food Products Ltd Announces Resignation of CFO and Appointment of New CFO</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CHORDIA+FOOD+PRODUCTS+LTD.&title=Chordia+Food+Products+Ltd+Announces+Resignation+of+CFO+and+Appointment+of+New+CFO&newsId=8f096bf4-9e88-4a08-9324-89b9519fe8fc&token=OGYwOTZiZjQtOWU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f096bf4-9e88-4a08-9324-89b9519fe8fc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:21:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Chordia Food Products Ltd has announced the resignation of Mrs. Sharvari Sandesh Kadam as the Chief Financial Officer (CFO) with immediate effect due to her other commitments. The company has appointed Mr. Rushikesh Popat Veer as the new CFO with effect from 14th January, 2026. Mr. Veer has given his consent to act as CFO and has certified that he is not disqualified under any provisions of the Companies Act, 2013 or the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Mrs. Sharvari Sandesh Kadam has resigned as the CFO of Chordia Food Products Ltd.</li><li>Mr. Rushikesh Popat Veer has been appointed as the new CFO of Chordia Food Products Ltd.</li><li>Mr. Veer has given his consent to act as CFO.</li><li>Mr. Veer is not disqualified under any provisions of the Companies Act, 2013 or the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9b8f92a4-6463-4cf5-8fe6-a99a300fa068.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CHORDIA FOOD PRODUCTS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>