<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:57:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[DCW] DCW Ltd Declares Interim Dividend of Rs. 0.10/- for FY 2025-26 and Reports Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DCW+LTD.&title=DCW+Ltd+Declares+Interim+Dividend+of+Rs.+0.10%2F-+for+FY+2025-26+and+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results&newsId=6db83af8-f4e9-4ac1-aae0-52c5f795a399&token=NmRiODNhZjgtZjRl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6db83af8-f4e9-4ac1-aae0-52c5f795a399</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:57:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>DCW Ltd, a leading company, has declared an interim dividend of Rs. 0.10/- per equity share for the Financial Year 2025-26. The record date for payment of this interim dividend is February 20, 2026. The company&apos;s un-audited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, have also been approved and are being made available on the company&apos;s website. The company&apos;s auditor, V. Sankar Aiyar &amp; Co., has issued a limited review report for the same period.</p><ul><li>DCW Ltd declares an interim dividend of Rs. 0.10/- per equity share for FY 2025-26</li><li>The record date for payment of this interim dividend is February 20, 2026</li><li>The company&apos;s un-audited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025, have been approved</li><li>The financial results are being made available on the company&apos;s website</li><li>V. Sankar Aiyar &amp; Co. has issued a limited review report for the same period</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2df3604a-3c0c-4c61-9297-630917be1c2a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DCW LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ESCORTS] Escorts Kubota Ltd. Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025, Declares Special Dividend, and Appoints New Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Escorts+Kubota+Ltd&title=Escorts+Kubota+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Declares+Special+Dividend%2C+and+Appoints+New+Directors&newsId=09ed6f47-6a6b-46fc-b8e1-fce43d220560&token=MDllZDZmNDctNmE2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09ed6f47-6a6b-46fc-b8e1-fce43d220560</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:56:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Escorts Kubota Ltd. has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company has declared a special dividend of 180% per fully paid-up equity share for the financial year 2025-26. The Board has also appointed two new additional directors, Mr. Hitoshi Sasaki and Mr. Satoshi Suzuki, who are nominees of Kubota Corporation. The company plans to invest in land in YEIDA Industrial area for setting up a Greenfield Project to increase production capacity for tractors, construction equipment, and other products.</p><ul><li>Unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025 announced</li><li>Special dividend of 180% per fully paid-up equity share declared for FY 2025-26</li><li>Appointment of two new additional directors, Mr. Hitoshi Sasaki and Mr. Satoshi Suzuki</li><li>Plan to invest in land for Greenfield Project to increase production capacity</li><li>Increase in production capacity for tractors, construction equipment, and other products</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7dc9f13e-bcb5-404a-9b78-3edf38d47503.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Escorts Kubota Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JSLINDL] JSL Industries Ltd. Reports Q3 and Nine Months Unaudited Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JSL+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=JSL+Industries+Ltd.+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=bdbe89fc-e94e-46ea-91a3-74ccd67ef2f0&token=YmRiZTg5ZmMtZTk0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bdbe89fc-e94e-46ea-91a3-74ccd67ef2f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:55:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>JSL Industries Ltd. has reported its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at INR 1,398.89 lakhs for the quarter and INR 3,913.89 lakhs for the nine months. The net profit for the quarter is INR 716.08 lakhs and INR 2,443.63 lakhs for the nine months. The company&apos;s total income and expenses for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, are also reported.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter is INR 1,398.89 lakhs</li><li>Revenue from operations for the nine months is INR 3,913.89 lakhs</li><li>Net profit for the quarter is INR 716.08 lakhs</li><li>Net profit for the nine months is INR 2,443.63 lakhs</li><li>The company has re-evaluated its intention with respect to its investment in the quoted equity shares of Jyoti Limited, and decided to hold these investments for the long term</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4b491f08-14a3-4d09-974d-b8571752f63d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JSL INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SOUTHERNIN] Southern Infoconsultants Ltd. to Approve Q4 Results on Feb 13, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Southern+Infosys+Ltd&title=Southern+Infoconsultants+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q4+Results+on+Feb+13%2C+2026&newsId=97ca4d92-62d0-472c-abff-375c4286564d&token=OTdjYTRkOTItNjJk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97ca4d92-62d0-472c-abff-375c4286564d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Southern Infoconsultants Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 13, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The meeting will be held at the company&apos;s registered office in New Delhi. The trading window for designated persons will remain closed till 48 hours after the financial results are made public.</p><ul><li>Southern Infoconsultants Ltd. to approve Q4 results on Feb 13, 2026</li><li>Meeting to be held at the company&apos;s registered office in New Delhi</li><li>Trading window for designated persons to remain closed till 48 hours after results are made public</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c43999ca-c1ce-4332-915f-fb6678ca7276.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Southern Infosys Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JSLINDL] JSL Industries Ltd. Reports Q3 and Nine Months Unaudited Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JSL+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=JSL+Industries+Ltd.+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=c5bc3419-c465-42b8-8751-9476926886bb&token=YzViYzM0MTktYzQ2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5bc3419-c465-42b8-8751-9476926886bb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>JSL Industries Ltd. has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at INR 1,398.89 lakhs for the quarter and INR 3,913.89 lakhs for the nine-month period. The profit before interest, depreciation, tax, and amortization (EBITDA) is INR 127.19 lakhs, INR 109.63 lakhs, and INR 327.40 lakhs for the quarter, nine months, and year ended December 31, 2025, respectively. The profit before tax for the year ended December 31, 2025, is INR 762.14 lakhs. The company has also reported an earning per equity share (EPS) of INR 7.47 and INR 3.81 for the quarter and year ended December 31, 2025, respectively.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for Q3 2025 is INR 1,398.89 lakhs.</li><li>Profit before tax for the year ended December 31, 2025, is INR 762.14 lakhs.</li><li>Earning per equity share (EPS) for Q3 2025 is INR 7.47.</li><li>The company has reported unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0d97fd42-5891-4996-b5f5-a3db3d11fdfa.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JSL INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[COARO] Coastal Roadways Reports Q3 and Nine Months Results for FY2025-26, Profit Before Tax Up 208</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=COASTAL+ROADWAYS+LTD.&title=Coastal+Roadways+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+FY2025-26%2C+Profit+Before+Tax+Up+208&newsId=7b4ecd1e-8dc3-446f-99d2-60e39c9f1b1b&token=N2I0ZWNkMWUtOGRj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b4ecd1e-8dc3-446f-99d2-60e39c9f1b1b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Coastal Roadways Ltd. has reported its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s profit before tax stands at INR 208 lakhs, compared to INR 186 lakhs in the same period last year. The company operates in two segments: Freight Division and Supply Chain Solutions Division. The results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors. The company has also restated the financial results for the impacted quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2024 due to a prior period error in accounting treatment of investments in mutual funds.</p><ul><li>Profit before tax for Q3 FY2025-26 is INR 208 lakhs</li><li>Profit before tax for nine months ended 31st December 2025 is INR 487 lakhs</li><li>The company operates in two segments: Freight Division and Supply Chain Solutions Division</li><li>Results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors</li><li>Financial results for the impacted quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2024 have been restated due to a prior period error in accounting treatment of investments in mutual funds</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/09ab5bb4-cff1-416e-9fc7-dad62e57c1bc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: COASTAL ROADWAYS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BIHSPONG] Bihar Sponge Iron Ltd. Reports Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025, Faces Legal Issue with Vanraj Steels</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BIHAR+SPONGE+IRON+LTD.&title=Bihar+Sponge+Iron+Ltd.+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025%2C+Faces+Legal+Issue+with+Vanraj+Steels&newsId=7bebc1c0-9efe-40b2-a4cb-a87d187fe5f3&token=N2JlYmMxYzAtOWVm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7bebc1c0-9efe-40b2-a4cb-a87d187fe5f3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bihar Sponge Iron Ltd. has reported its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 8,730.22 Lakhs for the quarter and 22,855.77 Lakhs for the nine months. However, the company is facing a legal issue as Vanraj Steels, which had temporary usage rights for the company&apos;s manufacturing facilities, has suddenly closed operations without official communication. The company is seeking legal opinion for further proceedings.</p><ul><li>Bihar Sponge Iron Ltd. reports Q3 and nine months financial results for 2025.</li><li>Revenue from operations stands at 8,730.22 Lakhs for the quarter and 22,855.77 Lakhs for the nine months.</li><li>Vanraj Steels, which had temporary usage rights for the company&apos;s manufacturing facilities, has suddenly closed operations without official communication.</li><li>The company is seeking legal opinion for further proceedings.</li><li>The financial results have been reviewed and approved by the Audit Committee and the Board of Directors.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fa0696ab-831b-45df-aab0-f2684a1bcbd4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BIHAR SPONGE IRON LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHANKARA] Shankara Building Products Ltd. Announces Q3 &amp; 9M Results for FY2025-26, Re-Appoints Managing Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shankara+Building+Products+Ltd&title=Shankara+Building+Products+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+%26+9M+Results+for+FY2025-26%2C+Re-Appoints+Managing+Director&newsId=f0b9e1da-d4b2-4c08-8aad-7a9e8f543f04&token=ZjBiOWUxZGEtZDRi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0b9e1da-d4b2-4c08-8aad-7a9e8f543f04</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:54:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shankara Building Products Ltd. has announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 420.40 crores for the quarter and 1,035.53 crores for the nine months. The company has also announced the re-appointment of Mr. Sukumar Srinivas as the Managing Director for a period of five years, subject to shareholder approval.</p><ul><li>Unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 and 9M FY2025-26 announced.</li><li>Revenue from operations stands at 420.40 crores for the quarter and 1,035.53 crores for the nine months.</li><li>Mr. Sukumar Srinivas re-appointed as Managing Director for a period of five years, subject to shareholder approval.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ef24bb38-2ce8-4918-8bac-70345d7d6802.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shankara Building Products Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SDL] Span Divergent Limited Reports Integrated Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months of FY2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Span+Divergent+Ltd-%24&title=Span+Divergent+Limited+Reports+Integrated+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+of+FY2025&newsId=0902950c-6880-4ca9-b1f0-c27305ee63c3&token=MDkwMjk1MGMtNjg4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0902950c-6880-4ca9-b1f0-c27305ee63c3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:52:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Span Divergent Limited has released its integrated unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The results are in accordance with the circular dated December 31, 2024, issued by SEBI. The filing is now available on the company&apos;s website at www.span.in for stakeholders&apos; reference.</p><ul><li>Span Divergent Limited has released its integrated unaudited financial results for the third quarter and nine months of the financial year 2025.</li><li>The results are in line with the SEBI circular dated December 31, 2024.</li><li>The financial filing for the aforementioned period is now accessible on the company&apos;s official website.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8d90e429-ceda-4de5-87e8-420afabbbad3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Span Divergent Ltd-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VALENCIA] Valencia Nutrition Approves Allotment of Equity Shares Worth Rs. 4,36,00,000 to Promoter</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Valencia+Nutrition+Ltd&title=Valencia+Nutrition+Approves+Allotment+of+Equity+Shares+Worth+Rs.+4%2C36%2C00%2C000+to+Promoter&newsId=859a4878-3c26-43e4-bb97-a147c38d5c3b&token=ODU5YTQ4NzgtM2My</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">859a4878-3c26-43e4-bb97-a147c38d5c3b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 09:52:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Valencia Nutrition Limited has approved the allotment of 10,90,000 equity shares to a promoter at an issue price of Rs. 40/- per share, including a share premium of Rs. 30/- per share, pursuant to the conversion of warrants. The total consideration for the shares is Rs. 4,36,00,000/-. This allotment is part of a larger issuance of 50,00,000 convertible warrants announced earlier. Post this allotment, 39,10,000 warrants remain outstanding for conversion.</p><ul><li>Valencia Nutrition has allotted 10,90,000 equity shares to a promoter.</li><li>The allotment is pursuant to the conversion of warrants issued earlier.</li><li>The total consideration for the shares is Rs. 4,36,00,000/-.</li><li>This allotment is part of a larger issuance of 50,00,000 convertible warrants.</li><li>39,10,000 warrants remain outstanding for conversion.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/11cbc7a5-11a9-45c5-9230-1d5db0301638.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Valencia Nutrition Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>