<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:26:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SUVENPHAR] Cohance Lifesciences Appoints Mr. Sunil Kumar Singh as Senior Management Personnel</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Suven+Pharmaceuticals+Ltd&title=Cohance+Lifesciences+Appoints+Mr.+Sunil+Kumar+Singh+as+Senior+Management+Personnel&newsId=08f1df2b-5ee4-4e7a-8a9c-52b8437919c1&token=MDhmMWRmMmItNWVl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08f1df2b-5ee4-4e7a-8a9c-52b8437919c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:52:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cohance Lifesciences Ltd has appointed Mr. Sunil Kumar Singh, Chief Quality Officer, as Senior Management Personnel of the Company with effect from January 19, 2026. Mr. Singh brings over 35 years of extensive leadership experience in pharmaceutical quality across APIs, formulations, CDMO and external manufacturing ecosystems. He has a proven track record in building future-ready quality organizations, strengthening regulatory trust, and enabling business growth through science-driven quality transformation, digitalization and proactive risk governance.</p><ul><li>Mr. Sunil Kumar Singh appointed as Senior Management Personnel of Cohance Lifesciences Ltd</li><li>Mr. Singh has over 35 years of experience in pharmaceutical quality</li><li>He has a proven track record in building future-ready quality organizations</li><li>Mr. Singh&apos;s appointment is effective from January 19, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9c15788d-7edb-4d17-bbfe-7362b8c6e92e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Suven Pharmaceuticals Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[OBEROIRLTY] Oberoi Realty Announces 9MFY26 and Q3FY26 Results: Revenue at Rs. 4,480.56 crores and Rs. 1,561.74 crores, PAT at Rs. 1,802.96 crores and Rs. 622.50 crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=OBEROI+REALTY+LTD.&title=Oberoi+Realty+Announces+9MFY26+and+Q3FY26+Results%3A+Revenue+at+Rs.+4%2C480.56+crores+and+Rs.+1%2C561.74+crores%2C+PAT+at+Rs.+1%2C802.96+crores+and+Rs.+622.50+crores&newsId=6c70aee1-c4fb-446a-9dcf-838e2577a47a&token=NmM3MGFlZTEtYzRm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c70aee1-c4fb-446a-9dcf-838e2577a47a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:51:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Oberoi Realty Limited, a Mumbai-based real estate development company, has announced its results for the third quarter and nine months of FY26. The company has recorded consolidated revenues of Rs. 1,561.74 crore for Q3FY26 and Rs. 4,480.56 crore for 9MFY26. The consolidated profit after tax was Rs. 622.50 crore for Q3FY26 and Rs. 1,802.96 crore for 9MFY26. The residential, commercial, and retail businesses delivered a steady performance, aligned with the company&apos;s focus on disciplined execution. Oberoi Realty remains optimistic about the year ahead, supported by a strong development pipeline, prudent capital management, and its unwavering focus on creating future-ready projects.</p><ul><li>Revenue for 9MFY26 is Rs. 4,480.56 crores and Q3FY26 is Rs. 1,561.74 crores</li><li>EBITDA for 9MFY26 is Rs. 2,619.22 crores and for Q3FY26 is Rs. 926.36 crores</li><li>Profit After Tax (PAT) for 9MFY26 is Rs. 1,802.96 crores and Q3FY26 is Rs. 622.50 crores</li><li>Steady performance in residential, commercial, and retail businesses</li><li>Optimistic about the year ahead with a strong development pipeline and prudent capital management</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/59892e44-eaec-4e39-8428-c7395cd1746e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: OBEROI REALTY LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GHUSHINE] Ghushine Fintrrade Ocean Ltd CFO Alok Bhopalsingh Jain Resigns Effective January 19, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ghushine+Fintrrade+Ocean+Ltd&title=Ghushine+Fintrrade+Ocean+Ltd+CFO+Alok+Bhopalsingh+Jain+Resigns+Effective+January+19%2C+2026&newsId=85c6376f-40e2-4162-b8f9-434f1c04ad18&token=ODVjNjM3NmYtNDBl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85c6376f-40e2-4162-b8f9-434f1c04ad18</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:31:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Auditor</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ghushine Fintrrade Ocean Ltd announced the resignation of its Chief Financial Officer (CFO), Mr. Alok Bhopalsingh Jain, effective from the closure of business hours on January 19, 2026. The board approved the resignation in its meeting on the same day. Mr. Jain will continue to serve as the Managing Director and Chief Executive Officer of the company.</p><ul><li>Alok Bhopalsingh Jain resigns as CFO of Ghushine Fintrrade Ocean Ltd.</li><li>Resignation takes effect from the closure of business hours on January 19, 2026.</li><li>Mr. Jain to continue serving as Managing Director and Chief Executive Officer.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f4c1cd6d-7d4b-4f37-886f-55440bf72379.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ghushine Fintrrade Ocean Ltd | Category: Auditor</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EKI] EKI Energy Services Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on January 22, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=EKI+Energy+Services+Ltd&title=EKI+Energy+Services+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+January+22%2C+2026&newsId=e1165d26-6148-4759-a448-54732c023193&token=ZTExNjVkMjYtNjE0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e1165d26-6148-4759-a448-54732c023193</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:31:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>EKI Energy Services Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 22, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for designated persons and their immediate relatives has been closed from January 01, 2026, and will reopen 48 hours after the declaration of the results.</p><ul><li>EKI Energy Services Ltd to approve Q3 and nine months financial results on January 22, 2026</li><li>Trading window for designated persons and their immediate relatives closed from January 01, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/30d4e874-8562-42c9-9ff2-41e067aa00b8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: EKI Energy Services Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GHUSHINE] Ghushine Fintrrade Ocean Ltd: CFO Alok Jain Resigns Effective January 19, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ghushine+Fintrrade+Ocean+Ltd&title=Ghushine+Fintrrade+Ocean+Ltd%3A+CFO+Alok+Jain+Resigns+Effective+January+19%2C+2026&newsId=0c98ed03-3675-4a6a-83da-7bec3515a31b&token=MGM5OGVkMDMtMzY3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c98ed03-3675-4a6a-83da-7bec3515a31b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ghushine Fintrrade Ocean Ltd announced the resignation of Mr. Alok Jain as Chief Financial Officer with effect from the closure of business hours of January 19, 2026. The board in its meeting held on the same day has considered and approved his resignation. Mr. Jain will continue to serve as Managing Director and Chief Executive Officer of the Company.</p><ul><li>Resignation of Mr. Alok Jain as Chief Financial Officer of Ghushine Fintrrade Ocean Ltd.</li><li>Mr. Jain will continue to serve as Managing Director and Chief Executive Officer of the Company.</li><li>The board has considered and approved the resignation in its meeting held on January 19, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e38bab2b-9bfc-4206-830e-8225512761dd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ghushine Fintrrade Ocean Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AURUM] Aurum PropTech Ltd Confirms No Deviation or Variation in Use of Rights Issue Proceeds as of December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Aurum+PropTech+Ltd&title=Aurum+PropTech+Ltd+Confirms+No+Deviation+or+Variation+in+Use+of+Rights+Issue+Proceeds+as+of+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=d121605d-99ba-41ce-a874-ed4d321be2b0&token=ZDEyMTYwNWQtOTli</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d121605d-99ba-41ce-a874-ed4d321be2b0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Aurum PropTech Ltd, in accordance with Regulation 32 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, has confirmed that there is no deviation or variation in the use of proceeds from the objects stated in the Letter of Offer for Rights Issue of the Company dated April 08, 2022. A statement confirming the same for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, duly reviewed by the Audit Committee, is attached.</p><ul><li>Aurum PropTech Ltd confirms no deviation or variation in the use of Rights Issue proceeds as of December 31, 2025.</li><li>Rights Issue of Rs. 334.18 crore (net of right issue expense) was raised in April 2022.</li><li>No deviation or variation in the utilization of these proceeds for the quarter ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>Statement reviewed by the Audit Committee.</li><li>Aurum PropTech Ltd is a company registered in India with CIN: L72300MH2013PLC244874.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/37bceb7a-b8dc-4bcf-b0bd-0398fc81d2a2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Aurum PropTech Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SOFTBPO] Softbpo Global Services EGM Adjourned Due to Want of Quorum</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SOFTBPO+GLOBAL+SERVICES+LTD.&title=Softbpo+Global+Services+EGM+Adjourned+Due+to+Want+of+Quorum&newsId=d42490b8-1810-4546-9de4-75a6c459045b&token=ZDQyNDkwYjgtMTgx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d42490b8-1810-4546-9de4-75a6c459045b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:57:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) of Softbpo Global Services Ltd, proposed to be held on January 19, 2026, was adjourned due to lack of quorum. The meeting has been rescheduled to Tuesday, January 27, 2026, at 11:30 a.m., at the same location. The company will send a separate notice for the adjourned meeting.</p><ul><li>Softbpo Global Services EGM was adjourned due to lack of quorum</li><li>The adjourned EGM is rescheduled to January 27, 2026</li><li>The meeting will take place at the same location</li><li>The company will send a separate notice for the adjourned meeting</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/084109e7-953f-4f32-889e-6e4dee9d224b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SOFTBPO GLOBAL SERVICES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CHALET] Chalet Hotels Ltd Receives Request for Reclassification of Promoter Group Entities to Public</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Chalet+Hotels+Ltd&title=Chalet+Hotels+Ltd+Receives+Request+for+Reclassification+of+Promoter+Group+Entities+to+Public&newsId=75f2c44f-bc51-4d87-bf80-e5160439674c&token=NzVmMmM0NGYtYmM1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75f2c44f-bc51-4d87-bf80-e5160439674c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:51:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Chalet Hotels Ltd has received a request for reclassification from the Promoter Group entities, Sundew Real Estate Private Limited and Pramaan Properties Private Limited, to be categorized as Public. This decision will be placed before the Board of Directors at its forthcoming meeting as per the provisions of Regulation 31A(8) of the Listing Regulations. The disclosure has also been placed on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Chalet Hotels Ltd received a request for reclassification of Promoter Group entities</li><li>The entities requested to be reclassified from Promoter Group to Public</li><li>The request includes Sundew Real Estate Private Limited and Pramaan Properties Private Limited</li><li>The decision will be placed before the Board of Directors at its forthcoming meeting</li><li>The disclosure has been placed on the company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9534c5da-be29-4d42-955b-1a6ed4d201b2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Chalet Hotels Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VERANDA] Veranda Learning Solutions Receives No Objection Letter from BSE for Composite Scheme of Arrangement</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Veranda+Learning+Solutions+Ltd&title=Veranda+Learning+Solutions+Receives+No+Objection+Letter+from+BSE+for+Composite+Scheme+of+Arrangement&newsId=4cd657e8-11b4-4dd3-b754-e5300cb07e24&token=NGNkNjU3ZTgtMTFi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4cd657e8-11b4-4dd3-b754-e5300cb07e24</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:46:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Veranda Learning Solutions Ltd. has received a &apos;no adverse observations&apos; observation letter from BSE Limited regarding the proposed Composite Scheme of Arrangement. The scheme involves Veranda Learning Solutions Limited, Veranda XL Learning Solutions Private Limited, and J.K.Shah Commerce Education Limited. The scheme is subject to applicable regulatory and other approvals. SEBI has provided comments on the scheme, including disclosure of ongoing proceedings, additional information submission, compliance with SEBI circulars, and more.</p><ul><li>Veranda Learning Solutions receives &apos;no adverse observations&apos; letter from BSE for the Composite Scheme of Arrangement.</li><li>SEBI provides comments on the Composite Scheme of Arrangement.</li><li>The scheme involves Veranda Learning Solutions Limited, Veranda XL Learning Solutions Private Limited, and J.K.Shah Commerce Education Limited.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/70a8a6cd-a54e-4213-bd38-e507f8b12d15.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Veranda Learning Solutions Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TORNTPHARM] Torrent Pharmaceuticals Ltd. Approves Allotment of Non-Convertible Debentures Worth INR 110 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TORRENT+PHARMACEUTICALS+LTD.&title=Torrent+Pharmaceuticals+Ltd.+Approves+Allotment+of+Non-Convertible+Debentures+Worth+INR+110+Billion&newsId=c48340fc-db91-466d-9a5a-fecb6d6bfc57&token=YzQ4MzQwZmMtZGI5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c48340fc-db91-466d-9a5a-fecb6d6bfc57</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Torrent Pharmaceuticals Ltd. has approved the allotment of Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs) worth INR 110 Billion. The company will issue 11,00,000 NCDs, divided into four series. The Series 1 and 2 Debentures will be worth INR 20 Billion and INR 24.9 Billion respectively, while the Series 3 and 4 Debentures will be worth INR 30 Billion and INR 35 Billion respectively. The tenure of the instruments ranges from 2 to 4 years, with the final maturity date ranging from 2026 to 2031. The coupon/interest offered ranges from 7.45% to 7.80% per annum.</p><ul><li>Torrent Pharmaceuticals Ltd. to issue Non-Convertible Debentures worth INR 110 Billion.</li><li>Four series of NCDs will be issued, ranging from INR 20 Billion to INR 35 Billion.</li><li>The tenure of the instruments ranges from 2 to 4 years.</li><li>The final maturity date ranges from 2026 to 2031.</li><li>The coupon/interest offered ranges from 7.45% to 7.80% per annum.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/83c82fcc-64c2-4592-9147-08d9bf37d8e0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TORRENT PHARMACEUTICALS LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>