<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 04:23:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ADANIGREEN] Adani Green Energy Provides Further Update on US SEC Matter Involving Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Adani+Green+Energy+Ltd&title=Adani+Green+Energy+Provides+Further+Update+on+US+SEC+Matter+Involving+Directors&newsId=ab689bec-627b-4e01-883a-4c58aaa9fb94&token=YWI2ODliZWMtNjI3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab689bec-627b-4e01-883a-4c58aaa9fb94</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 00:01:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Adani Green Energy Ltd. has provided a further update on a matter of civil nature brought by the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) against Mr. Gautam Adani and Mr. Sagar Adani in the United States District Court for the Eastern District of New York. The Defendants have agreed to accept service on behalf of the SEC without accepting the jurisdiction of the EDNY and are planning to move to dismiss the SEC&apos;s Complaint or file responsive pleadings. Adani Green Energy Limited is not a party to these proceedings, and no charges have been brought against the company. The Defendants have not been charged with violation of the United States Foreign Corrupt Practices Act.</p><ul><li>Adani Green Energy provides further update on US SEC matter involving directors</li><li>Defendants agree to accept service from the SEC without accepting jurisdiction</li><li>Defendants plan to move to dismiss the SEC&apos;s Complaint or file responsive pleadings</li><li>Adani Green Energy is not a party to the proceedings</li><li>No charges brought against the company</li><li>Defendants not charged with violation of United States Foreign Corrupt Practices Act</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/eb4fd5af-23bb-4df3-9e94-b0b4a46f7396.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Adani Green Energy Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DOLPHMED] Dolphin Medical Services Ltd. Defers Board Meeting to February 06, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DOLPHIN+MEDICAL+SERVICES+LTD.&title=Dolphin+Medical+Services+Ltd.+Defers+Board+Meeting+to+February+06%2C+2026&newsId=60b19d5f-e36d-4167-a877-6813574991b3&token=NjBiMTlkNWYtZTM2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60b19d5f-e36d-4167-a877-6813574991b3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 00:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dolphin Medical Services Ltd. has announced the deferment of its Board Meeting originally scheduled for January 30, 2026. The meeting, which was to consider and approve matters relating to the Quarter results, has been rescheduled to February 06, 2026. The meeting commenced at 09:00 P.M. and concluded at 10:30 P.M.</p><ul><li>Dolphin Medical Services Ltd. defers Board Meeting to February 06, 2026</li><li>The original date for the Board Meeting was January 30, 2026</li><li>The meeting was rescheduled to consider and approve Quarter results</li><li>The meeting commenced at 09:00 P.M. and concluded at 10:30 P.M.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0fec7a49-bf5a-4464-8965-86fc73139cdf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DOLPHIN MEDICAL SERVICES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[POWERGRID] POWERGRID Approves ¥173.14 Crore Investment for Thrissur VSC HVDC Station Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=POWER+GRID+CORPORATION+OF+INDIA+LTD.&title=POWERGRID+Approves+%C2%A5173.14+Crore+Investment+for+Thrissur+VSC+HVDC+Station+Augmentation&newsId=7ee48017-d28a-49d6-a58e-7bf116951e9e&token=N2VlNDgwMTctZDI4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ee48017-d28a-49d6-a58e-7bf116951e9e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 00:01:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd has received investment approval from the &apos;Committee of Directors on Investment on Projects&apos; for the augmentation of 1x500 MVA, 400/220kV ICT (3) at Thrissur VSC HVDC Station in Kerala. The project is estimated to cost ¥173.14 Crore and is scheduled to be commissioned by 21*&apos; August, 2027.</p><ul><li>POWERGRID&apos;s &apos;Committee of Directors on Investment on Projects&apos; approves ¥173.14 Crore investment for Thrissur VSC HVDC Station augmentation.</li><li>The project involves the augmentation of 1x500 MVA, 400/220kV ICT (3) at Thrissur VSC HVDC Station in Kerala.</li><li>The project is scheduled to be commissioned by 21*&apos; August, 2027.</li><li>This investment is a significant move by POWERGRID in the power transmission sector.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/56d97adb-4693-4a33-9c09-5fee621c557b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: POWER GRID CORPORATION OF INDIA LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[POWERGRID] Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd. to Withdraw Nominee Director from PTC India Limited Board</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=POWER+GRID+CORPORATION+OF+INDIA+LTD.&title=Power+Grid+Corporation+of+India+Ltd.+to+Withdraw+Nominee+Director+from+PTC+India+Limited+Board&newsId=41f9a8a0-6d7d-4768-8523-97a4fb2b37b7&token=NDFmOWE4YTAtNmQ3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41f9a8a0-6d7d-4768-8523-97a4fb2b37b7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 00:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In accordance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd.&apos;s Board of Directors has approved the proposal for withdrawing its Nominee Director from PTC India Limited&apos;s Board. This decision comes in pursuance of the Office Memorandum dated 16th January 2026 from the Ministry of Power (MoP), which led to the relinquishment of all promoter rights as set out in PTC&apos;s Articles of Association.</p><ul><li>Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd. to withdraw its Nominee Director from PTC India Limited&apos;s Board</li><li>Decision in accordance with Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Relinquishment of promoter rights following the Ministry of Power (MoP) Office Memorandum dated 16th January 2026</li><li>Affects the composition of PTC India Limited&apos;s Board</li><li>Highlights Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd.&apos;s commitment to regulatory compliance</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7ef283c8-8b27-4621-86c1-4467a80480f7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: POWER GRID CORPORATION OF INDIA LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MPSLTD] MPS Ltd Subsidiary Acquires Unbound Medicine, Inc. for USD 16.50 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MPS+LTD.&title=MPS+Ltd+Subsidiary+Acquires+Unbound+Medicine%2C+Inc.+for+USD+16.50+Million&newsId=2275ac65-8589-4d73-a462-da552b7f0812&token=MjI3NWFjNjUtODU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2275ac65-8589-4d73-a462-da552b7f0812</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 22:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>MPS North America LLC, a wholly owned subsidiary of MPS Ltd, has entered into a Stock Purchase Agreement to acquire 100% stake in Unbound Medicine, Inc., a U.S.-based healthcare learning technology company, for a total consideration of USD 16.50 Million. The acquisition aligns with MPS’ long-term strategy of scaling platform-led businesses while accelerating value creation through AI and domain-specific adjacencies.</p><ul><li>MPS North America LLC to acquire 100% stake in Unbound Medicine, Inc.</li><li>Total consideration of USD 16.50 Million</li><li>Unbound Medicine, Inc. is a U.S.-based healthcare learning technology company</li><li>Acquisition aligns with MPS’ long-term growth strategy</li><li>Unbound Medicine operates on a subscription-led model with ~97% gross retention</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c1a98311-c1cf-4cd3-97d7-7cce8c8e1376.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MPS LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAVFI] Savani Financials Ltd Forfeits 45442 Partly Paid-Up Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SAVANI+FINANCIALS+LTD.&title=Savani+Financials+Ltd+Forfeits+45442+Partly+Paid-Up+Equity+Shares&newsId=c674b0be-54e1-42bf-a82d-7a6268199802&token=YzY3NGIwYmUtNTRl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c674b0be-54e1-42bf-a82d-7a6268199802</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 22:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Savani Financials Ltd has approved the forfeiture of 45442 partly paid-up equity shares due to unpaid first and final call money of Rs. 2/- each. This decision comes after the company&apos;s Board of Directors meeting held on Friday, January 30, 2026, and in compliance with Regulation 30 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The shares were previously subject to a First and Final Call Notice dated September 14, 2024, and three reminders for first and final call on the partly paid-up equity shares dated December 10, 2024, February 21, 2025, and July 04, 2025.</p><ul><li>Savani Financials Ltd forfeits 45442 partly paid-up equity shares.</li><li>The forfeiture is due to unpaid first and final call money of Rs. 2/- each.</li><li>The decision comes after the company&apos;s Board of Directors meeting on January 30, 2026.</li><li>The shares were previously subject to a First and Final Call Notice and three reminders.</li><li>The forfeiture is in compliance with Regulation 30 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/41bbd115-a068-4bdb-bf89-9e0c564d238f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SAVANI FINANCIALS LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PERSISTENT] Persistent Systems&apos; Executive Vice President, Vijay Verma, Resigns Due to Personal Reasons</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PERSISTENT+SYSTEMS+LTD.&title=Persistent+Systems%27+Executive+Vice+President%2C+Vijay+Verma%2C+Resigns+Due+to+Personal+Reasons&newsId=0dec6ab6-5921-4ea8-9a9c-147de7111755&token=MGRlYzZhYjYtNTky</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0dec6ab6-5921-4ea8-9a9c-147de7111755</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 22:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Persistent Systems Ltd. has announced the resignation of Mr. Vijay Verma, Executive Vice President — Serviceline BU, due to personal reasons effective from the closure of business hours on January 30, 2026 (US Time). Mr. Verma joined the company in 2026 and has been serving as the Executive Vice President since then. There is no material reason for his resignation other than the personal reasons cited. The company has also announced that Ms. Nitha Puthran will assume the responsibilities previously held by Mr. Verma.</p><ul><li>Vijay Verma resigns from the position of Executive Vice President — Serviceline BU due to personal reasons.</li><li>His resignation will be effective from the closure of business hours on January 30, 2026 (US Time).</li><li>Ms. Nitha Puthran will assume the responsibilities previously held by Mr. Verma.</li><li>There is no material reason for Mr. Verma&apos;s resignation.</li><li>Ms. Puthran joined the company on January 2, 2026 (EST) and her appointment was previously announced.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/67871b78-abc2-47d0-b81e-0ef88400297f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PERSISTENT SYSTEMS LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAVFI] Savani Financials Ltd: No Deviation or Variation in Rights Issue Utilization for Quarter and Nine Months Ended December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SAVANI+FINANCIALS+LTD.&title=Savani+Financials+Ltd%3A+No+Deviation+or+Variation+in+Rights+Issue+Utilization+for+Quarter+and+Nine+Months+Ended+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=a9d65d06-a422-4a4d-b41f-93d622fba2f2&token=YTlkNjVkMDYtYTQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a9d65d06-a422-4a4d-b41f-93d622fba2f2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 22:32:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Savani Financials Ltd, now known as Mantra Capital Limited, has confirmed that there is no deviation or variation in the utilization of proceeds from the objects stated in the Letter of Offer for Rights Issue of the Company, dated April 10, 2024, for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The Audit Committee has reviewed and noted the statement of deviation and variations in its meeting held on January 30, 2026.</p><ul><li>Savani Financials Ltd, now known as Mantra Capital Limited, confirms no deviation or variation in Rights Issue utilization for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The Audit Committee has reviewed and noted the statement of deviation and variations in its meeting held on January 30, 2026.</li><li>The Rights Issue proceeds have been utilized as per the objects stated in the Letter of Offer, dated April 10, 2024.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/44a14f7e-7f44-42a5-91d1-9d99ba168320.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SAVANI FINANCIALS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PRIYALT] Priya Ltd. to Consider and Approve Q3 Financial Results on 06/02/2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PRIYA+LTD.-%24&title=Priya+Ltd.+to+Consider+and+Approve+Q3+Financial+Results+on+06%2F02%2F2026&newsId=7d2f3a25-b851-48f7-abb8-775825821419&token=N2QyZjNhMjUtYjg1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7d2f3a25-b851-48f7-abb8-775825821419</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 22:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Priya Ltd. has informed the BSE that its Board of Directors will meet on 06/02/2026 to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter ended on 31st December, 2025. The meeting will also take on record the Limited Review Report for the same quarter. The trading window for dealing in securities of the company is closed from 1st January, 2026 and will open after 48 hours of announcement of financial results to the public.</p><ul><li>Priya Ltd. to consider and approve Q3 financial results on 06/02/2026</li><li>Meeting to take place at the company&apos;s registered office</li><li>Un-audited financial results for the quarter ended on 31st December, 2025 to be considered</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities of the company is closed from 1st January, 2026</li><li>Trading window to open after 48 hours of announcement of financial results to the public</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/91b63f00-e1d9-4e86-96e2-8663e9afd6d5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PRIYA LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PRAXIS] Praxis Home Retail Ltd Appoints Shashwat Nigam as CEO and Additional Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Praxis+Home+Retail+Ltd&title=Praxis+Home+Retail+Ltd+Appoints+Shashwat+Nigam+as+CEO+and+Additional+Director&newsId=5fba4385-9ab5-4f8e-b79d-0952d6bc1afd&token=NWZiYTQzODUtOWFi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5fba4385-9ab5-4f8e-b79d-0952d6bc1afd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 22:31:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Praxis Home Retail Ltd has appointed Mr. Shashwat Nigam (DIN: 10277690) as Chief Executive Officer and additional Director with effect from February 03, 2026 for a term of three consecutive years, subject to the approval of shareholders. His appointment was approved in the meeting of the Board of Directors of the Company held on January 30, 2026. Mr. Nigam is a seasoned P&amp;L owner and operator with over 18 years of experience. He has a strong track record of organising businesses, restoring performance, and wiring operations for sustainable scale. Mr. Nigam has worked with the management team of the Company over the last 7 months as a consultant and part of the management advisory committee. He has initiated key turnaround actions, including organisation restructuring, KPI-driven execution, cash-flow prioritisation, technology stabilisation, category availability improvement, and active engagement with business stakeholders.</p><ul><li>Mr. Shashwat Nigam appointed as CEO and additional Director of Praxis Home Retail Ltd</li><li>Appointment is effective from February 03, 2026 for a term of three years</li><li>Mr. Nigam has over 18 years of experience in organising businesses and restoring performance</li><li>He has a strong track record of wiring operations for sustainable scale</li><li>Mr. Nigam has initiated key turnaround actions in his 7 months tenure as a consultant with the Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/87675a76-bbb6-4d86-b03e-f3159d5c2bae.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Praxis Home Retail Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>