<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 15:17:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[VASWANI] Vaswani Industries Ltd. Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025, Revealing Increased Revenue and Profit</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VASWANI+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Vaswani+Industries+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Revealing+Increased+Revenue+and+Profit&newsId=d39261ee-da0f-41af-8f68-69efbea0e6b9&token=ZDM5MjYxZWUtZGEw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d39261ee-da0f-41af-8f68-69efbea0e6b9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 15:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Vaswani Industries Ltd. has announced its un-audited standalone financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations has increased by 38.64% for the quarter and 42.35% for the nine months period, compared to the same periods in 2024. The profit before tax and exceptional items has also increased by 65.49% for the quarter and 45.58% for the nine months period. However, the profit for the period has decreased by 795.29 due to exceptional items and tax expense. The company&apos;s earnings per equity share (Par value Rs. 10 each) for the quarter are Rs. 0.24 (Basic) and Rs. 0.24 (Diluted). The financial results were reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations increased by 38.64% for the quarter and 42.35% for the nine months period.</li><li>Profit before tax and exceptional items increased by 65.49% for the quarter and 45.58% for the nine months period.</li><li>Profit for the period decreased by 795.29 due to exceptional items and tax expense.</li><li>Earnings per equity share (Par value Rs. 10 each) for the quarter are Rs. 0.24 (Basic) and Rs. 0.24 (Diluted).</li><li>Financial results reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/22bdc5e0-5734-4d12-898b-cbd5899b3787.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VASWANI INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PICTUREHS] Picturehouse Media Ltd: Independent Director, Mr. Gautam Shahi, Resigns</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PICTUREHOUSE+MEDIA+LTD.&title=Picturehouse+Media+Ltd%3A+Independent+Director%2C+Mr.+Gautam+Shahi%2C+Resigns&newsId=f9b61002-7a2b-49e6-adf1-907a1eff978f&token=ZjliNjEwMDItN2Ey</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9b61002-7a2b-49e6-adf1-907a1eff978f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 15:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Picturehouse Media Ltd announced the resignation of its Independent Director, Mr. Gautam Shahi, with effect from the close of business hours on 28th February 2026. The decision was due to a significant increase in Mr. Shahi&apos;s professional commitments in his legal practice, making it difficult for him to devote the required time and attention to his role as an Independent Director. Mr. Shahi confirmed that there are no other material reasons for his resignation.</p><ul><li>Mr. Gautam Shahi resigns from his position as Independent Director of Picturehouse Media Ltd.</li><li>The resignation is effective from the close of business hours on 28th February 2026.</li><li>The decision is due to increased professional commitments in Mr. Shahi&apos;s legal practice.</li><li>Mr. Shahi confirms no other material reasons for his resignation.</li><li>Picturehouse Media Ltd complies with the applicable provisions of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9f6ecbfc-d61e-41d7-af62-5febdca48016.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PICTUREHOUSE MEDIA LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KESAR] Kesar India Ltd Approves Allotment of 5,74,319 Equity Shares to Non-Promoters</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kesar+India+Ltd&title=Kesar+India+Ltd+Approves+Allotment+of+5%2C74%2C319+Equity+Shares+to+Non-Promoters&newsId=b1042f1a-78f3-47ad-9914-f1a2d1ff634b&token=YjEwNDJmMWEtNzhm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b1042f1a-78f3-47ad-9914-f1a2d1ff634b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 15:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Kesar India Ltd, in a meeting of the Preferential Issue Committee of the Board of Directors, approved the allotment of 5,74,319 equity shares to non-promoter allottees. The shares are being allotted pursuant to the conversion of 3,74,319 fully convertible warrants allotted on September 18, 2025, at an issue price of Rs. 350 each. The allottees include Gunjan Agarwal, Priyank Dhirendra Shah, Mohit Rajeshkumar Atlani, Mihir Atlani, Yash Suresh Atlani, Prachi Pranav Bhagat, Chintan Viijay Makhecha, Dhavan Govindram Medtiya, and Piyush Narayanlal Medtiya. The paid-up equity share capital of the company will increase to Rs. 28,57,32,290 divided into 2,85,73,229 equity shares of face value of Rs. 10 each.</p><ul><li>Kesar India Ltd approves allotment of 5,74,319 equity shares to non-promoter allottees.</li><li>The allotment is pursuant to the conversion of 3,74,319 fully convertible warrants allotted on September 18, 2025.</li><li>The allottees include Gunjan Agarwal, Priyank Dhirendra Shah, Mohit Rajeshkumar Atlani, Mihir Atlani, Yash Suresh Atlani, Prachi Pranav Bhagat, Chintan Viijay Makhecha, Dhavan Govindram Medtiya, and Piyush Narayanlal Medtiya.</li><li>The paid-up equity share capital of the company will increase to Rs. 28,57,32,290 divided into 2,85,73,229 equity shares of face value of Rs. 10 each.</li><li>The meeting of the Preferential Issue Committee of the Board of Directors was commenced at 07:45 P.M. and concluded at 08:00 P.M.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/93974a61-5ce3-44b3-adaf-c6f49f72d78d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kesar India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PVP] Independent Director, Mr. Gautam Shahi, Resigns from PVP Ventures Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PVP+VENTURES+LTD.&title=Independent+Director%2C+Mr.+Gautam+Shahi%2C+Resigns+from+PVP+Ventures+Ltd&newsId=7973ed80-3cc4-4753-9854-7f193d08d375&token=Nzk3M2VkODAtM2Nj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7973ed80-3cc4-4753-9854-7f193d08d375</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 14:51:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>PVP Ventures Ltd announced the resignation of its Independent Director, Mr. Gautam Shahi, with effect from the close of business hours on 28th February 2026. The decision was due to a significant increase in Mr. Shahi&apos;s professional commitments in his legal practice, making it difficult for him to devote the required time and attention to his role as an Independent Director. Mr. Shahi confirmed that there are no other material reasons for his resignation.</p><ul><li>Mr. Gautam Shahi resigns from his position as Independent Director of PVP Ventures Ltd</li><li>The resignation is effective from the close of business hours on 28th February 2026</li><li>The decision is due to increased professional commitments in Mr. Shahi&apos;s legal practice</li><li>Mr. Shahi confirmed that there are no other material reasons for his resignation</li><li>PVP Ventures Ltd complies with the applicable provisions of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1e01041d-aed6-4eec-af93-206e664f1bd6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PVP VENTURES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VASWANI] Vaswani Industries Ltd. Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VASWANI+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Vaswani+Industries+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025&newsId=a6567a9d-9c94-407a-b72f-55189924bbba&token=YTY1NjdhOWQtOWM5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a6567a9d-9c94-407a-b72f-55189924bbba</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 14:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Vaswani Industries Ltd. has announced its un-audited standalone financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations for the quarter is Rs. 8,501.03 lakhs and for the nine months is Rs. 32,411.88 lakhs. The net profit for the quarter is Rs. 796.42 lakhs and for the nine months is Rs. 13,432 lakhs. The total comprehensive income for the period is (Rs. 795.29) lakhs.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter is Rs. 8,501.03 lakhs</li><li>Revenue from operations for the nine months is Rs. 32,411.88 lakhs</li><li>Net profit for the quarter is Rs. 796.42 lakhs</li><li>Net profit for the nine months is Rs. 13,432 lakhs</li><li>Total comprehensive income for the period is (Rs. 795.29) lakhs</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c85b309b-59e1-4e2f-8bbe-485e5f9eb2d9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VASWANI INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PERSISTENT] Persistent Systems Ltd Establishes Wholly Owned Foreign Enterprise in China</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PERSISTENT+SYSTEMS+LTD.&title=Persistent+Systems+Ltd+Establishes+Wholly+Owned+Foreign+Enterprise+in+China&newsId=b8ed95bc-90b9-412c-8846-da169d1c0bae&token=YjhlZDk1YmMtOTBi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8ed95bc-90b9-412c-8846-da169d1c0bae</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 14:41:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Persistent Systems Pte. Ltd., Singapore, a wholly owned subsidiary of Persistent Systems Ltd, has established a Wholly Owned Foreign Enterprise (WFOE) in China. The new entity, Baixinteng System Service (Shanghai) Co. Ltd., also known as Persistent Systems (Shanghai) Co. Ltd., received its Business License from the Shanghai Administration for Market Regulation (SAMR) on February 28, 2026.</p><ul><li>Persistent Systems Pte. Ltd., Singapore, a wholly owned subsidiary of Persistent Systems Ltd, has established a Wholly Owned Foreign Enterprise (WFOE) in China.</li><li>The new entity is named Baixinteng System Service (Shanghai) Co. Ltd., also known as Persistent Systems (Shanghai) Co. Ltd.</li><li>The company has received the Business License from the Shanghai Administration for Market Regulation (SAMR) in China.</li><li>This expansion is in line with the company&apos;s strategic growth plans.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2c7bad3e-61bd-469e-9d3b-78fa5bcd51a4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PERSISTENT SYSTEMS LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GTIL] Gabion Technologies India Ltd Appoints Ms. Sonal Jhanwar as Company Secretary &amp; Compliance Officer and M/s. Himanshu SK Gupta &amp; Associates as Secretarial Auditor for F.Y. 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Gabion+Technologies+India+Ltd&title=Gabion+Technologies+India+Ltd+Appoints+Ms.+Sonal+Jhanwar+as+Company+Secretary+%26+Compliance+Officer+and+M%2Fs.+Himanshu+SK+Gupta+%26+Associates+as+Secretarial+Auditor+for+F.Y.+2025-26&newsId=ba729a25-b043-4446-8e6b-49caa65b3bb8&token=YmE3MjlhMjUtYjA0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba729a25-b043-4446-8e6b-49caa65b3bb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 14:31:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gabion Technologies India Ltd has appointed Ms. Sonal Jhanwar as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer and M/s. Himanshu SK Gupta &amp; Associates as the Secretarial Auditor for the financial year 2025-26. Ms. Sonal Jhanwar is a Qualified Company Secretary with experience in handling secretarial and compliance functions of listed and unlisted companies. M/s. Himanshu SK Gupta &amp; Associates is a peer-reviewed firm of Practicing Company Secretaries offering comprehensive corporate advisory and compliance solutions.</p><ul><li>Ms. Sonal Jhanwar appointed as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer of Gabion Technologies India Ltd.</li><li>M/s. Himanshu SK Gupta &amp; Associates appointed as Secretarial Auditor for the financial year 2025-26.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4e1fbcd9-cdbd-4704-86f4-5ccd49d273f5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Gabion Technologies India Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IFCI] IFCI Ltd Re-appoints Chief Risk Officer Jagdish Garwal for Another Year</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IFCI+LTD.&title=IFCI+Ltd+Re-appoints+Chief+Risk+Officer+Jagdish+Garwal+for+Another+Year&newsId=e5cf4b04-f6db-4c6d-bd2d-63ed591df8ee&token=ZTVjZjRiMDQtZjZk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5cf4b04-f6db-4c6d-bd2d-63ed591df8ee</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 14:31:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>IFCI Ltd, a leading NBFC in India, has announced the re-appointment of its Chief Risk Officer, Jagdish Garwal, for a period of one year. Garwal, who has been serving as the CRO for the last two years, has been re-appointed in accordance with the RBI (NBFC-Governance) Directions and the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations. He has a rich experience of around 32 years in IFCI and its subsidiary and has been instrumental in managing the company&apos;s risk profile. The re-appointment is effective from March 01, 2026, till February 28, 2027.</p><ul><li>IFCI Ltd re-appoints Jagdish Garwal as Chief Risk Officer for another year</li><li>Garwal has been serving as CRO for the last two years</li><li>Re-appointment is in accordance with RBI and SEBI regulations</li><li>Garwal has a rich experience of around 32 years in IFCI and its subsidiary</li><li>Re-appointment is effective from March 01, 2026, till February 28, 2027</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2a6ade26-6dd7-4b34-96b8-7e5d1236950f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IFCI LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RATHIST] Rathi Steel &amp; Power Ltd.: Fine Waived by BSE Limited After Waiver Request</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RATHI+STEEL+%26+POWER+LTD.-%24&title=Rathi+Steel+%26+Power+Ltd.%3A+Fine+Waived+by+BSE+Limited+After+Waiver+Request&newsId=edb893a3-9299-490f-8093-1a2d8ddf5d37&token=ZWRiODkzYTMtOTI5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">edb893a3-9299-490f-8093-1a2d8ddf5d37</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 14:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rathi Steel &amp; Power Ltd. has announced that a fine imposed by BSE Limited for non-compliance of Regulation 19(1) / 19(2) of the Listing Regulations has been favorably considered for waiver by the relevant department of the Exchange. The fine was levied due to the company&apos;s failure to constitute a Nomination and Remuneration Committee for the quarter ended on March 31, 2025. The waiver was communicated to the company via email dated February 26, 2026, which was received inadvertently after the 24-hour intimation requirement. The company has requested stock exchanges to take note of this development.</p><ul><li>Rathi Steel &amp; Power Ltd. was fined by BSE Limited for non-compliance of Regulation 19(1) / 19(2) of the Listing Regulations.</li><li>The company had failed to constitute a Nomination and Remuneration Committee for the quarter ended on March 31, 2025.</li><li>The fine imposed by BSE Limited has been favorably considered for waiver by the relevant department of the Exchange.</li><li>The waiver of the fine was communicated to the company via email dated February 26, 2026.</li><li>Rathi Steel &amp; Power Ltd. has requested stock exchanges to take note of this development.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/605f5084-95e8-466e-9cb3-8055afb20fbf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RATHI STEEL & POWER LTD.-$ | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IFCI] IFCI Ltd Renews Annual Maintenance Contract of R&amp;STA for One Year</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IFCI+LTD.&title=IFCI+Ltd+Renews+Annual+Maintenance+Contract+of+R%26STA+for+One+Year&newsId=5a6d9b95-82d6-4256-8411-d8df9fa5a285&token=NWE2ZDliOTUtODJk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a6d9b95-82d6-4256-8411-d8df9fa5a285</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 14:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>IFCI Ltd, in accordance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, has renewed the Annual Maintenance Contract of MCS Share Transfer Agent Ltd., the Registrar and Share Transfer Agent (R&amp;STA) for Equity Shares and Family Bonds. The contract, which was due for renewal, has been extended for a period of one year from March 01, 2026, to February 28, 2027, in line with the requirements of Regulation 7 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>IFCI Ltd renews Annual Maintenance Contract of R&amp;STA for one year.</li><li>The renewal is in accordance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li><li>The contract has been extended from March 01, 2026, to February 28, 2027.</li><li>MCS Share Transfer Agent Ltd. is the Registrar and Share Transfer Agent for Equity Shares and Family Bonds.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c926ce7c-2955-4fec-b4d8-2a483baf5eca.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IFCI LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>