<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 04:04:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SATIN] Satin Creditcare Network Ltd. Acquires Majority Stake in QTrino Labs Private Limited via Satin Technologies Ltd.</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Satin+Creditcare+Network+Ltd&title=Satin+Creditcare+Network+Ltd.+Acquires+Majority+Stake+in+QTrino+Labs+Private+Limited+via+Satin+Technologies+Ltd.&newsId=6b1ab85a-1749-432a-9554-bd730d44793b&token=NmIxYWI4NWEtMTc0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6b1ab85a-1749-432a-9554-bd730d44793b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 03:34:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Satin Creditcare Network Limited (&apos;SCNL&apos;) announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, Satin Technologies Limited (&apos;STL&apos;), has entered into a Share Subscription-cum- Shareholders Agreement on January 17, 2026, to acquire upto 76.40% equity share capital of QTrino Labs Private Limited (&apos;QTrino&apos;). QTrino is an IIT incubated deep-tech cybersecurity startup engaged in the development of cost-effective, cutting-edge, quantum-safe security solutions for enterprises and government institutions. The proposed acquisition will enable STL to expand its business footprint in advanced technology and cybersecurity domains, strengthen its solution offerings and enhance the overall technology resilience of the Satin Group. Upon completion of the transaction, QTrino will be consolidated as a subsidiary, marking the Group’s strategic entry into technology-driven cybersecurity businesses.</p><ul><li>Satin Creditcare Network Ltd. announces acquisition of 76.40% equity stake in QTrino Labs Private Limited.</li><li>Acquisition to be made through Satin Technologies Limited, a wholly owned subsidiary of SCNL.</li><li>QTrino is a deep-tech cybersecurity startup engaged in developing quantum-safe security solutions.</li><li>Proposed acquisition aims to strengthen SCNL&apos;s technology vision and resilience.</li><li>QTrino to be consolidated as a subsidiary upon completion of the transaction.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/61f6a36b-e361-496f-8524-3af720a67389.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Satin Creditcare Network Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AIRFLOA] Airfloa Rail Technology Ltd Addresses CSR Compliance Delay; No Impact on Operations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Airfloa+Rail+Technology+Ltd&title=Airfloa+Rail+Technology+Ltd+Addresses+CSR+Compliance+Delay%3B+No+Impact+on+Operations&newsId=f4556334-f03a-4462-9cd8-fba2d01b9102&token=ZjQ1NTYzMzQtZjAz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4556334-f03a-4462-9cd8-fba2d01b9102</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 03:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Airfloa Rail Technology Ltd has addressed a timing-related procedural delay in the transfer of certain unspent CSR amounts for FY20-FY23. The matter is compliance-related, has no impact on the company’s operations or profitability, and the Company will file necessary appeal with the Regional Director. The company has received adjudication orders from the RoC imposing penalties, which the management believes are not material to the company’s profitability.</p><ul><li>Airfloa Rail Technology Ltd has resolved a timing-related procedural delay in the transfer of certain unspent CSR amounts.</li><li>The matter has no impact on the company’s operations or profitability.</li><li>The company will file necessary appeal with the Regional Director.</li><li>The company has received adjudication orders from the RoC imposing penalties.</li><li>The management believes that these penalties are not material to the company’s profitability.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3b7d32c0-b980-4742-9ee6-720b8119a662.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Airfloa Rail Technology Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STEELCAS] Steelcast Ltd to Approve Q3 Results, Declare Third Interim Dividend for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=STEELCAST+LTD.&title=Steelcast+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+Results%2C+Declare+Third+Interim+Dividend+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=c9b0de70-0866-45c8-9813-9c87f1f85b19&token=YzliMGRlNzAtMDg2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9b0de70-0866-45c8-9813-9c87f1f85b19</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 03:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Steelcast Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 30th January 2026 to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will also consider the declaration of the third interim dividend for the Financial Year 2025-26 and fix 06.02.2026 as the Record Date for the purpose of Third Interim Dividend. The Trading Window for dealing in the securities of the Company will remain closed for all Designated Persons till 1st February, 2026.</p><ul><li>Steelcast Ltd to approve Q3 results for FY 2025-26</li><li>Consideration of declaration of third interim dividend for FY 2025-26</li><li>Record Date for the third interim dividend set to 06.02.2026</li><li>Trading Window for dealing in securities closed till 1st February, 2026 for Designated Persons</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e220b87c-fb44-4478-8f5d-3cdc5aa11dda.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: STEELCAST LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HCLTECH] HCLTech Selected by Team Global Express to Drive Logistics Operations with Al-Powered Solutions</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HCL+TECHNOLOGIES+LTD.&title=HCLTech+Selected+by+Team+Global+Express+to+Drive+Logistics+Operations+with+Al-Powered+Solutions&newsId=51dd24b2-d959-4f1c-b38d-9369cfc63e6b&token=NTFkZDI0YjItZDk1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">51dd24b2-d959-4f1c-b38d-9369cfc63e6b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 02:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>HCLTech, a leading global technology company, has been selected by Team Global Express, the largest multimodal logistics organization in Australia and New Zealand, to accelerate digital transformation with Al-powered solutions. The new agreement consolidates the logistics major’s multi-vendor IT landscape into a single, strategic partnership with HCLTech as the trusted advisor to drive efficiency, innovation and data-driven decision-making. HCLTech will be responsible for end-to-end managed IT services for Team Global Express across applications, hybrid cloud infrastructure, networks, cybersecurity, digital workplace and service management. Al Force, HCLTech’s GenAl-driven platform for service transformation, will drive automation, enhance compliance and elevate customer experience across Team Global Express’ operations.</p><ul><li>HCLTech selected by Team Global Express for digital transformation</li><li>Single, strategic partnership to consolidate multi-vendor IT landscape</li><li>HCLTech responsible for end-to-end managed IT services</li><li>Al Force to drive automation, enhance compliance and elevate customer experience</li><li>Partnership reinforces HCLTech’s credentials as a trusted technology leader in enterprise transformation and digital innovation</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0a19103f-3214-4f83-bcac-0af9ec8bf02f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HCL TECHNOLOGIES LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LUPIN] Lupin and Galenicum Sign License and Supply Agreement for Semaglutide in 23 Countries</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LUPIN+LTD.&title=Lupin+and+Galenicum+Sign+License+and+Supply+Agreement+for+Semaglutide+in+23+Countries&newsId=eaea8885-8579-4ab4-a613-e0bb4b10284c&token=ZWFlYTg4ODUtODU3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eaea8885-8579-4ab4-a613-e0bb4b10284c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 02:24:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Global pharma major Lupin Limited has signed a licensing and supply agreement with Galenicum Health, S.L.U. for finished formulations of injectable Semaglutide, a GLP-1 receptor agonist. The agreement covers 23 countries globally, including Canada, Europe, Southeast Asia, and Latin America. Lupin will handle regulatory submissions, approvals, and commercialization and distribution, while Galenicum will oversee development, manufacturing, and supply. Semaglutide is a generic form of glucagon-like peptide-1 (GLP-1) that helps regulate blood sugar and appetite, and is mainly prescribed for adults with Type 2 Diabetes and for long-term weight management in adults with obesity or overweight conditions.</p><ul><li>Lupin and Galenicum sign license and supply agreement for Semaglutide in 23 countries</li><li>Galenicum to oversee development, manufacturing, and supply, while Lupin handles regulatory submissions, approvals, and commercialization and distribution</li><li>Semaglutide is a generic form of GLP-1 that helps regulate blood sugar and appetite</li><li>Semaglutide is mainly prescribed for adults with Type 2 Diabetes and for long-term weight management in adults with obesity or overweight conditions</li><li>Lupin is committed to expanding access to Semaglutide for patients in these regions</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bfeb88c1-c34b-4279-aa98-9f49e3ba4f06.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LUPIN LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MASTEK] Mastek Ltd Declares Interim Dividend of Rs. 8 per Share for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MASTEK+LTD.&title=Mastek+Ltd+Declares+Interim+Dividend+of+Rs.+8+per+Share+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=2be6a1f5-cf88-4365-8475-7bf2145f38ab&token=MmJlNmExZjUtY2Y4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2be6a1f5-cf88-4365-8475-7bf2145f38ab</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:07:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mastek Ltd, at their board meeting held in Phoenix, Arizona, United States of America, approved and took on record the Unaudited Consolidated and Standalone Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company also declared an interim dividend of Rs. 8 (i.e. 160%) per Equity Share of the face value of Rs. 5 each, for the Financial Year 2025-26.</p><ul><li>Approval of Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Interim Dividend of Rs. 8 per Equity Share for the Financial Year 2025-26</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d2cbf1a0-c4c7-43e3-89de-09c52b9aa94c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MASTEK LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MASTEK] Mastek Ltd Declares Interim Dividend of Rs. 8 per Share for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MASTEK+LTD.&title=Mastek+Ltd+Declares+Interim+Dividend+of+Rs.+8+per+Share+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=e64e160e-cbcc-4fc9-b422-0af094a312ef&token=ZTY0ZTE2MGUtY2Jj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e64e160e-cbcc-4fc9-b422-0af094a312ef</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mastek Ltd, a leading technology and digital transformation solutions provider, announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s Board of Directors approved the unaudited consolidated and standalone financial results, which will be made available on the company&apos;s website and published in newspapers as per SEBI regulations. The Board also declared an interim dividend of Rs. 8 (160%) per equity share of the face value of Rs. 5 each for the Financial Year 2025-26, which will be paid to the eligible shareholders on or before February 17, 2026.</p><ul><li>Unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025 approved</li><li>Interim dividend of Rs. 8 (160%) per equity share declared for FY 2025-26</li><li>Dividend to be paid on or before February 17, 2026</li><li>Financial results to be made available on the company&apos;s website and published in newspapers</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/79e749ee-3dc8-47e7-b68e-741ef2f61fa5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MASTEK LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MASTEK] Mastek Ltd Declares Interim Dividend of Rs.8/- per Equity Share for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MASTEK+LTD.&title=Mastek+Ltd+Declares+Interim+Dividend+of+Rs.8%2F-+per+Equity+Share+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=6a56e813-da7c-4fce-b53e-27870b66e448&token=NmE1NmU4MTMtZGE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a56e813-da7c-4fce-b53e-27870b66e448</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mastek Ltd has declared an interim dividend of Rs.8/- (i.e. 160%) per Equity Share of the face value of Rs. 5 each, for the Financial Year 2025-26. The record date for the dividend is January 30, 2026. The Board also approved and took on record the Unaudited Consolidated and Standalone Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</p><ul><li>Mastek Ltd declares an interim dividend of Rs.8/- per Equity Share for FY 2025-26</li><li>The record date for the dividend is January 30, 2026</li><li>The Board approved and took on record the Unaudited Consolidated and Standalone Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b5e12b43-c441-43b2-a3ea-8eb73ea7fef9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MASTEK LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MASTEK] Mastek Ltd Declares Interim Dividend of Rs. 8 per Share for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MASTEK+LTD.&title=Mastek+Ltd+Declares+Interim+Dividend+of+Rs.+8+per+Share+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=f2979426-98a4-4c67-b871-d8bf31ba16e3&token=ZjI5Nzk0MjYtOThh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f2979426-98a4-4c67-b871-d8bf31ba16e3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mastek Ltd, a leading technology company, has declared an interim dividend of Rs. 8 (i.e. 160%) per Equity Share of the face value of Rs. 5 each, for the Financial Year 2025-26. The dividend will be paid to the equity shareholders whose names appear on the Register of Members of the Company / in the records of the Depositories as beneficial owners of the shares as on the Record Date, which is Friday, January 30, 2026. The decision was made at the Board Meeting held in Phoenix, Arizona, United States of America, on January 20, 2026 to January 21, 2026.</p><ul><li>Mastek Ltd declares an interim dividend of Rs. 8 per share for FY 2025-26.</li><li>The Record Date for dividend eligibility is Friday, January 30, 2026.</li><li>The decision was made at the Board Meeting held in Phoenix, Arizona, United States of America.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/21019e30-d47c-4a2d-8119-b5e6ffba4ca9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MASTEK LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RCCEMEN] RCC Cements Ltd Reports Zero Investor Complaints for Q4 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RCC+CEMENTS+LTD.&title=RCC+Cements+Ltd+Reports+Zero+Investor+Complaints+for+Q4+2025&newsId=b7aedd64-0a76-4de8-b499-f18422f4a800&token=YjdhZWRkNjQtMGE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7aedd64-0a76-4de8-b499-f18422f4a800</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:01:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>RCC Cements Ltd has released its Statement of Investor Complaints for the quarter ended 31st December, 2025. According to the report, there were no pending complaints at the beginning of the quarter, no new complaints received during the quarter, and no complaints left unresolved at the end of the quarter. This indicates a positive relationship with investors and a commitment to addressing any issues promptly.</p><ul><li>RCC Cements Ltd reported zero pending complaints at the beginning of Q4 2025</li><li>No new complaints were received during Q4 2025</li><li>All complaints received during the quarter were resolved</li><li>No complaints were left unresolved at the end of Q4 2025</li><li>This report indicates a positive relationship with investors and a commitment to addressing issues promptly</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8897ca87-1cef-43a9-9646-8123e163bdd0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RCC CEMENTS LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>