<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:39:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[NIPPOBATRY] Indo National Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025, Announces Acquisition and Investments</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDO-NATIONAL+LTD.&title=Indo+National+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Announces+Acquisition+and+Investments&newsId=f7e373f9-5993-461e-a246-edf6c1270aad&token=ZjdlMzczZjktNTk5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7e373f9-5993-461e-a246-edf6c1270aad</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:39:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indo National Ltd, a company based in Chennai, India, has reported its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 45,797.12 lakhs for the quarter and 36,086.35 lakhs for the nine months period. The company has also announced an acquisition of 46.76% equity shares of Medcuore Medical Solutions Private Limited, making it a subsidiary. Additionally, Indo National Ltd has invested 850 lakhs in Compulsory Convertible Preference shares (CCPS) of Axial Aero Private Limited. The company operates in the consumer goods segment, manufacturing and selling dry batteries and trading lighting products and other home appliances.</p><ul><li>Indo National Ltd reports Q3 and nine months results for 2025</li><li>Revenue from operations stands at 45,797.12 lakhs for the quarter</li><li>Acquisition of 46.76% equity shares of Medcuore Medical Solutions Private Limited</li><li>Investment of 850 lakhs in Compulsory Convertible Preference shares (CCPS) of Axial Aero Private Limited</li><li>Company operates in the consumer goods segment</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/27338350-5947-4b41-9ec4-15f5a4c49f64.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDO-NATIONAL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SPVGLOBAL] SPV Global Trading Ltd to Approve Q3 Financial Results on 10/02/2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SPV+Global+Trading+Ltd&title=SPV+Global+Trading+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+Financial+Results+on+10%2F02%2F2026&newsId=1d0c63ba-4634-4a85-a4f6-1b66c1c58df2&token=MWQwYzYzYmEtNDYz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d0c63ba-4634-4a85-a4f6-1b66c1c58df2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:39:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SPV Global Trading Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 10th February 2026 to consider and approve the Standalone and Consolidated Un-audited Financial Results for the third quarter ended 31 December 2025. The meeting will also consider any other matters with the permission of the Chair.</p><ul><li>SPV Global Trading Ltd to hold a Board Meeting on 10/02/2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the Standalone and Consolidated Un-audited Financial Results for Q3 2025</li><li>The meeting will also discuss any other matters with the permission of the Chair</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/800bf0b3-9da4-482f-a3f6-4ac69fed7e77.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SPV Global Trading Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AMFORG] Amforge Industries Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on February 11, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AMFORGE+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Amforge+Industries+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+February+11%2C+2026&newsId=a847897f-dede-4173-8b8a-d12e27fbed69&token=YTg0Nzg5N2YtZGVk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a847897f-dede-4173-8b8a-d12e27fbed69</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:38:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Amforge Industries Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 11, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The meeting will also consider the Limited Review Report for the same period. The trading window of the company will be closed from January 1, 2026, to February 13, 2026, in accordance with the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulation, 2015.</p><ul><li>Amforge Industries Ltd to consider and approve Q3 and nine months financial results for the period ending 31st December, 2025</li><li>The meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on 11th February, 2026</li><li>The trading window of the company will be closed from 1st January, 2026 to 13th February, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/478b608c-fca9-48bf-8258-77570e4acd64.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AMFORGE INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EMCURE] Emcure Pharmaceuticals Updates Key Managerial Personnel for Materiality Determination</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Emcure+Pharmaceuticals+Ltd&title=Emcure+Pharmaceuticals+Updates+Key+Managerial+Personnel+for+Materiality+Determination&newsId=8a7fcd2f-148e-49fb-adde-fe106ae92f77&token=OGE3ZmNkMmYtMTQ4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a7fcd2f-148e-49fb-adde-fe106ae92f77</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Emcure Pharmaceuticals Ltd. has updated the list of Key Managerial Personnel (KMP) authorized for determining the materiality of an event or information and for making disclosures to the Stock Exchanges. The update is in accordance with Regulation 30(5) of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The new KMP are Mr. Satish Mehta, Managing Director and CEO; Mr. Sunil Mehta, Whole-time Director; Mr. Tajuddin Shaikh, Chief Financial Officer; and Ms. Amruta Jana, Company Secretary and Compliance Officer. The contact details for these individuals are provided in the disclosure.</p><ul><li>Emcure Pharmaceuticals has updated its Key Managerial Personnel (KMP) for determining the materiality of events or information and making disclosures to Stock Exchanges.</li><li>The update is in accordance with Regulation 30(5) of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li><li>The new KMP include Mr. Satish Mehta, Managing Director and CEO; Mr. Sunil Mehta, Whole-time Director; Mr. Tajuddin Shaikh, Chief Financial Officer; and Ms. Amruta Jana, Company Secretary and Compliance Officer.</li><li>The contact details for the new KMP are provided in the disclosure.</li><li>Stakeholders are requested to take note of this update.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/19f96c15-10f9-49df-a301-e7e8e78ef88a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Emcure Pharmaceuticals Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TEAMLEASE] TeamLease Reports Q3FY26 Financial Results: EBITDA Grew by 11% Sequentially, PBT by 69%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TeamLease+Services+Ltd&title=TeamLease+Reports+Q3FY26+Financial+Results%3A+EBITDA+Grew+by+11%25+Sequentially%2C+PBT+by+69%25&newsId=afb9c611-9f36-4b96-845b-d59f462d7ede&token=YWZiOWM2MTEtOWYz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">afb9c611-9f36-4b96-845b-d59f462d7ede</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:38:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>TeamLease Services Limited, one of India’s largest staffing companies, announced its results for the third quarter (Q3FY26) and nine months (9MFY26) of the financial year ending March 31, 2026. The company reported a 4% increase in total revenue and an 8% increase in operating revenue compared to the same period last year. EBITDA grew by 11% sequentially and 22% year-over-year, while PBT grew by 69% sequentially, primarily driven by interest credit on tax refunds. The company lost approximately 27,000 headcount during the quarter, largely impacting the BFSI segment across General Staffing and Degree Apprenticeship business. The company added 107 new logos during the quarter and received an Income Tax refund of Rs.106.1 crore, resulting in net free cash of Rs.430 crore.</p><ul><li>EBITDA grew by 11% sequentially and 22% year-over-year.</li><li>PBT grew by 69% sequentially, primarily driven by interest credit on tax refunds.</li><li>Lost approximately 27,000 headcount during the quarter, largely impacting the BFSI segment across General Staffing and Degree Apprenticeship business.</li><li>Added 107 new logos during the quarter.</li><li>Received an Income Tax refund of Rs.106.1 crore, resulting in net free cash of Rs.430 crore.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ca3543ae-b8ec-487e-b497-4bf3d6a6154a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TeamLease Services Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NIRAVCOM] Nirav Commercials Ltd Approves Aluminium Business Sale to Related Party Hind Aluminium Industries Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NIRAV+COMMERCIALS+LTD.&title=Nirav+Commercials+Ltd+Approves+Aluminium+Business+Sale+to+Related+Party+Hind+Aluminium+Industries+Ltd&newsId=32a683a5-9e18-464a-8271-a45e972f754a&token=MzJhNjgzYTUtOWUx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32a683a5-9e18-464a-8271-a45e972f754a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:37:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Nirav Commercials Ltd has approved a Business Transfer Agreement (BTA) to sell its aluminium business under the brand name &apos;Elesar Focchi&apos; to Hind Aluminium Industries Ltd. The transaction is a Material Related Party Transaction, subject to the approval of shareholders by way of Slump Sale. The sale is expected to be completed by 31/03/2026. The income and networth of Elesar Focchi is 3047.45 Lakhs and 972.64 Lakhs respectively, contributing 100% of the revenue of the company. The consideration received from the sale is Rs. 1.25 Crores.</p><ul><li>Nirav Commercials Ltd approves the sale of its aluminium business to Hind Aluminium Industries Ltd</li><li>The transaction is a Material Related Party Transaction</li><li>The sale is expected to be completed by 31/03/2026</li><li>Elesar Focchi contributes 100% of the revenue of the company</li><li>The consideration received from the sale is Rs. 1.25 Crores</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5d3c0809-4824-49b2-ac5a-4af506141b23.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NIRAV COMMERCIALS LTD. | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NIITMTS] NIIT MTS and Abodoo Partner to Deliver Next-gen Skills Intelligence Solutions</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NIIT+Learning+Systems+Ltd&title=NIIT+MTS+and+Abodoo+Partner+to+Deliver+Next-gen+Skills+Intelligence+Solutions&newsId=d67189f4-1cb8-4e36-8af1-dfba86019859&token=ZDY3MTg5ZjQtMWNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d67189f4-1cb8-4e36-8af1-dfba86019859</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:35:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Partnership</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>NIIT Learning Systems Limited (NIIT MTS) and Abodoo, a skills intelligence and orchestration company, have announced a strategic partnership. The partnership aims to deliver next-generation skills intelligence and workforce development solutions to enterprises globally. By combining NIIT MTS&apos; expertise in managed learning, consulting services, and deep HCM technology experience with Abodoo&apos;s powerful skills intelligence technology, the partnership will enable organizations to map, measure, and develop skills in real time, closing critical skills gaps and improving workforce agility.</p><ul><li>NIIT MTS and Abodoo partnership to deliver next-gen skills intelligence solutions</li><li>Combination of NIIT MTS&apos; managed learning and consulting services with Abodoo&apos;s skills intelligence technology</li><li>Real-time skills mapping, measurement, and development</li><li>Closing critical skills gaps and improving workforce agility</li><li>Collaboration on joint webinars, thought leadership, and client-facing initiatives</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cc431684-3492-4696-9a67-5d7d3efb8905.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NIIT Learning Systems Ltd | Category: Partnership</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NIKHILAD] Nikhil Adhesives Ltd. to Approve Q4 Results of 2025 in Board Meeting on Feb 13, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NIKHIL+ADHESIVES+LTD.-%24&title=Nikhil+Adhesives+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q4+Results+of+2025+in+Board+Meeting+on+Feb+13%2C+2026&newsId=b4fcae60-dce9-4b1e-b108-a7ff1f10d919&token=YjRmY2FlNjAtZGNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4fcae60-dce9-4b1e-b108-a7ff1f10d919</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:33:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Nikhil Adhesives Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 13, 2026, at the company&apos;s registered office in Mumbai. The agenda includes the consideration and approval of the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended on 31st December 2025. The meeting also plans to discuss any other business with the permission of the Chair. In compliance with SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulation, 2015, the company&apos;s trading window has been closed from January 1, 2026, and will reopen 48 hours after the announcement of the unaudited financial results.</p><ul><li>Nikhil Adhesives Ltd. to hold a Board Meeting on Feb 13, 2026</li><li>Consideration and approval of unaudited financial results for Q4 2025</li><li>Trading window closed from Jan 1, 2026, as per SEBI regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a442ea14-83c0-4846-90b7-865872ae3071.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NIKHIL ADHESIVES LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IMFA] IMFA Appoints Ms Kiran Dhingra as Director for 5 Years</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDIAN+METALS+%26+FERRO+ALLOYS+LTD.&title=IMFA+Appoints+Ms+Kiran+Dhingra+as+Director+for+5+Years&newsId=e464fce9-1b4b-4001-9a3d-a09636e47419&token=ZTQ2NGZjZTktMWI0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e464fce9-1b4b-4001-9a3d-a09636e47419</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:33:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indian Metals &amp; Ferro Alloys Ltd (IMFA) has appointed Ms Kiran Dhingra as a Director on the Board of the Company for a term of 5 years, effective from 4th February 2026. Ms Dhingra, a retired civil servant with 38 years of experience, has been granted Security Clearance by the Office of the Director General of Civil Aviation, Government of India. She has a distinguished career and has held various senior positions in both Union Territories and the Government of India. Post-retirement, she has worked as a probono Chairperson of the National Institute of Fashion Technology and as an Independent Director on several company Boards.</p><ul><li>Ms Kiran Dhingra appointed as Director on IMFA Board for 5 years</li><li>Dhingra has an outstanding record with 38 years of civil service</li><li>She has held the post of Chief Secretary to the Government of Goa</li><li>Dhingra has vast experience in governance, planning, policy making and monitoring</li><li>She has been working as an Independent Director since 2013</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/56496211-9da7-44d1-9b7e-0cfe6f8f1457.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDIAN METALS & FERRO ALLOYS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JAINREC] Jain Resource Recycling Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on Feb 9, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jain+Resource+Recycling+Ltd&title=Jain+Resource+Recycling+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+Feb+9%2C+2026&newsId=41a61640-64b7-4813-8ab0-c231e9e9c88b&token=NDFhNjE2NDAtNjRi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41a61640-64b7-4813-8ab0-c231e9e9c88b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 09:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jain Resource Recycling Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 9, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in the company&apos;s equity shares by all designated persons and their immediate relatives has been closed from January 1, 2026, till the expiry of 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results.</p><ul><li>Jain Resource Recycling Ltd to approve Q3 and nine months financial results on Feb 9, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the company&apos;s equity shares by all designated persons and their immediate relatives is closed from January 1, 2026, till the expiry of 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/15f25ebd-4902-49d1-a5eb-77864afcd114.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jain Resource Recycling Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>