<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:31:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[KOTIC] Kothari Industrial Corporation Ltd Receives Listing Approval for 1131068 Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KOTHARI+INDUSTRIAL+CORPORATION+LTD.&title=Kothari+Industrial+Corporation+Ltd+Receives+Listing+Approval+for+1131068+Equity+Shares&newsId=be5ba279-2eb7-4768-bedd-4cb2f41af9e5&token=YmU1YmEyNzktMmVi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be5ba279-2eb7-4768-bedd-4cb2f41af9e5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kothari Industrial Corporation Ltd has received listing approval from the BSE Limited for 1131068 equity shares of Rs. 5/- each issued at a premium of Rs.202/- each, on a preferential basis, to Non-promoters. The approval was granted on 09.01.2026. The company is required to ensure compliance with the provisions of Regulation 167 of SEBI (ICDR) Regulations and SEBI&apos;s guidelines. If there is a change exceeding two per cent of the total paid-up share capital of the company, the company must file the shareholding pattern in XBRL mode as required under Regulations 31(1)(c) of SEBI LODR Regulations, 2015. Trading approval will be granted only after the company files listing approval from the National Stock Exchange of India Ltd. (if applicable) and confirmation letters from NSDL/CDSL about crediting the shares to the respective beneficiary accounts/admitting the capital to the depository system. The company should also note that as per Schedule XIX of ICDR Regulations, it should make an application for trading approval to the stock exchange/s within seven working days from the date of grant of listing approval by the stock exchange/s.</p><ul><li>Kothari Industrial Corporation Ltd receives listing approval for 1131068 equity shares</li><li>Shares issued at a premium of Rs.202/- each to Non-promoters</li><li>Company must comply with Regulation 167 of SEBI (ICDR) Regulations and SEBI&apos;s guidelines</li><li>Company to file shareholding pattern in XBRL mode if there is a change exceeding two per cent of the total paid-up share capital</li><li>Trading approval subject to filing of listing approval from NSE and confirmation letters from NSDL/CDSL</li><li>Company to apply for trading approval to the stock exchange/s within seven working days from the date of grant of listing approval by the stock exchange/s</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b87ee610-c330-40ad-ab6c-12a7c97029b1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KOTHARI INDUSTRIAL CORPORATION LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ARTEFACT] Artefact Projects Ltd Secures INR 4.98 Crore Contract from NHAI for Independent Engineer Services</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ARTEFACT+PROJECTS+LTD.&title=Artefact+Projects+Ltd+Secures+INR+4.98+Crore+Contract+from+NHAI+for+Independent+Engineer+Services&newsId=d4c1543d-0722-49be-b2fc-f141cd3354fa&token=ZDRjMTU0M2QtMDcy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4c1543d-0722-49be-b2fc-f141cd3354fa</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:24:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Award</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Artefact Projects Ltd has been awarded a project from the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) for Independent Engineer Services during the Operation and Maintenance Period for the eight-lane Vadodara Kim Expressway. The project is divided into two sections: from km 190.000 to km 217.500 (Package VII- Gandeva to Ena Section) and from km 217.500 to km 254.430 (Package Vi-Ena to Kim section) in the state of Gujarat under Bharatmala Pariyojana on HAM. The contracted fees for this project is INR 4,97,80,620/- (Rupees Four Crores Ninety Seven Lakhs Eighty Thousand Six Hundred and Twenty Only) excluding GST.</p><ul><li>Artefact Projects Ltd has been awarded a project from NHAI for Independent Engineer Services.</li><li>The project is for the eight-lane Vadodara Kim Expressway in Gujarat under Bharatmala Pariyojana on HAM.</li><li>The contracted fees for the project is INR 4,97,80,620/- excluding GST.</li><li>The project is divided into two sections: from km 190.000 to km 217.500 and from km 217.500 to km 254.430.</li><li>The project duration is 60 months.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9fc988ca-14fc-496f-bcae-08253a8b83f4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ARTEFACT PROJECTS LTD. | Category: Award</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DMART] Avenue Supermarts Ltd: Mr. Ignatius Navil Noronha to Step Down as Managing Director, Mr. Anshul Asawa to Take Over</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Avenue+Supermarts+Ltd&title=Avenue+Supermarts+Ltd%3A+Mr.+Ignatius+Navil+Noronha+to+Step+Down+as+Managing+Director%2C+Mr.+Anshul+Asawa+to+Take+Over&newsId=f82319c6-ea84-42b7-a331-46986bc8b60c&token=ZjgyMzE5YzYtZWE4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f82319c6-ea84-42b7-a331-46986bc8b60c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:21:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Avenue Supermarts Ltd, the company that operates the retail chain DMart, has announced a change in its management. Mr. Ignatius Navil Noronha, the current Managing Director, will complete his tenure on 31st January 2026. His position will be taken over by Mr. Anshul Asawa, who is currently the CEO Designate. Mr. Asawa will assume the role of Chief Executive Officer and Key Managerial Personnel from 1st February 2026 and will become the Managing Director from 1st April 2026 for a term of 3 years, subject to shareholder approval. The company has also designated Mr. Sachin Jaolekar, Mr. Dastgir Shaikh, Mr. Shyam Gupta, and Mr. Rushabh Ghiya as Senior Management Personnel.</p><ul><li>Mr. Ignatius Navil Noronha to step down as Managing Director of Avenue Supermarts Ltd.</li><li>Mr. Anshul Asawa to take over as Managing Director from 1st April 2026.</li><li>Mr. Anshul Asawa is currently the CEO Designate and will assume the role of Chief Executive Officer and Key Managerial Personnel from 1st February 2026.</li><li>Mr. Sachin Jaolekar, Mr. Dastgir Shaikh, Mr. Shyam Gupta, and Mr. Rushabh Ghiya designated as Senior Management Personnel.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/07e8c7fb-7d99-47e7-b91a-b4d406455f46.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Avenue Supermarts Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SKFINDIA] SKF India Ltd Appoints Three Additional Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SKF+India+Ltd&title=SKF+India+Ltd+Appoints+Three+Additional+Directors&newsId=8834dc2f-032e-4ac3-a00f-82f62169d8c6&token=ODgzNGRjMmYtMDMy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8834dc2f-032e-4ac3-a00f-82f62169d8c6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SKF India Ltd has appointed Mr. Magnus Lennart Prick, Mr. Bastian Thomas, and Mr. Antonio Molle as Additional Directors (Non-Executive, Non-Independent) on the Board of the company. The appointments are subject to the approval of the shareholders. The company also announced the resignation of Ms. Kerstin Enochsson, Mr. Karl Robin Joakim Landholm, and Mr. Mukund Vasudevan due to their other occupancies and commitments.</p><ul><li>SKF India Ltd has appointed Mr. Magnus Lennart Prick, Mr. Bastian Thomas, and Mr. Antonio Molle as Additional Directors.</li><li>The appointments are subject to the approval of the shareholders.</li><li>Ms. Kerstin Enochsson, Mr. Karl Robin Joakim Landholm, and Mr. Mukund Vasudevan have resigned from their positions.</li><li>The resignations are due to the directors&apos; other occupancies and commitments.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6cb58e94-9edc-4bb7-818d-cee39333a0f7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SKF India Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KALAMANDIR] Sai Silks (Kalamandir) Ltd to Approve Q4 2025 Unaudited Financial Results on Jan 19, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sai+Silks+%28Kalamandir%29+Ltd&title=Sai+Silks+%28Kalamandir%29+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+2025+Unaudited+Financial+Results+on+Jan+19%2C+2026&newsId=9ead9073-3087-459f-bf98-ccc2d3676d94&token=OWVhZDkwNzMtMzA4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ead9073-3087-459f-bf98-ccc2d3676d94</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sai Silks (Kalamandir) Ltd has announced that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on January 19, 2026. The agenda includes the consideration and approval of the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. This is in accordance with Regulation 29 and 33 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirement) Regulations 2015.</p><ul><li>Sai Silks (Kalamandir) Ltd to consider and approve unaudited financial results for Q4 2025</li><li>Board Meeting scheduled on January 19, 2026</li><li>Meeting in accordance with Regulation 29 and 33 of SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirement) Regulations 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a2e1c40a-d781-447b-8d7c-1451da734bdf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sai Silks (Kalamandir) Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUGSLLOYD] Sugs Lloyd Ltd Announces Resignation of Senior Management Personnel Mr. Akhilesh Kumar Anand</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sugs+Lloyd+Ltd&title=Sugs+Lloyd+Ltd+Announces+Resignation+of+Senior+Management+Personnel+Mr.+Akhilesh+Kumar+Anand&newsId=b60cc9d7-0c3f-4feb-a543-8ab39c1c96fd&token=YjYwY2M5ZDctMGMz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b60cc9d7-0c3f-4feb-a543-8ab39c1c96fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Auditor</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sugs Lloyd Ltd has informed about the resignation of Mr. Akhilesh Kumar Anand, General Manager-Business Development, who was designated as Senior Management Personnel (SMP). Mr. Anand has tendered his resignation due to personal commitments and to pursue other interests, effective from the close of business hours on 10th January 2026. The company has confirmed that there is no other material reason for his resignation and it does not reflect any concern or issue relating to the performance, conduct, or operations of the company.</p><ul><li>Mr. Akhilesh Kumar Anand has resigned from his position as General Manager-Business Development at Sugs Lloyd Ltd.</li><li>His resignation is due to personal commitments and a desire to pursue other interests.</li><li>The resignation will be effective from the close of business hours on 10th January 2026.</li><li>The resignation does not reflect any concern or issue relating to the performance, conduct, or operations of the company.</li><li>Mr. Anand&apos;s resignation is in compliance with the applicable provisions of the SEBI (LODR) Reg. 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0cc34dbc-e978-4ba0-b5f3-161d30055f01.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sugs Lloyd Ltd | Category: Auditor</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TITANIN] Independent Director, Sanjeev Sharma, Resigns from Titan Intech Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Titan+Intech+Ltd&title=Independent+Director%2C+Sanjeev+Sharma%2C+Resigns+from+Titan+Intech+Ltd&newsId=48a99bc3-ba21-463d-a129-168a3e0e2d14&token=NDhhOTliYzMtYmEy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48a99bc3-ba21-463d-a129-168a3e0e2d14</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Titan Intech Ltd announced the resignation of its Independent Director, Sanjeev Sharma, due to his increasing professional commitments. The resignation is effective immediately, and Mr. Sharma has also stepped down from all the Board Committees he was a part of. The company has complied with the necessary regulations and has requested to record the change.</p><ul><li>Sanjeev Sharma resigns as Independent Director from Titan Intech Ltd.</li><li>Resignation effective immediately.</li><li>Mr. Sharma has stepped down from all Board Committees.</li><li>Company has complied with necessary regulations.</li><li>Change in Board composition requested to be recorded.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5c7c2f31-4f13-4b63-a457-8a215585cea3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Titan Intech Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KVTOYS] K.V. Toys India Ltd to Acquire 65% Stake in Crayonix Stationery Private Limited for Rs 65000/-</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=K.+V.+Toys+India+Ltd&title=K.V.+Toys+India+Ltd+to+Acquire+65%25+Stake+in+Crayonix+Stationery+Private+Limited+for+Rs+65000%2F-&newsId=2639b8b9-9c31-4d73-993b-f2e800d3fb70&token=MjYzOWI4YjktOWMz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2639b8b9-9c31-4d73-993b-f2e800d3fb70</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>K.V. Toys India Ltd, a leading company in the manufacturing of toys, has announced its decision to acquire a 65% stake in Crayonix Stationery Private Limited for Rs 65000/- in cash. The proposed subsidiary company is engaged in the manufacturing of stationery items and gift sets. This acquisition is strategically aimed at expanding the Company&apos;s presence in the stationery and gifting market, establishing in-house manufacturing capabilities, expanding its product portfolio, and creating opportunities for sustainable revenue growth. The transaction is expected to be completed within 2 months, subject to the completion of customary conditions and receipt of necessary statutory and regulatory approvals. The proposed subsidiary company had a turnover of Not Applicable in Rupees lakhs and is based in India.</p><ul><li>K.V. Toys India Ltd to acquire 65% stake in Crayonix Stationery Private Limited</li><li>Acquisition for Rs 65000/- in cash</li><li>Proposed subsidiary company engaged in manufacturing of stationery items and gift sets</li><li>Strategic acquisition to expand Company&apos;s presence in stationery and gifting market</li><li>Expected completion within 2 months, subject to customary conditions and regulatory approvals</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/53653cc1-ebf8-46c1-a098-b81246b3bfba.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: K. V. Toys India Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DMART] Avenue Supermarts Ltd Reports 13.2% Increase in Standalone Total Revenue for Q3FY26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Avenue+Supermarts+Ltd&title=Avenue+Supermarts+Ltd+Reports+13.2%25+Increase+in+Standalone+Total+Revenue+for+Q3FY26&newsId=f5512574-d7a3-4914-8e61-74f07a5a492a&token=ZjU1MTI1NzQtZDdh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f5512574-d7a3-4914-8e61-74f07a5a492a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Avenue Supermarts Ltd, one of India&apos;s largest food &amp; grocery retailers, announced its standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The standalone Total Revenue for Q3FY26 stood at Rs.17,613 crore, representing a 13.2% y-o-y growth. EBITDA for Q3FY26 stood at Rs.1,481 crore, with an EBITDA margin of 8.4%. Net Profit stood at Rs.923 crore, with a PAT margin of 5.2%. The Company added 10 stores in Q3FY26, bringing the total to 442 as of December 31, 2025.</p><ul><li>Standalone Total Revenue up by 13.2% at Rs.17,613 Crore</li><li>Standalone PAT up by 17.6% at Rs.923 Crore</li><li>EBITDA of Rs.1,481 Crore; y-o-y growth of 19.9%</li><li>10 stores were added in Q3FY26</li><li>Basic EPS for Q3FY26 stood at Rs.14.19, as compared to Rs.12.06 for Q3FY25</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cef88deb-299b-4931-9219-72d3390400a8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Avenue Supermarts Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RML] Rane (Madras) Ltd Receives Show Cause Notice from Principal Commissioner of Income Tax, Chennai</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RANE+%28MADRAS%29+LTD.&title=Rane+%28Madras%29+Ltd+Receives+Show+Cause+Notice+from+Principal+Commissioner+of+Income+Tax%2C+Chennai&newsId=12c5087d-0005-4a6b-91b0-38cdd4a2ed61&token=MTJjNTA4N2QtMDAw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12c5087d-0005-4a6b-91b0-38cdd4a2ed61</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 12:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rane (Madras) Ltd has disclosed receiving a Show Cause Notice from the Principal Commissioner of Income Tax, Chennai. The notice is for disallowance of certain expenditures, specifically relating to a trademark fee and actuarial gain/loss on the Defined Benefit Plan of Gratuity. The disallowance amounts to approximately Rs.7.61 crores. The company, in consultation with its consultants and tax advisors, will be filing a suitable reply before the appropriate authority within the prescribed timelines.</p><ul><li>Rane (Madras) Ltd received a Show Cause Notice from the Principal Commissioner of Income Tax, Chennai</li><li>The notice is for disallowance of certain expenditures, specifically relating to a trademark fee and actuarial gain/loss on the Defined Benefit Plan of Gratuity</li><li>The total disallowance amounts to approximately Rs.7.61 crores</li><li>The company will be filing a suitable reply before the appropriate authority within the prescribed timelines</li><li>The notice was received on January 09, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/eb56013e-a3a3-4b3d-bae2-ee23f00cb2f9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RANE (MADRAS) LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>