<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:25:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[MALLCOM] Mallcom (India) Ltd to Approve Un-audited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended 31 December 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Mallcom+%28India%29+Ltd&title=Mallcom+%28India%29+Ltd+to+Approve+Un-audited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+31+December+2025&newsId=d7d39877-d2b4-4993-88ca-42796e143095&token=ZDdkMzk4NzctZDJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7d39877-d2b4-4993-88ca-42796e143095</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:25:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mallcom (India) Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 20th January 2026 to consider and approve the Un-audited Financial Results (Standalone and Consolidated) for the quarter and nine months ended 31 December 2025. The meeting will also address any other business with the Chairman&apos;s permission. The trading window for dealing in the company&apos;s securities, which was closed from 1st January 2026, will reopen 48 hours after the declaration of the Un-Audited Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Mallcom (India) Ltd to consider and approve Un-audited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended 31 December 2025</li><li>Trading window to reopen 48 hours after the declaration of the Un-Audited Financial Results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/faf6dee1-13d2-46a0-971f-90c1e39acaa3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Mallcom (India) Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GOGIACAP] Gogia Capital Growth Ltd. Approves Material Related Party Transaction &amp; Office Relocation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Gogia+Capital+Services+Limited&title=Gogia+Capital+Growth+Ltd.+Approves+Material+Related+Party+Transaction+%26+Office+Relocation&newsId=b691ecf3-07f6-4274-828e-594958ee1563&token=YjY5MWVjZjMtMDdm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b691ecf3-07f6-4274-828e-594958ee1563</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Gogia Capital Growth Ltd. held a Board Meeting on 13th January, 2026, where they approved a material related party transaction involving the sale of immovable property to Director Mr. Ankur Gogia for a consideration of Rs. 5,05,00,000. The transaction is proposed to be undertaken on an arm’s length basis at fair market value. The company also approved the change of its registered office to 31, Basement, DBS Bank Community Center, Basant Lok Vasant Vihar, New Delhi - 110057. Both decisions are subject to necessary approvals.</p><ul><li>Approval of a material related party transaction involving the sale of immovable property to Director Mr. Ankur Gogia.</li><li>The transaction is proposed to be undertaken on an arm’s length basis at fair market value.</li><li>Approval for the change of the company&apos;s registered office to a new location.</li><li>Both decisions are subject to necessary approvals from shareholders and regulatory bodies.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/43bcebf3-c04c-41d5-ac19-30b2cdfa3ef1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Gogia Capital Services Limited | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CINERAD] GTT Data Solutions Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Discuss Funds Raising on Jan 17, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CINERAD+COMMUNICATIONS+LTD.&title=GTT+Data+Solutions+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Discuss+Funds+Raising+on+Jan+17%2C+2026&newsId=b644507f-c1da-4ce9-9b8c-b5fad10b5d16&token=YjY0NDUwN2YtYzFk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b644507f-c1da-4ce9-9b8c-b5fad10b5d16</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:23:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>GTT Data Solutions Ltd has informed the BSE that the company&apos;s Board of Directors will meet on January 17, 2026, to consider and approve raising funds. The proposed fundraising may be executed through various methods, including private placement, public issue of equity/debt securities, preferential issue, or rights issue, in accordance with the Companies Act, 2013, and the SEBI (Issue of Capital and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2018. The trading window for directors, designated persons, and other connected persons will be closed during the aforementioned period.</p><ul><li>GTT Data Solutions Ltd to conduct a Board Meeting on January 17, 2026</li><li>The agenda includes the consideration and approval of funds raising</li><li>Fundraising may be carried out through various methods such as private placement, public issue, preferential issue, or rights issue</li><li>The proposed fundraising is subject to the Companies Act, 2013, and the SEBI (Issue of Capital and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2018</li><li>Trading window for directors, designated persons, and other connected persons will be closed during the aforementioned period</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cdd0bc21-e152-47b4-bc22-87b24b849339.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CINERAD COMMUNICATIONS LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAYAJIHOTL] Sayaji Hotels Ltd: Change in Chairman, Board Reconstitution and Committee Recomposition</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SAYAJI+HOTELS+LTD.&title=Sayaji+Hotels+Ltd%3A+Change+in+Chairman%2C+Board+Reconstitution+and+Committee+Recomposition&newsId=50c71024-2f1b-405b-bc4c-54b14e60c168&token=NTBjNzEwMjQtMmYx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50c71024-2f1b-405b-bc4c-54b14e60c168</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Sayaji Hotels Ltd at its meeting held on 13th January, 2026, considered several matters including the completion of tenure of Mr. Abhay Chintaman Chaudhari as Non-Executive Independent Director and Chairman of the Company, with effect from the closure of business hours on 22nd January, 2026. Mr. Nimeshkumar Gandhi is appointed as the new Chairman of the Board and the Company, effective from 23rd January, 2026. The Board also approved changes in the composition of the Board of Directors and the reconstitution of certain committees of the Board, effective from 23rd January, 2026.</p><ul><li>Completion of tenure of Mr. Abhay Chintaman Chaudhari as Non-Executive Independent Director and Chairman of Sayaji Hotels Ltd.</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Nimeshkumar Gandhi as the new Chairman of the Board and the Company.</li><li>Changes in the composition of the Board of Directors of Sayaji Hotels Ltd.</li><li>Reconstitution of certain committees of the Board of Directors of Sayaji Hotels Ltd.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/71036b7a-40c1-417f-825b-3778f3170ea1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SAYAJI HOTELS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NAVKARCORP] Navkar Corporation Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Navkar+Corporation+Ltd&title=Navkar+Corporation+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=7353eb94-e3f8-4f3a-8b0b-648d4f654059&token=NzM1M2ViOTQtZTNm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7353eb94-e3f8-4f3a-8b0b-648d4f654059</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:21:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Navkar Corporation Ltd has reported its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 18,584.74 lakhs for the quarter and 48,669.28 lakhs for the nine months ended. The net profit for the quarter is 435.47 lakhs, while the net loss for the nine months ended is 2,677.13 lakhs. The company operates in a single segment, which is Container Freight Station (CFS) and Inland Container Depot (ICD) Operations and related activities.</p><ul><li>Navkar Corporation Ltd has reported its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 18,584.74 lakhs for the quarter and 48,669.28 lakhs for the nine months ended.</li><li>The net profit for the quarter is 435.47 lakhs, while the net loss for the nine months ended is 2,677.13 lakhs.</li><li>The company operates in a single segment, which is Container Freight Station (CFS) and Inland Container Depot (ICD) Operations and related activities.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a8d29a5d-e698-41f3-8e9e-a50a1756ce48.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Navkar Corporation Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NAVKARCORP] Navkar Corporation Ltd Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Navkar+Corporation+Ltd&title=Navkar+Corporation+Ltd+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025&newsId=949f6404-1d05-4ae1-84cd-21f4ab04e2f1&token=OTQ5ZjY0MDQtMWQw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">949f6404-1d05-4ae1-84cd-21f4ab04e2f1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:21:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Navkar Corporation Ltd, a company engaged in Container Freight Station (CFS) and Inland Container Depot (ICD) Operations, has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a loss of Rs. 611.09 lakhs for the nine months ended 31 December, 2024 and year ended 31 March, 2025 from sale of certain assets. The company is in the process of evaluating the full impact of the new labour codes announced by the Government of India.</p><ul><li>Navkar Corporation Ltd reported a loss of Rs. 611.09 lakhs for the nine months ended 31 December, 2024 and year ended 31 March, 2025 from sale of certain assets.</li><li>The company is in the process of evaluating the full impact of the new labour codes announced by the Government of India.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8ba99b9b-e09f-4d63-ab78-3365696b0102.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Navkar Corporation Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SIGMA] Sigma Solve Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sigma+Solve+Ltd&title=Sigma+Solve+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=6873cc1a-00eb-46d1-82b3-7b389790775e&token=Njg3M2NjMWEtMDBl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6873cc1a-00eb-46d1-82b3-7b389790775e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:21:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sigma Solve Limited has released its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations for the nine months ended December 31, 2025, was ₹ 76,17,23,000 compared to ₹ 5,41,61,000 for the same period last year, indicating a significant growth of 1366.87%. The Board of Directors approved these results in a meeting on January 13, 2026.</p><ul><li>Sigma Solve Limited reported a revenue from operations of ₹ 76,17,23,000 for the nine months ended December 31, 2025, a growth of 1366.87% compared to the same period last year.</li><li>The company&apos;s other income for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, was ₹ 3,193.56.</li><li>The Board of Directors approved the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, in a meeting on January 13, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fe1b1837-305b-4e2f-939e-776056aace2f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sigma Solve Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IRCON] IRCON International Ltd Appoints New Statutory Foreign Branch Auditors for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IRCON+International+Ltd&title=IRCON+International+Ltd+Appoints+New+Statutory+Foreign+Branch+Auditors+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=5801859f-7344-4d4f-aea7-dcdb067d5731&token=NTgwMTg1OWYtNzM0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5801859f-7344-4d4f-aea7-dcdb067d5731</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:20:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>IRCON International Ltd has appointed new Statutory Foreign Branch Auditors for FY 2025-26. The appointment includes M/s KM Alam &amp; Co. for Bangladesh, M/s Jayasinghe &amp; Co. for Sri Lanka, Mr. Kerbal Athmane for Algeria, and M/s MyAsia Consulting Co. Ltd. for Myanmar. The auditors have been selected based on the recommendation of the Company and approved by the Office of the Comptroller and Auditor General of India (C&amp;AG). The appointment is subject to the conditions available on the CAG’s website to the extent these are applicable under the local laws of the respective countries.</p><ul><li>IRCON International Ltd has appointed new Statutory Foreign Branch Auditors for FY 2025-26</li><li>The appointed auditors include M/s KM Alam &amp; Co. for Bangladesh, M/s Jayasinghe &amp; Co. for Sri Lanka, Mr. Kerbal Athmane for Algeria, and M/s MyAsia Consulting Co. Ltd. for Myanmar</li><li>The auditors have been selected based on the recommendation of the Company and approved by the Office of the Comptroller and Auditor General of India (C&amp;AG)</li><li>The appointment is subject to the conditions available on the CAG’s website to the extent these are applicable under the local laws of the respective countries</li><li>M/s KM Alam &amp; Co. is one of the oldest audit firms in Bangladesh since 1967, M/s Jayasinghe &amp; Co. is a well-recognized firm in the Sri Lanka accounting fraternity, Mr. Kerbal Athmane is a Comptable Agrée with 16 years of experience, and M/s MyAsia Consulting Co. Ltd. has successfully advised and provided various consulting services to more than 400 local &amp; foreign clients in Myanmar</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1456b391-4994-46f0-b121-a8d3bac16c5a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IRCON International Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BINDALEXPO] Bindal Exports Limited Announces Resignation of Company Secretary &amp; Compliance Officer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Bindal+Exports+Ltd&title=Bindal+Exports+Limited+Announces+Resignation+of+Company+Secretary+%26+Compliance+Officer&newsId=9e0ff624-348b-43d2-b269-76ee4e7ef480&token=OWUwZmY2MjQtMzQ4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e0ff624-348b-43d2-b269-76ee4e7ef480</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:20:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bindal Exports Limited, in compliance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations &amp; Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, has announced the resignation of Mrs. Pratibha Bhutra from the post of Company Secretary &amp; Compliance Officer, effective from the close of business hours on January 13, 2026. The resignation was discussed and approved during the Board Meeting held on the same date. Mrs. Bhutra tendered her resignation due to personal reasons and has requested the Board to relieve her from her responsibilities and to give necessary intimation to the stock exchanges and file necessary forms with the ROC.</p><ul><li>Resignation of Mrs. Pratibha Bhutra as Company Secretary &amp; Compliance Officer of Bindal Exports Limited.</li><li>Resignation effective from the close of business hours on January 13, 2026.</li><li>Resignation discussed and approved during the Board Meeting held on January 13, 2026.</li><li>Mrs. Bhutra tendered her resignation due to personal reasons.</li><li>Bindal Exports Limited to relieve Mrs. Bhutra from her responsibilities, inform stock exchanges, and file necessary forms with the ROC.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b098de4e-a33c-42d3-b01e-9591b61808b5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Bindal Exports Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ATHCON] Athena Constructions Ltd. Announces Q2 and H1 2025 Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Athena+Constructions+Ltd&title=Athena+Constructions+Ltd.+Announces+Q2+and+H1+2025+Financial+Results&newsId=b971e61f-7134-4bfc-af9a-bce57e3314b3&token=Yjk3MWU2MWYtNzEz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b971e61f-7134-4bfc-af9a-bce57e3314b3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Athena Constructions Limited has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and six months ended September 30, 2025. The total income for the half-year stood at Rs. 75,00,000 with a net loss of Rs. 74,27,000. The company&apos;s revenue from operations was Rs. 7,32,000 and experienced a loss due to exceptional items of Rs. 36,48,000. The earnings per share (EPS) before and after extraordinary items were (0.49) and (0.22), respectively. The company&apos;s assets and liabilities statement showed net current liabilities of Rs. 4,707.12 lakhs and net long-term loans &amp; advances of Rs. 282.48 lakhs.</p><ul><li>Total income for H1 2025: Rs. 75,00,000</li><li>Net loss for H1 2025: Rs. 74,27,000</li><li>Revenue from operations: Rs. 7,32,000</li><li>Loss due to exceptional items: Rs. 36,48,000</li><li>Net current liabilities: Rs. 4,707.12 lakhs</li><li>Net long-term loans &amp; advances: Rs. 282.48 lakhs</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/24eea3ab-a7e2-4682-bada-f768f489dd15.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Athena Constructions Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>