<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:58:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SHAHLON] Shahlon Silk Industries Gets GPCB Approval for 5 MLD CETP-ZLD, Outlines Phased Expansion Strategy</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shahlon+Silk+Industries+Ltd&title=Shahlon+Silk+Industries+Gets+GPCB+Approval+for+5+MLD+CETP-ZLD%2C+Outlines+Phased+Expansion+Strategy&newsId=6732ef14-7508-4b95-b3d7-2de6f2fd0b59&token=NjczMmVmMTQtNzUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6732ef14-7508-4b95-b3d7-2de6f2fd0b59</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Shahlon Silk Industries Limited has received the &apos;Consent to Establish&apos; (CTE/NOC) from the Gujarat Pollution Control Board (GPCB) for its 5 MLD Common Effluent Treatment Plant (CETP) with Zero Liquid Discharge (ZLD) and 2 MLD Water Treatment Plant (WTP) with reservoir at Chhamuchhal, Taluka Mangrol, District Surat. The company has also submitted an application to the Industries Commissionerate, Government of Gujarat, seeking grant assistance under the Gujarat Industrial Policy 2020 for Common Environmental Infrastructure. The project is estimated to cost INR 67.93 crore and is scheduled to be completed by December 2026. The company has also started planning for a 20 MLD CETP project at Tadkeshwar, Taluka: Mandvi, District: Surat, to be implemented in a phased manner.</p><ul><li>Shahlon Silk Industries has obtained GPCB approval for a 5 MLD CETP-ZLD and 2 MLD WTP facility</li><li>The company has submitted a grant application under the Gujarat Industrial Policy 2020</li><li>The project is estimated to cost INR 67.93 crore and is scheduled for completion by December 2026</li><li>The facility is designed to enable centralized treatment and recycling of effluent generated by nearby textile units</li><li>The company has started planning for a 20 MLD CETP project in a phased manner</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3b867809-bdf3-4921-9de9-888ed2a91ee0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shahlon Silk Industries Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BLSE] BLS E-Services Ltd. to Acquire Atyati Technologies Private Limited for Rs. 154 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BLS+E-Services+Ltd&title=BLS+E-Services+Ltd.+to+Acquire+Atyati+Technologies+Private+Limited+for+Rs.+154+Crores&newsId=756459ee-d64c-4b12-8a21-13b916a35356&token=NzU2NDU5ZWUtZDY0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">756459ee-d64c-4b12-8a21-13b916a35356</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>BLS E-Services Ltd. has announced its decision to acquire 100% equity shares of Atyati Technologies Private Limited for a cash consideration of Rs. 154 Crores. The acquisition is expected to be completed by March 31, 2026, subject to necessary approvals. Atyati Technologies, established in 2006, is a Technology and Business Correspondent organization that enables banks to deliver financial services to rural and underbanked segments. It operates in Financial Inclusion, Lending to micro-customers, and technology solutions with an agent network spanning across 1 lac villages.</p><ul><li>BLS E-Services Ltd. to acquire Atyati Technologies Private Limited</li><li>100% equity shares to be acquired for a cash consideration of Rs. 154 Crores</li><li>Expected completion by March 31, 2026</li><li>Atyati Technologies operates in Financial Inclusion, Lending to micro-customers, and technology solutions</li><li>Atyati Technologies has an agent network spanning across 1 lac villages</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f6ae0877-b8f5-4d88-9b70-c1bcdf2e0eab.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BLS E-Services Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KTKBANK] Karnataka Bank&apos;s Founders&apos; Day Lecture by Shri Debasish Panda, IAS (Retd.) on 18-02-2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KARNATAKA+BANK+LTD.&title=Karnataka+Bank%27s+Founders%27+Day+Lecture+by+Shri+Debasish+Panda%2C+IAS+%28Retd.%29+on+18-02-2026&newsId=b853279d-fbfa-411c-8702-2f0780c6e2f0&token=Yjg1MzI3OWQtZmJm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b853279d-fbfa-411c-8702-2f0780c6e2f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:50:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Founders&apos; Day</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Karnataka Bank Ltd. has scheduled its 1024th Founders’ Day celebration on Wednesday, 18th February 2026 at 4.00 p.m. at the Bank’s Head Office, Mangaluru, Karnataka State. Shri Debasish Panda, IAS (Retd.), a visionary leader and transformative policy reformer, has consented to deliver the Founders’ Day Lecture. The event will be followed by an all-women classical music ensemble concert by renowned artists. The Founders’ Day celebrations will be streamed live in Bank’s official social media handles on Youtube and Facebook, and will be telecasted live by Popular TV Channels of the coastal Region, ‘Namma Kudla’ and ‘Namma TV’. The event will also be broadcast live through ‘All India Radio’ Mangaluru.</p><ul><li>Shri Debasish Panda, IAS (Retd.) to deliver the Founders’ Day Lecture.</li><li>Pioneering contributions across finance, insurance, public health, agriculture, law enforcement, and urban development.</li><li>Introduction of India&apos;s largest emergency response system (Dial 112) and modernization of urban governance in Greater Noida.</li><li>Technology-led governance, institutional building, and unwavering public service commitment.</li><li>Vision of ‘Insurance for All by 2047&apos;, redefinition of regulatory frameworks, and prioritization of customer-centric governance.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c80c1f57-d9ee-4bab-b213-b00b8d4c4d38.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KARNATAKA BANK LTD. | Category: Founders' Day</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PTC] PTC India Ltd Fixes Record Date for Interim Dividend Payment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PTC+INDIA+LTD.&title=PTC+India+Ltd+Fixes+Record+Date+for+Interim+Dividend+Payment&newsId=ff27e2a9-f280-4f43-bf16-26a83178b79f&token=ZmYyN2UyYTktZjI4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff27e2a9-f280-4f43-bf16-26a83178b79f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:44:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>PTC India Ltd has fixed the record date of 20th February 2026 for the purpose of ascertaining the name of members/beneficial owners entitled to receive an interim dividend of Rs. 3/ per share for the financial year 2025-26. The board of directors declared an interim dividend at the rate of 30% (Rs. 3/- per equity share of Rs. 10/- each) in its meeting held on 14th February 2026. Friday, 20th February 2026, has been fixed as the &apos;Record Date&apos; as per the SEBI Listing Regulations. The information will be hosted on the company&apos;s website: www.ptcindia.com.</p><ul><li>PTC India Ltd fixes record date for interim dividend payment</li><li>Interim dividend of Rs. 3/ per share for the financial year 2025-26</li><li>Board of directors declared an interim dividend at the rate of 30%</li><li>Record Date set for 20th February 2026</li><li>Information to be hosted on the company&apos;s website: www.ptcindia.com</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/34e5c596-15c2-4f26-815b-6c635255667b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PTC INDIA LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TORNTPOWER] Torrent Power to Acquire Nabha Power Limited for INR 6,889 Crores, Expanding Thermal Generation Footprint</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TORRENT+POWER+LTD.&title=Torrent+Power+to+Acquire+Nabha+Power+Limited+for+INR+6%2C889+Crores%2C+Expanding+Thermal+Generation+Footprint&newsId=939e6a08-def7-401e-8c0c-3737610c59da&token=OTM5ZTZhMDgtZGVm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">939e6a08-def7-401e-8c0c-3737610c59da</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Torrent Power Limited has entered into a definitive agreement with L&amp;T Power Development Limited to acquire 100% of equity stake and convertible instruments in Nabha Power Limited for an Enterprise Value of INR 6,889 Crores. Nabha Power Limited is a fully contracted thermal power asset with revenue of INR 4,866 crores and Adjusted EBITDA of INR 1,153 crores in FY 2025. The acquisition will increase Torrent’s operational capacity from ~5 GW to 6.4 GW and is expected to be value accretive from day one. The transaction is subject to requisite regulatory approvals and customary closing conditions.</p><ul><li>Torrent Power to acquire Nabha Power Limited for INR 6,889 Crores</li><li>Nabha Power Limited is a fully contracted thermal power asset with revenue of INR 4,866 crores and Adjusted EBITDA of INR 1,153 crores in FY 2025</li><li>The acquisition will increase Torrent’s operational capacity from ~5 GW to 6.4 GW</li><li>The transaction is expected to be value accretive from day one</li><li>The acquisition is subject to requisite regulatory approvals and customary closing conditions</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a664a219-4010-4ee7-bc58-d070cccfc547.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TORRENT POWER LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DSSL] Dynacons and Cygeniq Partner to Deliver AI-Driven Cybersecurity and Trusted AI Protection across India, Middle East &amp; APAC</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DYNACONS+SYSTEMS+%26+SOLUTIONS+LTD.&title=Dynacons+and+Cygeniq+Partner+to+Deliver+AI-Driven+Cybersecurity+and+Trusted+AI+Protection+across+India%2C+Middle+East+%26+APAC&newsId=de8d0283-85ab-4586-8b28-190ed6e8f5af&token=ZGU4ZDAyODMtODVh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de8d0283-85ab-4586-8b28-190ed6e8f5af</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:40:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Partnership</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Dynacons Systems &amp; Solutions Ltd., a leading provider of IT infrastructure, cybersecurity, and managed services, announced a strategic collaboration with Cygeniq Inc., US-based Al-native cybersecurity firm, to deliver next-generation AI-driven cyber defense and AI governance solutions across India, Middle East, and the Asia-Pacific region. The collaboration aims to help organizations improve cyber resilience, enhance compliance readiness, and proactively address rapidly evolving digital threats. The combined portfolio will include AI-enabled Governance, Risk, and Compliance (GRC), adversarial automated red teaming and protection, Al-driven cybersecurity intelligence, and specialized AI Advisory and Consulting Services.</p><ul><li>Dynacons and Cygeniq to deliver next-generation AI-driven cyber defense and AI governance solutions across India, Middle East, and APAC.</li><li>Collaboration aims to help organizations improve cyber resilience, enhance compliance readiness, and proactively address rapidly evolving digital threats.</li><li>Combined portfolio to include AI-enabled Governance, Risk, and Compliance (GRC), adversarial automated red teaming and protection, Al-driven cybersecurity intelligence, and specialized AI Advisory and Consulting Services.</li><li>Partnership designed to deliver scalable, future-ready security frameworks for enterprises, government, and institutional customers across the region.</li><li>Shared vision to accelerate adoption of Al-enabled cybersecurity services and help organizations respond to the growing complexity, speed, and sophistication of cyber risks in a rapidly evolving digital landscape.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6df18e48-ce36-49ad-8cad-cfc0ae0c488c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DYNACONS SYSTEMS & SOLUTIONS LTD. | Category: Partnership</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TECHNOE*] Techno Electric &amp; Engineering Company Ltd Changes Objects of Rs.1250 Crores QIP Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Techno+Electric+%26+Engineering+Company+Ltd&title=Techno+Electric+%26+Engineering+Company+Ltd+Changes+Objects+of+Rs.1250+Crores+QIP+Issue&newsId=8748731d-580f-4e05-9dfd-b40c50725d93&token=ODc0ODczMWQtNTgw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8748731d-580f-4e05-9dfd-b40c50725d93</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:39:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Techno Electric &amp; Engineering Company Ltd has changed the objects of its Rs.1250 Crores Qualified Institutional Placement (QIP) issue. The Investment in the subsidiary NERES XVI Power Transmission Limited, and in NERGS-I Power Transmission Limited for funding EPC works for TBCB projects has been revised from Rs.400 crore to 200 crore. The unutilized funds have been reallocated to Investment in Subsidiary, Techno Infra Developers Private Limited, for funding EPC works for data center situated in Chennai, thereby revising its allocation from Rs.350 crore to 7550 crore. The company has taken the approval from board of directors for the same.</p><ul><li>Techno Electric &amp; Engineering Company Ltd has changed the objects of its Rs.1250 Crores Qualified Institutional Placement (QIP) issue.</li><li>The Investment in the subsidiary NERES XVI Power Transmission Limited, and in NERGS-I Power Transmission Limited for funding EPC works for TBCB projects has been revised from Rs.400 crore to 200 crore.</li><li>The unutilized funds have been reallocated to Investment in Subsidiary, Techno Infra Developers Private Limited, for funding EPC works for data center situated in Chennai.</li><li>The company has taken the approval from board of directors for the same.</li><li>The Monitoring Agency Report is in line with the format prescribed by SEBI, capturing the comments on the utilization of the issue proceeds.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bca4ab16-e607-430b-83c1-d5377e4a2f11.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Techno Electric & Engineering Company Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[COSMOFIRST] Cosmo First Ltd Acquires Stake in Hexa Sunshine Private Limited for Hybrid Renewable Power Supply</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Cosmo+First+Ltd&title=Cosmo+First+Ltd+Acquires+Stake+in+Hexa+Sunshine+Private+Limited+for+Hybrid+Renewable+Power+Supply&newsId=db34df23-e174-4bed-bab8-e276298cf3a2&token=ZGIzNGRmMjMtZTE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db34df23-e174-4bed-bab8-e276298cf3a2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:37:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Cosmo First Ltd has entered into a Security Subscription and Shareholders’ Agreement with Hexa Sunshine Private Limited (SPV) and its holding company for the acquisition of a stake in the SPV. This acquisition is in connection with the supply of Hybrid Renewable Power for the Company’s manufacturing plants at Gujrat on a Group Captive consumer basis. The SPV, Hexa Sunshine Private Limited, was incorporated in April 2024 and did not have any income as on March 31, 2025. The proposed transaction is a cash consideration of up to Rs. 7,00,00,000/- (Rupees Seven Crores Only) for acquiring up to 26% shareholding in the SPV. The target entity is an SPV for implementing the project for hybrid renewable power supply to the Company.</p><ul><li>Cosmo First Ltd is acquiring a stake in Hexa Sunshine Private Limited for hybrid renewable power supply.</li><li>The SPV, Hexa Sunshine Private Limited, was incorporated in April 2024 and did not have any income as on March 31, 2025.</li><li>The proposed transaction is a cash consideration of up to Rs. 7,00,000/- (Rupees Seven Crores Only) for acquiring up to 26% shareholding in the SPV.</li><li>The target entity is an SPV for implementing the project for hybrid renewable power supply to the Company.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/46c797d5-a50d-4eea-955e-4ab97285e642.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Cosmo First Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TORNTPOWER] Torrent Power Ltd Acquires Nabha Power Limited for Rs. 3660.87 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TORRENT+POWER+LTD.&title=Torrent+Power+Ltd+Acquires+Nabha+Power+Limited+for+Rs.+3660.87+Crores&newsId=aa7bac18-4cb7-48a0-bc46-afd1dc1c0806&token=YWE3YmFjMTgtNGNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa7bac18-4cb7-48a0-bc46-afd1dc1c0806</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Torrent Power Ltd has entered into a Securities Purchase Agreement to acquire 100% of the equity stake and convertible instruments of Nabha Power Limited from L&amp;T Power Development Limited for an aggregate consideration of Rs. 3660.87 crores. Nabha Power Limited owns and operates a 2x700 MW coal based super critical thermal power plant at Village Nalash, Rajpura, Punjab. The turnover of NPL for FY 25 was INR 4421.54 Crore. This acquisition will enable Torrent Power to expand its current thermal generation portfolio and will extend its presence in Northern India. The acquisition is subject to approval from Competition Commission of India and is expected to be completed by 30th June 2026.</p><ul><li>Torrent Power Ltd to acquire 100% equity stake in Nabha Power Limited for Rs. 3660.87 crores</li><li>Nabha Power Limited owns and operates a 2x700 MW coal based super critical thermal power plant in Punjab</li><li>The acquisition will expand Torrent Power&apos;s thermal generation portfolio and extend its presence in Northern India</li><li>The acquisition is subject to approval from Competition Commission of India</li><li>Expected to be completed by 30th June 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/229c934e-7900-4a0e-b309-a525f0787346.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TORRENT POWER LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FEDERALBNK] Federal Bank Ltd Allots Warrants to Asia II Topco XIII Pte. Ltd. on Preferential Basis</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=FEDERAL+BANK+LTD.&title=Federal+Bank+Ltd+Allots+Warrants+to+Asia+II+Topco+XIII+Pte.+Ltd.+on+Preferential+Basis&newsId=435f280c-596b-4df7-aa3e-e39d27e2a05b&token=NDM1ZjI4MGMtNTk2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">435f280c-596b-4df7-aa3e-e39d27e2a05b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pursuant to Regulation 30 and other applicable regulations of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, Federal Bank Ltd has approved the allotment of warrants by way of preferential allotment on a private placement basis. The allotment is made to Asia II Topco XIII Pte. Ltd. at a price of INR 22.35 per warrant. The total number of warrants allotted is 27,29,74,043, with the total consideration received being INR 6196,51,07,761. The allotment has been undertaken in accordance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Issue of Capital and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2018 and other applicable rules/regulations.</p><ul><li>Federal Bank Ltd allots warrants to Asia II Topco XIII Pte. Ltd.</li><li>Allotment made on a preferential basis and on a private placement.</li><li>Price per warrant is INR 22.35.</li><li>Total number of warrants allotted: 27,29,74,043.</li><li>Total consideration received: INR 6196,51,07,761.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ae5de28c-6b88-47bb-91b0-d935f2d4bc3d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: FEDERAL BANK LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>