<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:38:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[BLS] BLS International Services Ltd Continues Strong Financial Performance in Q3FY26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BLS+International+Services+Ltd&title=BLS+International+Services+Ltd+Continues+Strong+Financial+Performance+in+Q3FY26&newsId=b39deca3-79ab-4e35-94a0-cef442cad065&token=YjM5ZGVjYTMtNzlh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b39deca3-79ab-4e35-94a0-cef442cad065</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:37:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>BLS International Services Ltd, a trusted global tech-enabled services partner for governments and citizens, announced its unaudited consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company reported a robust performance in Q3 &amp; 9M FY26, with revenue increasing to Rs. 736 Crores, up 43.6% YoY, and net profit standing at Rs. 170 Crores, a growth of 33.1% YoY.</p><ul><li>Secured a five-year global contract from the Slovak Republic to establish and operate Visa Application Centres in over 80 countries.</li><li>Secured Visa outsourcing contract from the High Commission of the Republic of Cyprus, extending its services in multiple countries.</li><li>Secured a project from the Bihar Government worth Rs. 100 Crores, for establishing Permanent Enrolment Centres (PEC) for Aadhar.</li><li>Renewed its nationwide contract with India’s Ministry of External Affairs to provide attestation and apostille services across 17 major centres.</li><li>Awarded a Three-Year contract from the Ministry of External Affairs, Govt. of India, to establish and operate Indian Visa Application Centres (VACs) across three major cities of China.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/acf1c09e-9ab6-4adc-871b-b94aa2361db6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BLS International Services Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GNA] G N A Axles Ltd Reappoints Directors: Jasvinder Singh, Ranbir Singh, and Maninder Singh</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=G+N+A+Axles+Ltd&title=G+N+A+Axles+Ltd+Reappoints+Directors%3A+Jasvinder+Singh%2C+Ranbir+Singh%2C+and+Maninder+Singh&newsId=cdab717e-cc4c-4ce0-98ee-758fef2adf96&token=Y2RhYjcxN2UtY2M0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cdab717e-cc4c-4ce0-98ee-758fef2adf96</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:37:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>G N A Axles Ltd has announced the reappointment of Mr. Jasvinder Singh as Executive Vice Chairman, Mr. Ranbir Singh as Managing Director &amp; CEO, and Mr. Maninder Singh as Executive Director. The reappointments are subject to the approval of the shareholders, which will be obtained through a postal ballot. The directors have confirmed that they are not debarred from holding the office of Directors by virtue of any SEBI order or any other such authority. Their profiles are attached as Annexure A.</p><ul><li>Reappointment of Mr. Jasvinder Singh as Executive Vice Chairman for a period of 5 years</li><li>Reappointment of Mr. Ranbir Singh as Managing Director &amp; CEO for a period of 5 years</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Maninder Singh as Executive Director for a period of 2 years</li><li>Appointments are subject to the approval of the shareholders</li><li>Directors have confirmed they are not debarred from holding the office of Directors by virtue of any SEBI order or any other such authority</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4451cd7e-1611-48a3-a40f-99ed6bb37fe4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: G N A Axles Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TIMESGTY] Team India Guaranty Ltd. to Approve Q4 Results for 2025 in February Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TIMES+GUARANTY+LTD.&title=Team+India+Guaranty+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q4+Results+for+2025+in+February+Board+Meeting&newsId=9dc4aca9-600f-47ff-8b86-fe30589b1d57&token=OWRjNGFjYTktNjAw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9dc4aca9-600f-47ff-8b86-fe30589b1d57</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:36:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Team India Guaranty Ltd. has informed the BSE that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on 13th February 2026. The agenda includes the consideration and approval of the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025, along with the Limited Review Report. The meeting also aims to consider and transit any other business as may be placed before the Board. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company for its designated persons has been closed from 1st January 2026 and will remain closed till the end of 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results.</p><ul><li>Team India Guaranty Ltd. to approve Q4 results for 2025 in February Board meeting</li><li>Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025 to be considered and approved</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company for its designated persons closed from 1st January 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bea6d556-6a52-419a-bac1-081de622c509.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TIMES GUARANTY LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[OLYMTFI] Olympic Management &amp; Financial Services Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Olympic+Management+%26+Financial+Services+Ltd&title=Olympic+Management+%26+Financial+Services+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=6ae0c205-7b59-42d2-8956-d4171a2f836e&token=NmFlMGMyMDUtN2I1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ae0c205-7b59-42d2-8956-d4171a2f836e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:34:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Olympic Management &amp; Financial Services Ltd, a company operating mainly in a single segment, has released its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 4.69 Lac for the quarter and 8.35 Lac for the nine months period. The net loss for the quarter is 1.90 Lac and 5.56 Lac for the nine months period. The company has not received any complaints during the quarter and the previous period/year figures have been regrouped and reclassified to make them comparable with current quarter figures.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter is 4.69 Lac</li><li>Revenue from operations for the nine months period is 8.35 Lac</li><li>Net loss for the quarter is 1.90 Lac</li><li>Net loss for the nine months period is 5.56 Lac</li><li>The company has not received any complaints during the quarter</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f92958d4-8343-48d5-87dd-a9c00a79d0c2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Olympic Management & Financial Services Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASHOKA] Ashoka Buildcon Subsidiary Wins SAR 351 Crore Contract in KSA Joint Venture</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ASHOKA+BUILDCON+LTD.&title=Ashoka+Buildcon+Subsidiary+Wins+SAR+351+Crore+Contract+in+KSA+Joint+Venture&newsId=4ed383a3-d02f-4bdc-8f8f-3225cb63f63d&token=NGVkMzgzYTMtZDAy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4ed383a3-d02f-4bdc-8f8f-3225cb63f63d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:33:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Ashoka Buildcon Ltd&apos;s wholly owned subsidiary in the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia, Ashoka Buildcon Limited for Contracting, has submitted a bid in a Joint Venture with BEC Arabia Contracting Co. to Diriyah Company for the &apos;Main Construction Works of Diriyah Il — Delivery Partner for One Hotel&apos; project. The Joint Venture has received a Letter of Acceptance for the project with a bid price of SAR 717,086,344.22, excluding VAT. Ashoka Buildcon holds a 49% stake in the Joint Venture, amounting to a share of SAR 351,372,308.67 (approximately INR 846.38 Crore) in the project bid price.</p><ul><li>Ashoka Buildcon&apos;s subsidiary wins a contract worth SAR 717,086,344.22 in KSA</li><li>The contract is for the &apos;Main Construction Works of Diriyah Il — Delivery Partner for One Hotel&apos; project</li><li>The Joint Venture has received a Letter of Acceptance for the project</li><li>Ashoka Buildcon holds a 49% stake in the Joint Venture</li><li>The Company&apos;s share in the project bid price is approximately INR 846.38 Crore</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/814ef9c6-dda4-4320-b003-adbf48c9de08.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ASHOKA BUILDCON LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MANGALAM] Mangalam Drugs &amp; Organics Ltd: Board Meeting Approves Changes in Management and Re-appointment of Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MANGALAM+DRUGS+%26+ORGANICS+LTD.&title=Mangalam+Drugs+%26+Organics+Ltd%3A+Board+Meeting+Approves+Changes+in+Management+and+Re-appointment+of+Director&newsId=196d06fb-ff50-4098-8449-37c5578ca5a9&token=MTk2ZDA2ZmItZmY1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">196d06fb-ff50-4098-8449-37c5578ca5a9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:33:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In a recent board meeting, Mangalam Drugs &amp; Organics Ltd announced the resignation of Independent Director Shri Rukmesh P. Dhandhania and appointed Mr. Jeevan Mukund Dalvi as the Chief Financial Officer. Additionally, the board approved the re-appointment of Dr. Praveen Saxena as an Independent Director for a term of five years, subject to shareholders&apos; approval with a special resolution.</p><ul><li>Resignation of Independent Director Shri Rukmesh P. Dhandhania</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Jeevan Mukund Dalvi as the Chief Financial Officer</li><li>Re-appointment of Dr. Praveen Saxena as an Independent Director for 5 years</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5b44d5c6-3910-4cbc-8cfc-a9eb96e6a29b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MANGALAM DRUGS & ORGANICS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GRINDWELL] Grindwell Norton Ltd. to Invest $11 Million in Sunsure Energy&apos;s SPV for Renewable Energy Sourcing</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GRINDWELL+NORTON+LTD.-%24&title=Grindwell+Norton+Ltd.+to+Invest+%2411+Million+in+Sunsure+Energy%27s+SPV+for+Renewable+Energy+Sourcing&newsId=10cbb6d5-7ec7-458f-b643-412a93820174&token=MTBjYmI2ZDUtN2Vj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">10cbb6d5-7ec7-458f-b643-412a93820174</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:32:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Grindwell Norton Ltd. has approved an investment of up to $11 Million in a Special Purpose Vehicle (SPV) of Sunsure Energy Private Limited. The SPV is for sourcing renewable energy through an Intra-State Transmission System based on solar power generation. The Board also approved the appointment of Mr. Girish T. Shajani as the Company Secretary, Compliance Officer, and Nodal Officer of the Company. The financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, were also approved and will be published in newspapers accordingly.</p><ul><li>Grindwell Norton Ltd. to invest up to $11 Million in Sunsure Energy&apos;s SPV</li><li>Investment aimed at sourcing renewable energy through an Intra-State Transmission System</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Girish T. Shajani as Company Secretary, Compliance Officer, and Nodal Officer</li><li>Approval of financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/41e296b3-3f78-48fc-a732-4fe7e3314f8d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GRINDWELL NORTON LTD.-$ | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[OLYMTFI] Olympic Management &amp; Financial Services Ltd. Reports Q3 2025 Unaudited Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Olympic+Management+%26+Financial+Services+Ltd&title=Olympic+Management+%26+Financial+Services+Ltd.+Reports+Q3+2025+Unaudited+Financial+Results&newsId=c9a4c96a-d0ca-42db-901a-93c5058cdb6f&token=YzlhNGM5NmEtZDBj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9a4c96a-d0ca-42db-901a-93c5058cdb6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Olympic Management &amp; Financial Services Ltd. held a Board Meeting on 06th February, 2026, where they considered and adopted the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter ended 31st December, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 4.69 Lacs, with a total income of 12.88 Lacs and a profit before tax of 1.48 Lacs. The earnings per equity share for continuing operations is 0.049.</p><ul><li>Q3 2025 Unaudited Financial Results adopted by the Board</li><li>Revenue from operations stands at 4.69 Lacs</li><li>Total income for the quarter is 12.88 Lacs</li><li>Profit before tax stands at 1.48 Lacs</li><li>Earnings per equity share for continuing operations is 0.049</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6b3fe769-bca9-434a-9259-c6761556e409.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Olympic Management & Financial Services Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PURITY] Purity Flexpack Ltd to Consider and Approve UFR 31.12.2025 on 12/02/2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PURITY+FLEX+PACK+LTD.&title=Purity+Flexpack+Ltd+to+Consider+and+Approve+UFR+31.12.2025+on+12%2F02%2F2026&newsId=1b9db805-335d-4191-836d-41a29a70a1c6&token=MWI5ZGI4MDUtMzM1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b9db805-335d-4191-836d-41a29a70a1c6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:28:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Purity Flexpack Ltd has announced that a meeting of the Board of Directors will be held on 12 February, 2026 at 11.00 a.m. at Vanseti, Nr. Baska, Halol GJ 389 350. The agenda of the meeting includes the consideration, approval, and taking on record of the Unaudited Financial Results of the Company for the quarter ended 31st December, 2025. Any other matter with the permission of the chair will also be discussed.</p><ul><li>Purity Flexpack Ltd Board Meeting scheduled on 12/02/2026</li><li>To consider and approve UFR 31.12.2025</li><li>Meeting to be held at Vanseti, Nr. Baska, Halol GJ 389 350</li><li>Discussion on other matters with the permission of the chair</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/05265f52-8a7b-4799-afcb-f651635ef17c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PURITY FLEX PACK LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BLS] BLS International Services Ltd Declares Interim Dividend, Changes RTA, and Reports Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BLS+International+Services+Ltd&title=BLS+International+Services+Ltd+Declares+Interim+Dividend%2C+Changes+RTA%2C+and+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=fc8041a2-949f-4ea6-9d38-ff6ef2e19564&token=ZmM4MDQxYTItOTQ5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc8041a2-949f-4ea6-9d38-ff6ef2e19564</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 09:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>BLS International Services Ltd announced a 15 interim dividend of Rs. 2.00 per equity share, changed its Registrar &amp; Transfer Agent (RTA) from Beetal Financial and Computer Services Private Limited to KFin Technologies Limited, and reported its standalone and consolidated un-audited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The company also declared February 13, 2026 as the record date for the purpose of determining the names of members eligible to receive the aforesaid interim dividend.</p><ul><li>Declared 15 interim dividend of Rs. 2.00 per equity share</li><li>Changed Registrar &amp; Transfer Agent (RTA) from Beetal Financial and Computer Services Private Limited to KFin Technologies Limited</li><li>Reported standalone and consolidated un-audited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended on December 31, 2025</li><li>Fixed February 13, 2026 as the record date for the purpose of determining the names of members eligible to receive the interim dividend</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8b4da1e9-a454-4d9f-831a-43a5e34db2d6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BLS International Services Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>