<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 21:29:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ZENIFIB] Zenith Fibres Ltd. Approves Q3 Results for FY2025-2026 with a Net Profit of Rs. 4.57 per Share</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ZENITH+FIBRES+LTD.-%24&title=Zenith+Fibres+Ltd.+Approves+Q3+Results+for+FY2025-2026+with+a+Net+Profit+of+Rs.+4.57+per+Share&newsId=d1ac12fe-ba04-4120-9646-0d4b61d29a37&token=ZDFhYzEyZmUtYmEw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d1ac12fe-ba04-4120-9646-0d4b61d29a37</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 21:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Zenith Fibres Ltd. announced the outcome of its Board Meeting held on 04.02.2026, which included the approval of the unaudited financial results for the third quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a revenue from operations of Rs. 1,410.08 crores and a net profit of Rs. 4.57 per share. The meeting also addressed the impact of the New Labour Codes and recognized liquidated damages income of Rs. 252.17 lakhs.</p><ul><li>Approval of unaudited financial results for Q3 FY2025-2026</li><li>Revenue from operations stands at Rs. 1,410.08 crores</li><li>Net profit of Rs. 4.57 per share</li><li>Recognition of liquidated damages income of Rs. 252.17 lakhs</li><li>No material impact from the implementation of New Labour Codes</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d44cf4bf-3c8f-4166-988e-99f623fe7de0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ZENITH FIBRES LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AROGRANITE] Aro Granite Industries Ltd. Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025, Appoints New Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ARO+GRANITE+INDUSTRIES+LTD.-%24&title=Aro+Granite+Industries+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Appoints+New+Independent+Director&newsId=8f422583-7139-4505-bda1-d89ef775e510&token=OGY0MjI1ODMtNzEz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f422583-7139-4505-bda1-d89ef775e510</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 21:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Aro Granite Industries Ltd. has announced its audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue stands at INR 13,274.87 lakhs with a total expense of INR 10,774.46 lakhs, resulting in a profit before tax of INR 2,500.41 lakhs. The company has also appointed Mr. Varathan Arul as an Additional Director in the category of Non-Executive and Independent Director for a period of 5 years. The meeting was concluded at 01:30 P.M. on February 04, 2026.</p><ul><li>Aro Granite Industries Ltd. announced its audited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended on December 31, 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s total revenue stands at INR 13,274.87 lakhs with a total expense of INR 10,774.46 lakhs.</li><li>The profit before tax stands at INR 2,500.41 lakhs.</li><li>Mr. Varathan Arul has been appointed as an Additional Director in the category of Non-Executive and Independent Director for a period of 5 years.</li><li>The appointment of Mr. Varathan Arul is subject to the approval of shareholders of the Company within a period of three months.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/86577d97-c1dd-4a41-afe2-e6dafa8b266f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ARO GRANITE INDUSTRIES LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HEALINV] Healthy Investments Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on Feb 11, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HEALTHY+INVESTMENTS+LTD.&title=Healthy+Investments+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+Feb+11%2C+2026&newsId=5ee0f38c-9797-43d9-992e-2150bdcc8c00&token=NWVlMGYzOGMtOTc5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ee0f38c-9797-43d9-992e-2150bdcc8c00</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 21:04:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Healthy Investments Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 11, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results of the company for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</p><ul><li>The meeting of the Board of Directors of Healthy Investments Ltd is scheduled on 11/02/2026.</li><li>The Board will consider and approve the un-audited financial results of the company for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7aac0db9-89a9-48aa-8064-908efd347b76.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HEALTHY INVESTMENTS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WOODSVILA] Woodsvilla Ltd to Approve Unaudited Financial Statements for Q4 2025 in Board Meeting on 12th February 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=WOODSVILLA+LTD.&title=Woodsvilla+Ltd+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Statements+for+Q4+2025+in+Board+Meeting+on+12th+February+2026&newsId=d26c202e-eae7-45fc-a062-98a89c376cf9&token=ZDI2YzIwMmUtZWFl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d26c202e-eae7-45fc-a062-98a89c376cf9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 21:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Woodsvilla Ltd has announced a board meeting scheduled on 12th February 2026 to consider and approve the un-audited financial statements for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The meeting will also approve the Limited Review Report of the company. This is in accordance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirements) Regulation 2015.</p><ul><li>Woodsvilla Ltd to hold a board meeting on 12th February 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the un-audited financial statements for Q4 2025</li><li>The meeting will also approve the Limited Review Report of the company</li><li>The meeting is in accordance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirements) Regulation 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dda0ea8f-433a-4a3d-ad9d-6d4d08357d81.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: WOODSVILLA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HINDALUMI] Hind Aluminium Industries Ltd. to Acquire Aluminium Business of Nirav Commercials Ltd. for Rs. 1.25 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HIND+ALUMINIUM+INDUSTRIES+LTD.-%24&title=Hind+Aluminium+Industries+Ltd.+to+Acquire+Aluminium+Business+of+Nirav+Commercials+Ltd.+for+Rs.+1.25+Crores&newsId=3dce6581-f803-47b9-b592-64babe7e36e7&token=M2RjZTY1ODEtZjgw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3dce6581-f803-47b9-b592-64babe7e36e7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 21:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Hind Aluminium Industries Ltd. has proposed to acquire the aluminium business of Nirav Commercials Ltd. under the brand name &apos;Elesar Focchi&apos; for a cash consideration of Rs. 1.25 Crores. The Target Business is primarily engaged in the manufacture and sale of aluminium grills, doors, and windows. The transaction is expected to be completed by March 31, 2026, and is in line with Hind Aluminium&apos;s growth strategy. The Target Business had a turnover of Rs. 9,72,64,000 in the Financial Year ended on March 31, 2025.</p><ul><li>Hind Aluminium Industries Ltd. to acquire the aluminium business of Nirav Commercials Ltd.</li><li>Transaction value is Rs. 1.25 Crores.</li><li>The Target Business is primarily engaged in the manufacture and sale of aluminium grills, doors, and windows.</li><li>The acquisition is in line with Hind Aluminium&apos;s growth strategy.</li><li>The Target Business had a turnover of Rs. 9,72,64,000 in the Financial Year ended on March 31, 2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/140d41b9-3bc3-497b-a714-19e446a50f00.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HIND ALUMINIUM INDUSTRIES LTD.-$ | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GALLANTT] Gallantt Ispat Ltd. Approves Standalone and Consolidated Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended 31st December, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Gallantt+Ispat+Ltd&title=Gallantt+Ispat+Ltd.+Approves+Standalone+and+Consolidated+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+31st+December%2C+2025&newsId=b39b7f05-b552-48ce-b352-8d5dbc98fd3f&token=YjM5YjdmMDUtYjU1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b39b7f05-b552-48ce-b352-8d5dbc98fd3f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 21:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gallantt Ispat Ltd. has announced the approval of its standalone and consolidated unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The company&apos;s total income stands at Rs. 60,861 lakhs for the quarter and Rs. 506,670 lakhs for the nine months period. The total expenses for the quarter and nine months are Rs. 92,295.92 lakhs and Rs. 280,675.89 lakhs respectively. The net profit for the period is Rs. 10,041.07 lakhs. The earnings per share (EPS) for the quarter is Rs. 14.98. The company&apos;s financial results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Gallantt Ispat Ltd. approves standalone and consolidated unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December, 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s total income for the quarter is Rs. 60,861 lakhs and Rs. 506,670 lakhs for the nine months period.</li><li>The total expenses for the quarter and nine months are Rs. 92,295.92 lakhs and Rs. 280,675.89 lakhs respectively.</li><li>The net profit for the period is Rs. 10,041.07 lakhs.</li><li>The earnings per share (EPS) for the quarter is Rs. 14.98.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ac5a4ec6-02a4-4f30-9d4a-cc47768c97f9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Gallantt Ispat Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GALLANTT] Gallantt Ispat Ltd. Approves Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Gallantt+Ispat+Ltd&title=Gallantt+Ispat+Ltd.+Approves+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=ca2f7554-edd8-4c00-885b-591e59a787dc&token=Y2EyZjc1NTQtZWRk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ca2f7554-edd8-4c00-885b-591e59a787dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 21:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gallantt Ispat Ltd. held a Board Meeting on 4th February, 2026, where they considered and approved the Standalone and Consolidated Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue for the quarter ended at Rs. 78,221,610 and for the nine months ended at Rs. 231,293,630. The total expenses for the quarter were Rs. 92,295,920 and for the nine months were Rs. 281,499,190. The net profit for the quarter was Rs. 10,041,070 and for the nine months was Rs. 36,099.530. The EPS for the quarter was Rs. 47.11 and for the nine months was Rs. 14.98. The results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Gallantt Ispat Ltd. approves Q3 and nine months financial results for 2025.</li><li>Revenue for the quarter ended at Rs. 78,221,610 and for the nine months at Rs. 231,293,630.</li><li>Total expenses for the quarter were Rs. 92,295,920 and for the nine months were Rs. 281,499,190.</li><li>Net profit for the quarter was Rs. 10,041,070 and for the nine months was Rs. 36,099.530.</li><li>EPS for the quarter was Rs. 47.11 and for the nine months was Rs. 14.98.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/099b25fb-d652-487b-b452-d1c8205e2c45.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Gallantt Ispat Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VIRATCRA] Virat Crane Industries Ltd to Approve Q3 Financial Results on February 14, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VIRAT+CRANE+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Virat+Crane+Industries+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+Financial+Results+on+February+14%2C+2026&newsId=2fc38e79-da06-4a42-9ce7-b3806be1ffe5&token=MmZjMzhlNzktZGEw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2fc38e79-da06-4a42-9ce7-b3806be1ffe5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 21:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Virat Crane Industries Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 14, 2026, to consider and approve the un-Audited financial results for the third quarter of the financial year ending on December 31, 2025. The meeting will also serve to inform about the closure of the trading window for all directors and designated persons of the company under the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Virat Crane Industries Ltd to consider and approve Q3 financial results for FY 2025-26 on February 14, 2026.</li><li>Trading window to be closed for 48 hours after financial results become publicly available for all directors and designated persons.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9328afe1-f220-45ee-ab45-dba2450f7832.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VIRAT CRANE INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAATVIKGL] Saatvik Green Energy Ltd Announces Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Saatvik+Green+Energy+Ltd&title=Saatvik+Green+Energy+Ltd+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=41fa771a-6c52-4f12-a99f-1f4843da02ce&token=NDFmYTc3MWEtNmM1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41fa771a-6c52-4f12-a99f-1f4843da02ce</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 21:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Saatvik Green Energy Ltd has announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The results were approved at the Board of Directors meeting held on February 04, 2026. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 12,570.22 million INR for the quarter and 29,407.79 million INR for the nine months ended.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter is 12,570.22 million INR</li><li>Revenue from operations for the nine months ended is 29,407.79 million INR</li><li>Board of Directors approved the financial results on February 04, 2026</li><li>Unaudited consolidated financial results include the interim financial results of 2 subsidiaries which have not been reviewed by their auditors</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3c223027-3d56-4e9d-8112-4d59aae191b9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Saatvik Green Energy Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[APOLLOTYRE] Apollo Tyres Ltd Announces Q3 Results, Capacity Expansion, and Interim Dividend</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=APOLLO+TYRES+LTD.&title=Apollo+Tyres+Ltd+Announces+Q3+Results%2C+Capacity+Expansion%2C+and+Interim+Dividend&newsId=67a79bb8-630c-455b-b382-1912aff0e3ef&token=NjdhNzliYjgtNjMw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67a79bb8-630c-455b-b382-1912aff0e3ef</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 20:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Apollo Tyres Ltd has announced its un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a profit before tax of Rs. 11,213.20 million for the quarter and Rs. 4,075.68 million for the nine months period. The Board of Directors has approved a capacity expansion at the company&apos;s plant in Andhra Pradesh for Passenger Car Radial (PCR) &amp; Truck Bus Radial (TBR) with an investment of approximately Rs. 5,810 crore. The company also declared an interim dividend of Rs. 3.50 per equity share for FY26.</p><ul><li>Apollo Tyres Ltd reported a profit before tax of Rs. 11,213.20 million for Q3 and Rs. 4,075.68 million for the nine months period ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s Board of Directors approved a capacity expansion at the company&apos;s plant in Andhra Pradesh for PCR &amp; TBR with an investment of approximately Rs. 5,810 crore.</li><li>The expansion is expected to add ~3.7 Mn Tyres per annum for PCR and ~1.3 Mn Tyres per annum for TBR.</li><li>The company has also declared an interim dividend of Rs. 3.50 per equity share for FY26.</li><li>The record date for determining the entitlement of the shareholders for the payment of Interim Dividend is February 10, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e6a6e66a-daf8-4b19-9b87-80198cfebb3c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: APOLLO TYRES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>