<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:57:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[UHZAVERI] U. H. Zaveri Ltd Approves Unaudited Standalone Financial Results for Q3 &amp; Nine Months Ended 31st December, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=U.+H.+Zaveri+Ltd&title=U.+H.+Zaveri+Ltd+Approves+Unaudited+Standalone+Financial+Results+for+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Ended+31st+December%2C+2025&newsId=79cceded-d6da-4b30-a5aa-f606d0b18568&token=NzljY2VkZWQtZDZk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79cceded-d6da-4b30-a5aa-f606d0b18568</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>U. H. Zaveri Ltd, a company with script code 541338, has announced its unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The results were reviewed and recommended by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors in a meeting held on 12th February, 2026. The closure period for dealing in the securities of the Company for Designated Persons and their immediate relatives will end 48 hours after the announcement of these results.</p><ul><li>U. H. Zaveri Ltd has announced its unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025.</li><li>The results were reviewed and recommended by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors in a meeting held on 12th February, 2026.</li><li>The closure period for dealing in the securities of the Company for Designated Persons and their immediate relatives will end 48 hours after the announcement of these results.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/387ecc5a-06af-4855-a120-aca5cb1e0247.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: U. H. Zaveri Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SOFTTECH] Softtech Engineers Ltd Reports Q3 and December 2025 Results with 304.40% Profit Before Tax</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Softtech+Engineers+Ltd&title=Softtech+Engineers+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+December+2025+Results+with+304.40%25+Profit+Before+Tax&newsId=4a1bfc38-f4c2-422c-b823-58db372118c5&token=NGExYmZjMzgtZjRj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a1bfc38-f4c2-422c-b823-58db372118c5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:54:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Softtech Engineers Ltd has reported its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, with a 304.40% increase in profit before tax compared to the same period last year. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 9,335.78 lakhs, with a total income of 9,626.37 lakhs for the quarter. The company&apos;s profit after tax is 227.42 lakhs, and earnings per share of face value Rs. 10/- per share is 1.64. The consolidated financial results include the financial results of nine subsidiaries.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations of 9,335.78 lakhs for the quarter</li><li>Profit before tax increased by 304.40% compared to the same period last year</li><li>Profit after tax of 227.42 lakhs for the quarter</li><li>Earnings per share of face value Rs. 10/- per share is 1.64</li><li>Consolidated financial results include the financial results of nine subsidiaries</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/18ed7b9b-95be-415c-861d-904e54694eee.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Softtech Engineers Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STARLENT] Starlineps Enterprises Ltd. Approves Q3 Results, MoU with DNB Textiles, and Writes Off Capital Work-in-Progress</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Starlineps+Enterprises+Ltd&title=Starlineps+Enterprises+Ltd.+Approves+Q3+Results%2C+MoU+with+DNB+Textiles%2C+and+Writes+Off+Capital+Work-in-Progress&newsId=91dcb8db-1a97-4f2a-8603-25f1e1b6a313&token=OTFkY2I4ZGItMWE5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">91dcb8db-1a97-4f2a-8603-25f1e1b6a313</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:52:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Starlineps Enterprises Ltd. has announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at ₹ 3685.95 lakh for the quarter and ₹ 7334.82 lakh for the nine months period. The Board also approved a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with DNB Textiles Private Limited for a loan up to ₹ 10 Crore. Additionally, the Board decided to write off the Capital work-in-progress of ₹ 529.36 Lacs. The meeting was held on 12th February 2026.</p><ul><li>Starlineps Enterprises Ltd. approves unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at ₹ 3685.95 lakh for the quarter and ₹ 7334.82 lakh for the nine months period.</li><li>Board approves MoU with DNB Textiles Private Limited for a loan up to ₹ 10 Crore.</li><li>Board decides to write off the Capital work-in-progress of ₹ 529.36 Lacs.</li><li>The meeting was held on 12th February 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a4f7fad6-e755-47b7-a762-682091eb4409.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Starlineps Enterprises Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KELLTONTEC] Kellton Tech Solutions Ltd. Approves Unaudited Financial Results for Q4 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kellton+Tech+Solutions+Ltd.&title=Kellton+Tech+Solutions+Ltd.+Approves+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q4+2025&newsId=06cb49f4-b583-426f-a356-802981f91d4b&token=MDZjYjQ5ZjQtYjU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06cb49f4-b583-426f-a356-802981f91d4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:49:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kellton Tech Solutions Ltd. has announced the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The Board of Directors approved the results during their meeting on February 12, 2026. The company&apos;s management is responsible for the preparation of the financial statements in accordance with Ind AS 34, Interim Financial Reporting, and other accounting principles generally accepted in India.</p><ul><li>The Board approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The results were prepared in accordance with Ind AS 34, Interim Financial Reporting, and other applicable accounting standards.</li><li>The review was conducted in accordance with the Standards on Review Engagements (SRE) 2410 issued by the ICAI.</li><li>The review provided moderate assurance that the statement is free from material misstatement.</li><li>The trading window for dealing in the securities of the company by the designated persons and their immediate relatives will reopen 48 hours after the announcement of the unaudited financial results.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8d78198d-bcb0-477f-a352-49001e3c1434.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kellton Tech Solutions Ltd. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZENITHHE] Zenith Healthcare Ltd Announces Q3 Results for FY 2025-2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ZENITH+HEALTH+CARE+LTD.&title=Zenith+Healthcare+Ltd+Announces+Q3+Results+for+FY+2025-2026&newsId=4372a1cb-4830-49b7-b7ad-3f6f390909f0&token=NDM3MmExY2ItNDgz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4372a1cb-4830-49b7-b7ad-3f6f390909f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:47:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Zenith Healthcare Ltd has announced its un-audited financial results for the quarter ended on 31st December 2025. The total income for the quarter stands at INR 252.5 lacs, with a net profit of INR 539.22 lacs. The company operates in the Pharmaceuticals Trading segment. The financial results have been reviewed by the Board of Directors and the Statutory Auditors.</p><ul><li>Total income for the quarter is INR 252.5 lacs</li><li>Net profit for the quarter is INR 539.22 lacs</li><li>The company operates in the Pharmaceuticals Trading segment</li><li>Financial results have been reviewed by the Board of Directors</li><li>Statutory Auditors have carried out limited review of the financial results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a124b8dc-4919-4381-bfa9-2f686a1c3d81.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ZENITH HEALTH CARE LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZSARACOM] Saraswati Commercial India Ltd. Approves Un-Audited Standalone &amp; Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 &amp; Nine Months Ended 31st December, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SARASWATI+COMMERCIAL+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Saraswati+Commercial+India+Ltd.+Approves+Un-Audited+Standalone+%26+Consolidated+Financial+Results+for+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Ended+31st+December%2C+2025&newsId=402d77be-3107-40ad-89b9-a77c1d72aaa9&token=NDAyZDc3YmUtMzEw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">402d77be-3107-40ad-89b9-a77c1d72aaa9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:47:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Saraswati Commercial India Ltd. has considered and approved the Un-Audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The results will be published in newspapers and uploaded on the website of the company and the stock exchanges where the equity shares of the company are listed. The meeting of the Board of Directors was commenced at 4:30 p.m. and concluded at 5.45 p.m. on 12th February, 2026.</p><ul><li>Un-Audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December, 2025 approved.</li><li>Results will be published in newspapers and uploaded on the website of the company and the stock exchanges.</li><li>Meeting of the Board of Directors held on 12th February, 2026 from 4:30 p.m. to 5.45 p.m.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9db4c7f0-d338-4338-9248-47f860316569.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SARASWATI COMMERCIAL (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AMBALALSA] Ambalal Sarabhai Enterprises Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AMBALAL+SARABHAI+ENTERPRISES+LTD.&title=Ambalal+Sarabhai+Enterprises+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025&newsId=c95d6c2e-ca37-4f31-a0c5-57bc24ce7d38&token=Yzk1ZDZjMmUtY2Ez</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c95d6c2e-ca37-4f31-a0c5-57bc24ce7d38</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ambalal Sarabhai Enterprises Ltd has reported its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at Rs. 13,137.17 lakhs for the quarter and Rs. 19,618.53 lakhs for the nine months. The net profit for the quarter is Rs. 1,130.21 lakhs and for the nine months is Rs. 1,072.55 lakhs. The company has also reported an exceptional item of Rs. 81.99 lakhs due to the New Labour Codes implementation.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter is Rs. 13,137.17 lakhs</li><li>Revenue from operations for the nine months is Rs. 19,618.53 lakhs</li><li>Net profit for the quarter is Rs. 1,130.21 lakhs</li><li>Net profit for the nine months is Rs. 1,072.55 lakhs</li><li>Exceptional item of Rs. 81.99 lakhs due to New Labour Codes implementation</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8d997f39-5f42-4d5e-a3a1-35a05dcba1d3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AMBALAL SARABHAI ENTERPRISES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NPST] Network People Services Technologies Clarifies Utilization of Preferential Allotment Proceeds</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Network+People+Services+Technologies+Ltd&title=Network+People+Services+Technologies+Clarifies+Utilization+of+Preferential+Allotment+Proceeds&newsId=c2089fc5-24f8-4e02-8d9e-16f9f0193f99&token=YzIwODlmYzUtMjRm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c2089fc5-24f8-4e02-8d9e-16f9f0193f99</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Network People Services Technologies Ltd. has issued a clarification addressing certain observations made by the Monitoring Agency report regarding the utilization of a portion of the proceeds from the Preferential Allotment. The company clarified that the allotment was carried out in compliance with the SEBI ICDR Regulations, the Companies Act, 2013, and applicable Stock Exchange regulations. The undisclosed utilization was for general corporate purposes, including office rent and employee salaries, which are essential operational costs. The management confirmed that there has been no diversion or misutilisation of funds, and the utilisation is aligned with the intent of the objects stated in the Notice of Preferential Allotment and the scope of &apos;General Corporate Purpose&apos; under SEBI ICDR Regulations.</p><ul><li>Network People Services Technologies Ltd. addresses observations made by the Monitoring Agency report regarding the utilization of Preferential Allotment proceeds.</li><li>The company clarified that the allotment was carried out in compliance with relevant regulations.</li><li>Undisclosed utilization was for general corporate purposes, including office rent and employee salaries.</li><li>The management confirmed that there has been no diversion or misutilisation of funds.</li><li>The utilisation is aligned with the intent of the objects stated in the Notice of Preferential Allotment and the scope of &apos;General Corporate Purpose&apos; under SEBI ICDR Regulations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2bf757d3-314a-4015-9f1f-f375aec4f472.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Network People Services Technologies Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IRCTC] Indian Railway Catering and Tourism Corporation Ltd Declares 2nd Interim Dividend of €3.50 per share for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Indian+Railway+Catering+and+Tourism+Corporation+Ltd&title=Indian+Railway+Catering+and+Tourism+Corporation+Ltd+Declares+2nd+Interim+Dividend+of+%E2%82%AC3.50+per+share+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=e992e079-4d7f-42bc-9a97-8a0366cb1f7a&token=ZTk5MmUwNzktNGQ3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e992e079-4d7f-42bc-9a97-8a0366cb1f7a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indian Railway Catering and Tourism Corporation Ltd (IRCTC) announced its un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at ₹ 340,624.11 lakhs, ₹ 375,514.36 lakhs, and ₹ 467,477.10 lakhs for the respective periods. IRCTC declared a 2nd interim dividend of €3.50 per share for the financial year 2025-26, with Friday, February 20, 2026, as the record date. The company&apos;s net profit after tax from continuing operations is ₹ 106,679.47 lakhs, ₹ 95,670.90 lakhs, and ₹ 131,465.61 lakhs for the respective periods.</p><ul><li>Un-audited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended on December 31, 2025, approved</li><li>Declared 2nd interim dividend of €3.50 per share for FY 2025-26</li><li>Revenue from operations stands at ₹ 340,624.11 lakhs, ₹ 375,514.36 lakhs, and ₹ 467,477.10 lakhs for the respective periods</li><li>Net profit after tax from continuing operations is ₹ 106,679.47 lakhs, ₹ 95,670.90 lakhs, and ₹ 131,465.61 lakhs for the respective periods</li><li>The financial results have been prepared in accordance with Indian Accounting Standards (Ind-AS)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/57a31c04-cd88-4b69-b19a-d8fd0887ff3b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Indian Railway Catering and Tourism Corporation Ltd | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CUPID] Cupid Limited Reconstitutes Board Committees</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CUPID+LTD.-%24&title=Cupid+Limited+Reconstitutes+Board+Committees&newsId=a19ea001-17bd-4521-933c-95692d6911c2&token=YTE5ZWEwMDEtMTdi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a19ea001-17bd-4521-933c-95692d6911c2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 12:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cupid Limited, a company with the CIN No.: L25193MH1993PLC0O70846, has reconstituted its Board Committees. The Nomination Committee now includes Mr. Rajinder Singh Loona and Mr. Thallapaka Venkateswara Rao as Non-Executive &amp; Independent Directors. The Remuneration Committee comprises Mrs. Rajni Mishra as a Non-Executive &amp; Independent Director. The Corporate Social Responsibility Committee is chaired by Mr. Aditya Kumar Halwasiya, the Chairman and Managing Director, with Mr. Akshay Kumar as a Non-Executive &amp; Independent Director. The Committee also includes Mr. Ajay Kumar Halwasiya, an Executive Director. The reconstitution was passed by circulation on February 12, 2026.</p><ul><li>Cupid Limited reconstitutes its Board Committees</li><li>Mr. Rajinder Singh Loona and Mr. Thallapaka Venkateswara Rao appointed as Nomination Committee members</li><li>Mrs. Rajni Mishra appointed as a Remuneration Committee member</li><li>Mr. Aditya Kumar Halwasiya chairs the Corporate Social Responsibility Committee</li><li>Mr. Akshay Kumar and Mr. Ajay Kumar Halwasiya also part of the Corporate Social Responsibility Committee</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/643f8435-b39f-4820-a05e-d48d40606e1c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CUPID LTD.-$ | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>