<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 01:56:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[AVEER] Promoter Group Member Rajkumar Hukmichand Chordia Acquires 2,26,087 Shares of Aveer Foods Ltd. Upon Exercise of Warrants</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Aveer+Foods+Ltd&title=Promoter+Group+Member+Rajkumar+Hukmichand+Chordia+Acquires+2%2C26%2C087+Shares+of+Aveer+Foods+Ltd.+Upon+Exercise+of+Warrants&newsId=db667fa3-df38-47f9-8968-7f439b2fa20f&token=ZGI2NjdmYTMtZGYz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db667fa3-df38-47f9-8968-7f439b2fa20f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 00:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In a recent development, Mr. Rajkumar Hukmichand Chordia, a member of the promoter group and acquirer, has acquired 2,26,087 equity shares of Aveer Foods Limited. This acquisition took place on 6th February 2025 upon exercise of warrants originally allotted to him on 20th March 2025. This acquisition has been reported to the Exchange as per the format prescribed by SEBI under Regulation 29(2) of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</p><ul><li>Mr. Rajkumar Hukmichand Chordia, a member of the promoter group and acquirer, has acquired 2,26,087 equity shares of Aveer Foods Limited.</li><li>The acquisition took place on 6th February 2025 upon exercise of warrants originally allotted to him on 20th March 2025.</li><li>This acquisition has been reported to the Exchange as per the format prescribed by SEBI under Regulation 29(2) of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</li><li>Mr. Rajkumar Hukmichand Chordia&apos;s shareholding increased from 38.47% to 43.52% post-acquisition.</li><li>This acquisition is a significant development for Aveer Foods Limited and its shareholders.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/db542116-4080-4d17-9c73-a3f14bbe8642.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Aveer Foods Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAFARIND] Safari Industries India Ltd. Announces Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SAFARI+INDUSTRIES+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Safari+Industries+India+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=d1242a02-ce84-47a6-88f5-57c3e95c84db&token=ZDEyNDJhMDItY2U4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d1242a02-ce84-47a6-88f5-57c3e95c84db</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 23:46:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Safari Industries India Ltd. met on 10th February 2026 and approved the un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 1,769.66 crores for the nine-month period. The results will be uploaded on the company&apos;s website and published in newspapers as per Listing Regulations. The meeting commenced at 11:00 am (IST) and concluded at 2:30 pm (IST).</p><ul><li>Safari Industries India Ltd. announces Q3 and nine months financial results for 2025.</li><li>Revenue from operations for the nine-month period stands at 1,769.66 crores.</li><li>The results are approved by the Board of Directors in a meeting held on 10th February 2026.</li><li>The results will be made available on the company&apos;s website and published in newspapers as per Listing Regulations.</li><li>The meeting of the Board of Directors commenced at 11:00 am (IST) and concluded at 2:30 pm (IST).</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2359b006-fa0e-41ad-9f49-e781434e9347.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SAFARI INDUSTRIES (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[REGAAL] Regaal Resources Ltd Receives Show Cause Notice from Registrar of Companies, Kolkata</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Regaal+Resources+Ltd&title=Regaal+Resources+Ltd+Receives+Show+Cause+Notice+from+Registrar+of+Companies%2C+Kolkata&newsId=396cb5e9-e0ee-4d5b-9d36-78358974d259&token=Mzk2Y2I1ZTktZTBl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">396cb5e9-e0ee-4d5b-9d36-78358974d259</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Regaal Resources Ltd has received a show cause notice from the Registrar of Companies (ROC), Kolkata, dated 9th February 2026, for E-Adjudication of Default under Section 450 read with Section 454 and 178 (8) of the Companies Act, 2013. The company has filed a suo-moto application under Section 450 and 178 (8) of the Companies Act for Adjudication of Offences for contravention of several rules including delay in constitution of Audit Committee and Nomination and Remuneration Committee, non-attachment of valuation report of Registered valuer, and allotment of equity shares in physical mode instead of Demat mode. The ROC has proposed a penalty of Rs.22,00,000/- on the company and Rs 12,00,000/- on the officers in default. The company is examining the notice and will take appropriate steps including submission of a reply.</p><ul><li>Regaal Resources Ltd received a show cause notice from the Registrar of Companies (ROC), Kolkata for E-Adjudication of Default.</li><li>The company has filed a suo-moto application under Section 450 and 178 (8) of the Companies Act for Adjudication of Offences.</li><li>The proposed penalties are Rs.22,00,000/- on the company and Rs 12,00,000/- on the officers in default.</li><li>The company is examining the notice and will take appropriate steps including submission of a reply.</li><li>The notice pertains to several rule contraventions including delay in constitution of Audit Committee and Nomination and Remuneration Committee, non-attachment of valuation report of Registered valuer, and allotment of equity shares in physical mode instead of Demat mode.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4ef6f5cc-a1c6-4a1b-b1a9-1433b6925a2c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Regaal Resources Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INRADIA] India Radiators Ltd. Announces Equity Shareholders Meeting for Scheme of Amalgamation on March 13, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDIA+RADIATORS+LTD.&title=India+Radiators+Ltd.+Announces+Equity+Shareholders+Meeting+for+Scheme+of+Amalgamation+on+March+13%2C+2026&newsId=066418ca-1bf4-43b7-be5d-6b5497781537&token=MDY2NDE4Y2EtMWJm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">066418ca-1bf4-43b7-be5d-6b5497781537</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:35:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>India Radiators Ltd. has announced a meeting of equity shareholders to be held on March 13, 2026, at 10.00 A.M. (IST) through video conference and/or other audio and visual means. The meeting is being conducted in accordance with the directions of the Hon’ble National Company Law Tribunal (Court — I), Chennai Bench in the matter of the Scheme of Amalgamation with Mercantile Ventures Limited. The notice, explanatory statement, and accompanying documents have been dispatched to equity shareholders through electronic mode and are also available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>India Radiators Ltd. to merge with Mercantile Ventures Limited</li><li>Meeting of equity shareholders to be held on March 13, 2026</li><li>Meeting to be conducted through video conference and/or other audio and visual means</li><li>Notice and explanatory statement dispatched to equity shareholders through electronic mode</li><li>Documents available on the company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/df4163eb-f9b3-447a-9a52-cf72ca86e71f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDIA RADIATORS LTD. | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[REGAAL] Regaal Resources Ltd Faces Penalties Under Companies Act, 2013: No Material Impact on Financial Operations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Regaal+Resources+Ltd&title=Regaal+Resources+Ltd+Faces+Penalties+Under+Companies+Act%2C+2013%3A+No+Material+Impact+on+Financial+Operations&newsId=873fffe8-5950-4be6-b6ec-3d310a7bec8a&token=ODczZmZmZTgtNTk1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">873fffe8-5950-4be6-b6ec-3d310a7bec8a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Regaal Resources Ltd has received an order for adjudication of penalties under Section 454 of the Companies Act, 2013 from the Registrar of Companies, Kolkata. The order, dated 9th February 2026, is for the violation of Section 450 of the Companies Act, 2013 due to the filing of Return of Allotment (Form PAS-3) without attaching the Valuation report of a Registered valuer as required by Rule 12(7) of the Companies (Prospectus and Allotment of Securities) Rules, 2014. The company and its officers in default have been imposed penalties of Rs. 20,00,000 and Rs. 5,00,000 respectively. However, the company has stated that there is no material impact on its financial operations or other activities.</p><ul><li>Regaal Resources Ltd faces penalties under the Companies Act, 2013</li><li>Order issued by the Registrar of Companies, Kolkata for violation of Section 450</li><li>Penalties imposed on the company and its officers: Rs. 20,00,000 and Rs. 5,00,000 respectively</li><li>Violation pertains to the filing of Return of Allotment (Form PAS-3) without a Valuation report</li><li>No material impact on financial operations or other activities of the company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1d64ac44-2663-4b23-80a9-dcad78f68f3b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Regaal Resources Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SICALLOG] Sical Logistics Board Meeting Rescheduled to February 12, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SICAL+LOGISTICS+LTD.&title=Sical+Logistics+Board+Meeting+Rescheduled+to+February+12%2C+2026&newsId=09e21aec-2031-42a4-bfd2-6d2b5994fcec&token=MDllMjFhZWMtMjAz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09e21aec-2031-42a4-bfd2-6d2b5994fcec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sical Logistics Limited has informed the exchange that the board meeting scheduled for February 10, 2026, has been postponed and rescheduled to February 12, 2026. The meeting was initially scheduled to consider, discuss, and decide various matters in connection with the Rights Issue, including the specific terms of the Rights Issue. However, due to the Stock Exchanges still considering the Draft Letter of Offer, the Board has decided to reschedule its meeting. The Rights Issue is for an amount not exceeding Rs. 11,000 Lakhs, and the Company had already submitted an application for in-principle approval for the Rights Issue to the Stock Exchanges.</p><ul><li>Sical Logistics Limited board meeting rescheduled to February 12, 2026</li><li>The meeting was initially scheduled for February 10, 2026, to consider various matters in connection with the Rights Issue</li><li>The Rights Issue is for an amount not exceeding Rs. 11,000 Lakhs</li><li>Application for in-principle approval for the Rights Issue submitted to the Stock Exchanges</li><li>The Stock Exchanges are still considering the Draft Letter of Offer</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f245197f-61c7-422b-b641-8cedff6ae444.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SICAL LOGISTICS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SICALLOG] Sical Logistics Postpones Board Meeting to February 12, 2026 for Rights Issue Discussion</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SICAL+LOGISTICS+LTD.&title=Sical+Logistics+Postpones+Board+Meeting+to+February+12%2C+2026+for+Rights+Issue+Discussion&newsId=f7c5b9bd-f01d-4702-ab58-d2129bf11c30&token=ZjdjNWI5YmQtZjAx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7c5b9bd-f01d-4702-ab58-d2129bf11c30</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sical Logistics Limited has informed the exchange that the board meeting scheduled for February 10, 2026 has been postponed to February 12, 2026. The meeting was initially scheduled to consider, discuss and decide various matters in connection with the Rights Issue, including the specific terms of the Rights Issue. However, due to the Stock Exchanges still considering the Draft Letter of Offer, the Board has decided to reschedule its meeting.</p><ul><li>Sical Logistics postpones board meeting to February 12, 2026</li><li>The meeting was initially scheduled to discuss the Rights Issue</li><li>The postponement is due to the Stock Exchanges still considering the Draft Letter of Offer</li><li>The Rights Issue is for an amount not exceeding Rs. 11,000 Lakhs</li><li>The record date, timing of the Rights Issue and other terms and conditions are yet to be decided</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2f0d465d-584b-4f4a-93a8-174c9a07ae14.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SICAL LOGISTICS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RCL] Radhagobind Commercial Ltd to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Radhagobind+Commercial+Ltd&title=Radhagobind+Commercial+Ltd+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+2025&newsId=ce6600bc-c924-4619-92f8-3b0111437735&token=Y2U2NjAwYmMtYzky</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce6600bc-c924-4619-92f8-3b0111437735</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 20:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Radhagobind Commercial Ltd has announced a meeting on 14th February 2026 to consider and approve the unaudited Financial Results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The meeting will be held at the corporate office in Kochi, Kerala. The Resolution Professional, Mr. Najeeb T P, will convene and preside over the meeting. This intimation is in compliance with the SEBI (LODR) Regulations.</p><ul><li>Radhagobind Commercial Ltd to consider and approve unaudited Financial Results for Q3 2025</li><li>Meeting to be held on 14th February 2026 at the corporate office in Kochi, Kerala</li><li>Resolution Professional, Mr. Najeeb T P, to convene and preside over the meeting</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9dfd318d-5882-45fd-ab39-a53a0922eff1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Radhagobind Commercial Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INRADIA] India Radiators Ltd. Announces Equity Shareholders Meeting for Scheme of Amalgamation on March 13, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDIA+RADIATORS+LTD.&title=India+Radiators+Ltd.+Announces+Equity+Shareholders+Meeting+for+Scheme+of+Amalgamation+on+March+13%2C+2026&newsId=97a19d15-ef7b-4990-b3eb-c2d53f80856e&token=OTdhMTlkMTUtZWY3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97a19d15-ef7b-4990-b3eb-c2d53f80856e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>India Radiators Ltd. has announced a meeting of equity shareholders to be held on March 13, 2026, at 10.00 A.M. (IST) through video conference and/or other audio and visual means. The meeting is convened as per the directions of the Hon’ble National Company Law Tribunal (Court — I), Chennai Bench in the matter of the Scheme of Amalgamation with Mercantile Ventures Limited. The notice of the meeting, explanatory statement, and accompanying documents are available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>India Radiators Ltd. and Mercantile Ventures Limited are planning a Scheme of Amalgamation.</li><li>The meeting is convened as per the directions of the Hon’ble National Company Law Tribunal (Court — I), Chennai Bench.</li><li>The meeting will be held through video conference and/or other audio and visual means.</li><li>The notice of the meeting, explanatory statement, and accompanying documents are available on the company&apos;s website.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d8b360b5-8f7a-49a8-93cb-26d820298ecc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDIA RADIATORS LTD. | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RSYSTEMINT] R Systems Reports Robust FY2025 Performance with 17.8% YoY Growth in Normalized EBITDA</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=R+Systems+International+Limited&title=R+Systems+Reports+Robust+FY2025+Performance+with+17.8%25+YoY+Growth+in+Normalized+EBITDA&newsId=4163a7d9-c086-48bd-a203-c74210559f87&token=NDE2M2E3ZDktYzA4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4163a7d9-c086-48bd-a203-c74210559f87</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>R Systems International Limited, a leading digital product engineering company, reported a robust financial performance for the year ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s consolidated revenue was Rs. 19,582 mn (US$ 224.8 mn), representing a YoY growth of 12.4% in INR terms and 8.0% in US$ terms. The Adj. EBITDA was Rs. 3,427 mn (US$ 39.3 mn), reflecting a YoY growth of 17.8%. The Adj. net profit after taxes was Rs. 1,936 mn (US$ 22.2 mn), indicating a YoY growth of 24.6%. The company also reported a YoY growth of 27.0% in Adj. EBITDA and 27.4% in Adj. net profit after taxes for the quarter ended December 31, 2025.</p><ul><li>Revenue of Rs. 19,582 mn (US$ 224.8 mn) with a YoY growth of 12.4% in INR terms and 8.0% in US$ terms</li><li>Adj. EBITDA of Rs. 3,427 mn (US$ 39.3 mn) i.e. 17.5%</li><li>Adj. Net profit after taxes of Rs. 1,936 mn (US$ 22.2 mn) with a YoY growth of 24.6%</li><li>Q4 revenue of Rs 555 crores and an EBITDA margin of 18.3%</li><li>Successful completion of the acquisition of Novigo Solutions, enhancing capabilities in automation and Agentic AI</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/87c95ae5-521f-4a7e-a618-dcecf66475af.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: R Systems International Limited | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>