<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:38:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[GAYAPROJ] Gayatri Projects Ltd Announces 35th AGM for FY 2023-24 on 27th February 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GAYATRI+PROJECTS+LTD.&title=Gayatri+Projects+Ltd+Announces+35th+AGM+for+FY+2023-24+on+27th+February+2026&newsId=92b181a4-e902-4064-9643-95b77609b352&token=OTJiMTgxYTQtZTkw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">92b181a4-e902-4064-9643-95b77609b352</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:37:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gayatri Projects Ltd has announced the notice for its 35th Annual General Meeting (AGM) for the financial year 2023-24. The AGM is scheduled to be held on 27th February 2026 at 3.00 PM through Video Conference (VC) / Other Audio Visual Means (OAVM). The annual report for FY 2023-24 along with the notice was sent to the shareholders on 5th February 2026 through electronic mode on their registered e-mail ids. The AGM will be held for 44353 shareholders who have valid email ids.</p><ul><li>Gayatri Projects Ltd announces 35th AGM for FY 2023-24</li><li>AGM scheduled for 27th February 2026 at 3.00 PM</li><li>Meeting to be held through Video Conference (VC) / Other Audio Visual Means (OAVM)</li><li>Annual report for FY 2023-24 sent to shareholders on 5th February 2026</li><li>AGM notification sent to 44353 shareholders with valid email ids</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a50a6fb8-eb18-459d-af34-d32f2d5125ef.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GAYATRI PROJECTS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GAYAPROJ] Gayatri Projects Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q3 Results of FY 2025-2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GAYATRI+PROJECTS+LTD.&title=Gayatri+Projects+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+Results+of+FY+2025-2026&newsId=5eaae7cc-3d44-4c98-98cf-092db80210d0&token=NWVhYWU3Y2MtM2Q0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5eaae7cc-3d44-4c98-98cf-092db80210d0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gayatri Projects Ltd, a prominent player in the industry, has announced a board meeting scheduled for 14th February 2026. The primary agenda of the meeting is to consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated Financial Results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. This development is in accordance with Regulation 29 and 33 of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Gayatri Projects Ltd has scheduled a Board Meeting on 14th February 2026.</li><li>The meeting aims to consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated Financial Results for Q3 FY 2025-2026.</li><li>The announcement is in compliance with Regulation 29 and 33 of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/aff1cfa1-8a7d-4c1a-b0a4-a39824805751.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GAYATRI PROJECTS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DIFFNKG] Diffusion Engineers Ltd to Participate in Dolat Capital Corporate Conference on 18th February, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Diffusion+Engineers+Ltd&title=Diffusion+Engineers+Ltd+to+Participate+in+Dolat+Capital+Corporate+Conference+on+18th+February%2C+2026&newsId=4a6db682-3e60-4c56-b7e9-86596d4be23f&token=NGE2ZGI2ODItM2U2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a6db682-3e60-4c56-b7e9-86596d4be23f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Diffusion Engineers Ltd has announced its participation in the Dolat Capital Corporate Conference scheduled for 18th February, 2026 at Grand Hyatt, Santacruz East. The conference is being organized by Dolat Capital. The management of the company will participate in the event, discussing generally available information and not any Unpublished Price Sensitive Information as per the company&apos;s Code of Practices and Procedures for Fair Disclosure of Unpublished Price Sensitive Information.</p><ul><li>Diffusion Engineers Ltd to participate in Dolat Capital Corporate Conference on 18th February, 2026</li><li>The conference is organized by Dolat Capital at Grand Hyatt, Santacruz East</li><li>The management of the company will discuss generally available information</li><li>The discussion will not include any Unpublished Price Sensitive Information</li><li>The event is in line with the company&apos;s Code of Practices and Procedures for Fair Disclosure of Unpublished Price Sensitive Information</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/48197443-c2ab-4f41-9b1d-5d3b31b56b59.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Diffusion Engineers Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SPECFOOD] Spectrum Foods Ltd to Approve Q3 Results on Feb 13, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SPECTRUM+FOODS+LTD.&title=Spectrum+Foods+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+Results+on+Feb+13%2C+2026&newsId=580c86d9-a7c2-4231-8f29-4415f2bc69a7&token=NTgwYzg2ZDktYTdj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">580c86d9-a7c2-4231-8f29-4415f2bc69a7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:34:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Spectrum Foods Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 13, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the third quarter ended on December 31, 2025. The meeting will also take on record the Limited Review Report given by the Statutory Auditors for the same period. Other corporate matters may also be discussed.</p><ul><li>Spectrum Foods Ltd to approve Q3 results on Feb 13, 2026</li><li>Unaudited financial results for the quarter ended on Dec 31, 2025 to be considered</li><li>Limited Review Report by Statutory Auditors for Q3 2025 to be taken on record</li><li>Other corporate matters may also be discussed</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8dcb9a9c-9f20-4975-add7-a6f6150ea108.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SPECTRUM FOODS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SARDAEN] Sarda Energy &amp; Minerals Q3 FY26 Results: Consolidated PAT Up 59% to Rs. 954 Cr</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SARDA+ENERGY+%26+MINERALS+LTD.-%24&title=Sarda+Energy+%26+Minerals+Q3+FY26+Results%3A+Consolidated+PAT+Up+59%25+to+Rs.+954+Cr&newsId=ec784a13-baa3-4bb1-92c7-fda74d87f08e&token=ZWM3ODRhMTMtYmFh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ec784a13-baa3-4bb1-92c7-fda74d87f08e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:34:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Sarda Energy &amp; Minerals Limited announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s Q3 FY26 performance showed a Consolidated PAT increase of 59% to Rs. 954 Cr, revenue growth of 32% YoY to Rs. 4,669 Cr, and EBITDA growth of 53% YoY to Rs. 1,672 Cr. The Energy segment continued to contribute significantly to profitability, and the addition of two new PPAs improved earnings visibility. The company remains focused on disciplined capital allocation, harnessing operational efficiencies, and strengthening integration across businesses for sustainable and profitable expansion.</p><ul><li>Consolidated PAT up 59% to Rs. 954 Cr in Q3 FY26</li><li>Revenue increased by 32% YoY to Rs. 4,669 Cr in Q3 FY26</li><li>EBITDA grew 53% YoY to Rs. 1,672 Cr in Q3 FY26</li><li>Two new PPAs signed, improving medium-term revenue visibility</li><li>Robust balance sheet with low leverage, providing financial flexibility for expansion and growth initiatives</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a252553a-a96c-4b2e-a4b2-fb6889611765.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SARDA ENERGY & MINERALS LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HARIOMPIPE] Hariom Pipe Industries Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Unaudited Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Hariom+Pipe+Industries+Ltd&title=Hariom+Pipe+Industries+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=1380d7e8-9f08-4405-b75f-74e382659ac9&token=MTM4MGQ3ZTgtOWYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1380d7e8-9f08-4405-b75f-74e382659ac9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:33:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hariom Pipe Industries Ltd has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The Board of Directors approved the results in a meeting held on February 07, 2026. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 36,285.39 lakhs for the quarter and 149.47 lakhs for the nine-month period. The total income for the quarter is 36,434.85 lakhs and for the nine-month period is 22,919.55 lakhs. The net profit for the quarter is 3,096.73 lakhs and for the nine-month period is 33,586.74 lakhs. The earnings per share (EPS) for the quarter is 3.75 and for the nine-month period is 48.31.</p><ul><li>Hariom Pipe Industries Ltd has reported its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 36,285.39 lakhs for the quarter and 149.47 lakhs for the nine-month period.</li><li>The net profit for the quarter is 3,096.73 lakhs and for the nine-month period is 33,586.74 lakhs.</li><li>The earnings per share (EPS) for the quarter is 3.75 and for the nine-month period is 48.31.</li><li>The Board of Directors approved the results in a meeting held on February 07, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/594f0620-9108-4d02-942b-824b6b0a1065.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Hariom Pipe Industries Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EQUIPPP] Equippp Social Impact Technologies Ltd to Approve Q4 2025 Financial Results on Feb 12, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Equippp+Social+Impact+Technologies+Ltd&title=Equippp+Social+Impact+Technologies+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+2025+Financial+Results+on+Feb+12%2C+2026&newsId=8f1a525c-a448-4e4f-8982-2c52635eb35f&token=OGYxYTUyNWMtYTQ0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f1a525c-a448-4e4f-8982-2c52635eb35f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Equippp Social Impact Technologies Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 12, 2026, to consider and approve the Standalone and Consolidated Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will be held through Video Conferencing/ and other audio visual means. In accordance with the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, the Trading Window for dealing in the securities of the Company has been closed from January 01st, 2026 till the close of business hours of February 14th, 2026.</p><ul><li>Equippp Social Impact Technologies Ltd to approve Q4 2025 financial results on Feb 12, 2026</li><li>Board meeting scheduled on Feb 12, 2026 through Video Conferencing</li><li>Considering and approving Standalone and Consolidated Unaudited Financial Results for Q4 2025</li><li>Trading Window closed from Jan 01st, 2026 till Feb 14th, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2ca7e56b-72bb-4f22-bfce-769daa29f725.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Equippp Social Impact Technologies Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UTLINDS] UTL Industries Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=UTL+Industries+Limited&title=UTL+Industries+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025&newsId=d9f1e2db-1602-4bf5-9a41-329552cfad34&token=ZDlmMWUyZGItMTYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d9f1e2db-1602-4bf5-9a41-329552cfad34</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:32:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>UTL Industries Ltd has reported its unaudited financial results for the quarter and period ended on 31st December 2025. The company operates in two segments: Construction and Telecom Short Message Service (SMS). The total revenue for the nine months ended on 31st December 2025 is Rs. 15,98,00,000. The company&apos;s net profit for the quarter is Rs. 6,22,00,000 and for the nine months is Rs. 3,69,00,000. The financial figures have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>UTL Industries Ltd reported a net profit of Rs. 6,22,00,000 for the quarter ended on 31st December 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s net profit for the nine months ended on 31st December 2025 is Rs. 3,69,00,000.</li><li>The total revenue for the nine months ended on 31st December 2025 is Rs. 15,98,00,000.</li><li>The financial figures have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</li><li>The company operates in two segments: Construction and Telecom Short Message Service (SMS).</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/11b679f6-5c28-46cd-a248-6af325db2913.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: UTL Industries Limited | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LGBBROSLTD] LG Balakrishnan &amp; Bros Ltd Announces Q3 2025 Financial Results with Net Profit of INR 23.53 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=L.G.BALAKRISHNAN+%26+BROS.LTD.&title=LG+Balakrishnan+%26+Bros+Ltd+Announces+Q3+2025+Financial+Results+with+Net+Profit+of+INR+23.53+Crores&newsId=1998dbe2-d85c-4890-a6eb-63b3fd3306eb&token=MTk5OGRiZTItZDg1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1998dbe2-d85c-4890-a6eb-63b3fd3306eb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>LG Balakrishnan &amp; Bros Ltd, a company based in Coimbatore, Tamil Nadu, India, has announced its quarterly audited financial results for the period ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at INR 2,04,102.05 Lakhs, with a net profit of INR 23.53 Crores. The Board of Directors has also approved the re-appointment of Dr. Vinay Balaji Naidu as a Non-Executive Independent Director for a second term of five consecutive years.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations stands at INR 2,04,102.05 Lakhs</li><li>Net profit for the quarter is INR 23.53 Crores</li><li>Dr. Vinay Balaji Naidu recommended for re-appointment as Non-Executive Independent Director</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3fec5e3a-2678-42a3-b5b5-a4834a9cf4fd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: L.G.BALAKRISHNAN & BROS.LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AMINTAN] Amin Tannery Ltd: Promoter Veqarul Amin Pledges 29.88% Shares with SBICAP Trustee Company Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Amin+Tannery+Ltd&title=Amin+Tannery+Ltd%3A+Promoter+Veqarul+Amin+Pledges+29.88%25+Shares+with+SBICAP+Trustee+Company+Limited&newsId=9863c2e1-29d0-424f-ac37-37d61b306e2a&token=OTg2M2MyZTEtMjlk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9863c2e1-29d0-424f-ac37-37d61b306e2a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Pledge</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Exchange has received a disclosure under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011 from Amin Tannery Ltd. The disclosure is regarding the pledge of 3,22,62,439 equity shares by promoter Veqarul Amin with SBICAP Trustee Company Limited. This pledge represents 29.88% of the total diluted share capital and 28.88% of the total voting rights of the company. The shares were pledged on 6th February 2026. The total equity share capital of the company after the pledge is Rs. 10,79,73,360/- consisting of 10,79,73,360 equity shares of Re. 1/- each. Veqarul Amin holds 5,17,38,034 (47.92%) shares in the company, out of which 3,22,62,439 shares were pledged. Co-promoter Rumana Amin holds 1,17,23,400 (10.86%) shares, which were not pledged.</p><ul><li>Veqarul Amin pledges 29.88% shares with SBICAP Trustee Company Limited</li><li>Shares pledged on 6th February 2026</li><li>Total equity share capital after pledge is Rs. 10,79,73,360/- consisting of 10,79,73,360 equity shares</li><li>Veqarul Amin holds 47.92% shares, out of which 3,22,62,439 shares were pledged</li><li>Rumana Amin holds 10.86% shares, which were not pledged</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0469ECAB_9189_4545_8124_E15772B76572_175356.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Amin Tannery Ltd | Category: Pledge</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>