<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:56:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[RSWM] RSWM Ltd Announces Changes in Senior Management Personnel</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RSWM+LTD.&title=RSWM+Ltd+Announces+Changes+in+Senior+Management+Personnel&newsId=23c27e77-9fdf-4102-95ce-f7992fa57665&token=MjNjMjdlNzctOWZk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23c27e77-9fdf-4102-95ce-f7992fa57665</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:52:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>RSWM Ltd, a textile company, has announced changes in its senior management personnel. Shri Rajesh Singh, Business Head- Denim, has tendered his resignation, which will be effective from February 28, 2026. Shri Ashish Bhatnagar, Chief Marketing Officer — Domestic and Export Marketing (Denim), has been designated as Deputy Business Head- Denim and Senior Management Personnel of the Company, effective from March 1, 2026.</p><ul><li>Shri Rajesh Singh has resigned from his position as Business Head- Denim at RSWM Ltd.</li><li>His resignation will be effective from the close of business hours on February 28, 2026.</li><li>Shri Ashish Bhatnagar has been designated as Deputy Business Head- Denim and Senior Management Personnel of the Company.</li><li>Shri Bhatnagar has been associated with the Company since 2019 and presently holds the position of Chief Marketing Officer — Domestic and Export Marketing (Denim).</li><li>The changes are pursuant to the recommendation of the Nomination and Remuneration Committee and approval of the Board of Directors.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9cd43b37-b8b8-4601-a022-4b1ed14926d4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RSWM LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STARHFL] Star Housing Finance Ltd Changes Corporate Office Address</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Star+Housing+Finance+Ltd&title=Star+Housing+Finance+Ltd+Changes+Corporate+Office+Address&newsId=e38f356a-7438-4968-8ba1-e48e57a93ed4&token=ZTM4ZjM1NmEtNzQz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e38f356a-7438-4968-8ba1-e48e57a93ed4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:51:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Star Housing Finance Ltd has announced a change in its corporate office address. The new address will be Office No. 1222, 12™ Floor, The Summit Business Park, Near W.E. Highway Metro Station, Andheri East, Mumbai 400093, effective from February 23, 2026. The old address was Office no 221, 2nd Floor, Platinum Techno Park, Near Raghuleela Mall, Vashi, Thane, Navi Mumbai- 400703. All stakeholders are requested to update their records and the website accordingly.</p><ul><li>Star Housing Finance Ltd is changing its corporate office address.</li><li>The new address is Office No. 1222, 12™ Floor, The Summit Business Park, Near W.E. Highway Metro Station, Andheri East, Mumbai 400093.</li><li>The effective date of the change is February 23, 2026.</li><li>The old address was Office no 221, 2nd Floor, Platinum Techno Park, Near Raghuleela Mall, Vashi, Thane, Navi Mumbai- 400703.</li><li>Stakeholders are requested to update their records and the website.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9c67dbb5-d4bb-40f8-b5d9-ad5e532bebd1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Star Housing Finance Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MTARTECH] Promoter Madhavi Mitta Sells 18,000 Equity Shares of MTAR Technologies Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MTAR+Technologies+Ltd&title=Promoter+Madhavi+Mitta+Sells+18%2C000+Equity+Shares+of+MTAR+Technologies+Ltd&newsId=e1fccedc-4681-4b7d-bae3-ba101f833207&token=ZTFmY2NlZGMtNDY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e1fccedc-4681-4b7d-bae3-ba101f833207</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Sale</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Madhavi Mitta, a promoter of MTAR Technologies Ltd, has sold 18,000 equity shares on the market. This disclosure was made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. The sale took place from 20.02.2026 to 24.02.2026.</p><ul><li>Madhavi Mitta, a promoter of MTAR Technologies Ltd, sold 18,000 equity shares</li><li>The sale took place from 20.02.2026 to 24.02.2026</li><li>The shares were sold on the market</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0445B25F_D266_4EA8_912C_9032F5793B5A_180228.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MTAR Technologies Ltd | Category: Sale</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HINDALCO] Hindalco Industries&apos; Subsidiary, Novelis Inc., Enters Subscription Agreement with AV Minerals</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HINDALCO+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Hindalco+Industries%27+Subsidiary%2C+Novelis+Inc.%2C+Enters+Subscription+Agreement+with+AV+Minerals&newsId=51cebe50-65e4-472b-852a-6faf61e5fa7f&token=NTFjZWJlNTAtNjVl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">51cebe50-65e4-472b-852a-6faf61e5fa7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:47:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Hindalco Industries Ltd. announced that Novelis Inc., a wholly owned subsidiary, has entered into a subscription agreement with AV Minerals (Netherlands) N.V. AV Minerals, the sole shareholder of Novelis, agreed to purchase 13,33,333 common shares of Novelis for $19,99,99,950 at a price of $150 per share. This agreement is in accordance with Regulation 30 of the Securities Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. Novelis has filed a Form 8-K with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission, which can be accessed here. The information is also available on the websites of the Company and Novelis.</p><ul><li>Hindalco Industries&apos; subsidiary, Novelis Inc., enters into a subscription agreement with AV Minerals</li><li>AV Minerals to purchase 13,33,333 common shares of Novelis for $19,99,99,950</li><li>The agreement is in accordance with Regulation 30 of the Securities Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Novelis has filed a Form 8-K with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission</li><li>The information is also available on the websites of the Company and Novelis</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cae4b90f-c0d0-4499-bc86-03a27ee5a4e1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HINDALCO INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AFIL] Subhash Rathod &amp; Others Acquire Shares in Akme Fintrade (India) Ltd via Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Akme+Fintrade+%28India%29+Ltd&title=Subhash+Rathod+%26+Others+Acquire+Shares+in+Akme+Fintrade+%28India%29+Ltd+via+Open+Market&newsId=c184e125-fedd-4f94-ace6-3f9f20f65ae9&token=YzE4NGUxMjUtZmVk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c184e125-fedd-4f94-ace6-3f9f20f65ae9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Subhash Rathod and others have acquired shares in Akme Fintrade (India) Ltd through the open market. The total number of shares acquired is 426,749,960, which amounts to 6.783% of the total diluted share/voting capital of the company after the acquisition. This acquisition was made between 20th and 24th February 2026.</p><ul><li>Subhash Rathod and others have acquired shares in Akme Fintrade (India) Ltd.</li><li>The acquisition was made through the open market.</li><li>The total number of shares acquired is 426,749,960.</li><li>This acquisition amounts to 6.783% of the total diluted share/voting capital of the company after the acquisition.</li><li>The acquisition was made between 20th and 24th February 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/E105338F_042E_43FE_A76F_DD7A0143A99E_180457.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Akme Fintrade (India) Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IYKOTHITE] Iykot Hitech Toolroom Ltd. Announces Share Purchase Agreement with Aspect Global Ventures</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IYKOT+HITECH+TOOLROOM+LTD.&title=Iykot+Hitech+Toolroom+Ltd.+Announces+Share+Purchase+Agreement+with+Aspect+Global+Ventures&newsId=e4dcfbc1-956c-42ab-a112-46c36d0cfc47&token=ZTRkY2ZiYzEtOTU2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e4dcfbc1-956c-42ab-a112-46c36d0cfc47</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Iykot Hitech Toolroom Ltd. has announced the execution of a Share Purchase Agreement (SPA) with Aspect Global Ventures Private Limited. The SPA involves the sale of 35,89,080 equity shares, representing 34.58% of the company&apos;s total existing voting equity share capital, by promoters Ms. Annjana Dugar, Ms. Likhitta Dugar, Mr. Padam Dugar, and Mr. Antariksh Dugar. The transaction is subject to certain conditions and will result in an open offer to public shareholders.</p><ul><li>Iykot Hitech Toolroom Ltd. has entered into a Share Purchase Agreement with Aspect Global Ventures Private Limited.</li><li>The SPA involves the sale of 35,89,080 equity shares by promoters Ms. Annjana Dugar, Ms. Likhitta Dugar, Mr. Padam Dugar, and Mr. Antariksh Dugar.</li><li>The sale represents 34.58% of the company&apos;s total existing voting equity share capital.</li><li>The transaction is subject to certain conditions and will result in an open offer to public shareholders.</li><li>The company has also approved the forfeiture and cancellation of 99,01,931 partly paid-up equity shares.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/29a9164e-7dcb-4394-94ab-20b015375961.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IYKOT HITECH TOOLROOM LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IYKOTHITE] Iykot Hitech Toolroom Ltd. Announces Share Purchase Agreement with Aspect Global Ventures</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IYKOT+HITECH+TOOLROOM+LTD.&title=Iykot+Hitech+Toolroom+Ltd.+Announces+Share+Purchase+Agreement+with+Aspect+Global+Ventures&newsId=53bd1fb5-74d7-408e-b57a-95d148496629&token=NTNiZDFmYjUtNzRk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53bd1fb5-74d7-408e-b57a-95d148496629</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:43:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Iykot Hitech Toolroom Ltd. has announced that promoters Ms. Annjana Dugar, Ms. Likhitta Dugar, Mr. Padam Dugar, and Mr. Antariksh Dugar have executed a Share Purchase Agreement (SPA) with Aspect Global Ventures Private Limited. The SPA involves the sale of 35,89,080 (Thirty-Five Lakh Eighty-Nine Thousand and Eighty) fully paid-up equity shares, constituting 34.58% of the existing voting share capital of the company, at a price of Rs. 8/- per equity share. The transaction is subject to certain conditions and will require Aspect Global Ventures to make an Open Offer to the public shareholders of the company.</p><ul><li>Iykot Hitech Toolroom Ltd. promoters sell 34.58% stake to Aspect Global Ventures</li><li>Share Purchase Agreement (SPA) executed on 24th February, 2026</li><li>Aspect Global Ventures to make an Open Offer to public shareholders</li><li>Transaction subject to certain conditions</li><li>Iykot Hitech Toolroom Ltd. to forfeit and cancel 99,01,931 partly paid-up equity shares</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3fe03b24-e1e4-400d-9ec0-3a03dbe6b119.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IYKOT HITECH TOOLROOM LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDSWFTLAB] Ind-Swift Laboratories Approves Allotment of 51,00,000 Equity Shares Upon Conversion of Warrants</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IND-SWIFT+LABORATORIES+LTD.&title=Ind-Swift+Laboratories+Approves+Allotment+of+51%2C00%2C000+Equity+Shares+Upon+Conversion+of+Warrants&newsId=651e0201-f715-4630-8772-f4c2a88c43ca&token=NjUxZTAyMDEtZjcx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">651e0201-f715-4630-8772-f4c2a88c43ca</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:42:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Ind-Swift Laboratories Ltd. has approved the allotment of 51,00,000 equity shares following the conversion of warrants. The warrants were allotted on August 30, 2024, to Essix Biosciences Limited, a Promoter &amp; Promoter Group entity, at an issue price of Rs. 121/- each on a preferential basis. This allotment has increased the company&apos;s paid-up equity share capital to Rs. 86.71 crores. The preferential issue committee meeting was held on February 24, 2026.</p><ul><li>Ind-Swift Laboratories has approved the allotment of 51,00,000 equity shares upon conversion of warrants.</li><li>The warrants were allotted to Essix Biosciences Limited, a Promoter &amp; Promoter Group entity, at an issue price of Rs. 121/- each.</li><li>This allotment has increased the company&apos;s paid-up equity share capital to Rs. 86.71 crores.</li><li>The preferential issue committee meeting was held on February 24, 2026.</li><li>The warrants were allotted on August 30, 2024.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d0fd3cea-e2f6-4dbb-80e8-6da1ce4c0225.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IND-SWIFT LABORATORIES LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[POOJA] Poojawestern Metaliks Ltd Postpones Board Meeting to Consider Rights Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Poojawestern+Metaliks+Ltd&title=Poojawestern+Metaliks+Ltd+Postpones+Board+Meeting+to+Consider+Rights+Issue&newsId=8233a775-defd-4504-a3e4-33fb1355cf93&token=ODIzM2E3NzUtZGVm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8233a775-defd-4504-a3e4-33fb1355cf93</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:41:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Right Issue</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Poojawestern Metaliks Ltd has informed the BSE that the meeting of the Board of Directors, originally scheduled for 24th February 2026, has been postponed to 27th February 2026. The meeting will consider and approve the Rights Issue of the company, including terms and conditions such as the Issue Price and ratio of rights equity shares. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the company has been closed for Connected Persons, Insiders, Designated Persons and their immediate relatives covered under the Code of Conduct to Regulate, Monitor and Report Trading by Designated Persons of the Company adopted under Securities and Exchange Board of India (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, as amended, with effect from Tuesday, February 16, 2026 till 48 hours after the announcement of outcome of the committee.</p><ul><li>Poojawestern Metaliks Ltd postpones Board Meeting to 27th February 2026</li><li>Meeting to consider and approve Rights Issue of the company</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the securities of the company closed for Connected Persons, Insiders, Designated Persons and their immediate relatives</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7201832e-30ec-473a-b865-d1fbaf4b0cfc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Poojawestern Metaliks Ltd | Category: Right Issue</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SFL] Sheela Foam Ltd. Closes Trading Window for Interim Dividend Consideration in Upcoming Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sheela+Foam+Ltd&title=Sheela+Foam+Ltd.+Closes+Trading+Window+for+Interim+Dividend+Consideration+in+Upcoming+Board+Meeting&newsId=3f949f48-367d-4a5f-a8ba-01f141c0ef5b&token=M2Y5NDlmNDgtMzY3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3f949f48-367d-4a5f-a8ba-01f141c0ef5b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:40:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sheela Foam Ltd. has announced the closure of its trading window to consider an interim dividend for the financial year 2025-26. This decision comes in light of the upcoming Board Meeting scheduled on 2nd March, 2026. The trading window for dealing in shares of the company will remain closed for persons specified under the Code from Wednesday, 25th February, 2026 till Wednesday, 04th March, 2026 (both days inclusive) as per the Company&apos;s Code of Conduct framed under the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Sheela Foam Ltd. closes trading window for interim dividend consideration</li><li>Interim dividend proposal for financial year 2025-26 to be considered in the upcoming Board Meeting on 2nd March, 2026</li><li>Trading window closure from Wednesday, 25th February, 2026 till Wednesday, 04th March, 2026 (both days inclusive)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5a79aac1-4874-472c-acf9-76208ac5acda.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sheela Foam Ltd | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>