<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 06:33:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[MOTHERSON] Motherson Secures Government Incentives Under ECMS for Consumer Electronics Enclosures Production</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Samvardhana+Motherson+International+Ltd&title=Motherson+Secures+Government+Incentives+Under+ECMS+for+Consumer+Electronics+Enclosures+Production&newsId=98a7f82f-2cc3-4dd0-9c4f-f291b5aeb682&token=OThhN2Y4MmYtMmNj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98a7f82f-2cc3-4dd0-9c4f-f291b5aeb682</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 06:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Motherson Electronic Components Private Limited (MECPL), a subsidiary of Samvardhana Motherson International Limited (SAMIL), has successfully secured incentives under the Government of India’s Production Linked Incentive (PLI) Scheme. MECPL has been included among the beneficiaries of the Electronics Components Manufacturing Scheme (ECMS) for the production of enclosures for the consumer electronics industry. The incentives, lasting six years from FY 26 to FY 31, amount to an expected cumulative investment of Rs. 1,900 crores, and are expected to create over 5,000 employment opportunities at the Kanchipuram, Tamil Nadu plant. This development highlights Motherson&apos;s commitment to strengthening domestic manufacturing and contributing to &apos;Make in India&apos;.</p><ul><li>Motherson secures incentives under the Government of India’s Production Linked Incentive (PLI) Scheme.</li><li>Included in the Electronics Components Manufacturing Scheme (ECMS) for the production of enclosures for the consumer electronics industry.</li><li>Expected cumulative investment of Rs. 1,900 crores over six years, from FY 26 to FY 31.</li><li>Creation of over 5,000 employment opportunities at the Kanchipuram, Tamil Nadu plant.</li><li>Reflects Motherson&apos;s strong capabilities and readiness to scale operations in high value segments such as consumer electronics.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/793d49b5-6cd1-4f9c-a44e-cf6a438bd380.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JUSTO] Promoter Puspamitra Das Acquires 1,000 Equity Shares of Justo Realfintech Ltd via Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Justo+Realfintech+Ltd&title=Promoter+Puspamitra+Das+Acquires+1%2C000+Equity+Shares+of+Justo+Realfintech+Ltd+via+Open+Market&newsId=36bdc32d-8356-4aa4-a1d8-534b53fec7d4&token=MzZiZGMzMmQtODM1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">36bdc32d-8356-4aa4-a1d8-534b53fec7d4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 06:27:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Puspamitra Das, a promoter of Justo Realfintech Ltd, has acquired 1,000 equity shares of the company through the open market. The acquisition took place on 2nd January 2026. Before the acquisition, the promoter held 38.18% voting rights in the company. After the acquisition, the holding increased to 38.185%. The company&apos;s equity share capital and total voting capital remain unchanged at INR 18,79,81,420 consisting of 1,87,98,142 Equity Shares of Rs. 10 each.</p><ul><li>Puspamitra Das, a promoter of Justo Realfintech Ltd, acquired 1,000 equity shares through the open market.</li><li>The acquisition took place on 2nd January 2026.</li><li>Before the acquisition, the promoter held 38.18% voting rights in the company.</li><li>After the acquisition, the holding increased to 38.185%.</li><li>The company&apos;s equity share capital and total voting capital remain unchanged.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/EAD600AD_FB9B_4DC3_ADDB_75972D7A05F2_115558.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Justo Realfintech Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NAHARSPING] Nahar Spinning Mills Ltd. Reports Dematerialization of 2082 Shares in December 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NAHAR+SPINNING+MILLS+LTD.&title=Nahar+Spinning+Mills+Ltd.+Reports+Dematerialization+of+2082+Shares+in+December+2025&newsId=9295af34-1b97-4c69-b01d-0624a42be98f&token=OTI5NWFmMzQtMWI5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9295af34-1b97-4c69-b01d-0624a42be98f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 06:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Nahar Spinning Mills Ltd. has reported the dematerialization of 2082 equity shares in December 2025. After due verification of Share Certificates, the share certificates have been cancelled and substituted with the name of Depository as Registered Owner in the company&apos;s record. As of January 2026, the total holding of National Securities Depository Ltd. (NSDL) and Central Depository Services Ltd. (CDSL) is 35660939 equity shares.</p><ul><li>2082 equity shares dematerialized in December 2025</li><li>Share certificates cancelled and substituted with Depository as Registered Owner</li><li>Total holding of NSDL and CDSL as on January 2026 is 35660939 equity shares</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/77292a7d-e039-40ab-a407-b42bba79f2cd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NAHAR SPINNING MILLS LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAHARAHOUS] Sahara Housingfina Corporation Ltd Closes Trading Window for Designated Persons till 48 hours after Q1 2026 Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SAHARA+HOUSINGFINA+CORPORATION+LTD.&title=Sahara+Housingfina+Corporation+Ltd+Closes+Trading+Window+for+Designated+Persons+till+48+hours+after+Q1+2026+Results&newsId=b892d567-1042-45f2-b734-c8b6d1714fac&token=Yjg5MmQ1NjctMTA0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b892d567-1042-45f2-b734-c8b6d1714fac</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 06:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sahara Housingfina Corporation Ltd has announced the closure of the trading window for all designated persons and their immediate relatives from 1st January 2026. The window will remain closed until 48 hours after the announcement of the audited financial results for the quarter ended 31st March 2026. This decision is in accordance with the Company’s Code of Conduct for Regulating, Monitoring and Reporting of Trading by designated persons &amp; their immediate relatives and SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, as amended. All designated persons of the Company and their immediate relative(s) have been informed not to trade in the securities of the Company during the aforementioned period.</p><ul><li>Sahara Housingfina Corporation Ltd closes trading window for designated persons and their immediate relatives.</li><li>The closure is from 1st January 2026 until 48 hours after the Q1 2026 results announcement.</li><li>This decision is in accordance with the Company’s Code of Conduct and SEBI regulations.</li><li>Designated persons and their immediate relatives have been informed not to trade during the closure period.</li><li>The trading window closure is to ensure compliance with insider trading regulations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6e3bac18-7ad5-4b86-8be1-f58f70a73d95.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SAHARA HOUSINGFINA CORPORATION LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SYSCHEM] Syschem India Ltd Commences Commercial Production of New and Expanded Units</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SYSCHEM+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Syschem+India+Ltd+Commences+Commercial+Production+of+New+and+Expanded+Units&newsId=ebdc729e-176a-43bd-b5cc-116254601bae&token=ZWJkYzcyOWUtMTc2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ebdc729e-176a-43bd-b5cc-116254601bae</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 06:07:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Syschem India Ltd has started the commercial production from 5th January, 2026, for its new production unit and expanded existing unit. The new production unit, named &apos;Ganga&apos;, is located at Village Bargodam, Tehsil Kalka, District Panchkula, Haryana. It is manufacturing products like &apos;Cloxacillin Sodium, Dicloxacillin Sodium and Flucloxacillin Sodium&apos; with an installed capacity of 600 MT per annum. The existing unit, named &apos;SARU&apos;, has also started commercial production of &apos;Amoxicillin&apos; with an installed capacity of 1200 MT per annum. These developments are expected to enhance the overall production capacity, improve operational efficiency, and meet growing market demand.</p><ul><li>Syschem India Ltd starts commercial production of new production unit &apos;Ganga&apos;</li><li>New unit located at Village Bargodam, Tehsil Kalka, District Panchkula, Haryana</li><li>Producing &apos;Cloxacillin Sodium, Dicloxacillin Sodium and Flucloxacillin Sodium&apos; with 600 MT annual capacity</li><li>Commercial production of expanded existing unit &apos;SARU&apos; started</li><li>Producing &apos;Amoxicillin&apos; with 1200 MT annual capacity</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bbef9726-e1a1-4376-ba6f-1b930443575c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SYSCHEM (INDIA) LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SCHAEFFLER] Schaeffler India Ltd Announces Special Window for Re-lodgment of Transfer Requests of Physical Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Schaeffler+India+Ltd&title=Schaeffler+India+Ltd+Announces+Special+Window+for+Re-lodgment+of+Transfer+Requests+of+Physical+Shares&newsId=1b107959-0043-4b23-9783-da13aa3b5e2e&token=MWIxMDc5NTktMDA0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b107959-0043-4b23-9783-da13aa3b5e2e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 06:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Schaeffler India Ltd has announced the details for opening a special window for re-lodgement of transfer requests of physical shares. The announcement was made through the company&apos;s social media channels, including Facebook. The link to the Facebook post is provided for reference.</p><ul><li>Schaeffler India Ltd has opened a special window for re-lodgment of transfer requests of physical shares.</li><li>The announcement was made through the company&apos;s social media channels.</li><li>The special window is a business update aimed at facilitating share transfers.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c548a71c-2bb6-4395-be59-89c0e66bf846.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Schaeffler India Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZSANMCOM] Sanmitra Commercial Ltd Receives Open Offer for Acquisition of 26.00% Equity Shares by Ankit Jalan and Anuj Jalan</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SANMITRA+COMMERCIAL+LTD.&title=Sanmitra+Commercial+Ltd+Receives+Open+Offer+for+Acquisition+of+26.00%25+Equity+Shares+by+Ankit+Jalan+and+Anuj+Jalan&newsId=dc612324-2312-45b4-8323-137fe112c5c5&token=ZGM2MTIzMjQtMjMx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc612324-2312-45b4-8323-137fe112c5c5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 05:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Navigant Corporate Advisors Ltd, on behalf of Ankit Jalan (Acquirer-1) and Anuj Jalan (Acquirer-2), along with Manju Jalan (PAC-1), Radhika Jalan (PAC-2), Prachi Jalan (PAC-3), Ritu Jalan (PAC-4), Divyanshi Jalan (PAC-5) and Daivik Jalan (PAC-6), have made an open offer for the acquisition of up to 1,49,76,000 Equity Shares of Rs. 10/- each representing 26.00% of the expanded equity and voting share capital of Sanmitra Commercial Limited. The offer price is Rs. 15/- (Rupees Fifteen Only) per equity share payable in cash. The Committee of Independent Directors of Sanmitra Commercial Limited is of the opinion that the offer price is in accordance with the relevant regulations prescribed in the Takeover Code and prima facie appear to be justified.</p><ul><li>Ankit Jalan and Anuj Jalan, along with Manju Jalan, Radhika Jalan, Prachi Jalan, Ritu Jalan, Divyanshi Jalan, and Daivik Jalan, are acquiring up to 26.00% of the expanded equity and voting share capital of Sanmitra Commercial Limited.</li><li>The offer price is Rs. 15/- (Rupees Fifteen Only) per equity share payable in cash.</li><li>The Committee of Independent Directors of Sanmitra Commercial Limited has opined that the offer price is in accordance with the relevant regulations and prima facie appear to be justified.</li><li>The completion of dispatch of the Letter of Offer to all the Public Shareholders of Sanmitra Commercial Limited was completed on 30th December, 2025.</li><li>There has been no competitive bid to this Offer.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/85C47197-19BD-40DB-9F23-358F36B7C6A9-111641.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SANMITRA COMMERCIAL LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BONDADA] Bondada Engineering Ltd Secures LoA from APTRANSCO for 225 MW BESS Project</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Bondada+Engineering+Ltd&title=Bondada+Engineering+Ltd+Secures+LoA+from+APTRANSCO+for+225+MW+BESS+Project&newsId=686cbbc9-5f4b-4bd1-986e-e8677c29621d&token=Njg2Y2JiYzktNWY0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">686cbbc9-5f4b-4bd1-986e-e8677c29621d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 05:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Bondada Engineering Limited has received a Letter of Award (LOA) from AP TRANSCO for the development of a 225 MW / 450 MWh Standalone Battery Energy Storage System (BESS) project. This order is strategically significant as it establishes a long-term annuity-based revenue stream, enhancing revenue stability, cash flow visibility and return predictability. The project will contribute significantly to revenues post construction phase and generate stable, long-term annuity income, thereby enhancing shareholder value and earnings visibility.</p><ul><li>Bondada Engineering Ltd has received an LOA from APTRANSCO for a 225 MW / 450 MWh Standalone BESS project.</li><li>The project will establish a long-term annuity-based revenue stream, enhancing revenue stability, cash flow visibility and return predictability.</li><li>The project will contribute significantly to revenues post construction phase and generate stable, long-term annuity income.</li><li>The order is strategically significant and strengthens the Company’s long-term growth visibility.</li><li>The project aligns with India’s grid-scale energy transition and storage-led infrastructure development initiatives.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f2786200-74cb-4633-8d88-4e191b46abe7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Bondada Engineering Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CENTRALBK] Central Bank of India Discloses Q3 FY 2025-26 Business Figures: Total Business Surges by 15.80% Y-o-Y</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CENTRAL+BANK+OF+INDIA&title=Central+Bank+of+India+Discloses+Q3+FY+2025-26+Business+Figures%3A+Total+Business+Surges+by+15.80%25+Y-o-Y&newsId=3eee72ae-adc8-4493-9940-75a46083f426&token=M2VlZTcyYWUtYWRj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3eee72ae-adc8-4493-9940-75a46083f426</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 05:50:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Central Bank of India has released its provisional business figures for the third quarter of the financial year 2025-26, as of 31.12.2025. The bank&apos;s total business has shown a significant growth of 15.80% Y-o-Y and 10.18% Y-T-D. Total deposits have increased by 3.28% Y-o-Y and 9.17% Y-T-D, with CASA deposits growing by 8.53% Y-o-Y and 5.26% Y-T-D. The CASA percentage stands at 47.12%, a decrease of 206 bps from the previous year and 179 bps from the beginning of the year. Gross advances have increased by 19.57% Y-o-Y and 11.61% Y-T-D. The bank&apos;s CD ratio stands at 72.06%, an increase of 381 bps from the previous year and 153 bps from the beginning of the year. These figures are subject to review by the bank&apos;s Statutory Central Auditors.</p><ul><li>Total Business surges by 15.80% Y-o-Y</li><li>Total Deposits increase by 3.28% Y-o-Y and 9.17% Y-T-D</li><li>CASA Deposits grow by 8.53% Y-o-Y and 5.26% Y-T-D</li><li>Gross Advances increase by 19.57% Y-o-Y and 11.61% Y-T-D</li><li>CD Ratio stands at 72.06%, an increase of 381 bps Y-o-Y and 153 bps Y-T-D</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6b7c2a64-0f83-49b4-8f35-c614619b1693.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CENTRAL BANK OF INDIA | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ORIENTABRA] Orient Ceratech Ltd: Share Price Movement Attributed to Market Conditions</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ORIENT+ABRASIVES+LTD.-%24&title=Orient+Ceratech+Ltd%3A+Share+Price+Movement+Attributed+to+Market+Conditions&newsId=c2235533-917f-4e62-842b-32ab342ca2e3&token=YzIyMzU1MzMtOTE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c2235533-917f-4e62-842b-32ab342ca2e3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 05:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Orient Ceratech Ltd has clarified that there have been no material events or announcements affecting the movement of its security prices, other than those disclosed. The company emphasizes its commitment to good corporate governance and compliance with regulations. The movement in share prices is attributed to market conditions, with no involvement from the company&apos;s management.</p><ul><li>Orient Ceratech Ltd denies any undisclosed material events affecting share price movement.</li><li>The company reaffirms its commitment to good corporate governance and regulatory compliance.</li><li>Share price movement is attributed solely to market conditions.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/eb38edc4-ee6a-4b94-9d39-010b640502bf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ORIENT ABRASIVES LTD.-$ | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>