<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:32:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ESHAMEDIA] Esha Media Research Ltd to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q4 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Esha+Media+Research+Limited&title=Esha+Media+Research+Ltd+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q4+2025&newsId=3876d5e9-baf8-4fb0-ad6d-58ba80dd6285&token=Mzg3NmQ1ZTktYmFm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3876d5e9-baf8-4fb0-ad6d-58ba80dd6285</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Esha Media Research Ltd has announced a Board Meeting on 13th February 2026 to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, along with the Limited Review Report of the company. This is in compliance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Esha Media Research Ltd scheduled a Board Meeting on 13th February 2026</li><li>The meeting aims to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for Q4 2025</li><li>The results will be accompanied by the Limited Review Report of the company</li><li>This is in compliance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/212d3a7d-3601-4341-8cf1-5490206eb66c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Esha Media Research Limited | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RUBYMILLS] Ruby Mills Ltd. to Incorporate Three Wholly Owned Subsidiaries for Solar Open Access Project Investment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RUBY+MILLS+LTD.&title=Ruby+Mills+Ltd.+to+Incorporate+Three+Wholly+Owned+Subsidiaries+for+Solar+Open+Access+Project+Investment&newsId=a8efa259-c5d0-4dd8-8d24-1a23c7ec673b&token=YThlZmEyNTktYzVk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8efa259-c5d0-4dd8-8d24-1a23c7ec673b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Ruby Mills Ltd. announced the outcome of its Board Meeting held on 19.01.2026, revealing the approval to incorporate three wholly owned subsidiaries in Mumbai, India. These subsidiaries will be created to invest in a Solar Open Access project, providing the Company with flexibility in managing the investment at a later stage. The incorporation is subject to necessary approvals and compliance with the applicable provisions of the Companies Act, 2013 and SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. Once the subsidiaries are incorporated, appropriate disclosures will be made to the stock exchanges as required under Regulation 30 of the SEBI Listing Regulations and SEBI Circulars.</p><ul><li>Ruby Mills Ltd. to incorporate three wholly owned subsidiaries</li><li>Subsidiaries created for investing in a Solar Open Access project</li><li>Flexibility in managing the investment at a later stage</li><li>Incorporation subject to necessary approvals</li><li>Appropriate disclosures to be made to stock exchanges post-incorporation</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b8f2b0df-9cb7-45f8-8181-be9287570bbb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RUBY MILLS LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ACGL] Automobile Corporation of Goa Ltd: Q3 Results, Interim Dividend Declaration, and Appointment of Additional Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AUTOMOBILE+CORPORATION+OF+GOA+LTD.-%24&title=Automobile+Corporation+of+Goa+Ltd%3A+Q3+Results%2C+Interim+Dividend+Declaration%2C+and+Appointment+of+Additional+Directors&newsId=f459c7b2-39e7-4365-8cd7-1d6392ae46da&token=ZjQ1OWM3YjItMzll</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f459c7b2-39e7-4365-8cd7-1d6392ae46da</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:29:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Automobile Corporation of Goa Ltd has announced its audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company has declared an interim dividend of Rs.5/- per equity share for the financial year 2025-26. The board has also appointed Dr. Renu Sharma and Mrs. Rekha Bagry Nair as Additional Directors and Independent Directors for a tenure of 5 years.</p><ul><li>Automobile Corporation of Goa Ltd has announced its Q3 results for the year 2025.</li><li>The company has declared an interim dividend of Rs.5/- per equity share for the financial year 2025-26.</li><li>Dr. Renu Sharma and Mrs. Rekha Bagry Nair have been appointed as Additional Directors and Independent Directors of the company.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8cc13e14-da55-49c1-a42f-7d2961092ace.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AUTOMOBILE CORPORATION OF GOA LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZSWASTSA] E &amp; E Enterprises Ltd to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q4 2025 in Board Meeting on 28th January 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SWASTIK+SAFE+DEPOSIT+%26+INVESTMENTS+LTD.&title=E+%26+E+Enterprises+Ltd+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q4+2025+in+Board+Meeting+on+28th+January+2026&newsId=fa8d9510-8100-4d34-9e3c-a7b986d2fec4&token=ZmE4ZDk1MTAtODEw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa8d9510-8100-4d34-9e3c-a7b986d2fec4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:28:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>E &amp; E Enterprises Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 28th January 2026 to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter ended on 31st December 2025. This meeting is being held in compliance with the SEBI Listing Regulations. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the company will be closed from 1st January 2026 to 30th January 2026 (both days inclusive).</p><ul><li>E &amp; E Enterprises Ltd to approve unaudited financial results for Q4 2025.</li><li>Board Meeting scheduled on 28th January 2026.</li><li>Compliance with SEBI Listing Regulations.</li><li>Trading window for securities to be closed from 1st January 2026 to 30th January 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/df6b37eb-735e-4588-8854-268b8d542784.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SWASTIK SAFE DEPOSIT & INVESTMENTS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ATHCON] Athena Constructions Ltd Closes Trading Window for Designated Persons till January 01, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Athena+Constructions+Ltd&title=Athena+Constructions+Ltd+Closes+Trading+Window+for+Designated+Persons+till+January+01%2C+2026&newsId=f865edb3-0dd3-4b07-9470-c322479c990c&token=Zjg2NWVkYjMtMGRk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f865edb3-0dd3-4b07-9470-c322479c990c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:28:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Athena Constructions Ltd has announced the closure of its trading window for all designated persons and their immediate relatives. The closure is in accordance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015. The trading window will remain closed from Thursday, January 01, 2026 till 48 hours after the declaration of unaudited financial results for the quarter ending December 31, 2025. The date of the Board of Directors&apos; meeting to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the third quarter ended on December 31, 2025 will be informed in due course. Designated persons, connected persons, insiders, and their immediate relatives are advised not to trade in the Shares of the Company during the aforesaid period of closure of the trading window.</p><ul><li>Athena Constructions Ltd closes trading window for designated persons and their immediate relatives.</li><li>Closure is in accordance with Securities and Exchange Board of India (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015.</li><li>Trading window to remain closed from January 01, 2026 till 48 hours after the declaration of unaudited financial results for the quarter ending December 31, 2025.</li><li>Date of Board of Directors&apos; meeting to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the third quarter ended on December 31, 2025 will be informed in due course.</li><li>Designated persons, connected persons, insiders, and their immediate relatives are advised not to trade in the Shares of the Company during the aforesaid period.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6c07a2a2-dcc1-46d2-83fc-a56b971346cc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Athena Constructions Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NOCIL] NOCIL Ltd to Consider and Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NOCIL+LTD.&title=NOCIL+Ltd+to+Consider+and+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=629db890-a1e8-49e9-8fff-c5ec3090a790&token=NjI5ZGI4OTAtYTFl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">629db890-a1e8-49e9-8fff-c5ec3090a790</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:27:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>NOCIL Ltd has announced a Board Meeting scheduled on 11th February 2026. The meeting will consider and approve the Un-Audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results along with the Limited Review Report for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The meeting will be held at Mafatlal House, 4th Floor, Backbay Reclamation, Mumbai 400 020.</p><ul><li>NOCIL Ltd scheduled a Board Meeting on 11th February 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the Un-Audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025</li><li>The meeting will be held at Mafatlal House, 4th Floor, Backbay Reclamation, Mumbai 400 020</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/be102168-68cb-4ba2-b9f3-ef8dbc9bb8b5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NOCIL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ACGL] Automobile Corporation of Goa Ltd. Declares Interim Dividend, Appoints New Directors, and Reports Q3 Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AUTOMOBILE+CORPORATION+OF+GOA+LTD.-%24&title=Automobile+Corporation+of+Goa+Ltd.+Declares+Interim+Dividend%2C+Appoints+New+Directors%2C+and+Reports+Q3+Results+for+2025&newsId=9bbab4e8-1f38-4049-8658-8019c6c4a450&token=OWJiYWI0ZTgtMWYz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9bbab4e8-1f38-4049-8658-8019c6c4a450</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:27:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Automobile Corporation of Goa Ltd. has announced its audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company has reported a net profit and has declared an interim dividend of Rs.5/- per equity share for the financial year 2025-26. The record date for the dividend is January 29, 2026. The company has also appointed two new Additional Directors and Independent Directors, Dr. Renu Sharma and Mrs. Rekha Bagry Nair, for a tenure of 5 years. Dr. Sharma is a distinguished retired IAS officer with extensive experience in public administration, governance, and finance. Mrs. Nair is an independent professional with over 20 years of experience in tax and advisory, specializing in tax and regulatory aspects of mergers and acquisitions.</p><ul><li>Automobile Corporation of Goa Ltd. reported a net profit for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The company declared an interim dividend of Rs.5/- per equity share for the financial year 2025-26.</li><li>Dr. Renu Sharma and Mrs. Rekha Bagry Nair were appointed as Additional Directors and Independent Directors for a tenure of 5 years.</li><li>Dr. Sharma is a distinguished retired IAS officer with extensive experience in public administration, governance, and finance.</li><li>Mrs. Nair is an independent professional with over 20 years of experience in tax and advisory, specializing in tax and regulatory aspects of mergers and acquisitions.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cc5a4911-a7af-4598-a6e6-f96653d71916.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AUTOMOBILE CORPORATION OF GOA LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WARDINMOBI] Wardwizard Innovations &amp; Mobility Ltd: No Pending Price-Sensitive Information, Price Movement Market-Driven</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Wardwizard+Innovations+%26+Mobility+Ltd&title=Wardwizard+Innovations+%26+Mobility+Ltd%3A+No+Pending+Price-Sensitive+Information%2C+Price+Movement+Market-Driven&newsId=c9e5d86e-b3a7-4301-b985-97afc8a0a1b5&token=YzllNWQ4NmUtYjNh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9e5d86e-b3a7-4301-b985-97afc8a0a1b5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:24:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Wardwizard Innovations &amp; Mobility Ltd has clarified that there is no pending price-sensitive information that could have led to the significant movement in the price behavior of the company&apos;s shares. The company has consistently made disclosures as required under Regulation 30 of the Securities Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The company ensures that all required information/announcements will be duly disclosed to the stock exchanges as per applicable regulations.</p><ul><li>Wardwizard Innovations &amp; Mobility Ltd clarifies there is no pending price-sensitive information</li><li>Price movement is market-driven</li><li>Company has consistently made disclosures as required under Regulation 30 of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Wardwizard Innovations &amp; Mobility Ltd will continue to adhere to the said Regulations within stipulated time</li><li>Company ensures stock exchanges are duly informed of all required information/announcements</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e704eb2f-ca36-457f-8b0c-755e8c7c0431.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Wardwizard Innovations & Mobility Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KAKA] Kaka Industries Ltd. Shifts Registered Office Within Ahmedabad</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kaka+Industries+Ltd&title=Kaka+Industries+Ltd.+Shifts+Registered+Office+Within+Ahmedabad&newsId=1050dd09-1ea0-41d3-9010-43f15c8310c3&token=MTA1MGRkMDktMWVh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1050dd09-1ea0-41d3-9010-43f15c8310c3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:22:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kaka Industries Ltd. has announced the shifting of its registered office from Plot No. 67, Bhagwati Nagar, Opp Nilkanth Arcade, Opp Kathwada Gidc, Kuha-Kanbha Road, Odhav, Ahmedabad-382415, Gujarat, India to 501 &amp; 601, Sahitya Business Park, Nr. Sahjanand Business Park, S.P. Ring Road, Nikol, Ahmedabad, Gujarat- 382350. The board meeting to approve the shift took place from 03:10 P.M. to 03:40 P.M. on 2nd January, 2026.</p><ul><li>Kaka Industries Ltd. is shifting its registered office within Ahmedabad, Gujarat.</li><li>The shift is from Plot No. 67, Bhagwati Nagar, Opp Nilkanth Arcade, Opp Kathwada Gidc, Kuha-Kanbha Road, Odhav to 501 &amp; 601, Sahitya Business Park, Nr. Sahjanand Business Park, S.P. Ring Road, Nikol.</li><li>The shift was approved in a board meeting held from 03:10 P.M. to 03:40 P.M. on 2nd January, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5df44843-4f2d-4dca-9d98-8de2642c1995.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kaka Industries Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ACGL] Automobile Corporation of Goa Ltd.: Board Approves Q3 Results, Interim Dividend, and Appoints New Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AUTOMOBILE+CORPORATION+OF+GOA+LTD.-%24&title=Automobile+Corporation+of+Goa+Ltd.%3A+Board+Approves+Q3+Results%2C+Interim+Dividend%2C+and+Appoints+New+Directors&newsId=1506fb7a-dbde-4546-8528-ff5e49c85c69&token=MTUwNmZiN2EtZGJk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1506fb7a-dbde-4546-8528-ff5e49c85c69</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:22:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Automobile Corporation of Goa Ltd. met on January 19, 2026, and approved the audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company declared an interim dividend of Rs.5/- per equity share for the financial year 2025-26. The board also appointed Dr. Renu Sharma and Mrs. Rekha Bagry Nair as Additional Directors and Independent Directors for a tenure of 5 years. Dr. Renu Sharma is a distinguished retired IAS officer with extensive experience in public administration, governance, and finance, while Mrs. Rekha Bagry Nair is an independent professional with over 20 years of experience in tax and advisory.</p><ul><li>Board approved audited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Interim dividend of Rs.5/- per equity share declared for FY 2025-26</li><li>Dr. Renu Sharma appointed as Additional Director and Independent Director for 5 years</li><li>Mrs. Rekha Bagry Nair appointed as Additional Director and Independent Director for 5 years</li><li>Appointments subject to approval of shareholders</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/49648ebd-3892-4af1-9b1a-4812bb0b847c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AUTOMOBILE CORPORATION OF GOA LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>