<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 01:43:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[BERGEPAINT] Berger Paints India Ltd Releases Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BERGER+PAINTS+INDIA+LTD.&title=Berger+Paints+India+Ltd+Releases+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=f0b9c49f-220a-4406-8458-a9f425625b13&token=ZjBiOWM0OWYtMjIw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0b9c49f-220a-4406-8458-a9f425625b13</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 00:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Berger Paints India Ltd has released its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December, 2025. The audio recording of the investor presentation is now available on the company&apos;s website. This disclosure is made in accordance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015 (as amended).</p><ul><li>Berger Paints India Ltd has announced its financial results for Q3 and nine months of 2025.</li><li>The audio recording of the investor presentation is accessible on the company&apos;s website.</li><li>This disclosure is in compliance with the SEBI regulations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5861eb6d-1441-492d-a7a7-f493516f351c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BERGER PAINTS INDIA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAVFI] Savani Financials Ltd. Announces EGM for Capital Increase and Preferential Issue of Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SAVANI+FINANCIALS+LTD.&title=Savani+Financials+Ltd.+Announces+EGM+for+Capital+Increase+and+Preferential+Issue+of+Equity+Shares&newsId=dfb371bc-7ade-437a-a547-c9029d7bb10c&token=ZGZiMzcxYmMtN2Fk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dfb371bc-7ade-437a-a547-c9029d7bb10c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 00:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Savani Financials Ltd., formerly known as Mantra Capital Limited, has announced an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) to be held on February 27, 2026. The meeting will be conducted through video conferencing or other audio-video means. The agenda includes two special items: rescinding a previous resolution related to an increase in authorized capital and considering a new proposal for an increase in authorized capital. Additionally, the EGM will consider a proposal for the preferential issue of equity shares on a private placement basis. The record date for determining eligible members for voting on EGM resolutions is February 20, 2026. Remote e-voting will commence on February 24, 2026, and end on February 26, 2026.</p><ul><li>Savani Financials Ltd. announces EGM for capital increase and preferential issue of equity shares.</li><li>The EGM will be held on February 27, 2026, through video conferencing or other audio-video means.</li><li>The agenda includes rescinding a previous resolution related to an increase in authorized capital and considering a new proposal for an increase in authorized capital.</li><li>The EGM will also consider a proposal for the preferential issue of equity shares on a private placement basis.</li><li>The record date for determining eligible members for voting on EGM resolutions is February 20, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2030cb92-550d-4890-a348-7a6101327a2e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SAVANI FINANCIALS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BLACKROSE] Black Rose Industries Ltd to Approve Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q4 2025 on Feb 12, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BLACK+ROSE+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Black+Rose+Industries+Ltd+to+Approve+Unaudited+Standalone+and+Consolidated+Financial+Results+for+Q4+2025+on+Feb+12%2C+2026&newsId=986f93dd-45ef-4f1a-898f-aa2b6156c048&token=OTg2ZjkzZGQtNDVl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">986f93dd-45ef-4f1a-898f-aa2b6156c048</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:37:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Black Rose Industries Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 12, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The meeting is in accordance with the Company&apos;s Internal Code for Prevention of Insider Trading, which closed the trading window for dealing in the Company’s Securities for Directors/Officers, Designated Employees, and their immediate relatives from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the announcement of the Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Black Rose Industries Ltd to consider and approve Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q4 2025</li><li>Meeting scheduled on 12th February 2026</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the Company’s Securities closed for Directors/Officers, Designated Employees, and their immediate relatives from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the announcement of the Financial Results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/32be6f14-5bad-4fc9-8c9a-3dc4941475c9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BLACK ROSE INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PADMAIND] Padmanabh Industries Ltd. Announces Q3 Results with 64.52% Increase in Other Income</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Padmanabh+Industries+Limited&title=Padmanabh+Industries+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+Results+with+64.52%25+Increase+in+Other+Income&newsId=19cbaa93-b82b-4a6a-b843-0df5c838b3dd&token=MTljYmFhOTMtYjgy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19cbaa93-b82b-4a6a-b843-0df5c838b3dd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Padmanabh Industries Ltd. announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 731.49 lacs, with other income amounting to 311.30 lacs, a significant increase of 64.52% from the previous year. The total revenue (net) expenses amounted to 64.52 lacs. The profit before tax stands at 22.46 lacs, and the net profit for the period from continuing operations is 19.39 lacs. The earnings per share for continuing operations is 0.02. The financial statements have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations stands at 731.49 lacs</li><li>Other income increased by 64.52% to 311.30 lacs</li><li>Profit before tax stands at 22.46 lacs</li><li>Net profit for the period from continuing operations is 19.39 lacs</li><li>Earnings per share for continuing operations is 0.02</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bb77e9ca-35a5-4342-b65e-8636c4d113d8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Padmanabh Industries Limited | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAILIFE] Sai Life Sciences Announces Q3FY26 Results: Revenue Up By 43%, EBITDA Up By 79%, Net Profit Up By 199%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sai+Life+Sciences+Ltd&title=Sai+Life+Sciences+Announces+Q3FY26+Results%3A+Revenue+Up+By+43%25%2C+EBITDA+Up+By+79%25%2C+Net+Profit+Up+By+199%25&newsId=745b474f-f496-42a7-a837-41936fa05fd5&token=NzQ1YjQ3NGYtZjQ5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">745b474f-f496-42a7-a837-41936fa05fd5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Sai Life Sciences Limited, a leading Contract Research, Development and Manufacturing Organizations (CRDMO), has announced its financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 2025. The company reported a significant increase in revenue, EBITDA, and net profit. The revenue from operations was INR 556 crores for Q3FY26, a 27% year-on-year increase. EBITDA stood at INR 191 crores for Q3FY26, a 54% year-on-year increase. The net profit stood at INR 100 crores for Q3FY26, an 86% year-on-year increase. For the nine months ended December 2025, the revenue from operations was INR 1,590 crores, a 43% year-on-year increase. The EBITDA stood at INR 472 crores, a 79% year-on-year increase. The net profit stood at INR 245 crores, a 199% year-on-year increase.</p><ul><li>Revenue from Operations for Q3FY26 was INR 556 crores, a 27% year-on-year increase.</li><li>EBITDA for Q3FY26 was INR 191 crores, a 54% year-on-year increase.</li><li>Net Profit for Q3FY26 was INR 100 crores, an 86% year-on-year increase.</li><li>Revenue from Operations for 9MFY26 was INR 1,590 crores, a 43% year-on-year increase.</li><li>EBITDA for 9MFY26 was INR 472 crores, a 79% year-on-year increase.</li><li>Net Profit for 9MFY26 was INR 245 crores, a 199% year-on-year increase.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8624c0b0-2d34-4869-bca9-d421e136cad1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sai Life Sciences Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PPLPHARMA] Piramal Critical Care and Blue-Zone Technologies Collaborate to Capture, Collect and Recycle Waste Anaesthesia Gas</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Piramal+Pharma+Ltd&title=Piramal+Critical+Care+and+Blue-Zone+Technologies+Collaborate+to+Capture%2C+Collect+and+Recycle+Waste+Anaesthesia+Gas&newsId=269eb977-9f59-40c4-a6ae-39a215df01fb&token=MjY5ZWI5NzctOWY1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">269eb977-9f59-40c4-a6ae-39a215df01fb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:32:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Piramal Critical Care, Inc. (PCC) and Blue-Zone Technologies Ltd. (Blue-Zone) have announced an agreement to collaborate on full lifecycle technology to capture and recycle waste anaesthetic gases. This collaboration will support customers’ efforts to minimize the environmental impact of volatile anaesthetics and ensure the continued use of these essential products for general anaesthesia. Pending regulatory approval in Europe, Blue-Zone will offer its Phoenix Deltasorb® waste anaesthetic gas capture system to PCC’s customers in Europe, initially in France and Germany. PCC will process captured waste anaesthetic gas using Blue- Zone’s technology to produce Sevoflurane USP for human use in Canada. The parties anticipate that the scope of the waste anaesthetic gas capture, collection and recycling, and the marketing of Sevoflurane USP using waste anaesthetic gas, will expand into additional geographies.</p><ul><li>Piramal Critical Care and Blue-Zone Technologies announce a collaboration to capture and recycle waste anaesthetic gases.</li><li>The collaboration aims to minimize the environmental impact of volatile anaesthetics and ensure the continued use of these essential products for general anaesthesia.</li><li>Pending regulatory approval in Europe, Blue-Zone will offer its Phoenix Deltasorb® waste anaesthetic gas capture system to PCC’s customers in Europe.</li><li>PCC will process captured waste anaesthetic gas using Blue- Zone’s technology to produce Sevoflurane USP for human use in Canada.</li><li>The parties anticipate expanding the scope of the waste anaesthetic gas capture, collection and recycling into additional geographies.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bc0a4c0f-9f42-421d-a70e-072740be1d01.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Piramal Pharma Ltd | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SEQUENT] Viyash Scientific Ltd: Q3 FY26 Revenues Up 10.9%, EBITDA* Surges 64.4%, PAT Increases 15.5%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SEQUENT+SCIENTIFIC+LTD.&title=Viyash+Scientific+Ltd%3A+Q3+FY26+Revenues+Up+10.9%25%2C+EBITDA%2A+Surges+64.4%25%2C+PAT+Increases+15.5%25&newsId=85581325-dc20-4edf-a26f-8c3ad0c007fe&token=ODU1ODEzMjUtZGMy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85581325-dc20-4edf-a26f-8c3ad0c007fe</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Viyash Scientific Ltd, a leading integrated pharmaceutical company, announced its financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The results reflect the first quarter where the merged entity&apos;s results are being presented. The company reported a 10.9% increase in revenues and a significant 64.4% surge in EBITDA*. The net profit also increased by 15.5% in Q3 FY26. The company is poised for growth with a strong balance sheet and market position.</p><ul><li>Revenues for Q3 FY26 at INR 8,584 Million, up by 10.9%</li><li>EBITDA* for Q3 FY26 at INR 1,854 Million, up by 64.4%</li><li>PAT for Q3 FY26 up by 15.5% including exceptional merger related costs</li><li>Net Debt / EBITDA at 0.38 x</li><li>Company to build Companion animal portfolio &amp; CDMO services</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/015fd3ff-17ad-4aa2-bf1b-ba83674af806.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SEQUENT SCIENTIFIC LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ONMOBILE] OnMobile Reports 4.5% QoQ Revenue Growth in Q3FY26, Gaming Revenue Surges 27.5% QoQ</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=OnMobile+Global+Ltd.&title=OnMobile+Reports+4.5%25+QoQ+Revenue+Growth+in+Q3FY26%2C+Gaming+Revenue+Surges+27.5%25+QoQ&newsId=8e8c357e-82e0-414c-af8f-dcec6c50d764&token=OGU4YzM1N2UtODJl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8e8c357e-82e0-414c-af8f-dcec6c50d764</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 20:31:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>OnMobile Global Limited, a global leader in mobile gaming and entertainment, announced its financial results for the Third Quarter of FY26 ended Dec 31, 2025. The company reported a 4.5% QoQ increase in revenue, with Q3FY26 revenue at INR 1,369 Mn. The Mobile Gaming Revenue for the quarter was INR 453 Mn, a significant increase of 27.5% QoQ. The gaming subscriber base stands at 13.7Mn, with a closing gross cash balance of INR 1385Mn. The company&apos;s President &amp; COO, Bikram Singh Sherawat, expressed satisfaction with the results, highlighting the strategic importance of gaming and the expansion into Africa. The Global CFO, Radhika Venugopal, also noted the financial growth and operational efficiency of the company.</p><ul><li>Q3FY26 revenue at INR 1,369 Mn up by 4.5 % QoQ.</li><li>Q3FY26 EBITDA at INR 81 Mn.</li><li>Q3FY26 Mobile Gaming Revenue at INR 453 Mn up by 27.5% QoQ.</li><li>Gaming subscriber base at 13.7Mn.</li><li>Closing Gross Cash balance at INR 1385Mn.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7cf2d1da-0ec4-4e77-a89d-2e99b2ef3fcc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: OnMobile Global Ltd. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VASWANI] Vaswani Industries Ltd Closes Trading Window Ahead of Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VASWANI+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Vaswani+Industries+Ltd+Closes+Trading+Window+Ahead+of+Board+Meeting&newsId=d0e2ceb8-e0ed-4d8d-b3a3-2503966d0fd8&token=ZDBlMmNlYjgtZTBl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d0e2ceb8-e0ed-4d8d-b3a3-2503966d0fd8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:44:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vaswani Industries Ltd has announced the closure of its trading window from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The decision comes in anticipation of the Board of Directors&apos; meeting scheduled on February 13, 2026, to consider these financial results. The trading window for dealing in the company&apos;s securities will remain closed for Directors, KMPs, designated employees, and other covered persons under the Insider Trading Code till 48 hours after the conclusion of the Board Meeting, i.e., up to February 15, 2026.</p><ul><li>Vaswani Industries Ltd closes trading window from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of Q4 2025 financial results</li><li>Board of Directors meeting scheduled on February 13, 2026, to consider these financial results</li><li>Trading window to remain closed for Directors, KMPs, designated employees, and other covered persons under the Insider Trading Code till 48 hours after the Board Meeting</li><li>Trading window to reopen on February 15, 2026</li><li>Announcement made to keep stakeholders informed</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e0f12d33-b330-499d-9ef3-b5c2f84d6732.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VASWANI INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VASWANI] Vaswani Industries Ltd to Approve Q4 Results on Feb 13, 2026; Trading Window Closed</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VASWANI+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Vaswani+Industries+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+Results+on+Feb+13%2C+2026%3B+Trading+Window+Closed&newsId=142c0f8d-5a6c-4dac-af8b-969ce9b82995&token=MTQyYzBmOGQtNWE2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">142c0f8d-5a6c-4dac-af8b-969ce9b82995</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vaswani Industries Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 13, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited standalone financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. In accordance with the Company’s Code of Conduct for Prevention of Insider Trading, the trading window for trading in the Company’s equity shares has been closed from January 01, 2026, till the expiry of 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results.</p><ul><li>Vaswani Industries Ltd to consider and approve Q4 results on Feb 13, 2026</li><li>Trading Window closed from Jan 01, 2026, till 48 hours after result declaration</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/eb9b906d-1564-466b-ab4b-278840564bdc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VASWANI INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>