<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:23:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[GISOLUTION] Teamo Productions HQ Ltd to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 &amp; Nine Months Ended Dec 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GI+ENGINEERING+SOLUTIONS+LTD.&title=Teamo+Productions+HQ+Ltd+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Ended+Dec+31%2C+2025&newsId=de393c46-2883-4bdf-b809-9b4b2c8a2100&token=ZGUzOTNjNDYtMjg4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de393c46-2883-4bdf-b809-9b4b2c8a2100</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 17:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Teamo Productions HQ Ltd has announced a meeting of the Board of Directors on January 14, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in securities of the company remains closed for the Designated Persons and their immediate relatives till the expiry of 48 hours after the declaration of un-audited financial results.</p><ul><li>Teamo Productions HQ Ltd to consider and approve unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended Dec 31, 2025</li><li>The meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on Jan 14, 2026</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities of the company remains closed for Designated Persons and their immediate relatives</li><li>The closure of the trading window will last till the expiry of 48 hours after the declaration of un-audited financial results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/94c227d7-a1fb-4c30-afbd-84255cdc77a3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GI ENGINEERING SOLUTIONS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INFY*] Infosys Science Foundation Honors Outstanding Researchers with the Infosys Prize 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INFOSYS+LTD.&title=Infosys+Science+Foundation+Honors+Outstanding+Researchers+with+the+Infosys+Prize+2025&newsId=32ba2361-bb90-4f3d-a2c2-91330c848a66&token=MzJiYTIzNjEtYmI5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32ba2361-bb90-4f3d-a2c2-91330c848a66</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 17:11:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Award</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Infosys Science Foundation (ISF) awarded the winners of the Infosys Prize 2025 at a felicitation ceremony in Bengaluru. The prize, now in its 17th year, recognizes researchers under the age of 40 and includes a pure gold medal, a citation, and a prize purse of USD 100,000. The winners were felicitated by Nobel laureate Randy Schekman across six categories: Economics, Engineering and Computer Science, Humanities and Social Sciences, Life Sciences, Mathematical Sciences, and Physical Sciences.</p><ul><li>The Infosys Prize 2025 recognizes exceptional researchers under the age of 40 across six categories.</li><li>Winners were awarded a pure gold medal, a citation, and a prize purse of USD 100,000.</li><li>The awards were presented by Nobel laureate Randy Schekman.</li><li>The Infosys Science Foundation has been awarding the Infosys Prize since 2009.</li><li>The prize aims to celebrate success in research and stand as a marker of excellence in various fields.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ff569a44-3fcc-433a-8c53-8c142fa75adf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INFOSYS LTD. | Category: Award</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RAILTEL] RailTel Corporation of India Ltd Announces Changes in Senior Management Personnel</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RailTel+Corporation+of+India+Ltd&title=RailTel+Corporation+of+India+Ltd+Announces+Changes+in+Senior+Management+Personnel&newsId=9cfdfd53-1d77-404f-89e8-c38755add62a&token=OWNmZGZkNTMtMWQ3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9cfdfd53-1d77-404f-89e8-c38755add62a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 17:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>RailTel Corporation of India Ltd has announced changes in its senior management personnel. Dr. Sharad Sharma, Sh. Deepak Prakash, and Sh. Ramphool Garg have been re-designated, pursuant to Regulation 30 of the SE BI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. Dr. Sharma, who was the Executive Director, will no longer be part of the senior management. Similarly, Sh. Deepak Prakash and Sh. Ramphool Garg, who were Pr. Executive Directors, will also not be part of the senior management. However, they will continue with the Company in their new roles as ED/TM/ADI/WR/RCIL, ED/POM/NR/RCIL, and ED/TM/Jaipur/NR/RCIL respectively. These changes will be effective from January 10, 2026.</p><ul><li>RailTel Corporation of India Ltd announces changes in senior management personnel</li><li>Dr. Sharad Sharma, Sh. Deepak Prakash, and Sh. Ramphool Garg have been re-designated</li><li>Dr. Sharma, Sh. Deepak Prakash, and Sh. Ramphool Garg will no longer be part of the senior management</li><li>Dr. Sharma, Sh. Deepak Prakash, and Sh. Ramphool Garg will continue with the Company in their new roles</li><li>Changes will be effective from January 10, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/23b2c621-bc7c-4e8b-9d5b-20f75b283cf3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RailTel Corporation of India Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SCHAND] S Chand and Company Ltd Acquires 100% Stake in CPD Singapore Education Services Pte. Limited for SGD 1,500,000</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=S+Chand+and+Company+Ltd&title=S+Chand+and+Company+Ltd+Acquires+100%25+Stake+in+CPD+Singapore+Education+Services+Pte.+Limited+for+SGD+1%2C500%2C000&newsId=879b5e7b-8054-46f1-a9b2-848cdf65a8a3&token=ODc5YjVlN2ItODA1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">879b5e7b-8054-46f1-a9b2-848cdf65a8a3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>S Chand and Company Ltd, through its wholly owned subsidiary New Saraswati House (India) Private Limited, has agreed to acquire 100% ownership in CPD Singapore Education Services Pte. Limited for a total consideration of SGD 1,500,000. CPD Singapore is a Singapore-based provider of education-support services and publisher of International Curriculum (IB/IGCSE) school books. The acquisition is structured to be completed in two tranches. Upon completion, CPD Singapore will become a step-down subsidiary of S Chand and Company Ltd. The transaction does not fall under related party transactions and no promoter/promoter group/group companies have interest in this transaction.</p><ul><li>S Chand and Company Ltd to acquire 100% stake in CPD Singapore Education Services Pte. Limited</li><li>Transaction value of SGD 1,500,000 (Singapore Dollars One Million Five Hundred Thousand)</li><li>Acquisition to be completed in two tranches</li><li>CPD Singapore provides education-support services and publishes International Curriculum (IB/IGCSE) school books</li><li>No related party transactions involved</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/29dc46cf-14a4-4960-94dc-a273912662e7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: S Chand and Company Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ORIENTCEM] Orient Cement Ltd Shifts Registered Office from Orissa to Gujarat</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Orient+Cement+Ltd&title=Orient+Cement+Ltd+Shifts+Registered+Office+from+Orissa+to+Gujarat&newsId=c33dd6bb-8c53-4efa-b9b2-d6eddc1538ed&token=YzMzZGQ2YmItOGM1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c33dd6bb-8c53-4efa-b9b2-d6eddc1538ed</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 16:21:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Orient Cement Limited has informed the Stock Exchange about the change in its Registered Office address. The company has shifted its Registered office from ‘Unit VIII, Plot No.7, Bhoinagar, Bhubaneswar, Orissa, 751012’ to ‘Adani Corporate House, Shantigram, Near Vaishnodevi Circle, S. G. Highway, Anmedabad - 382421, Gujarat’ effective from 9th January, 2026. This shift follows a special resolution to alter the provisions of its Memorandum of Association with respect to the place of the Registered Office.</p><ul><li>Orient Cement Ltd has shifted its Registered Office from Orissa to Gujarat.</li><li>The new Registered Office address is &apos;Adani Corporate House, Shantigram, Near Vaishnodevi Circle, S. G. Highway, Anmedabad - 382421, Gujarat&apos;.</li><li>The shift will be effective from 9th January, 2026.</li><li>The shift follows a special resolution to alter the provisions of its Memorandum of Association.</li><li>The order for the change of state was confirmed by an order of the Regional Director on 18/12/2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/65bbd954-9147-4718-afe4-9cdd43292b6f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Orient Cement Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ELNET] Elnet Technologies Ltd. to Appoint Mrs. A.R. Rajalakshmi as Non-Executive Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ELNET+TECHNOLOGIES+LTD.-%24&title=Elnet+Technologies+Ltd.+to+Appoint+Mrs.+A.R.+Rajalakshmi+as+Non-Executive+Director&newsId=4510862a-c777-44a3-a6ca-97ecc93717e8&token=NDUxMDg2MmEtYzc3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4510862a-c777-44a3-a6ca-97ecc93717e8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:54:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Elnet Technologies Limited has called for an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) to appoint Mrs. A.R. Rajalakshmi as a Non-Executive Director. The EGM is scheduled to be held on Tuesday, February 03, 2026, at 11:30 A.M. (IST) through Video Conferencing (‘VC’)/ Other Audio-Visual Means (‘OAVM’). The notice of the EGM has been sent to all the members of the Company whose email addresses are registered with the Company or Depositories or Registrar and Share Transfer Agent of the Company. The remote e-voting period commences on Friday, January 30, 2026 at 9.00 a.m. (IST) and ends on Monday, February 02, 2026 5.00 p.m. (IST).</p><ul><li>Elnet Technologies Limited has called for an EGM to appoint Mrs. A.R. Rajalakshmi as a Non-Executive Director.</li><li>The EGM will be held on Tuesday, February 03, 2026, at 11:30 A.M. (IST) through VC/OAVM.</li><li>The notice of the EGM has been sent to all registered members.</li><li>The remote e-voting period commences on Friday, January 30, 2026 at 9.00 a.m. (IST) and ends on Monday, February 02, 2026 5.00 p.m. (IST).</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4119ba2e-f5b8-441e-8304-823d5d5af246.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ELNET TECHNOLOGIES LTD.-$ | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ELNET] Elnet Technologies Ltd. to Appoint Mrs. A.R. Rajalakshmi as Non-Executive Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ELNET+TECHNOLOGIES+LTD.-%24&title=Elnet+Technologies+Ltd.+to+Appoint+Mrs.+A.R.+Rajalakshmi+as+Non-Executive+Director&newsId=5f92c1f0-27d4-4d50-8b6f-d8d4d00d1c99&token=NWY5MmMxZjAtMjdk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f92c1f0-27d4-4d50-8b6f-d8d4d00d1c99</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:42:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Elnet Technologies Ltd. has announced an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) to appoint Mrs. A.R. Rajalakshmi as a Non-Executive Director. The EGM will be held on Tuesday, February 03, 2026, at 11.30 A.M. (IST) through Video Conferencing (‘VC’)/ Other Audio-Visual Means (‘OAVM’). The Notice of EGM has been sent to all the members of the Company whose email addresses are registered with the Company or Depositories or Registrar and Share Transfer Agent of the Company. The remote e- voting period commences on Friday, January 30, 2026 at 9.00 a.m. (IST) and ends on Monday, February 02nd, 2026 5.00 p.m. (IST).</p><ul><li>Elnet Technologies Ltd. to hold Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM)</li><li>Mrs. A.R. Rajalakshmi to be appointed as Non-Executive Director</li><li>EGM to be held on Tuesday, February 03, 2026</li><li>Meeting to be held through Video Conferencing (‘VC’)/ Other Audio-Visual Means (‘OAVM’)</li><li>Remote e-voting from January 30, 2026 to February 02, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/817d5bd4-f5cb-47cc-9478-c9841becc465.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ELNET TECHNOLOGIES LTD.-$ | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WAAREERTL] CEO of Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd Resigns After 10 Years</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Waaree+Renewable+Technologies+Ltd&title=CEO+of+Waaree+Renewable+Technologies+Ltd+Resigns+After+10+Years&newsId=ad4da952-ff4a-4de9-8184-3fa25c1f4c76&token=YWQ0ZGE5NTItZmY0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad4da952-ff4a-4de9-8184-3fa25c1f4c76</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kamlesh Harchandani, the CEO of Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd, has resigned from his position effective from the close of business hours on January 09, 2026. Harchandani has been with the company for over a decade and has decided to move on to new professional and personal chapters that align with his long-term aspirations and goals.</p><ul><li>Kamlesh Harchandani resigns from his position as CEO- Data Center Business at Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd.</li><li>Harchandani has been with the company for over a decade.</li><li>He is transitioning to new professional and personal chapters.</li><li>The resignation is effective from the close of business hours on January 09, 2026.</li><li>Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd is a subsidiary of Waaree Energies Limited.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/63f9451b-6ab7-4f0a-b399-22eb951dd5f3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GEE] GEE Ltd Board Meeting on January 16, 2026 to Approve Q3 Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GEE+LTD.&title=GEE+Ltd+Board+Meeting+on+January+16%2C+2026+to+Approve+Q3+Results&newsId=724620fb-547c-4daf-9d19-ae1d93c39528&token=NzI0NjIwZmItNTQ3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">724620fb-547c-4daf-9d19-ae1d93c39528</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>GEE Ltd, a company based in Maharashtra, India, has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 16, 2026, through video conferencing at 03.30 P.M (IST) to consider and approve the Standalone Un-Audited Financial Results of the Company along with Limited Review Report for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The trading window will remain closed till 48 hours after the announcement of the financial results.</p><ul><li>GEE Ltd Board Meeting scheduled on January 16, 2026</li><li>Meeting to consider and approve Q3 FY2025-26 financial results</li><li>Trading window to remain closed till 48 hours after the announcement of the results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/42cfbfb5-f63c-447e-9777-2b5aa5262f1e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GEE LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IOC] Indian Oil Corporation Ltd Announces Changes in Senior Management Personnel</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDIAN+OIL+CORPORATION+LTD.&title=Indian+Oil+Corporation+Ltd+Announces+Changes+in+Senior+Management+Personnel&newsId=8f89a531-8973-4261-bd58-f2682e3ad5e6&token=OGY4OWE1MzEtODk3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f89a531-8973-4261-bd58-f2682e3ad5e6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 15:11:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indian Oil Corporation Ltd has announced changes in its senior management personnel. Pursuant to the Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations 2015, the following officials have been promoted to Senior Management Personnel (Executive Directors- One level below the Board of Directors): Sanjib Biswas, G R K Murthy, R R Raje, Samarendra Nath Jha, Nitin Bhatnagar, Sanjay Bhandari, Puneet Agarwal, Madhavi B. Patra, Girish Ranjan, and Sumit Basu. Their profiles and XBRL files will be provided in due course. This announcement is for information and record purposes.</p><ul><li>Indian Oil Corporation Ltd announces changes in senior management personnel</li><li>Promotion of officials to Senior Management Personnel (Executive Directors- One level below the Board of Directors)</li><li>Promoted officials include Sanjib Biswas, G R K Murthy, R R Raje, Samarendra Nath Jha, Nitin Bhatnagar, Sanjay Bhandari, Puneet Agarwal, Madhavi B. Patra, Girish Ranjan, and Sumit Basu</li><li>Profiles and XBRL files of the promoted officials will be provided in due course</li><li>Announcement made pursuant to the Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/346f9433-df87-48b4-bef6-fc215669e0b1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDIAN OIL CORPORATION LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>