<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:25:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SUVENPHAR] Cohance Lifesciences Grants 3,89,668 Stock Options Under ESOP 2023</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Suven+Pharmaceuticals+Ltd&title=Cohance+Lifesciences+Grants+3%2C89%2C668+Stock+Options+Under+ESOP+2023&newsId=37604cba-5601-482d-a7e3-ec0671a65f95&token=Mzc2MDRjYmEtNTYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37604cba-5601-482d-a7e3-ec0671a65f95</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 22:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cohance Lifesciences Ltd has approved the grant of 3,89,668 stock options to eligible employees under the Employee Stock Option Plan 2023 (ESOP 2023). This includes 2,18,077 stock options granted pursuant to the Scheme of Amalgamation between Cohance Lifesciences Limited and erstwhile Cohance Lifesciences Limited. The options have a vesting period of not earlier than 1 year and not later than 10 years from the date of grant. The exercise period is up to 3 years from the date of vesting.</p><ul><li>Grant of 3,89,668 stock options to eligible employees under ESOP 2023</li><li>Includes 2,18,077 stock options granted pursuant to Scheme of Amalgamation</li><li>Vesting period of not earlier than 1 year and not later than 10 years from the date of grant</li><li>Exercise period is up to 3 years from the date of vesting</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/69f63bdc-1bd5-40b7-89e3-b572ce2a8e47.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Suven Pharmaceuticals Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FMNL] Future Market Networks Ltd Announces Merger Application with Metawear Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=FUTURE+MARKET+NETWORKS+LTD.&title=Future+Market+Networks+Ltd+Announces+Merger+Application+with+Metawear+Limited&newsId=da6ce433-8f8d-4ea8-ae92-9af75a06b22b&token=ZGE2Y2U0MzMtOGY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">da6ce433-8f8d-4ea8-ae92-9af75a06b22b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 22:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Merger</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Future Market Networks Ltd has filed an application for approval of merger between Metawear Limited and itself with the National Company Law Tribunal, Mumbai Bench. The merger application was submitted on 17th January, 2025, following in-principle approval from stock exchanges BSE and NSE. The company will keep stock exchanges updated on further developments regarding the scheme.</p><ul><li>Future Market Networks Ltd and Metawear Limited have applied for merger under section 230 to section 232 and other applicable provisions of the Companies Act, 2013.</li><li>The merger application has been submitted to the National Company Law Tribunal, Mumbai Bench on 17th January, 2025.</li><li>In-principle approval has been received from stock exchanges BSE and NSE.</li><li>Future Market Networks Ltd will keep stock exchanges updated on further developments regarding the merger scheme.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8d3f744a-255b-4a1f-8e4f-9821daba43ca.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: FUTURE MARKET NETWORKS LTD. | Category: Merger</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAMHI] Samhi Hotels Ltd Incorporates Wholly-Owned Subsidiary SAMHI Skyline Private Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Samhi+Hotels+Ltd&title=Samhi+Hotels+Ltd+Incorporates+Wholly-Owned+Subsidiary+SAMHI+Skyline+Private+Limited&newsId=e445e377-5032-4235-ad8f-e0e4e2bdd3cc&token=ZTQ0NWUzNzctNTAz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e445e377-5032-4235-ad8f-e0e4e2bdd3cc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:51:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Samhi Hotels Ltd has incorporated a wholly-owned subsidiary company named SAMHI Skyline Private Limited on 16th January 2026. The new subsidiary has been registered with an authorized share capital of INR 10,00,000 (Indian Rupees Ten Lakhs Only) and will carry on the business to purchase, manage, own, acquire, lease, promote, takeover or lease and to operate and run hotels, holiday resorts, motels, cottages, and accommodations of all description in India or abroad. The entire Paid-up Share Capital of INR 1,00,000 (Indian Rupees One Lakh Only) will be held by SAMHI Hotels Limited, the Holding Company.</p><ul><li>Samhi Hotels Ltd incorporates a wholly-owned subsidiary, SAMHI Skyline Private Limited</li><li>New subsidiary registered with an authorized share capital of INR 10,00,000</li><li>SAMHI Skyline to operate in the Hotel business with all facilities in India or abroad</li><li>The entire Paid-up Share Capital of INR 1,00,000 held by SAMHI Hotels Limited, the Holding Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c15d827f-69eb-427d-af63-e128997a0a36.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Samhi Hotels Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WELCORP] Welspun Corp Ltd Acquires 2.57% Stake in Welspun Mauritius Holdings for USD 5.962 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Welspun+Corp+Limited&title=Welspun+Corp+Ltd+Acquires+2.57%25+Stake+in+Welspun+Mauritius+Holdings+for+USD+5.962+Million&newsId=f200901a-b37e-47f5-abdd-d93847485558&token=ZjIwMDkwMWEtYjM3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f200901a-b37e-47f5-abdd-d93847485558</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Welspun Corp Ltd has approved the acquisition of a 2.57% equity stake in Welspun Mauritius Holdings Limited (WMHL) from Welspun Pipes Inc., USA, a wholly-owned subsidiary of the Company. The transaction is valued at not more than USD 5.962 million and is expected to streamline the Company’s overseas holding structure. The transaction does not have any material impact on the operations, financial position, or profitability of the Company.</p><ul><li>Welspun Corp Ltd to acquire a 2.57% equity stake in Welspun Mauritius Holdings Limited</li><li>Transaction valued at not more than USD 5.962 million</li><li>Objective is to streamline the Company’s overseas holding structure</li><li>No material impact on the operations, financial position, or profitability of the Company</li><li>Transaction to be completed by FY 2025-2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f3274b19-324d-45b4-9b6f-3e60a7a7e04b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Welspun Corp Limited | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WELCORP] Welspun Corp Ltd Acquires 2.57% Equity Stake in Welspun Mauritius Holdings Limited for USD 5.962 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Welspun+Corp+Limited&title=Welspun+Corp+Ltd+Acquires+2.57%25+Equity+Stake+in+Welspun+Mauritius+Holdings+Limited+for+USD+5.962+Million&newsId=d16d68be-5e3c-4889-b079-2e99f6e83c5e&token=ZDE2ZDY4YmUtNWUz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d16d68be-5e3c-4889-b079-2e99f6e83c5e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:11:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Welspun Corp Ltd has approved the acquisition of a 2.57% equity stake in Welspun Mauritius Holdings Limited from Welspun Pipes Inc., USA, a wholly-owned subsidiary of the Company. The transaction is valued at not exceeding USD 5.962 million, subject to regulatory compliances. Upon completion, Welspun Mauritius Holdings Limited will become a direct wholly-owned subsidiary of the Company. The objective of the proposed acquisition is to streamline the Company’s overseas holding structure.</p><ul><li>Welspun Corp Ltd to acquire 2.57% equity stake in Welspun Mauritius Holdings Limited</li><li>Transaction valued at not exceeding USD 5.962 million</li><li>Welspun Mauritius Holdings Limited to become direct wholly-owned subsidiary of the Company</li><li>Acquisition aimed at streamlining the Company’s overseas holding structure</li><li>No impact on the Consolidated Financials</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/204e5916-4599-4808-a823-ec22f10581ee.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Welspun Corp Limited | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[THYROCARE] Thyrocare Technologies Ltd: Statutory Auditor M S K A &amp; Associates Converts to LLP</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Thyrocare+Technologies+Ltd&title=Thyrocare+Technologies+Ltd%3A+Statutory+Auditor+M+S+K+A+%26+Associates+Converts+to+LLP&newsId=2a8b53e6-520b-400d-8575-d4dc9a4e8842&token=MmE4YjUzZTYtNTIw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a8b53e6-520b-400d-8575-d4dc9a4e8842</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:11:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Auditor Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Thyrocare Technologies Ltd has been informed about the conversion of its Statutory Auditor, M S K A &amp; Associates, into a Limited Liability Partnership (LLP) under the Limited Liability Partnership Act, 2008. The new name of the auditor is MSKA&amp; Associates LLP (LLPIN: ACT-3789), with ICAI Firm Registration Number 105047W (Old) / W101187 (New). This conversion does not result in a change of audit responsibilities, resignation, or appointment of a new auditor; the audit engagement continues uninterrupted.</p><ul><li>Thyrocare Technologies Ltd&apos;s Statutory Auditor, M S K A &amp; Associates, has converted into a Limited Liability Partnership (LLP) named MSKA&amp; Associates LLP.</li><li>The conversion does not lead to any changes in audit responsibilities, resignation, or appointment of a new auditor.</li><li>The audit engagement continues uninterrupted.</li><li>MSKA&amp; Associates LLP has ICAI Firm Registration Number 105047W (Old) / W101187 (New).</li><li>The conversion is in compliance with Regulation 30 and Schedule III of the SEBI Listing Regulations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c393293d-02b4-432b-8537-0a2ab3f6c3d3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Thyrocare Technologies Ltd | Category: Auditor Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WAAREEENER] Waaree Energies Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results on Jan 21, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Waaree+Energies+Ltd&title=Waaree+Energies+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+on+Jan+21%2C+2026&newsId=9904c9d6-1536-4bfe-94df-c7bc24a834b6&token=OTkwNGM5ZDYtMTUz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9904c9d6-1536-4bfe-94df-c7bc24a834b6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 15:57:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Waaree Energies Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 21, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results (Standalone and Consolidated) for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting is scheduled in accordance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, and the Company&apos;s Insider Trading Code under the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company will be closed for all the Directors, Key Managerial Persons, Designated Persons of the Company and their Immediate Relatives from January 01, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of the Unaudited Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Waaree Energies Ltd to consider and approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>The meeting is scheduled in accordance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>The trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company will be closed for all the Directors, Key Managerial Persons, Designated Persons of the Company and their Immediate Relatives from January 01, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of the Unaudited Financial Results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c1801134-ae2a-4328-95f6-68f00fe4cec8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Waaree Energies Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DODLA] Dodla Dairy Ltd to Approve Q4 2025 Financial Results on Jan 27, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Dodla+Dairy+Ltd&title=Dodla+Dairy+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+2025+Financial+Results+on+Jan+27%2C+2026&newsId=b3ac448c-53f7-40d7-84c0-0c261cd2dde9&token=YjNhYzQ0OGMtNTNm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3ac448c-53f7-40d7-84c0-0c261cd2dde9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 15:51:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dodla Dairy Ltd has announced a meeting of the Board of Directors on January 27, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. The meeting will take place at the company&apos;s registered office in Hyderabad, Telangana, India. The trading window for all designated persons and their immediate relatives will remain closed until 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results.</p><ul><li>Dodla Dairy Ltd to approve Q4 2025 financial results on Jan 27, 2026</li><li>The meeting will be held at the company&apos;s registered office in Hyderabad, Telangana, India</li><li>Trading window to remain closed until 48 hours after the declaration of financial results</li><li>The unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter ended 31 December 2025 will be considered and approved</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a17801ce-f3e4-4f64-8d99-d898613265af.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Dodla Dairy Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDIGO] InterGlobe Aviation Committed to Addressing Operational Disruptions and Ensuring Robustness</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=InterGlobe+Aviation+Ltd&title=InterGlobe+Aviation+Committed+to+Addressing+Operational+Disruptions+and+Ensuring+Robustness&newsId=c2cd68a7-20ec-4ef5-8dd0-22f8b96d7098&token=YzJjZDY4YTctMjBl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c2cd68a7-20ec-4ef5-8dd0-22f8b96d7098</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 15:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>InterGlobe Aviation Ltd, the company behind IndiGo, has received orders from the Directorate General of Civil Aviation of India regarding major operational disruptions in early December 2025. The company, through its Board and Management, has committed to addressing the issues and taking appropriate measures in a thoughtful and timely manner. An in-depth review of internal processes has been underway to ensure the airline&apos;s resilience and robustness. IndiGo remains committed to serving India and contributing to its growth as a Global aviation major by 2030.</p><ul><li>InterGlobe Aviation Ltd received orders from the Directorate General of Civil Aviation regarding operational disruptions in December 2025.</li><li>Company committed to addressing the issues and taking appropriate measures.</li><li>An in-depth review of internal processes is underway to ensure resilience and robustness.</li><li>IndiGo remains committed to serving India and contributing to its growth as a Global aviation major by 2030.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b1a2ab00-df29-496b-9c9c-575078bc528e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: InterGlobe Aviation Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CGPOWER] CG Power Secures ¥900 Crore Power Transformers Order from Tallgrass for US Data Center Segment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CG+Power+and+Industrial+Solutions+Ltd&title=CG+Power+Secures+%C2%A5900+Crore+Power+Transformers+Order+from+Tallgrass+for+US+Data+Center+Segment&newsId=d26e5f12-2af4-4848-b7fd-90f228d417e6&token=ZDI2ZTVmMTItMmFm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d26e5f12-2af4-4848-b7fd-90f228d417e6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 15:22:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>CG Power and Industrial Solutions Limited has secured a landmark order valued at ~¥900 Crore ($99.2M) from Tallgrass Integrated Logistics Solutions LLC USA, for a large-scale data center project in the United States. This order marks CG&apos;s entry into the global data center segment and is the largest single order ever won by CG. The transformers will be designed, manufactured, and tested at CG’s state-of-the-art facilities in India and will be executed over a delivery period of 12 to 20 months.</p><ul><li>CG Power has secured a landmark order valued at ~¥900 Crore ($99.2M) from Tallgrass for a large-scale data center project in the United States.</li><li>This order marks CG&apos;s entry into the global data center segment and is the largest single order ever won by CG.</li><li>The transformers will be designed, manufactured, and tested at CG’s state-of-the-art facilities in India.</li><li>The delivery period for the order is 12 to 20 months.</li><li>This win opens up a significant long-term opportunity pipeline in global data center projects for CG.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cf147f40-4b55-4061-a3ff-50bbc5a8fdd7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CG Power and Industrial Solutions Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>