<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:28:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[KMSUGAR] K M Sugar Mills Clarifies Unauthorized Transfer of 0.54% Shares Due to Stockholding Corporation of India’s Error</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=K.M.SUGAR+MILLS+LTD.&title=K+M+Sugar+Mills+Clarifies+Unauthorized+Transfer+of+0.54%25+Shares+Due+to+Stockholding+Corporation+of+India%E2%80%99s+Error&newsId=6c118134-2abc-41a5-9f56-b9aab9b2dfa6&token=NmMxMTgxMzQtMmFi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c118134-2abc-41a5-9f56-b9aab9b2dfa6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:25:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>K M Sugar Mills Ltd issued a general update to clarify the movement in promoter shareholding. Stockholding Corporation of India Limited (SCI) had erroneously transferred 5,00,000 (0.54%) equity shares to an incorrect demat account on 11th December 2025. This transfer was solely due to an inadvertent error attributable to SCI, without any prior intimation, authorization, or instruction from the promoters or promoter group. The error occurred during the closure of the demat account held by Jhunjhunwala Securities Private Limited (promoter group) with SCI. The promoters reserve the right to hold SCI accountable for the error. No trading or acquisition of the aforesaid equity shares has taken place, and no disclosure is required under SEBI regulations. The company shall update further as and when SCI rectifies the error.</p><ul><li>K M Sugar Mills clarifies unauthorized transfer of 0.54% shares</li><li>Transfer due to Stockholding Corporation of India’s inadvertent error</li><li>No trading or acquisition of the shares has taken place</li><li>Promoters reserve the right to hold SCI accountable</li><li>Company to update further upon error rectification by SCI</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4e1578ae-16a2-42fd-a234-c0ceaa390694.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: K.M.SUGAR MILLS LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IDEAFORGE] Ideaforge Technology Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on Jan 22, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ideaforge+Technology+Ltd&title=Ideaforge+Technology+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+Jan+22%2C+2026&newsId=2e3d2864-2265-42c8-a564-c38740e4274d&token=MmUzZDI4NjQtMjI2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e3d2864-2265-42c8-a564-c38740e4274d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:19:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ideaforge Technology Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 22, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited (Standalone &amp; Consolidated) Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company will remain closed up to 48 hours after the declaration of the Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Ideaforge Technology Ltd to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company will be closed up to 48 hours after the declaration of the Financial Results.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/10aab62f-ac6f-495e-b6e7-b89299c42f46.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ideaforge Technology Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZSANMCOM] Sanmitra Commercial Ltd Proposes Name Change to Tandhan Industries/Polyventure Ltd and Shifting of Registered Office to West Bengal</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SANMITRA+COMMERCIAL+LTD.&title=Sanmitra+Commercial+Ltd+Proposes+Name+Change+to+Tandhan+Industries%2FPolyventure+Ltd+and+Shifting+of+Registered+Office+to+West+Bengal&newsId=fd0f2cb6-ee7f-41ac-8639-89711342faa8&token=ZmQwZjJjYjYtZWU3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd0f2cb6-ee7f-41ac-8639-89711342faa8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sanmitra Commercial Ltd announced that its Board of Directors has approved a proposal to change the company&apos;s name to Tandhan Industries Limited or Tandhan Polyventure Limited, subject to shareholder and regulatory approval. The Board also approved the shifting of the company&apos;s Registered Office from Maharashtra to West Bengal, pending necessary approvals. An Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) will be convened for shareholder approval. The decisions were made during a Board meeting held on January 7, 2026.</p><ul><li>Proposal to change the name of Sanmitra Commercial Ltd to Tandhan Industries/Polyventure Limited</li><li>Shift of the Registered Office from Maharashtra to West Bengal</li><li>Pending necessary approvals from shareholders and regulatory authorities</li><li>Plans to convene an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) for shareholder approval</li><li>Board meeting held on January 7, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/50bb2a57-f717-4668-a3ff-64a8e720fc19.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SANMITRA COMMERCIAL LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RADIOCITY] Music Broadcast Ltd Declares Interim Dividend &amp; Redemption Amount for NCRPS Holders</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Music+Broadcast+Ltd&title=Music+Broadcast+Ltd+Declares+Interim+Dividend+%26+Redemption+Amount+for+NCRPS+Holders&newsId=53680f5b-6412-4b80-af93-f95f6d77572b&token=NTM2ODBmNWItNjQx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53680f5b-6412-4b80-af93-f95f6d77572b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:14:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Music Broadcast Ltd has declared an interim dividend for the Financial Year 2025-26 at the rate of 0.1% on the Non-Convertible Non-Cumulative Redeemable Preference Shares (NCRPS) of the Company, amounting to 0.01/- (Rupees One Paisa) per NCRPS. The Board has also approved the redemption of the aforementioned NCRPS at 120/- (Rupees One Hundred and Twenty only) per NCRPS upon maturity. The dividend and redemption amount will be paid to the eligible NCRPS holders whose names appear in the register of members as on the Record Date i.e. Friday, January 09, 2026. The company has also informed about the tax deduction and withholding tax rate variations depending on the residential status of the shareholder and the exemptions as enumerated in the Income-tax Act, 1961.</p><ul><li>Music Broadcast Ltd declares an interim dividend for NCRPS holders</li><li>The dividend rate is 0.1% on the NCRPS of the Company</li><li>The redemption amount is approved at 120/- (Rupees One Hundred and Twenty only) per NCRPS upon maturity</li><li>The dividend and redemption amount will be paid to the eligible NCRPS holders</li><li>The tax deduction and withholding tax rate varies depending on the shareholder&apos;s residential status and exemptions</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/824c38fc-15aa-4eb7-8f4d-d94cf5d84bf7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Music Broadcast Ltd | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UJJIVANSFB] Ujjivan Small Finance Bank Ltd to Approve Q4 Results on January 22, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ujjivan+Small+Finance+Bank+Ltd&title=Ujjivan+Small+Finance+Bank+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+Results+on+January+22%2C+2026&newsId=39932215-17a4-47d7-bd83-93179e62fa9a&token=Mzk5MzIyMTUtMTdh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">39932215-17a4-47d7-bd83-93179e62fa9a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:10:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ujjivan Small Finance Bank Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 22, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in Equity Shares of the Bank by its designated persons and their dependent(s) will be closed from January 01, 2026, and will open 48 hours after the announcement of the aforesaid Financial Results. The PAN freeze for each of the aforesaid designated persons has been enabled through the depositories for the stated period.</p><ul><li>Ujjivan Small Finance Bank Ltd to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for Q4 2025</li><li>Trading window for dealing in Equity Shares to be closed from January 01, 2026</li><li>Trading window to open 48 hours after the announcement of Q4 2025 financial results</li><li>PAN freeze for designated persons enabled through depositories for the period</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3cc2c9e4-ad15-4c91-ac16-d85687833df3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ujjivan Small Finance Bank Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BI] Bilcare Limited Announces Change in Email Address of Registrar and Transfer Agent</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BILCARE+LTD.-%24&title=Bilcare+Limited+Announces+Change+in+Email+Address+of+Registrar+and+Transfer+Agent&newsId=5e6bcdb3-c7fe-4dde-a2b6-c176493b897a&token=NWU2YmNkYjMtYzdm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5e6bcdb3-c7fe-4dde-a2b6-c176493b897a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:09:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bilcare Limited has informed the stock exchange about the change in the email address of its Registrar and Transfer Agent (RTA), MUFG Intime India Private Limited. The new email address for investor communications is investor.helpdesk@in.mpms.mufg.com. The RTA&apos;s office address and other details remain unchanged.</p><ul><li>Bilcare Limited has announced a change in the email address of its Registrar and Transfer Agent (RTA).</li><li>The new email address for investor communications is investor.helpdesk@in.mpms.mufg.com.</li><li>The RTA&apos;s office address and other details remain unchanged.</li><li>The update was shared with the stock exchange for record.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1e4fbf86-a4e3-4948-bded-412e8d8ce7c3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BILCARE LTD.-$ | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GOLDIAM] Goldiam International Ltd Opens 13th Store in Delhi</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GOLDIAM+INTERNATIONAL+LTD.&title=Goldiam+International+Ltd+Opens+13th+Store+in+Delhi&newsId=37e6522c-bf9c-43d8-9a75-3227e1883dd1&token=MzdlNjUyMmMtYmY5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37e6522c-bf9c-43d8-9a75-3227e1883dd1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:06:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Goldiam International Ltd has announced the opening of its 13th retail store under the brand name ‘ORIGEM’ in Paschim Vihar, Delhi. This expansion aligns with the company&apos;s long-term strategy of increasing its retail presence and strengthening customer engagement across key markets. The new store is located at A3/1, Ground Floor, Western Side, Paschim Vihar, Delhi-110063.</p><ul><li>Goldiam International Ltd opens its 13th retail store under the brand name ‘ORIGEM’ in Delhi.</li><li>The new store is located at Paschim Vihar, aligning with the company&apos;s strategy to expand its retail presence and engage with customers in key markets.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/83b61677-ed92-42e8-a09d-941d8e5e994e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GOLDIAM INTERNATIONAL LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ITCONS] ITCONS E-Solutions Ltd Allots 6,97,200 Equity Shares Following Warrant Conversion</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ITCONS+E-Solutions+Ltd&title=ITCONS+E-Solutions+Ltd+Allots+6%2C97%2C200+Equity+Shares+Following+Warrant+Conversion&newsId=da74e42c-3413-4ebd-b9b8-2288658d1ec8&token=ZGE3NGU0MmMtMzQx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">da74e42c-3413-4ebd-b9b8-2288658d1ec8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 05:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>ITCONS E-Solutions Ltd has allotted 6,97,200 equity shares following the conversion of warrants by various investors. The allotment was made at a price of Rs. 53.25 per share warrant, amounting to Rs. 3,71,25,900. The new equity shares rank pari passu with the existing shares. The company&apos;s paid-up equity capital has increased from Rs. 6,50,59,260 to Rs. 7,20,31,260. There are 78,65,600 warrants still outstanding for conversion within 18 months from the date of warrant allotment.</p><ul><li>ITCONS E-Solutions Ltd allotted 6,97,200 equity shares following warrant conversion.</li><li>The allotment was made at a price of Rs. 53.25 per share warrant, amounting to Rs. 3,71,25,900.</li><li>The new equity shares rank pari passu with the existing shares.</li><li>The company&apos;s paid-up equity capital has increased from Rs. 6,50,59,260 to Rs. 7,20,31,260.</li><li>78,65,600 warrants are still outstanding for conversion within 18 months.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/288b78ae-ef9c-4e3d-a122-f4c2c450b15b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ITCONS E-Solutions Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ELECTCAST] Supreme Court Upholds Dismissal of Insolvency Application Against Electrosteel Castings Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ELECTROSTEEL+CASTINGS+LTD.&title=Supreme+Court+Upholds+Dismissal+of+Insolvency+Application+Against+Electrosteel+Castings+Ltd&newsId=c2a5e090-1e40-4db2-858a-57afbc018a44&token=YzJhNWUwOTAtMWU0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c2a5e090-1e40-4db2-858a-57afbc018a44</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 05:45:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In a recent development, the Hon’ble Supreme Court has upheld the judgement dated 24 January 2024 of the Hon’ble National Company Law Appellate Tribunal (NCLAT) which dismissed the application of UV Asset Reconstruction Company Limited against Electrosteel Castings Ltd under Section 7 of the Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code, 2016. The Supreme Court reaffirmed that the Company cannot be treated as a guarantor for financial facilities availed by Electrosteel Steels Limited. The Apex Court also held that the approval and / or implementation of the Resolution Plan of Vedanta Limited for ESL does not result in extinguishment of the entire debt, thereby allowing claims against Third Security Providers. This disclosure is in continuation of the company&apos;s earlier intimation dated 25 January 2024.</p><ul><li>Supreme Court upholds dismissal of UV Asset Reconstruction Company&apos;s insolvency application against Electrosteel Castings Ltd</li><li>Company cannot be treated as a guarantor for financial facilities availed by Electrosteel Steels Limited</li><li>Supreme Court allows claims against Third Security Providers as debt not fully extinguished</li><li>Disclosure is in continuation of the company&apos;s earlier intimation dated 25 January 2024</li><li>Relates to the judgement dated 24 January 2024 of the Hon’ble National Company Law Appellate Tribunal (NCLAT)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/160263e0-3861-43fb-bf6a-f4a02a1b05c7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ELECTROSTEEL CASTINGS LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADANIGREEN] Adani Green Energy Ltd Incorporates New Subsidiary Adani Ecogen Seven Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Adani+Green+Energy+Ltd&title=Adani+Green+Energy+Ltd+Incorporates+New+Subsidiary+Adani+Ecogen+Seven+Limited&newsId=ea743843-c89b-4ee9-9ecf-95777d59def2&token=ZWE3NDM4NDMtYzg5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ea743843-c89b-4ee9-9ecf-95777d59def2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 05:41:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Adani Renewable Energy Holding Eleven Limited, a wholly-owned subsidiary of Adani Green Energy Ltd, has incorporated a new wholly-owned subsidiary, Adani Ecogen Seven Limited (AE7L) on January 02, 2026. AE7L is registered in India and is yet to commence its business operations. The main objective of AE7L is to generate, develop, transform, distribute, transmit, sale, and supply any kind of power or electrical energy using wind energy, solar energy, or other renewable sources of energy.</p><ul><li>Adani Green Energy Ltd has incorporated a new wholly-owned subsidiary, Adani Ecogen Seven Limited (AE7L)</li><li>AE7L is registered in India and is yet to commence its business operations</li><li>AE7L&apos;s main objective is to generate, develop, transform, distribute, transmit, sale, and supply any kind of power or electrical energy using renewable sources of energy</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/17eb51d9-1015-45bf-89f3-ba49ff6d98a8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Adani Green Energy Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>