<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:57:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[KREONFIN] Kreon Finnancial Services Ltd to Approve Q3 Financial Results on Feb 13, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KREON+FINNANCIAL+SERVICES+LTD.&title=Kreon+Finnancial+Services+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+Financial+Results+on+Feb+13%2C+2026&newsId=0418cd10-950f-4276-b8b0-246c5b340c8f&token=MDQxOGNkMTAtOTUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0418cd10-950f-4276-b8b0-246c5b340c8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kreon Finnancial Services Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 13, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will also take note of compliances for the same quarter. The trading window for dealing in securities of the Company has been closed from January 01, 2026, and will remain closed till 48 hours after the declaration of the unaudited financial results.</p><ul><li>Kreon Finnancial Services Ltd to approve Q3 financial results on Feb 13, 2026</li><li>The meeting will also take note of compliances for the quarter ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities of the Company is closed from January 01, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ccf860c3-0cc6-4200-aeaf-66b5bde96805.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KREON FINNANCIAL SERVICES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SEPC] SEPC Limited Crosses FY25 Performance Benchmarks Within First 9 Months of FY26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SEPC+Ltd&title=SEPC+Limited+Crosses+FY25+Performance+Benchmarks+Within+First+9+Months+of+FY26&newsId=4945691b-735b-497f-9896-a9599f17ab40&token=NDk0NTY5MWItNzM1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4945691b-735b-497f-9896-a9599f17ab40</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 04:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>SEPC Limited, one of India&apos;s leading Engineering, Procurement and Construction (EPC) companies, has announced its Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 &amp; 9M FY26. The company has reported a 53.28% increase in Total Revenue and a 168.66% increase in Net Profit for the 9M FY26 compared to the same period last year. The Net Profit Margin has also increased by 215 Bps. The company has a strong pipeline and is well positioned to sustain momentum and drive long-term growth.</p><ul><li>Total Revenue for 9M FY26 increased by 53.28% compared to 9M FY25</li><li>Net Profit for 9M FY26 increased by 168.66% compared to 9M FY25</li><li>Net Profit Margin for 9M FY26 increased by 215 Bps compared to 9M FY25</li><li>SEPC Limited has a strong pipeline and is well positioned to sustain momentum and drive long-term growth</li><li>The company has reported strong operating momentum in Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue of ~796.89 crore, EBITDA of ~83.60 crore and net profit of ~39.81 crore</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3cb36ff1-b7f5-40dd-b9ac-0c52817aae29.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SEPC Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HITECH] Hi-Tech Pipes Ltd. Commences Commercial Production at Sikandrabad Unit-III, U.P. - Achieving 1 Million Tons Annual Installed Capacity</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Hi-Tech+Pipes+Ltd&title=Hi-Tech+Pipes+Ltd.+Commences+Commercial+Production+at+Sikandrabad+Unit-III%2C+U.P.+-+Achieving+1+Million+Tons+Annual+Installed+Capacity&newsId=7dcf5df9-4171-4d4d-9b4b-ad7313202ed6&token=N2RjZjVkZjktNDE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7dcf5df9-4171-4d4d-9b4b-ad7313202ed6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Hi-Tech Pipes Limited, a leading manufacturer of steel tubes, hollow sections, and value-added steel products in India, has started commercial production at its Sikandrabad Unit-III in Uttar Pradesh. This commissioning marks a significant milestone, achieving 1 million tons of annual installed capacity. The new facility enhances proximity to key consumption centers, improves supply chain efficiency, reduces logistics costs, and enables faster response to customer requirements across various segments. Hi-Tech Pipes Limited aims to add another 1 million tons of capacity over the medium term, aligning with its vision of building a robust, pan-India, and globally competitive manufacturing platform.</p><ul><li>Hi-Tech Pipes Limited commences commercial production at its Sikandrabad Unit-III, U.P.</li><li>Achievement of 1 million tons annual installed capacity</li><li>New facility enhances proximity to key consumption centers and improves supply chain efficiency</li><li>Targeting an additional 1 million tons of capacity over the medium term</li><li>Expanded capacity and diversified product offerings position Hi-Tech Pipes Limited to capitalize on both domestic and global demand opportunities</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2812fcd4-4879-484c-8609-2d8effb0ba91.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Hi-Tech Pipes Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AXISCADES] AXISCADES wins large production order for supplying avionics hardware for LCA Mk1A Program</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Axiscades+Technologies+Ltd&title=AXISCADES+wins+large+production+order+for+supplying+avionics+hardware+for+LCA+Mk1A+Program&newsId=8260b4db-bb7b-4fd3-a8ed-6edbbdecbd68&token=ODI2MGI0ZGItYmI3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8260b4db-bb7b-4fd3-a8ed-6edbbdecbd68</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:43:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>AXISCADES Technologies Limited, a chip to product company and a pioneer in Aerospace, Defence, Electronics, Semiconductor and Artificial Intelligence (ESAI), announced a new win in its Defence division. Its subsidiary, Mistral Solutions, received an order valued at approximately ¥80 crore under the LCA Mk1A programme of Hindustan Aeronautics Limited (HAL). This strategic win underscores AXISCADES Group’s strong commitment to the indigenisation of advanced avionics systems. Mistral Solutions will supply electronic hardware for the Mission Computer and Smart Multifunction Display. The systems will be manufactured and delivered from AXISCADES’ newly commissioned DAL (Devanahalli Atmanirbhar Complex) facility located at the Bangalore Aerospace Park.</p><ul><li>AXISCADES Technologies Limited announces new win in Defence division by its subsidiary Mistral Solutions</li><li>Mistral Solutions received an order valued at approximately ¥80 crore under the LCA Mk1A programme of HAL</li><li>Mistral Solutions will supply electronic hardware for the Mission Computer and Smart Multifunction Display</li><li>The systems will be manufactured and delivered from AXISCADES’ newly commissioned DAL (Devanahalli Atmanirbhar Complex) facility</li><li>This strategic win underscores AXISCADES Group’s strong commitment to the indigenisation of advanced avionics systems</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d8aeff0b-1ae0-40a7-aa2d-1365c3c7c3a1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Axiscades Technologies Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AXISCADES] Axiscaedes&apos; Subsidiary, Mistral Solutions, Bags Order for Supplying Mission Computer and Smart Display Unit Across Multiple Years</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Axiscades+Technologies+Ltd&title=Axiscaedes%27+Subsidiary%2C+Mistral+Solutions%2C+Bags+Order+for+Supplying+Mission+Computer+and+Smart+Display+Unit+Across+Multiple+Years&newsId=6ab72f45-aed4-49d0-9536-b9f764ba74e3&token=NmFiNzJmNDUtYWVk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ab72f45-aed4-49d0-9536-b9f764ba74e3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:38:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Pursuant to provisions of Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, Axiscaedes Technologies Ltd&apos;s subsidiary, Mistral Solutions Private Limited, has received an order for supplying Mission Computer and Smart Display Unit across multiple years. The order is from Hindustan Aeronautics Limited, a domestic entity. The broad consideration or size of the order is around Rs. 80 Crores. The order does not fall within related party transactions and there is no interest of the promoter/promoter group or group companies in the entity that awarded the order.</p><ul><li>Axiscaedes&apos; subsidiary, Mistral Solutions, receives order from Hindustan Aeronautics Limited</li><li>Order is for supplying Mission Computer and Smart Display Unit across multiple years</li><li>Order value is around Rs. 80 Crores</li><li>No related party transactions involved</li><li>No interest of the promoter/promoter group or group companies in the entity that awarded the order</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fdce55c5-afd9-450a-892f-78b9131d04aa.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Axiscades Technologies Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BLUECLOUDS] Blue Cloud Softech to Invest up to US$1 Billion in Next-Generation AI-Powered Data Center Business</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Blue+Cloud+Softech+Solutions+Ltd&title=Blue+Cloud+Softech+to+Invest+up+to+US%241+Billion+in+Next-Generation+AI-Powered+Data+Center+Business&newsId=9a6a375a-5996-46f5-af94-7551fc5b3888&token=OWE2YTM3NWEtNTk5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a6a375a-5996-46f5-af94-7551fc5b3888</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Blue Cloud Softech Solutions Ltd. (BCSSL) has announced a strategic plan to invest up to US$1 Billion in a nationwide AI-native next-generation data center and digital cloud infrastructure platform across India. The proposed infrastructure program envisions the creation of up to 800 MW of data center capacity over multiple phases. The investment will focus on building a future-ready digital backbone, aligned with India’s AI, semiconductor, defense, space, and digital public infrastructure initiatives. The differentiating factors of BCSSL’s infrastructure platform include Al-Orchestrated Data Centers, High-Density Al Compute Design, Al-Driven Cooling and Energy Optimization, Sovereign-by-Design Architecture, and Autonomous Cybersecurity Frameworks.</p><ul><li>Investment of up to US$1 Billion in next-generation AI-powered data center business</li><li>Creation of up to 800 MW of data center capacity over multiple phases</li><li>Aligned with India’s AI, semiconductor, defense, space, and digital public infrastructure initiatives</li><li>Incorporation of Al-Orchestrated Data Centers, High-Density Al Compute Design, Al-Driven Cooling and Energy Optimization, Sovereign-by-Design Architecture, and Autonomous Cybersecurity Frameworks</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/19cda363-7d81-4736-8394-52e388c19128.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Blue Cloud Softech Solutions Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DEEDEV] Dee Development Engineers Ltd Reports INR 92.77 Crores Order Inflow for January 2026 with PPA Tariff Confirmation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Dee+Development+Engineers+Ltd&title=Dee+Development+Engineers+Ltd+Reports+INR+92.77+Crores+Order+Inflow+for+January+2026+with+PPA+Tariff+Confirmation&newsId=a5352048-3484-43be-b1cc-0171b74578a6&token=YTUzNTIwNDgtMzQ4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5352048-3484-43be-b1cc-0171b74578a6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 03:04:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Dee Development Engineers Ltd has reported an order inflow of INR 92.77 crores for January 2026. The company is also L1 for orders worth INR 391 crores. There are Power Purchase Agreements (PPA) in place with Punjab State Power Corporation Limited for the Biomass Power Generation business, with an average billing of INR 80 crore per year. The PPA has been extended for another 10 years. The tariff of DEE Development Engineers Limited (Power Division) has been revised to Rs. 5.877 per unit, but the Company had filed an appeal before the Hon’ble High Court of Punjab &amp; Haryana against the order of Hon’ble PSERC. The Hon’ble High Court has stayed the operation of the Commission’s order. The total value of orders executed during the period represents the aggregate amount of invoices raised on customers, but the revenue recognized under Indian GAAP may differ from the invoiced amount.</p><ul><li>Order inflow of INR 92.77 crores for January 2026</li><li>L1 for orders worth INR 391 crores</li><li>PPA in place with Punjab State Power Corporation Limited</li><li>PPA extended for another 10 years</li><li>Tariff of DEE Development Engineers Limited revised to Rs. 5.877 per unit</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/034332f4-40db-4d0f-a94b-5b38318dd128.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Dee Development Engineers Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASMS] Bartronics India Ltd Appoints Dr. Raja Krishna Murthy as Head — Agri Tech Business to Drive Scalable Agri-Tech and Climate Tech Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BARTRONICS+INDIA+LTD.&title=Bartronics+India+Ltd+Appoints+Dr.+Raja+Krishna+Murthy+as+Head+%E2%80%94+Agri+Tech+Business+to+Drive+Scalable+Agri-Tech+and+Climate+Tech+Growth&newsId=fd6c1083-d472-433d-9e41-9567f6513134&token=ZmQ2YzEwODMtZDQ3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd6c1083-d472-433d-9e41-9567f6513134</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 02:49:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bartronics India Limited (BIL), a rural financial inclusion and technology company, has appointed Dr. Raja Krishna Murthy M as Head — Agri Tech Business. This appointment aligns with Bartronics’ strategic focus on Project Avio Agritech, its integrated agri-tech platform designed to create new, scalable revenue streams across agri-commerce, sustainable agriculture, digital advisory, and high-integrity carbon and climate solutions. Dr. Raja brings over 21 years of experience in agribusiness transformation, climate-smart and regenerative agriculture, ESG-aligned programs, and carbon market operations. He has led and managed agriculture and sustainability initiatives impacting over 2.8 lakh farmers directly. Bartronics’ agri and carbon strategy is anchored in its established rural infrastructure, which currently connects with approximately 40 million farmers across 5,000 villages. Project Avio Agritech is designed to monetise this reach by enabling structured agri-value chains, carbon aggregation, and climate-aligned outcomes linked to global markets, while simultaneously improving farm productivity, resilience, and farmer incomes.</p><ul><li>Bartronics India Ltd appoints Dr. Raja Krishna Murthy as Head — Agri Tech Business</li><li>Appointment aligns with Bartronics’ strategic focus on Project Avio Agritech</li><li>Dr. Raja brings over 21 years of experience in agribusiness transformation</li><li>Bartronics’ agri and carbon strategy anchored in its established rural infrastructure</li><li>Project Avio Agritech designed to monetise reach and improve farm productivity, resilience, and farmer incomes</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/959f2ccd-453f-4c8e-838a-405d2a96ad50.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BARTRONICS INDIA LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UFMINDL] UFM Industries Ltd to Consider and Approve Unaudited Financial Results on 14/02/2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=UFM+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=UFM+Industries+Ltd+to+Consider+and+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+on+14%2F02%2F2026&newsId=3e4c0a9b-9bc0-4250-a4cd-fcfb1d9fd0b4&token=M2U0YzBhOWItOWJj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e4c0a9b-9bc0-4250-a4cd-fcfb1d9fd0b4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 02:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>UFM Industries Ltd has announced that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on 14th February 2026. The agenda includes the consideration and approval of the Unaudited Financial Results for the third quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. This announcement is in accordance with Regulation 29 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>UFM Industries Ltd to consider and approve Unaudited Financial Results on 14/02/2026</li><li>Meeting of the Board of Directors scheduled on 14th February 2026</li><li>Consideration and approval of Unaudited Financial Results for the third quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025</li><li>In accordance with Regulation 29 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/13243c30-fc8c-4afb-8a3f-8ef6c2459fcb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: UFM INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CIPLA] Cipla Ltd. Concludes GST Department Inspection with No Material Impact</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CIPLA+LTD.&title=Cipla+Ltd.+Concludes+GST+Department+Inspection+with+No+Material+Impact&newsId=e0586e77-a705-4325-957c-35f9a0a095c2&token=ZTA1ODZlNzctYTcw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0586e77-a705-4325-957c-35f9a0a095c2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 20:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cipla Ltd. has notified the conclusion of an Inspection/Search by the Goods &amp; Service Tax Department, Maharashtra on 7th February, 2026. The company has provided all necessary documents, clarifications and details as requested. There is no material impact on the company&apos;s financials, operations, or other activities due to the inspection/search.</p><ul><li>Cipla Ltd. has concluded an Inspection/Search by the Goods &amp; Service Tax Department, Maharashtra on 7th February, 2026.</li><li>The company has provided all necessary documents, clarifications, and details as requested.</li><li>There is no material impact on the company&apos;s financials, operations, or other activities due to the inspection/search.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2e2d7405-f32d-48be-921c-cb43f85e3a8d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CIPLA LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>