<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:43:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[HOMEFIRST] True North Fund V LLP Acquires 2.71% Stake in Home First Finance Company India Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Home+First+Finance+Company+India+Ltd&title=True+North+Fund+V+LLP+Acquires+2.71%25+Stake+in+Home+First+Finance+Company+India+Ltd&newsId=06b5144b-1501-41ce-956b-ed2cf4bf5eab&token=MDZiNTE0NGItMTUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06b5144b-1501-41ce-956b-ed2cf4bf5eab</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:42:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>True North Fund V LLP has acquired 2,808,585 shares, which is 2.71% of the total voting rights, in Home First Finance Company India Ltd. The acquisition was made through the open market. Prior to the acquisition, True North Fund V LLP held 7,737,825 shares, which is 7.45% of the total voting rights. After the acquisition, True North Fund V LLP now holds 49,29,240 shares, which is 4.74% of the total voting rights.</p><ul><li>True North Fund V LLP has acquired 2.71% stake in Home First Finance Company India Ltd</li><li>The acquisition was made through the open market</li><li>Prior to the acquisition, True North Fund V LLP held 7.45% stake in the company</li><li>After the acquisition, True North Fund V LLP now holds 4.74% stake in the company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/69DAE2C6_A2FC_4F3F_A892_C7373561A8C1_150432.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Home First Finance Company India Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VIPIND] VIP Industries Ltd. Clarifies on &apos;Carlton&apos; Trademark Usage Amidst Pending Litigation and Competitor&apos;s License Acquisition</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=V.I.P.INDUSTRIES+LTD.-%24&title=VIP+Industries+Ltd.+Clarifies+on+%27Carlton%27+Trademark+Usage+Amidst+Pending+Litigation+and+Competitor%27s+License+Acquisition&newsId=37f35af8-3bec-4738-900c-be055a443fdf&token=MzdmMzVhZjgtM2Jl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37f35af8-3bec-4738-900c-be055a443fdf</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:37:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>VIP Industries Ltd., in accordance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, has released communications regarding the ongoing litigation concerning the usage of the &apos;Carlton&apos; trademark for travel luggage in India. The matter is sub-judice, with proceedings in CS (COMM) No. 730 of 2019 and CS (COMM) No. 52 of 2020 pending before the Delhi High Court. The counterparty, Carlton Shoes Limited &amp; Ors, has not yet filed their affidavits of evidence for any witness. The Supreme Court of India has granted VIP Industries the liberty to dispose of existing &apos;Carlton&apos; branded inventory before June 01, 2026. Recently, competitor Safari Industries (India) Limited has acquired a long-term license to use the &apos;Carlton&apos; trademark in India from Carlton Shoes Limited, creating potential confusion for customers, distributors, and stakeholders. VIP Industries Ltd. intends to pursue the matters till final determination and assert its right to use the &apos;Carlton&apos; trademark for luggage in India.</p><ul><li>VIP Industries Ltd. communicates on the status of the &apos;Carlton&apos; trademark litigation in India.</li><li>The Delhi High Court is yet to determine the right of the company to use the &apos;Carlton&apos; trademark for travel luggage in India.</li><li>The Supreme Court of India has granted VIP Industries the liberty to dispose of existing &apos;Carlton&apos; branded inventory before June 01, 2026.</li><li>Safari Industries (India) Limited has acquired a long-term license to use the &apos;Carlton&apos; trademark in India from Carlton Shoes Limited.</li><li>VIP Industries Ltd. will pursue the matters till final determination and protect its right to use the &apos;Carlton&apos; trademark for luggage in India.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5b15d7fd-4ff1-4cdd-8fbd-5b1982cf713f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: V.I.P.INDUSTRIES LTD.-$ | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GROWINGTON] Manju Mundhra Acquires 1.7% Stake in Growington Ventures India Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Growington+Ventures+India+Ltd&title=Manju+Mundhra+Acquires+1.7%25+Stake+in+Growington+Ventures+India+Ltd&newsId=c3cf2333-e851-4323-adc3-f2a46d4d0425&token=YzNjZjIzMzMtZTg1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c3cf2333-e851-4323-adc3-f2a46d4d0425</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:32:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Manju Mundhra, along with Naresh Kumar Mundhra, has acquired a 1.7% stake in Growington Ventures India Ltd. The acquisition was made through open market transactions, as per the disclosure made under Regulation 29(1) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. The total equity share capital of the company stands at Rs 64,22,15,760/- after the acquisition.</p><ul><li>Manju Mundhra acquires 1.7% stake in Growington Ventures India Ltd</li><li>Acquisition made through open market transactions</li><li>Total equity share capital of the company stands at Rs 64,22,15,760/- after the acquisition</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/A793CA2F_84A0_49D5_BBEE_1E01DBB46558_150053.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Growington Ventures India Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ETT] Laddu Gopal Online Services Ltd Postpones Rights Issue Committee Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ETT+Ltd&title=Laddu+Gopal+Online+Services+Ltd+Postpones+Rights+Issue+Committee+Meeting&newsId=aefdbeae-5274-461f-abbf-c31f331942b8&token=YWVmZGJlYWUtNTI3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aefdbeae-5274-461f-abbf-c31f331942b8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Right Issue</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Laddu Gopal Online Services Ltd, formerly known as ETT Limited, has postponed the meeting of the Rights Issue Committee scheduled for March 02, 2026. The meeting was intended to consider and approve fixing record date, issue price, entitlement ratio, and other terms and conditions related to the rights issue, as approved by the Board of Directors in their meeting on February 23, 2026. However, due to the in-principle approval from the Stock Exchange being under process, the meeting has been postponed and will be held within the next working day post receipt of the in-principle approval letter from the stock exchange.</p><ul><li>Laddu Gopal Online Services Ltd postpones Rights Issue Committee meeting</li><li>Meeting was scheduled for March 02, 2026</li><li>In-principle approval from Stock Exchange is under process</li><li>Meeting to be held within next working day post receipt of approval</li><li>Rights Issue approved by Board of Directors on February 23, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9f6a7785-7d70-4ba3-860a-0db445db3220.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ETT Ltd | Category: Right Issue</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MHSGRMS] Promoter Bhagchand Sukhwani Acquires 1.00% Shares in Mahasagar Travels Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MAHASAGAR+TRAVELS+LTD.&title=Promoter+Bhagchand+Sukhwani+Acquires+1.00%25+Shares+in+Mahasagar+Travels+Ltd&newsId=ccba4d9c-67a2-4f88-ab14-160ef3af3155&token=Y2NiYTRkOWMtNjdh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ccba4d9c-67a2-4f88-ab14-160ef3af3155</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bhagchand Sukhwani, a promoter of Mahasagar Travels Ltd, has acquired 1.00% shares of the company under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. The total shares held by the promoter and promoter group before the inter-se transfer were 31.29% of the company&apos;s paid-up capital. Post-transfer, the shares held by the promoter group remain the same.</p><ul><li>Bhagchand Sukhwani, a promoter of Mahasagar Travels Ltd, has acquired 1.00% shares of the company.</li><li>The acquisition was made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</li><li>Before the acquisition, the promoter and promoter group held 31.29% of the company&apos;s paid-up capital.</li><li>Post-transfer, the shares held by the promoter group remain the same.</li><li>The acquisition was made through an inter-se transfer.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/BCB80D96_E48B_46B0_B0B2_989AE740D101_145236.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MAHASAGAR TRAVELS LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AMBARPIL] Pradeep Kumar Chunilal Khetani Acquires 0.27% Shares in Ambar Protein Industries Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ambar+Protein+Industries+Ltd&title=Pradeep+Kumar+Chunilal+Khetani+Acquires+0.27%25+Shares+in+Ambar+Protein+Industries+Ltd&newsId=60c1667b-a893-4b86-959a-0664662d5476&token=NjBjMTY2N2ItYTg5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60c1667b-a893-4b86-959a-0664662d5476</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pradeep Kumar Chunilal Khetani has acquired 15748 equity shares, which amounts to 0.27% of the total shares in Ambar Protein Industries Ltd. The acquisition took place on 26th and 27th February, 2026 in the open market. Before the acquisition, Mr. Khetani held 11.60% of the shares in the company. After the acquisition, his holding increased to 11.87%.</p><ul><li>Pradeep Kumar Chunilal Khetani acquires 0.27% shares in Ambar Protein Industries Ltd</li><li>The acquisition took place on 26th and 27th February, 2026</li><li>The acquisition was made in the open market</li><li>Before the acquisition, Mr. Khetani held 11.60% of the shares in the company</li><li>After the acquisition, Mr. Khetani&apos;s holding increased to 11.87%</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/E13B51AC_E39E_4800_BAC6_C28C1EDA2053_145836.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ambar Protein Industries Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VIDLI] Kamats Worldwide Food Services Pvt Ltd Acquires Shares in Vikram Kamats Hospitality Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vidli+Restaurants+Ltd&title=Kamats+Worldwide+Food+Services+Pvt+Ltd+Acquires+Shares+in+Vikram+Kamats+Hospitality+Ltd&newsId=2a4c31be-5ba3-4214-8ec6-8a440b7cb04c&token=MmE0YzMxYmUtNWJh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a4c31be-5ba3-4214-8ec6-8a440b7cb04c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:28:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kamats Worldwide Food Services Pvt Ltd, a Promoter of Vikram Kamats Hospitality Ltd (formerly known as Vidli Restaurants Limited), has acquired shares in the company. The acquisition was made through preferential allotment. The total voting rights of the company have increased from 20.74% to 22.78% as a result of this acquisition.</p><ul><li>Kamats Worldwide Food Services Pvt Ltd, a Promoter, has acquired shares in Vikram Kamats Hospitality Ltd through preferential allotment.</li><li>The total voting rights of Vikram Kamats Hospitality Ltd have increased from 20.74% to 22.78% due to the acquisition.</li><li>The acquisition was made on 2nd March, 2026.</li><li>The equity share capital of Vikram Kamats Hospitality Ltd has increased from Rs. 17,13,58,650/- to Rs. 17,28,98,650/- as a result of the acquisition.</li><li>The total voting capital of the company has increased from 1,71,35,865 Equity shares to 1,72,89,865 Equity shares.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2DF2B2B2_6392_42F6_9BC1_3B7A615F9EA4_145555.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vidli Restaurants Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ABATEAS] Promoter Group Al Salama Eye Research Foundation Discloses Securities Holding Change in Abate As Industries Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Abate+As+Industries+Ltd&title=Promoter+Group+Al+Salama+Eye+Research+Foundation+Discloses+Securities+Holding+Change+in+Abate+As+Industries+Ltd&newsId=b0536b00-53cc-474d-b0aa-75a2c8f0695b&token=YjA1MzZiMDAtNTNj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b0536b00-53cc-474d-b0aa-75a2c8f0695b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Abate As Industries Ltd has received a disclosure under Regulation 7(2) of the PIT Regulations, 2015 from Al Salama Eye Research Foundation, a Promoter Group. The disclosure reveals a change in the holding of securities. The transaction involves 12,79,132 Equity shares worth Rs. 1,05,31,010, which were purchased on 26th February 2023. This brings the total securities held by the Promoter Group to 13,61,334 Equity shares.</p><ul><li>Al Salama Eye Research Foundation, a Promoter Group, discloses change in securities holding in Abate As Industries Ltd</li><li>Transaction involves 12,79,132 Equity shares worth Rs. 1,05,31,010</li><li>Shares were purchased on 26th February 2023</li><li>Post-transaction, the Promoter Group holds 13,61,334 Equity shares</li><li>Disclosure received under Regulation 7(2) of the PIT Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8fd702eb-9fd4-435f-b18b-2610497f725e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Abate As Industries Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SURYAKR] Rajvi Logitrade Ltd: Board Approves Related Party Transactions, Appointments, and E-Voting Process</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SURYAKRIPA+FINANCE+LTD.&title=Rajvi+Logitrade+Ltd%3A+Board+Approves+Related+Party+Transactions%2C+Appointments%2C+and+E-Voting+Process&newsId=896f3fbd-cede-4a12-9c69-1ff0935a9695&token=ODk2ZjNmYmQtY2Vk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">896f3fbd-cede-4a12-9c69-1ff0935a9695</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:26:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rajvi Logitrade Ltd held a Board Meeting on 02/03/2026, where several key decisions were made. The Board approved Related Party Transactions with RCC Limited for the Financial Years 2025-2026 and 2026-2027, subject to shareholder approval. An Extra Ordinary General Meeting is scheduled for 27/03/2026 to seek shareholder approval on various matters, including the appointment of Mr. Hardik Dilipbhai Naygandhi as Non-Executive &amp; Independent Director, and approval of Related Party Transactions with Mr. Bhupendrasinh Dalpatsinh Rana and RCC Limited. The company also appointed M/s. Jogi Dipak &amp; Co. Practicing Company Secretary as Scrutinizer for the Extra-ordinary General Meeting and Central Depository Services (India) Limited as the Depository to handle the remote E voting process. The schedule of events for the E-voting process and the Extra-Ordinary General Meeting was also approved.</p><ul><li>Board approved Related Party Transactions with RCC Limited for the Financial Years 2025-2026 and 2026-2027</li><li>Extra Ordinary General Meeting scheduled for 27/03/2026 to seek shareholder approval on various matters</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Hardik Dilipbhai Naygandhi as Non-Executive &amp; Independent Director</li><li>Approval of Related Party Transactions with Mr. Bhupendrasinh Dalpatsinh Rana and RCC Limited</li><li>Appointment of M/s. Jogi Dipak &amp; Co. Practicing Company Secretary as Scrutinizer for the Extra-ordinary General Meeting and Central Depository Services (India) Limited as the Depository to handle the remote E voting process</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f413382d-0d84-4bd3-9517-bffd3f518be6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SURYAKRIPA FINANCE LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VSTIND] VST Industries Ltd. Updates Key Managerial Personnel for Material Event Determination and Disclosures</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VST+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=VST+Industries+Ltd.+Updates+Key+Managerial+Personnel+for+Material+Event+Determination+and+Disclosures&newsId=06918195-e662-43e3-95a1-55c05d1e40bd&token=MDY5MTgxOTUtZTY2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06918195-e662-43e3-95a1-55c05d1e40bd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 09:25:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>VST Industries Ltd. has updated the contact details of its Key Managerial Personnel who have been authorized to determine materiality of an event or information and for the purpose of making disclosures to stock exchange(s) under Regulation 30(5) of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The Key Managerial Personnel include Mr. Piyush Srivastava, Managing Director &amp; CEO, Mr. Anish Gupta, Chief Financial Officer, and Mr. Phani K. Mangipudi, Company Secretary and Vice-President- Legal &amp; Secretarial.</p><ul><li>VST Industries Ltd. has updated the contact details of its Key Managerial Personnel</li><li>The Key Managerial Personnel are authorized to determine materiality of an event or information and for the purpose of making disclosures to stock exchange(s)</li><li>The update is in accordance with Regulation 30(5) of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>The Key Managerial Personnel include Mr. Piyush Srivastava, Managing Director &amp; CEO, Mr. Anish Gupta, Chief Financial Officer, and Mr. Phani K. Mangipudi, Company Secretary and Vice-President- Legal &amp; Secretarial</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6c8f08c9-2646-4886-8d0d-0e54da71c6ec.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VST INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>