<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:22:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[RUDRA] Rudra Global Infra Products Ltd Announces Q3 2025 Financial Results with 15,858.96 Lacs Revenue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Rudra+Global+Infra+Products+Ltd&title=Rudra+Global+Infra+Products+Ltd+Announces+Q3+2025+Financial+Results+with+15%2C858.96+Lacs+Revenue&newsId=7121ffe5-6b76-47f2-ad0f-88dc4e8b1dca&token=NzEyMWZmZTUtNmI3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7121ffe5-6b76-47f2-ad0f-88dc4e8b1dca</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rudra Global Infra Products Ltd has announced its financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations (net of taxes) stands at 15,858.96 Lacs, representing a significant increase from the previous quarter. The total income, including other business income, is 15,858.96 Lacs. The company&apos;s expenses amount to 14,871.69 Lacs, resulting in a profit before exceptional items and tax of 987.27 Lacs. After considering exceptional items and tax, the net profit after tax from business operations is 737.56 Lacs.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations stands at 15,858.96 Lacs</li><li>Total income, including other business income, is 15,858.96 Lacs</li><li>Profit before exceptional items and tax is 987.27 Lacs</li><li>After considering exceptional items and tax, the net profit after tax from business operations is 737.56 Lacs</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5e9c7f47-491d-44bc-affc-bba224c80f40.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Rudra Global Infra Products Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HINDPETRO] HPCL and ADNOC Gas Sign 10-Year LNG Supply Agreement</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HINDUSTAN+PETROLEUM+CORPORATION+LTD.&title=HPCL+and+ADNOC+Gas+Sign+10-Year+LNG+Supply+Agreement&newsId=d303cc8c-06e5-491c-a081-eab8656c6015&token=ZDMwM2NjOGMtMDZl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d303cc8c-06e5-491c-a081-eab8656c6015</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:11:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Gas Supply Agreement</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd (HPCL) and Abu Dhabi Gas Liquefaction Company (ADNOC Gas), a subsidiary of ADNOC Gas, have signed a Sale Purchase Agreement (SPA) for the supply of Liquefied Natural Gas (LNG) on a long-term basis. The agreement, which lasts for 10 years, will see HPCL receive LNG at its 5 Million Tonne per annum LNG Storage and Regasification Terminal at Chhara, Gujarat. The supplied LNG will support HPCL&apos;s refineries, City Gas Distribution (CGD) network, and gas demand across various sectors, such as Fertilizers, Power, Petrochemicals, and other Industries. This agreement strengthens the economic ties between India and the UAE, highlighting the importance of LNG in supporting India&apos;s energy transition. The supply under this agreement is a significant milestone in India&apos;s energy security and HPCL&apos;s commitment to cleaner energy transition.</p><ul><li>HPCL and ADNOC Gas sign a 10-year Sale Purchase Agreement for LNG supply</li><li>LNG to be received at HPCL&apos;s 5 Million Tonne per annum LNG Storage and Regasification Terminal at Chhara, Gujarat</li><li>Supplies will support HPCL&apos;s refineries, City Gas Distribution (CGD) network, and various sectors like Fertilizers, Power, Petrochemicals, and other Industries</li><li>Agreement strengthens India-UAE economic ties and supports India&apos;s energy transition</li><li>Significant milestone in India&apos;s energy security and HPCL&apos;s commitment to cleaner energy transition</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bc91d99a-9680-4a66-beac-110041f6e61f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HINDUSTAN PETROLEUM CORPORATION LTD. | Category: Gas Supply Agreement</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JSWENERGY] JSW Energy Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JSW+Energy+Ltd&title=JSW+Energy+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025&newsId=c735994b-1029-473e-9bd5-f9969c351751&token=YzczNTk5NGItMTAy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c735994b-1029-473e-9bd5-f9969c351751</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:07:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>JSW Energy Ltd has informed the BSE that its Board of Directors will meet on 23rd January 2026 to consider and approve the unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the company, which was closed for all Designated Persons from 1st January 2026, will open on Monday, 26th January 2026.</p><ul><li>JSW Energy Ltd scheduled a Board Meeting on 23rd January 2026</li><li>The meeting aims to consider and approve the unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025</li><li>The trading window for dealing in the securities of the company will open on Monday, 26th January 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3fbd92a4-f984-4543-b2ea-14ce4bfc6efd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JSW Energy Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FILTRON] Filtron Engineers Ltd: Approval of Appointment of New Managing Directors and Resignation of Current Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=FILTRON+ENGINEERS+LTD.&title=Filtron+Engineers+Ltd%3A+Approval+of+Appointment+of+New+Managing+Directors+and+Resignation+of+Current+Directors&newsId=e5c39584-67dd-418d-a791-f5ec7245b2dd&token=ZTVjMzk1ODQtNjdk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5c39584-67dd-418d-a791-f5ec7245b2dd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Filtron Engineers Ltd announced the appointment of Mr. Jayesh Sheshmal Rawal and Mr. Tarak Bipinchandra Gor as Additional Directors Designated as Managing Directors, and Mr. Ankit Jayesh Rawal as Additional Non-Executive Director. The appointments are subject to shareholders&apos; approval. The board also noted the resignation of Mr. Sadanand Ganapati Hegde and Mr. Gajanan Chidambar Hegde from their respective positions. The board has reconstituted all committees in light of the change in management control.</p><ul><li>Approval of appointment of Mr. Jayesh Sheshmal Rawal, Mr. Tarak Bipinchandra Gor as Additional Directors Designated as Managing Directors</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Ankit Jayesh Rawal as Additional Non-Executive Director</li><li>Resignation of Mr. Sadanand Ganapati Hegde and Mr. Gajanan Chidambar Hegde</li><li>Reconstitution of all board committees</li><li>Subject to shareholders&apos; approval</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a709e589-3e52-4ae0-a802-b5ec7f35d06f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: FILTRON ENGINEERS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[APOLLO] Apollo Micro Systems Invests ₹30,000 Lakhs in New Electronics Manufacturing Facility in Hyderabad</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Apollo+Micro+Systems+Ltd&title=Apollo+Micro+Systems+Invests+%E2%82%B930%2C000+Lakhs+in+New+Electronics+Manufacturing+Facility+in+Hyderabad&newsId=0a5a53cb-ec21-4dd5-a852-3b6a83c802e4&token=MGE1YTUzY2ItZWMy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a5a53cb-ec21-4dd5-a852-3b6a83c802e4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 15:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Apollo Micro Systems Ltd. (AMS), a leading defence and aerospace technology company, is expanding its Weapon Integration facilities in Hyderabad with an investment of approximately ₹30,000 lakhs. The company has been allotted Plot Nos. 4 and 5, admeasuring a total area of 22,988.00 Sq.mts, at TSIIC - Hardware Park Phase II, Hyderabad. The facility will be used for manufacturing, assembly, integration, and testing of Weapon System Platforms such as Grad Rockets, Anti-Submarine Warfare Rockets, Anti-Tank Mines, Artillery Munitions and other similar products. This expansion aligns with the company’s long-term growth strategy and reinforces its commitment to enhancing indigenous manufacturing capabilities, strengthening technological innovation, and supporting the growing demand in the defence sector.</p><ul><li>Apollo Micro Systems to invest ₹30,000 lakhs in a new electronics manufacturing facility in Hyderabad.</li><li>The company has been allotted 22,988.00 Sq.mts of land at TSIIC - Hardware Park Phase II, Hyderabad.</li><li>The facility will be used for manufacturing, assembly, integration, and testing of Weapon System Platforms.</li><li>This expansion aligns with the company’s long-term growth strategy and reinforces its commitment to enhancing indigenous manufacturing capabilities.</li><li>The new facility will strengthen technological innovation and support the growing demand in the defence sector.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/83fcf362-2aa2-42e4-b273-b7b9b11658b7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Apollo Micro Systems Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RUDRA] Rudra Global Infra Products Ltd Announces Q3 2025 Financial Results with 15,858.96 Lacs Revenue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Rudra+Global+Infra+Products+Ltd&title=Rudra+Global+Infra+Products+Ltd+Announces+Q3+2025+Financial+Results+with+15%2C858.96+Lacs+Revenue&newsId=5e539881-6f8f-40b6-8a05-82f473110d78&token=NWU1Mzk4ODEtNmY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5e539881-6f8f-40b6-8a05-82f473110d78</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:57:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rudra Global Infra Products Ltd has announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The company reported a revenue from operations (net of taxes) of 15,858.96 Lacs, an increase from the previous quarter. The total income stood at 15,858.96 Lacs, 13,650.96 Lacs, and 14,874.29 Lacs for Q3, YTD, and 9M, respectively. The total expenses were 14,871.69 Lacs, 13,498.00 Lacs, and 38,089.72 Lacs for Q3, YTD, and 9M, respectively. The profit before exceptional items and tax was 987.27 Lacs, 152.96 Lacs, and 1,314.67 Lacs for Q3, YTD, and 9M, respectively. The net profit after tax from business operations was 737.56 Lacs, 118.62 Lacs, and 157.71 Lacs for Q3, YTD, and 9M, respectively. The earnings per share from continuing operations were 0.12 for both basic and diluted. The company&apos;s total comprehensive income was 737.56 Lacs, 118.62 Lacs, and 157.71 Lacs for Q3, YTD, and 9M, respectively.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations (net of taxes) for Q3 2025 is 15,858.96 Lacs</li><li>Profit before exceptional items and tax for Q3 2025 is 987.27 Lacs</li><li>Net profit after tax from business operations for Q3 2025 is 737.56 Lacs</li><li>Earnings per share from continuing operations for Q3 2025 is 0.12</li><li>Total comprehensive income for Q3 2025 is 737.56 Lacs</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/da4abdee-b971-4cbf-9a95-6fa9c0adc1c2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Rudra Global Infra Products Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TCIEXP*] TCI Express Ltd: No Pending Transfer Requests for Physical Shares as of January 6, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TCI+Express+Ltd&title=TCI+Express+Ltd%3A+No+Pending+Transfer+Requests+for+Physical+Shares+as+of+January+6%2C+2026&newsId=5891de6b-19e6-402b-af3f-dd49641bced3&token=NTg5MWRlNmItMTll</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5891de6b-19e6-402b-af3f-dd49641bced3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:47:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>According to the report issued by TCI Express Ltd&apos;s Registrar &amp; Share Transfer Agent, KFIN Technologies Limited, there are no pending transfer requests for physical shares as of January 6, 2026. This is in line with the SEBI Circular SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MISRD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97 dated July 2, 2025, which provided a special window for the re-lodgment of transfer requests for physical shares.</p><ul><li>TCI Express Ltd has no pending transfer requests for physical shares as of January 6, 2026.</li><li>The report was issued by KFIN Technologies Limited, the company&apos;s Registrar &amp; Share Transfer Agent.</li><li>The update is in accordance with the SEBI Circular SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MISRD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97 dated July 2, 2025.</li><li>The circular provided a special window for the re-lodgment of transfer requests for physical shares.</li><li>No requests were received, processed, approved, or rejected for processing during the months specified in the report.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0e280013-12ce-4def-872c-451a7605c146.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TCI Express Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TRISHAKT] Trishakti Industries Ltd. Raises Rs. 61817100 through Preferential Issue and Warrants Allotment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TRISHAKTI+ELECTRONICS+%26+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Trishakti+Industries+Ltd.+Raises+Rs.+61817100+through+Preferential+Issue+and+Warrants+Allotment&newsId=3df53e18-b3d5-4f56-82a3-b2622b12bf5d&token=M2RmNTNlMTgtYjNk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3df53e18-b3d5-4f56-82a3-b2622b12bf5d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Trishakti Industries Ltd. has raised a total of Rs. 61817100 through preferential issue of equity shares and allotment of warrants. The equity shares were issued at Rs. 158.10 each, raising Rs. 23082600, while the warrants were allotted at the same price, raising Rs. 38734500. The funds will be primarily utilized for business expansion, repayment of existing debt, acquisition of strategic investments, meeting working capital requirements, and for general corporate purposes.</p><ul><li>Trishakti Industries Ltd. raises Rs. 61817100 through preferential issue and warrants allotment</li><li>Rs. 23082600 raised through preferential issue of 1,46,000 Equity Shares</li><li>Rs. 38734500 raised through allotment of warrants</li><li>Funds to be utilized for business expansion, debt repayment, strategic investments, working capital requirements, and general corporate purposes</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f1202f59-95f6-4705-b9a6-f92db6dc6343.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TRISHAKTI ELECTRONICS & INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TCIEXP*] TCI Express Ltd Faces GST Demand Order of INR 51,36,02,450 for FY 2017-18 to 2021-22</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TCI+Express+Ltd&title=TCI+Express+Ltd+Faces+GST+Demand+Order+of+INR+51%2C36%2C02%2C450+for+FY+2017-18+to+2021-22&newsId=682dbcc8-4c80-4fc3-9799-b6b9d44a6dbd&token=NjgyZGJjYzgtNGM4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">682dbcc8-4c80-4fc3-9799-b6b9d44a6dbd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:41:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>TCI Express Ltd has been issued a demand order under Section 74(1) of the Central Goods and Services Tax Act, 2017 (‘CGST Act, 2017’) and corresponding provisions of Haryana GST Act, 2017, for the period FY 2017-18 to 2021-22. The demand order, which includes interest and penalty, amounts to INR 51,36,02,450. The Company will be filing an appeal against the order with the GST Appropriate Authority. There is no material impact on the financials, operations, or other activities of the Company.</p><ul><li>TCI Express Ltd faces a GST demand order of INR 51,36,02,450 for FY 2017-18 to 2021-22</li><li>The demand order includes interest and penalty as per Section 74(1) of the CGST Act, 2017 and corresponding provisions of Haryana GST Act, 2017</li><li>The Company will be filing an appeal against the order with the GST Appropriate Authority</li><li>No material impact on the financials, operations, or other activities of the Company</li><li>The Company became aware of the information on January 16, 2025, and promptly made the requisite disclosure to the Stock Exchange</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/70544752-60db-49a0-bf85-643ed07cb2cd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TCI Express Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SGFRL] Suyog Gurbaxani Funicular Ropeways Ltd Completes and Inaugurates Ropeway Project at Haji Malang</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Suyog+Gurbaxani+Funicular+Ropeways+Ltd&title=Suyog+Gurbaxani+Funicular+Ropeways+Ltd+Completes+and+Inaugurates+Ropeway+Project+at+Haji+Malang&newsId=10018a3c-9eca-4357-99b9-e37b845d1c93&token=MTAwMThhM2MtOWVj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">10018a3c-9eca-4357-99b9-e37b845d1c93</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Suyog Gurbaxani Funicular Ropeways Ltd has successfully completed and inaugurated the ropeway project at Haji Malang, Maharashtra. The project was developed and completed under an Engineering, Procurement and Construction (EPC) Agreement with Supreme Suyog Funicular Ropeways Private Limited. This disclosure is being made in the ordinary course of business and shareholders are requested to take note of this development.</p><ul><li>Suyog Gurbaxani Funicular Ropeways Ltd has completed a ropeway project at Haji Malang, Maharashtra.</li><li>The project was developed and completed under an Engineering, Procurement and Construction (EPC) Agreement with Supreme Suyog Funicular Ropeways Private Limited.</li><li>The project has been successfully inaugurated on 18 January, 2026.</li><li>This disclosure is being made in the ordinary course of business.</li><li>Shareholders are requested to take note of this development.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/426518ac-7287-4772-84bb-c3190aca53d9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Suyog Gurbaxani Funicular Ropeways Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>