<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:43:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SHAQUAK] Shantanu Sheorey Aquakult Ltd to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q4 2025 in Board Meeting on 11th February 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHANTANU+SHEOREY+AQUAKULT+LTD.&title=Shantanu+Sheorey+Aquakult+Ltd+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q4+2025+in+Board+Meeting+on+11th+February+2026&newsId=5b44cdcc-001d-446a-8987-8d485569a643&token=NWI0NGNkY2MtMDAx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b44cdcc-001d-446a-8987-8d485569a643</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shantanu Sheorey Aquakult Ltd has announced a Board Meeting scheduled for 11th February 2026. The meeting will consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The trading window for dealing in shares of the company will be closed for Directors/ KMP‘s/ Designated Employees/ Connected Persons until 48 hours after the information is made public, in accordance with SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015 and the Company’s Code of Internal Procedures and Conduct for Regulating, Monitoring and Reporting of Trading by Insiders.</p><ul><li>Shantanu Sheorey Aquakult Ltd scheduled a Board Meeting on 11th February 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025</li><li>Trading window for dealing in shares of the company will be closed for Directors/ KMP‘s/ Designated Employees/ Connected Persons until 48 hours after the information is made public</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/13be18cc-5f67-4619-af93-6e7e2302156f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHANTANU SHEOREY AQUAKULT LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHK] S H Kelkar and Company Ltd Announces Q3 &amp; 9M FY2026 Results: Revenue from Operations at Rs. 1,718 crore, EBITDA at Rs. 182 crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=S+H+Kelkar+and+Company+Ltd&title=S+H+Kelkar+and+Company+Ltd+Announces+Q3+%26+9M+FY2026+Results%3A+Revenue+from+Operations+at+Rs.+1%2C718+crore%2C+EBITDA+at+Rs.+182+crore&newsId=7cc6ea3d-7fcd-49c3-8c29-a364dce31fbd&token=N2NjNmVhM2QtN2Zj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7cc6ea3d-7fcd-49c3-8c29-a364dce31fbd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>S H Kelkar and Company Limited (SHK), the largest Indian origin Fragrance and Flavour Company in India, has announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a revenue from operations of Rs. 1,718 crore and an EBITDA of Rs. 182 crore for the nine months ended FY2026. The company is investing in strategic initiatives for long-term growth, including strengthening global Creative Development Centres and expanding capacity. The US Creative Development Centre secured its first customer order during the quarter.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations at Rs. 1,718 crore for 9M FY2026</li><li>EBITDA stood at Rs. 182 crore for 9M FY2026</li><li>Adjusted EBITDA at Rs. 240 crore for 9M FY2026</li><li>US Creative Development Centre secured its first customer order</li><li>Investing in strategic initiatives for long-term growth</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f67c1c48-dded-4dfe-96f2-44d781cb4d87.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: S H Kelkar and Company Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BRIJLEAS] Brijlaxmi Leasing &amp; Finance Ltd to Approve Q3 Financial Statements on Feb 14, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BRIJLAXMI+LEASING+%26+FINANCE+LTD.&title=Brijlaxmi+Leasing+%26+Finance+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+Financial+Statements+on+Feb+14%2C+2026&newsId=421782e5-d455-44c0-9336-99c332e067c4&token=NDIxNzgyZTUtZDQ1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">421782e5-d455-44c0-9336-99c332e067c4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Brijlaxmi Leasing &amp; Finance Ltd has scheduled a Board Meeting on February 14, 2026, to consider and approve the Un-Audited Financial Statements for the Third Quarter ended on December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in securities of the Company will be closed from January 1, 2026, for all designated persons and will open 48 hours after the announcement of the results.</p><ul><li>Brijlaxmi Leasing &amp; Finance Ltd to hold a Board Meeting on February 14, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve Un-Audited Financial Statements for Q3 2025</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities to close on January 1, 2026</li><li>Trading window to open 48 hours after the announcement of results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8767e587-043c-4132-877b-b50096ef72bb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BRIJLAXMI LEASING & FINANCE LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ANANTRAJ] Anant Raj Cloud Partners with Submer Technologies to Boost Al Infrastructure in India</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Anant+Raj+Limited-%24&title=Anant+Raj+Cloud+Partners+with+Submer+Technologies+to+Boost+Al+Infrastructure+in+India&newsId=a1f01ee0-837c-46d8-8e7f-4c09aeb25d8f&token=YTFmMDFlZTAtODM3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a1f01ee0-837c-46d8-8e7f-4c09aeb25d8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Anant Raj Cloud, a subsidiary of Anant Raj Limited, has entered into a strategic collaboration with Submer Technologies, S.L. to enhance Al infrastructure at Anant Raj Data centers. This partnership aims to deliver modular, sustainable Al datacenters and Neocloud, supporting India’s digital economy. The collaboration is a prime example of the EU-India Trade Deal in action, bringing world-class liquid-cooling technology from Spain and combining it with the robust infrastructure and operational support of India. This partnership strengthens a single, accountable source for Al datacenter design, build and scalable operation, and enables customers to access Al-ready infrastructure and compute through a unified, end-to-end model aligned with India’s sovereignty requirements.</p><ul><li>Anant Raj Cloud has partnered with Submer Technologies to enhance Al infrastructure in India.</li><li>The partnership aims to deliver modular, sustainable Al datacenters and Neocloud, supporting India’s digital economy.</li><li>The collaboration is a prime example of the EU-India Trade Deal in action, bringing world-class liquid-cooling technology from Spain.</li><li>This partnership strengthens a single, accountable source for Al datacenter design, build and scalable operation.</li><li>The collaboration enables customers to access Al-ready infrastructure and compute through a unified, end-to-end model aligned with India’s sovereignty requirements.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a60094ab-d00d-4618-af61-f5f6d1ea086c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Anant Raj Limited-$ | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GRAVITY] Gravity India Ltd. Corrects Typographical Errors in Q3 Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GRAVITY+%28INDIA%29+LTD.-%24&title=Gravity+India+Ltd.+Corrects+Typographical+Errors+in+Q3+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=750d435a-5a79-4fa2-a867-e568a9f72eee&token=NzUwZDQzNWEtNWE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">750d435a-5a79-4fa2-a867-e568a9f72eee</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gravity India Ltd. has corrected typographical errors in its Q3 financial results for the year ended December 31, 2025. The errors were in the figures for revenue from operations and other income for the nine months ended December 31, 2025. The correct figures are 7,995.06 lacs for revenue from operations and 41.76 lacs for other income. The total revenue and profit figures remain unchanged. The company has uploaded the revised unaudited financial results along with the limited review reports.</p><ul><li>Gravity India Ltd. has corrected typographical errors in its Q3 financial results for 2025.</li><li>The errors were in the figures for revenue from operations and other income for the nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The correct figures for the nine months ended December 31, 2025, are 7,995.06 lacs for revenue from operations and 41.76 lacs for other income.</li><li>The total revenue and profit figures remain unchanged.</li><li>The company has uploaded the revised unaudited financial results along with the limited review reports.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b4fed76c-53df-4b0a-8291-814c90200477.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GRAVITY (INDIA) LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SMLISUZU] SML Mahindra Ltd Reports January 2026 Production, Sales, and Export Figures</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SML+ISUZU+LIMITED&title=SML+Mahindra+Ltd+Reports+January+2026+Production%2C+Sales%2C+and+Export+Figures&newsId=de6cc6af-9ca4-4158-b396-1f01ec623a25&token=ZGU2Y2M2YWYtOWNh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de6cc6af-9ca4-4158-b396-1f01ec623a25</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>SML Mahindra Ltd has released its production, sales, and export figures for January 2026. The company produced 4597 vehicles in January 2026 compared to 1681 vehicles in January 2025, marking a significant increase. In terms of sales, 925 vehicles were sold in January 2026, up from 1220 vehicles in January 2025. Export figures also saw a change, with 100 vehicles exported in January 2026 compared to 117 vehicles in January 2025. These figures are requested to be taken on record.</p><ul><li>Production increased from 1681 vehicles in Jan&apos;25 to 4597 vehicles in Jan&apos;26</li><li>Sales decreased from 1220 vehicles in Jan&apos;25 to 925 vehicles in Jan&apos;26</li><li>Export figures decreased from 117 vehicles in Jan&apos;25 to 100 vehicles in Jan&apos;26</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0ce9ef57-1be3-4037-ab79-45eb9fa405f6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SML ISUZU LIMITED | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LWSKNIT] LWS Knitwear Ltd to Consider and Approve Q4 Results on Feb 13, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LWS+KNITWEAR+LTD.&title=LWS+Knitwear+Ltd+to+Consider+and+Approve+Q4+Results+on+Feb+13%2C+2026&newsId=d66fc72c-6b93-4ef2-8b9e-9a1625b3fc50&token=ZDY2ZmM3MmMtNmI5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d66fc72c-6b93-4ef2-8b9e-9a1625b3fc50</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>LWS Knitwear Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 13, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter ended 31.12.2025. The meeting will also consider the Limited Review Report on Un-Audited Financial Results by the Statutory Auditor. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the company will remain closed for all insiders from January 1, 2026, till the end of 48 hours after the declaration of financial results for the Quarter Ended 31%t December, 2025.</p><ul><li>LWS Knitwear Ltd to consider and approve Q4 results on Feb 13, 2026</li><li>Un-Audited financial results for the quarter ended 31.12.2025 will be considered</li><li>Limited Review Report on Un-Audited Financial Results by the Statutory Auditor will be taken on record</li><li>Trading Window for dealing in the securities of the Company will remain closed for all insiders from Jan 1, 2026</li><li>Trading Window to open 48 hours after the declaration of financial results for the Quarter Ended 31%t December, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9bf6f01a-5c73-4705-a44d-7acda9e54c78.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LWS KNITWEAR LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PACEDIGITK] Pace Digitek Ltd Announces Q3 2025 Financial Results with 670.80 Profit and 2,333.77 Total Comprehensive Income</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Pace+Digitek+Ltd&title=Pace+Digitek+Ltd+Announces+Q3+2025+Financial+Results+with+670.80+Profit+and+2%2C333.77+Total+Comprehensive+Income&newsId=69a5988c-645d-4ab6-8a70-9942773e2eb8&token=NjlhNTk4OGMtNjQ1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69a5988c-645d-4ab6-8a70-9942773e2eb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pace Digitek Ltd, formerly known as Pace Digitek Private Limited and Pace Digitek Infra Private Limited, has announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 12,538.38 million, with a total income of 14,547.51 million. The profit before tax for the period is 5,293.32 million, and the profit after tax is 670.80 million. The total comprehensive income for the period is 2,333.77 million. The company&apos;s earnings per share (EPS) is not annualized and stands at 3.35 (Rupee) for basic and 3.35 (Rupee) for diluted.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations stands at 12,538.38 million</li><li>Profit before tax for the period is 5,293.32 million</li><li>Profit after tax is 670.80 million</li><li>Total comprehensive income for the period is 2,333.77 million</li><li>EPS is 3.35 (Rupee) for basic and diluted</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/61ae864a-7c72-4fa9-b1a8-d0936c2a8fad.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Pace Digitek Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JKIPL] Jinkushal Industries Announces Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jinkushal+Industries+Ltd&title=Jinkushal+Industries+Announces+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=b8e319c5-620e-4dc1-8896-d39dc1d1a66b&token=YjhlMzE5YzUtNjIw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8e319c5-620e-4dc1-8896-d39dc1d1a66b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jinkushal Industries Limited has announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a 27% year-on-year increase in standalone turnover, driven by export-led growth. A strategic inventory build-up was also undertaken at the overseas subsidiary to strengthen market access and increase the share of higher-margin used and refurbished machines. The company also balanced sales momentum by increasing focus on other international markets in response to temporary demand deferrals in Mexico.</p><ul><li>Standalone turnover increased by approximately 27% year-on-year, driven by export-led growth</li><li>Strategic inventory positioning undertaken at overseas subsidiary to strengthen market access</li><li>Continued focus on higher-margin refurbished and value-added equipment</li><li>Balanced geographic execution across multiple international markets</li><li>Expected progression as inventory is monetised</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e7081089-ddbb-4de6-b88d-ac84300665e4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jinkushal Industries Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JKIPL] Jinkushal Industries Ltd Submits Statement of No Deviation in IPO Fund Utilization</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jinkushal+Industries+Ltd&title=Jinkushal+Industries+Ltd+Submits+Statement+of+No+Deviation+in+IPO+Fund+Utilization&newsId=caf38068-f25a-4f3a-af51-f329fec0bd64&token=Y2FmMzgwNjgtZjI1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">caf38068-f25a-4f3a-af51-f329fec0bd64</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jinkushal Industries Ltd, a machinery, mining, and logistics company, has submitted a statement of no deviation in the utilization of funds raised from their Initial Public Offer (IPO). The IPO proceeds, totaling Rs. 11615.45 Lakhs, were raised through a public issue that closed on 29th September 2025. The funds were utilized for long-term applicable cable working capital requirements and general corporate purposes. The utilization of funds was reviewed by the Audit Committee and found to be in line with the objects stated in the prospectus.</p><ul><li>Jinkushal Industries Ltd submits Statement of Deviation as per Regulation 32 of SEBI</li><li>No deviation in the utilization of IPO funds during the quarter ended 31st December 2025</li><li>Funds utilized for long-term applicable cable working capital requirements and general corporate purposes</li><li>The Audit Committee has reviewed and taken the statement on record</li><li>Total funds raised through IPO: Rs. 11615.45 Lakhs</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d0410855-ffc8-4380-9677-f2243996ff40.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jinkushal Industries Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>