<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:47:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[EQUITASBNK] Equitas Small Finance Bank Reports 36% YoY Growth in Q3FY26 Profit After Tax</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Equitas+Small+Finance+Bank+Ltd&title=Equitas+Small+Finance+Bank+Reports+36%25+YoY+Growth+in+Q3FY26+Profit+After+Tax&newsId=f9132a73-2b2b-4a78-a288-6c2d6fa54ffd&token=ZjkxMzJhNzMtMmIy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9132a73-2b2b-4a78-a288-6c2d6fa54ffd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:47:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Equitas Small Finance Bank Limited has reported a 36% YoY growth in profit after tax (PAT) for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The bank&apos;s gross advances grew by 16% YoY and 11% QoQ, while disbursements increased by 28% YoY and 22% QoQ. Deposits grew by 7% YoY, and the quarterly PAT stood at Rs. 90 Crs. The bank&apos;s networth stands at Rs. 5,946 Crs as of December 31, 2025. The bank also made a one-time incremental provision of Rs. 29.52 crs due to the implementation of new Labour Code in Q3FY26.</p><ul><li>Gross Advances grew by 16% YoY and 11% QoQ</li><li>Disbursements grew by 28% YoY &amp; 22% QoQ</li><li>Deposits grew by 7% YoY</li><li>Quarterly PAT of Rs. 90 Crs, a growth of 36% YoY &amp; 273% QoQ</li><li>One-time incremental provision of Rs. 29.52 crs due to the implementation of new Labour Code in Q3FY26</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c7d47eee-8fcd-4732-b3ff-6cba33a4308b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Equitas Small Finance Bank Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDOWIND] Indowind Energy Ltd. Reports Un-Audited Financial Results for Q3 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDOWIND+ENERGY+LTD.&title=Indowind+Energy+Ltd.+Reports+Un-Audited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+2025&newsId=c271958b-fa4d-44d4-adb0-84ed64ae15eb&token=YzI3MTk1OGItZmE0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c271958b-fa4d-44d4-adb0-84ed64ae15eb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:47:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indowind Energy Ltd. has reported its un-audited financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at ₹ 600.96 lakhs for the quarter and ₹ 3,510.34 lakhs for the nine months ended December 31, 2025. The profit before tax for the quarter is ₹ 727.94 lakhs and ₹ 350.63 lakhs for the nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s total comprehensive income for the period is ₹ 727.94 lakhs and ₹ 350.63 lakhs for the nine months ended December 31, 2025.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter is ₹ 600.96 lakhs</li><li>Profit before tax for the quarter is ₹ 727.94 lakhs</li><li>Total comprehensive income for the period is ₹ 727.94 lakhs</li><li>Revenue from operations for the nine months ended December 31, 2025 is ₹ 3,510.34 lakhs</li><li>Profit before tax for the nine months ended December 31, 2025 is ₹ 350.63 lakhs</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5a369020-f8b4-40f8-a67b-e40a155f6142.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDOWIND ENERGY LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JUBLINGREA] Jubilant Ingrevia Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q3 Results and Interim Dividend for FY2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jubilant+Ingrevia+Ltd&title=Jubilant+Ingrevia+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+Results+and+Interim+Dividend+for+FY2026&newsId=ac80f6f5-6952-4d4a-91bd-6e7b9b7c95fc&token=YWM4MGY2ZjUtNjk1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac80f6f5-6952-4d4a-91bd-6e7b9b7c95fc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:47:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jubilant Ingrevia Ltd has announced a board meeting scheduled for February 04, 2026. The meeting will consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results of the Company for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. Additionally, the board will discuss a proposal for payment of Interim Dividend for the financial year 2026, if any.</p><ul><li>Jubilant Ingrevia Ltd has scheduled a board meeting for February 04, 2026</li><li>The board will consider and approve the Q3 results for the period ending December 31, 2025</li><li>A proposal for interim dividend payment for FY2026 will be discussed</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c2e5c866-f52d-407b-a3b3-d0bd8d08a8de.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jubilant Ingrevia Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SANINFRA] Sanmit Infra Schedules Board Meeting to Consider Term Loan and Equity Share Consolidation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sanmit+Infra+Limited&title=Sanmit+Infra+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Consider+Term+Loan+and+Equity+Share+Consolidation&newsId=c7b18f3f-fa98-4068-8c33-18e011d9ac29&token=YzdiMThmM2YtZmE5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7b18f3f-fa98-4068-8c33-18e011d9ac29</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sanmit Infra Ltd has informed the BSE that its Board of Directors will meet on February 04, 2026, to consider and approve several key items. The agenda includes terms and conditions of a Letter of Intent for a Term Loan from SIDBI under the STEP Scheme, and other related documents. The Board will also consider recommending a proposal for the consolidation of equity shares of a face value of Rs. 1/-, subject to shareholder approval in the upcoming Extra-ordinary General Meeting. Any other item will also be discussed.</p><ul><li>Sanmit Infra schedules Board Meeting on February 04, 2026</li><li>Consideration of Terms and Conditions of Letter of Intent for Term Loan from SIDBI under STEP Scheme</li><li>Consolidation of equity shares of face value of Rs. 1/- to be discussed</li><li>Proposal to be recommended to shareholders in the Extra-ordinary General Meeting</li><li>Discussion of any other item on the agenda</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dc9281e5-c5ed-4b31-9490-9ef4c17c971a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sanmit Infra Limited | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NMDC] NMDC Ltd. to Consider and Approve Q3 FY2025-26 Financial Results and Interim Dividend</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NMDC+LTD.&title=NMDC+Ltd.+to+Consider+and+Approve+Q3+FY2025-26+Financial+Results+and+Interim+Dividend&newsId=04341f91-5c05-40c8-b8c4-b5ba60c3b052&token=MDQzNDFmOTEtNWMw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04341f91-5c05-40c8-b8c4-b5ba60c3b052</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:46:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>NMDC Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 3rd February 2026 to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results (Standalone and Consolidated) for the quarter ended on 31st December 2025. The meeting will also discuss the proposal for declaration of Interim dividend for financial year 2025-26. In compliance with the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015 and the Company&apos;s Internal Code of Conduct for Prevention of Insider Trading, the trading window for dealing with the securities of the Company will be closed for all Insiders including Designated Persons and their immediate relatives from 15th January 2026 to 5th February 2026.</p><ul><li>NMDC Ltd. to consider and approve Unaudited Financial Results (Standalone and Consolidated) for Q3 FY2025-26</li><li>Proposal for declaration of Interim dividend for financial year 2025-26</li><li>Trading window for dealing with the securities of the Company to be closed for Insiders from 15th January 2026 to 5th February 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e73b535f-ad40-4a3e-b473-189fad0ad4d8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NMDC LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WIPRO] Wipro Unveils New Al-Powered Operating Model for Enterprise Functions</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=WIPRO+LTD.&title=Wipro+Unveils+New+Al-Powered+Operating+Model+for+Enterprise+Functions&newsId=a5840cfc-30fe-40c7-bb4a-1fa0db2c6584&token=YTU4NDBjZmMtMzBm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5840cfc-30fe-40c7-bb4a-1fa0db2c6584</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:46:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Wipro Limited, a leading technology services and consulting company, has announced the launch of a new operating model for enterprise functions. The model combines advisory, AI, and enterprise transformation services, and brings end-to-end accountability across four core functional areas: People &amp; Change; Supply Chain &amp; Operations; Finance Transformation; and Sales, Marketing &amp; Customer Experience (CX). This new, consulting-led, AI-powered model aims to connect boardroom strategy to scaled operations, and position Wipro as a leading partner for reimagining, designing, running, and continuously transforming core enterprise functions.</p><ul><li>Wipro&apos;s new operating model combines advisory, AI, and enterprise transformation services.</li><li>The model brings end-to-end accountability across four core functional areas.</li><li>Wipro aims to connect boardroom strategy to scaled operations with this new model.</li><li>The new model is expected to position Wipro as a leading partner for enterprise function transformation.</li><li>Wipro&apos;s new integrated model redefines the traditional services model, with consulting as the upstream transformation engine.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/92a3000a-01ed-4891-b8bf-81716b469c0a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: WIPRO LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GOCOLORS] Go Fashion Fixes Record Date for Buyback of Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Go+Fashion+%28India%29+Ltd&title=Go+Fashion+Fixes+Record+Date+for+Buyback+of+Shares&newsId=a6855779-cbdb-4705-8977-236850eb87d1&token=YTY4NTU3NzktY2Jk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a6855779-cbdb-4705-8977-236850eb87d1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:46:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Buyback</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Go Fashion (India) Ltd has fixed 09 February, 2026 as the Record Date for the purpose of determining the entitlement and the names of equity shareholders who are eligible to participate in the buyback. This follows the company&apos;s earlier announcement of board approval for the buyback of equity shares.</p><ul><li>Go Fashion (India) Ltd has fixed a Record Date for its share buyback</li><li>The Record Date is set for 09 February, 2026</li><li>This decision follows the company&apos;s board approval for the buyback of equity shares</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e0a3f7e5-47cc-44f4-9778-4bbe27bbbe20.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Go Fashion (India) Ltd | Category: Buyback</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UDS] Updater Services Ltd. to Consider and Approve Standalone and Consolidated Un-audited Financial Results on Feb 05, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Updater+Services+Ltd&title=Updater+Services+Ltd.+to+Consider+and+Approve+Standalone+and+Consolidated+Un-audited+Financial+Results+on+Feb+05%2C+2026&newsId=566c2767-10d7-4646-9358-412748703f60&token=NTY2YzI3NjctMTBk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">566c2767-10d7-4646-9358-412748703f60</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:46:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Updater Services Ltd. has informed the BSE that the Board of Directors will meet on February 05, 2026, to consider and approve the Standalone and Consolidated Un-audited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, along with the Limited Review Report. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company has been closed from January 01, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of the audited Financial Results for the Quarter and Nine months ended December 31, 2025, in accordance with the Code of Conduct to Regulate, Monitor and Report Trading by Insiders.</p><ul><li>Updater Services Ltd. to consider and approve Standalone and Consolidated Un-audited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company closed from January 01, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of the audited Financial Results.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2c10e0a2-b651-480d-bc4d-da4c1fe191e6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Updater Services Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FGP] FGP Ltd Announces Q3 and 9M Unaudited Financial Results for 2025, Commences Commodity Trading</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=FGP+LTD.&title=FGP+Ltd+Announces+Q3+and+9M+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+2025%2C+Commences+Commodity+Trading&newsId=77699a62-44d5-483a-b673-20d4c47aab57&token=Nzc2OTlhNjItNDRk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77699a62-44d5-483a-b673-20d4c47aab57</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>FGP Ltd, a company registered under CIN-1.26100M1[1962P1.C012406], announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The company commenced commodity trading activities during the current quarter, resulting in two business segments: Business Centre and Commodity Trading. The company&apos;s revenue, expenses, assets, and liabilities are now reported under these two segments. The financial results were reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors at their respective meetings held on January 29, 2026. The company charged an incremental liability of 0.87 lakhs to the Profit and Loss Account for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025, due to the reassessment of employee benefit obligations relating to gratuity and leave encashment in accordance with the New Labour Codes, 2025.</p><ul><li>FGP Ltd announced its unaudited financial results for Q3 and 9M 2025</li><li>Company commenced commodity trading activities during the current quarter</li><li>Financial results are now reported under two business segments: Business Centre and Commodity Trading</li><li>Incremental liability of 0.87 lakhs charged to the Profit and Loss Account for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025</li><li>Financial results reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0ae01295-3b0f-424c-aab4-decdd347567b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: FGP LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PAYTM*] One 97 Communications Ltd Grants 5,15,617 Stock Options Under Employee Stock Option Scheme 2019</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=One+97+Communications+Ltd&title=One+97+Communications+Ltd+Grants+5%2C15%2C617+Stock+Options+Under+Employee+Stock+Option+Scheme+2019&newsId=123ba1dc-7f88-4396-97d9-529cd56a9e07&token=MTIzYmExZGMtN2Y4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">123ba1dc-7f88-4396-97d9-529cd56a9e07</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 12:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>One 97 Communications Ltd, a company listed on the National Stock Exchange of India Limited and BSE Limited, granted 5,15,617 stock options under the One 97 Employees Stock Option Scheme 2019. The exercise price per share is X 9/-. The options are capable of being exercised anytime during the entire period of continuous active employment from the date of vesting. 1,00,281 equity shares were allotted to eligible employees upon exercise of vested options. The issued, subscribed and paid-up equity share capital of the Company stands increased to X 63,98,28,416 (consisting of 63,98,28,416 equity shares of face value of X 1 each).</p><ul><li>Grant of 5,15,617 stock options under One 97 Employees Stock Option Scheme 2019.</li><li>Exercise Price is X 9/- per stock option.</li><li>Stock Options granted shall be capable of being exercised anytime during the entire period of continuous active employment from the date of vesting.</li><li>Allotment of 1,00,281 equity shares to eligible employees upon exercise of vested options.</li><li>Issued, subscribed and paid-up equity share capital of the Company stands increased to X 63,98,28,416.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c4bb8ee9-f9f0-4bf6-962d-c7c93a0e44c4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: One 97 Communications Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>