<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 06:28:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[COALINDIA] Coal India Subsidiary Bharat Coking Coal Limited Files Prospectus for IPO with RoC</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=COAL+INDIA+LTD.&title=Coal+India+Subsidiary+Bharat+Coking+Coal+Limited+Files+Prospectus+for+IPO+with+RoC&newsId=5865d6df-f8a5-44a4-8b97-c495fe954512&token=NTg2NWQ2ZGYtZjhh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5865d6df-f8a5-44a4-8b97-c495fe954512</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 06:22:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Coal India Ltd has announced the filing of a prospectus by its subsidiary, Bharat Coking Coal Limited (BCCL), with the Registrar of Companies (RoC), Ranchi. This filing is in accordance with the Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements Regulations, 2015 and is a part of the Initial Public Offering (IPO) of up to 465,700,000 Equity Shares by way of an Offer for Sale. The prospectus was filed on January 14, 2026, following the red herring prospectus dated January 2, 2026, and the addendum-cum-corrigendum dated January 7, 2026.</p><ul><li>Coal India subsidiary Bharat Coking Coal Limited files prospectus for IPO with RoC</li><li>IPO involves up to 465,700,000 Equity Shares by way of an Offer for Sale</li><li>Filing is in accordance with Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements Regulations, 2015</li><li>Prospectus filed on January 14, 2026</li><li>Follows red herring prospectus dated January 2, 2026, and addendum-cum-corrigendum dated January 7, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/50d932fa-da75-40be-9da4-6c951d27825b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: COAL INDIA LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RAILTEL] RailTel Corporation of India Ltd Receives Order Worth INR 15,99,31,980 from Food Safety And Standards Authority Of India</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RailTel+Corporation+of+India+Ltd&title=RailTel+Corporation+of+India+Ltd+Receives+Order+Worth+INR+15%2C99%2C31%2C980+from+Food+Safety+And+Standards+Authority+Of+India&newsId=3937236f-b566-4995-9f4b-e3ea991d5ece&token=MzkzNzIzNmYtYjU2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3937236f-b566-4995-9f4b-e3ea991d5ece</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 06:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Order Received</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>RailTel Corporation of India Ltd, a Navratna PSU, has announced that it has received a Work Order from the Food Safety And Standards Authority Of India. The order, valued at INR 15,99,31,980, is a domestic contract for Cloud Services. The order was received on 13th January 2026 and is to be executed by 5th January 2029. The company confirmed that neither the promoter/promoter group nor group companies have any interest in the entity that awarded the order and the order does not fall under related party transactions.</p><ul><li>Order received from Food Safety And Standards Authority Of India</li><li>Value of the order is INR 15,99,31,980</li><li>Domestic contract for Cloud Services</li><li>Order to be executed by 5th January 2029</li><li>Does not fall under related party transactions</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fd9df2e4-87ae-4abb-b2c7-cba0249c1e0a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RailTel Corporation of India Ltd | Category: New Order Received</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ACCELYA] Accelya Solutions India Ltd to Consider and Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Quarter and Six Months Ended 31st December, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Accelya+Solutions+India+Ltd&title=Accelya+Solutions+India+Ltd+to+Consider+and+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Quarter+and+Six+Months+Ended+31st+December%2C+2025&newsId=9f22442c-fe2f-4229-9dd8-0cf6cb1e713c&token=OWYyMjQ0MmMtZmUy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9f22442c-fe2f-4229-9dd8-0cf6cb1e713c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 06:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Accelya Solutions India Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 29th January, 2026 to consider the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and six months ended 31st December, 2025. The meeting will also consider the declaration of interim dividend, if any. The record date for payment of interim dividend, if declared, will be 6th February, 2026.</p><ul><li>Accelya Solutions India Ltd to consider unaudited financial results for quarter and six months ended 31st December, 2025</li><li>Board meeting scheduled on 29th January, 2026</li><li>Interim dividend declaration, if any, to be considered</li><li>Record date for payment of interim dividend set for 6th February, 2026</li><li>Announcement made in compliance with SEBI regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b1fff1a4-40ba-4728-8e11-33fd9104ff98.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Accelya Solutions India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TCS] TCS and AMD Announce Strategic Collaboration to Drive AI Adoption at Scale</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TATA+CONSULTANCY+SERVICES+LTD.&title=TCS+and+AMD+Announce+Strategic+Collaboration+to+Drive+AI+Adoption+at+Scale&newsId=a2335201-aadf-4264-8ae4-c8128a1c35f5&token=YTIzMzUyMDEtYWFk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2335201-aadf-4264-8ae4-c8128a1c35f5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 06:05:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>AI Adoption</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) and AMD have announced a strategic collaboration to help enterprises scale AI adoption from pilots to production, modernize legacy environments, and build secure, high-performance digital workplaces. The companies plan to co-develop industry-specific AI and GenAI solutions, engage in joint investments in talent, and develop industry-specific GenAI frameworks for sectors such as life sciences, manufacturing, and BFSI. The collaboration also aims to deliver tailored accelerators, frameworks, and best practices to boost AI performance across both training and inference workloads.</p><ul><li>TCS and AMD to co-develop industry-specific AI and GenAI solutions</li><li>Joint investments in talent to build a deep pool of experts</li><li>Development of industry-specific GenAI frameworks for life sciences, manufacturing, and BFSI</li><li>Tailored accelerators, frameworks, and best practices to boost AI performance</li><li>TCS to rapidly upskill and certify associates on cutting-edge AMD hardware and software technologies</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/aaf3a2ba-c8a7-44f1-8432-948430f2abbf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TATA CONSULTANCY SERVICES LTD. | Category: AI Adoption</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KMSMEDI] KMS Medisurgi Ltd Exempted from Corporate Governance Report for Q4 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KMS+Medisurgi+Ltd&title=KMS+Medisurgi+Ltd+Exempted+from+Corporate+Governance+Report+for+Q4+2025&newsId=be62da19-1ac7-42f9-a426-545e37f7fc4f&token=YmU2MmRhMTktMWFj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be62da19-1ac7-42f9-a426-545e37f7fc4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 05:58:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>KMS Medisurgi Ltd, a company listed on the BSE SME Platform, has announced that it is exempted from the compliance with the corporate governance provisions as specified in regulations 17, 17A, 18, 19, 20, 21,22, 23, 24, 24A, 25, 26, 27 and clauses (b) to (i) and (t) of sub-regulation (2) of regulation 46 and para C, D and E of Schedule V. This exemption is due to the company&apos;s paid up equity share capital not exceeding rupees ten crore and net worth not exceeding rupees twenty five crore, as on the last day of the previous financial year. Consequently, the company is not required to disclose Report on Corporate Governance pursuant to Regulation 27 (2) of the SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations 2015 for the Quarter ended 31° December, 2025.</p><ul><li>KMS Medisurgi Ltd is exempted from corporate governance report for Q4 2025</li><li>The exemption is due to the company&apos;s equity share capital and net worth not exceeding the specified limits</li><li>The company is listed on the BSE SME Platform</li><li>The exemption is in accordance with Regulation 15(2) of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>The company is not required to disclose Report on Corporate Governance for Q4 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6934f771-0adf-46c1-9350-f35bd7339b84.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KMS Medisurgi Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TRENT] Trent Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q3 and Nine-Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TRENT+LTD.&title=Trent+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine-Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=d94a61e4-9d59-49f0-8189-83d4bd2bf85c&token=ZDk0YTYxZTQtOWQ1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d94a61e4-9d59-49f0-8189-83d4bd2bf85c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 05:51:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Trent Ltd, a well-known name, has informed the BSE that its Board of Directors will meet on 4th February 2026 to consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the third quarter and nine-months ended 31st December 2025. This is in accordance with Regulation 29(1) and 50(1) of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations 2015. The company has also closed its trading window from 25th December 2025 to 6th February 2026 in line with the &apos;Tata Code of Conduct for Prevention of Insider Trading&apos;.</p><ul><li>Trent Ltd to consider and approve Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 and nine-months ended 31st December 2025.</li><li>Board meeting scheduled on 4th February 2026.</li><li>Trading window closed from 25th December 2025 to 6th February 2026 as per &apos;Tata Code of Conduct for Prevention of Insider Trading&apos;.</li><li>In accordance with Regulation 29(1) and 50(1) of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/29102547-4028-43d2-bd7a-0362ac9d4190.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TRENT LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BAJAJ-AUTO] Bajaj Mobility AG Announces Restructuring, Expects EUR 1 Billion Revenue in 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BAJAJ+AUTO+LTD.&title=Bajaj+Mobility+AG+Announces+Restructuring%2C+Expects+EUR+1+Billion+Revenue+in+2025&newsId=4661063c-e3b6-4ed6-912e-5e9f1d169394&token=NDY2MTA2M2MtZTNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4661063c-e3b6-4ed6-912e-5e9f1d169394</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 05:43:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Bajaj Mobility AG (formerly PIERER Mobility AG), a step-down subsidiary of Bajaj Auto Limited, has announced the continuation of its consistent restructuring process. The company expects consolidated sales for the past fiscal year 2025 to be just over EUR 1 billion, marking a reduction of approximately 46% compared to the previous year. The restructuring has led to a significant reduction in motorcycle inventory and the sale of 209,704 units in 2025. As part of the restructuring, KTM AG is initiating a global rightsizing program, which includes a reduction of around 500 employees, mainly in white-collar areas and middle management. The company aims to strengthen its competitiveness in the long term by reducing fixed costs, streamlining structures, focusing the product and project portfolio, and optimizing its international location and management network.</p><ul><li>Bajaj Mobility AG expects EUR 1 billion revenue in 2025, despite a 46% reduction compared to the previous year</li><li>The restructuring process has led to a significant reduction in motorcycle inventory</li><li>KTM AG is initiating a global rightsizing program, including a reduction of around 500 employees</li><li>The restructuring aims to strengthen the company&apos;s competitiveness in the long term</li><li>The company is focusing on reducing fixed costs, streamlining structures, and optimizing its international location and management network</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b0c507b6-b0c6-4292-bc0c-36074c88bb15.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BAJAJ AUTO LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IGARASHI] Igarashi Motors India Ltd Announces No Transfer Requests Re-lodged in December 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IGARASHI+MOTORS+INDIA+LTD.&title=Igarashi+Motors+India+Ltd+Announces+No+Transfer+Requests+Re-lodged+in+December+2025&newsId=e1ec69b2-e4cc-4654-9225-04314f4eec1d&token=ZTFlYzY5YjItZTRj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e1ec69b2-e4cc-4654-9225-04314f4eec1d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 05:28:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Igarashi Motors India Ltd has announced that there were no transfer requests re-lodged during the period from December 01, 2025 to January 06, 2026, as per the SEBI circular No. SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97 dated July 02, 2025. The company will continue to adhere to the SEBI guidelines for processing of transfer requests.</p><ul><li>Igarashi Motors India Ltd announced no transfer requests re-lodged in December 2025</li><li>The announcement is in line with the SEBI circular No. SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97 dated July 02, 2025</li><li>The company will continue to adhere to SEBI guidelines for processing of transfer requests</li><li>The information will be available on the company&apos;s website and Stock Exchange&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/515852c2-5699-4517-be15-85428c4741c5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IGARASHI MOTORS INDIA LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KALYANKJIL] Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd Appoints Ms. Radhika Ramani and Mr. C.R. Rajagopal as Additional Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kalyan+Jewellers+India+Ltd&title=Kalyan+Jewellers+India+Ltd+Appoints+Ms.+Radhika+Ramani+and+Mr.+C.R.+Rajagopal+as+Additional+Directors&newsId=19432541-2706-4680-ad4e-1a020299b4c3&token=MTk0MzI1NDEtMjcw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19432541-2706-4680-ad4e-1a020299b4c3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 05:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd announced the appointment of Ms. Radhika Ramani and Mr. C.R. Rajagopal as Additional Directors (Non-Executive &amp; Independent) to its Board, effective January 14, 2026. The appointments are for a term of five consecutive years, up to January 13, 2031, and are subject to shareholder approval. Ms. Ramani brings over 25 years of global experience in media, communications and growth strategy, while Mr. Rajagopal is a Chartered Accountant with over 35 years of experience in finance, governance and enterprise advisory. The appointments are aligned with the Company’s continued focus on strengthening corporate governance, independent oversight and long-term value creation.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Ms. Radhika Ramani and Mr. C.R. Rajagopal as Additional Directors (Non-Executive &amp; Independent)</li><li>Appointments are for a term of five consecutive years, up to January 13, 2031, and are subject to shareholder approval</li><li>Ms. Ramani brings over 25 years of global experience in media, communications and growth strategy</li><li>Mr. Rajagopal is a Chartered Accountant with over 35 years of experience in finance, governance and enterprise advisory</li><li>Appointments are aligned with the Company’s continued focus on strengthening corporate governance, independent oversight and long-term value creation</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/30712149-4f3f-4de2-b8ed-d923a449881b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VTMLTD] VTM Ltd Approves Proposal for Listing Equity Shares on National Stock Exchange of India Limited (NSE)</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VTM+LTD.&title=VTM+Ltd+Approves+Proposal+for+Listing+Equity+Shares+on+National+Stock+Exchange+of+India+Limited+%28NSE%29&newsId=897622cd-5be2-49b2-8184-0ec621f443a3&token=ODk3NjIyY2QtNWJl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">897622cd-5be2-49b2-8184-0ec621f443a3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 05:24:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>VTM Ltd held a Board Meeting on 14th January 2026 and approved the proposal for listing of the Company’s equity shares on the National Stock Exchange of India Limited (NSE). The Board has approved the engagement of CS Mr. Amogh Diwan and CS Mr. Rohan Shinde as Consultants for the purpose of advising, assisting and supporting the Company in relation to the proposed listing. The meeting was held via video conference and commenced at 10.00 AM and concluded at 10.20 AM. The Company will make an application to the NSE for obtaining in-principle approval for listing and trading of the aforesaid equity shares.</p><ul><li>VTM Ltd approves proposal for listing of equity shares on NSE</li><li>Board has approved the engagement of CS Mr. Amogh Diwan and CS Mr. Rohan Shinde as Consultants</li><li>Company will make an application to the NSE for obtaining in-principle approval for listing and trading</li><li>Listing of 10,05,69,000 (Ten Crore Fifty Lakh Sixty-Nine Thousand) equity shares of face value %1/- (Rupee One only)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dde480b1-3f2d-4716-8358-a074fa04043e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VTM LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>