<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:26:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[INDIASHLTR] India Shelter Finance Corporation Ltd: Board Meeting Approves Q3 Results, NCD Issuance, and Promoter Re-classification</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=India+Shelter+Finance+Corporation+Ltd&title=India+Shelter+Finance+Corporation+Ltd%3A+Board+Meeting+Approves+Q3+Results%2C+NCD+Issuance%2C+and+Promoter+Re-classification&newsId=15f231a1-82bb-437c-8208-87b10ea26706&token=MTVmMjMxYTEtODJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">15f231a1-82bb-437c-8208-87b10ea26706</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:24:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>India Shelter Finance Corporation Ltd held a board meeting on February 07, 2026, where they approved the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The board also approved the issuance of Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs) up to Rs. 1000 crores and the re-classification of promoter/promoter group to the public category. The company has maintained a 110% security cover on its secured listed non-convertible debentures and allotted 7,25,259 equity shares to employees under the approved employee stock option plan.</p><ul><li>Approval of Q3 financial results</li><li>Plan to raise funds through NCD issuance</li><li>Promoter re-classification from promoter/promoter group to public category</li><li>Maintaining 110% security cover on secured listed non-convertible debentures</li><li>Allotment of equity shares to employees under the approved employee stock option plan</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9e687f3f-c831-4887-adca-2bb244f414e7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: India Shelter Finance Corporation Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SIMPLEXCAS] Simplex Castings Ltd. Reappoints Internal Auditor, Plans Fund Raising &amp; EGM</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SIMPLEX+CASTINGS+LTD.&title=Simplex+Castings+Ltd.+Reappoints+Internal+Auditor%2C+Plans+Fund+Raising+%26+EGM&newsId=db3bd595-b2bd-4a97-b41f-1b96ed86e8d0&token=ZGIzYmQ1OTUtYjJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db3bd595-b2bd-4a97-b41f-1b96ed86e8d0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:22:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Simplex Castings Ltd. has reappointed M/s M D N &amp; Associates as the Internal Auditor for the financial year 2026-27. The company also plans to raise funds up to INR 50.15 Cr by issuing equity shares on a preferential basis. An Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) has been called on 2nd March, 2026, to seek shareholders’ approval on matters approved by the Board.</p><ul><li>Reappointment of M/s M D N &amp; Associates as Internal Auditor</li><li>Plan to raise funds up to INR 50.15 Cr through preferential issue of equity shares</li><li>Calling of 02/2025-26 Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) of the members</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1f33a702-2d97-472b-92b9-a41a9474cb07.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SIMPLEX CASTINGS LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SURANAT&amp;P] Surana Telecom and Power Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Surana+Telecom+And+Power+Limited&title=Surana+Telecom+and+Power+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=41d06a61-91c2-42a8-8d1a-19c8eee2b101&token=NDFkMDZhNjEtOTFj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41d06a61-91c2-42a8-8d1a-19c8eee2b101</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:22:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Surana Telecom and Power Ltd has announced its financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 2,167.90 lakhs for the quarter and 3,212.41 lakhs for the nine months period. The total income for the quarter is 2,848.73 lakhs and 4,403.59 lakhs for the nine months. The company&apos;s profit before tax for the quarter is 517.24 lakhs and 996.68 lakhs for the nine months. The financial results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for Q3 is 2,167.90 lakhs</li><li>Revenue from operations for nine months is 3,212.41 lakhs</li><li>Profit before tax for Q3 is 517.24 lakhs</li><li>Profit before tax for nine months is 996.68 lakhs</li><li>Financial results reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6efb56de-3cf8-40ff-b3bf-1e40662ad29c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Surana Telecom And Power Limited | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ALFREDHE] Alfred Herbert India Ltd. Reports Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ALFRED+HERBERT+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Alfred+Herbert+India+Ltd.+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=44e61c19-5887-4228-b213-7195abe69fc6&token=NDRlNjFjMTktNTg4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">44e61c19-5887-4228-b213-7195abe69fc6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:22:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Alfred Herbert India Ltd. has released its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The results were approved by the Board of Directors in a meeting held on 7th February, 2026. The company&apos;s revenue from operations, finance costs, and other comprehensive income have been reported.</p><ul><li>Alfred Herbert India Ltd. reported its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025.</li><li>The results were approved by the Board of Directors in a meeting held on 7th February, 2026.</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue from operations, finance costs, and other comprehensive income have been reported.</li><li>The review was conducted in accordance with the Standard on Review Engagement (SRE) 2410 issued by the Institute of Chartered Accountants of India.</li><li>No material misstatement was found in the statement.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/953069d4-7a4d-4ba3-bddd-76387e6a14c3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ALFRED HERBERT (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SIMPLEXCAS] Simplex Castings Ltd. to Raise Funds Up to INR 50.15 Cr via Preferential Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SIMPLEX+CASTINGS+LTD.&title=Simplex+Castings+Ltd.+to+Raise+Funds+Up+to+INR+50.15+Cr+via+Preferential+Issue&newsId=ca283788-afc2-4c69-92da-126c9fc547bc&token=Y2EyODM3ODgtYWZj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ca283788-afc2-4c69-92da-126c9fc547bc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Simplex Castings Ltd. has announced its intention to raise funds up to INR 50.15 Cr by issuing equity shares on a preferential basis. The decision was made during the Board of Directors meeting held on 7th February 2026. The proposed allotment includes 4,04,860 shares for Giants Fund Limited, 4,04,860 shares for Surya Jagdishchand, and several other investors. The issue price is determined at Rs.494/- per share, including a premium of Rs.484/-. The shares will be locked in as per the SEBI (ICDR) Regulations, 2018.</p><ul><li>Simplex Castings Ltd. to raise funds up to INR 50.15 Cr</li><li>Funds to be raised via preferential issue of equity shares</li><li>4,04,860 shares proposed for Giants Fund Limited and Surya Jagdishchand</li><li>Issue price set at Rs.494/- per share with a premium of Rs.484/-</li><li>Shares to be locked in as per SEBI (ICDR) Regulations, 2018</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/63e122dd-5270-4122-b21d-aa92a93c894c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SIMPLEX CASTINGS LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BENTCOM] Bentley Commercial Enterprises Ltd Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BENTLEY+COMMERCIAL+ENTERPRISES+LTD.&title=Bentley+Commercial+Enterprises+Ltd+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025&newsId=e828ad1e-fcef-40bc-a01a-f84a8e5d8822&token=ZTgyOGFkMWUtZmNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e828ad1e-fcef-40bc-a01a-f84a8e5d8822</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:22:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bentley Commercial Enterprises Ltd has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at ₹ 0.48 Crore for the quarter and ₹ 1.43 Crore for the nine months period. The profit before tax for the quarter is ₹ 187.08 Lakhs and ₹ 479.03 Lakhs for the nine months period. The total comprehensive income for the period is ₹ 17,032.44 Lakhs. The company operates in a single segment and the figures have been re-grouped/reworked/re-arranged to make them comparable.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter is ₹ 0.48 Crore</li><li>Profit before tax for the quarter is ₹ 187.08 Lakhs</li><li>Total comprehensive income for the period is ₹ 17,032.44 Lakhs</li><li>The company operates in a single segment</li><li>Figures have been re-grouped/reworked/re-arranged to make them comparable</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/992a996a-3529-4e84-bf14-dddc8694cff3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BENTLEY COMMERCIAL ENTERPRISES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EUROPRATIK] Euro Pratik Sales Ltd Announces Q3 Results, Appoints New Internal Auditor, and Enters Joint Venture</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Euro+Pratik+Sales+Ltd&title=Euro+Pratik+Sales+Ltd+Announces+Q3+Results%2C+Appoints+New+Internal+Auditor%2C+and+Enters+Joint+Venture&newsId=5a0837d1-8592-40b5-8995-9536d984aa23&token=NWEwODM3ZDEtODU5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a0837d1-8592-40b5-8995-9536d984aa23</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:22:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Euro Pratik Sales Ltd has announced its un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter ended 31st December, 2025. The company&apos;s Board of Directors approved the results and appointed M/s. D N A &amp; Associates, Chartered Accountants, Mumbai as the Internal Auditors for the financial year 2026-27. The Board also approved a joint venture agreement with Mr. Srikanth Mundada and his nominees to form a new joint venture Limited Liability Partnership, &apos;Hues Plydecor LLP&apos;, to carry on the business of surface decorative products in Southern part of India.</p><ul><li>Un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 2025 approved</li><li>M/s. D N A &amp; Associates appointed as Internal Auditors for FY 2026-27</li><li>Joint venture agreement with Mr. Srikanth Mundada and his nominees</li><li>New joint venture Limited Liability Partnership to be incorporated as &apos;Hues Plydecor LLP&apos;</li><li>Business of surface decorative products in Southern part of India</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/001eaf92-ffcc-44b5-9ac7-11f59c2226df.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Euro Pratik Sales Ltd | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EUROPRATIK] Euro Pratik Sales Ltd Re-appoints Internal Auditor &amp; Enters Joint Venture Agreement</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Euro+Pratik+Sales+Ltd&title=Euro+Pratik+Sales+Ltd+Re-appoints+Internal+Auditor+%26+Enters+Joint+Venture+Agreement&newsId=f755b831-63ba-476e-9175-7621f8179195&token=Zjc1NWI4MzEtNjNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f755b831-63ba-476e-9175-7621f8179195</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:22:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Euro Pratik Sales Ltd, a company based in Mumbai, India, has announced the re-appointment of M/s. D N A &amp; Associates as its Internal Auditor for the financial year 2026-27. The company has also entered into a joint venture agreement with Mr. Srikanth Mundada and his nominees to form a new joint venture Limited Liability Partnership, &apos;Hues Plydecor LLP&apos;, to carry on the business of surface decorative products in Southern India. The company will contribute up to Rs. 1000.00 Lakh, holding 51% of the total contribution.</p><ul><li>Re-appointment of M/s. D N A &amp; Associates as Internal Auditor for the financial year 2026-27</li><li>Entry into a joint venture agreement with Mr. Srikanth Mundada and his nominees</li><li>Formation of a new joint venture Limited Liability Partnership, &apos;Hues Plydecor LLP&apos;</li><li>Business expansion in Southern India in the surface decorative products sector</li><li>Company&apos;s contribution of up to Rs. 1000.00 Lakh, holding 51% of the total contribution</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d8eb6479-583b-421e-9012-7f4ffaaa5d0e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Euro Pratik Sales Ltd | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EXCELSOFT] Excelsoft Technologies Reports Strong Q3 &amp; 9M FY26 with 110% YoY Net Profit Surge</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Excelsoft+Technologies+Ltd&title=Excelsoft+Technologies+Reports+Strong+Q3+%26+9M+FY26+with+110%25+YoY+Net+Profit+Surge&newsId=857c3721-1a10-4178-809d-489807c27df7&token=ODU3YzM3MjEtMWEx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">857c3721-1a10-4178-809d-489807c27df7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Excelsoft Technologies, a global provider of digital learning solutions, announced its unaudited consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a 29% YoY increase in total income for Q3 FY26 and an 18% YoY increase for 9M FY26. The net profit surged by 40% YoY in Q3 FY26 and 110% YoY in 9M FY26. The improved profitability was driven by scale benefits, stronger performance in high-margin segments, and disciplined cost management. Excelsoft added 10 new clients and formed a dedicated AI taskforce with AQA (UK) to advance secure, ethical, and human-centered AI models for e-marking of handwritten scripts in high-stakes assessments.</p><ul><li>Net Profit Surges 110% YoY in 9M FY26</li><li>Total income rises 18% YoY to X204.44 crore in 9M FY26</li><li>Improved profitability driven by scale benefits, stronger performance in high-margin segments, and disciplined cost management</li><li>Added 10 new clients</li><li>Formed a dedicated AI taskforce with AQA (UK)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/eacf88dc-9a07-49ac-81d9-918e663351e2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Excelsoft Technologies Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CSL] Continental Securities Ltd Approves Conversion of 5,00,000 Warrants into Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Continental+Securities+Ltd&title=Continental+Securities+Ltd+Approves+Conversion+of+5%2C00%2C000+Warrants+into+Equity+Shares&newsId=dac188db-a55f-4a80-88d0-2058e106562e&token=ZGFjMTg4ZGItYTU1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dac188db-a55f-4a80-88d0-2058e106562e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:21:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Continental Securities Ltd has considered and approved the conversion of 5,00,000 warrants into 5,00,000 Equity shares of face value of Rs. 2/- at a premium of Rs. 19/- each. The warrants were allotted on February 07, 2026, on a preferential basis to allottees of the Non-Promoter Group. The company has received the balance 75% of the total consideration with respect to warrants from the investor, and hence converting the same into Equity Shares. This decision has increased the paid-up equity capital of the Company from 35,99,06,000/- to 6,09,06,000/-.</p><ul><li>Continental Securities Ltd has approved the conversion of 5,00,000 warrants into Equity shares</li><li>The warrants were allotted on February 07, 2026, on a preferential basis to allottees of the Non-Promoter Group</li><li>The company has received the balance 75% of the total consideration with respect to warrants from the investor</li><li>The conversion has increased the paid-up equity capital of the Company from 35,99,06,000/- to 6,09,06,000/-</li><li>The warrants were allotted at a premium of Rs. 19/- each</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/590e4338-1651-4a53-9a4a-631b1bf7a0d1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Continental Securities Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>