<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 04:09:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[HGS] HGS Launches AMLens: A Next-Gen Al Solution for AML Operations, Reducing Case Analysis Time by 75%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HINDUJA+GLOBAL+SOLUTIONS+LTD.&title=HGS+Launches+AMLens%3A+A+Next-Gen+Al+Solution+for+AML+Operations%2C+Reducing+Case+Analysis+Time+by+75%25&newsId=ca0c6bc7-bc16-4a13-9741-fb3d1e765dd8&token=Y2EwYzZiYzctYmMx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ca0c6bc7-bc16-4a13-9741-fb3d1e765dd8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 04:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>HGS, a leading provider of digital experience and business process management services, has announced the launch of AMLens, a next-generation Al-powered solution designed to transform and accelerate Anti-Money Laundering (AML) operations for financial institutions. AMLens integrates machine learning and Natural Language Processing (NLP) to reduce case analysis time and false positives, enabling banks to meet stringent regulatory standards while boosting investigator productivity.</p><ul><li>AMLens reduces case analysis time by 75%, providing a significant boost in investigator productivity.</li><li>It integrates machine learning and Natural Language Processing (NLP) to reduce false positives and meet regulatory standards.</li><li>AMLens supports AML teams across detection, triage, contextualization, and summarization by providing a modular, explainable Al ecosystem.</li><li>It automates the collection and consolidation of fragmented data into a single, analyst-friendly format.</li><li>AMLens is built on a modular, API-first design for integration with existing client systems and is available to target market segments including Retail &amp; Consumer Banking, Payments &amp; Fintech, Credit Card &amp; Lending, and Wealth Management.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fc8aeb15-8142-454f-9d05-d22669dcf4b1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HINDUJA GLOBAL SOLUTIONS LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KINGSINFR] Kings Infra Ventures Ltd Outlines ‘The Way Forward’ Strategic Roadmap; Focuses on Financial Consolidation, Core Growth, and Institutional Value Creation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kings+Infra+Ventures+Limited&title=Kings+Infra+Ventures+Ltd+Outlines+%E2%80%98The+Way+Forward%E2%80%99+Strategic+Roadmap%3B+Focuses+on+Financial+Consolidation%2C+Core+Growth%2C+and+Institutional+Value+Creation&newsId=9c95ecef-1a83-4beb-ad9e-8ebbe2cd03e4&token=OWM5NWVjZWYtMWE4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c95ecef-1a83-4beb-ad9e-8ebbe2cd03e4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 04:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Strategic Roadmap</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Kings Infra Ventures Limited has articulated a refined strategic roadmap aimed at consolidating its market standing and accelerating value creation for its stakeholders. The ‘Way Forward’ strategy emphasizes a transition towards sustainable growth, operational excellence in aquaculture and exports, and the unlocking of institutional value from its infrastructure and real estate assets. The company is adopting a decentralized corporate structure, focusing on a more focused growth model, enhancing both topline and bottom-line performance through its core aquaculture and export verticals, and reinforcing its position as a pioneer in aquaculture.</p><ul><li>Articulating a refined strategic roadmap for sustainable growth and value creation</li><li>Adopting a decentralized corporate structure for operational excellence</li><li>Focusing on a more focused growth model in aquaculture and export verticals</li><li>Unlocking institutional value from infrastructure and real estate assets</li><li>Fast-tracking the development of the Kings Maritime Aquaculture Technology Park in Visakhapatnam</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/37c69d5f-e624-4f46-b5de-42a4986501aa.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kings Infra Ventures Limited | Category: Strategic Roadmap</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHKARTP] Shree Karthik Papers Ltd Promoters Confirm No Encumbrance on Shares as of December 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHREE+KARTHIK+PAPERS+LTD.&title=Shree+Karthik+Papers+Ltd+Promoters+Confirm+No+Encumbrance+on+Shares+as+of+December+2025&newsId=31ee4d87-0185-4921-b971-4f966b055743&token=MzFlZTRkODctMDE4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">31ee4d87-0185-4921-b971-4f966b055743</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 03:45:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>According to the statement of SEBI (Acquisition of shares) of LODR 2015 for December 2025, the promoters of Shree Karthik Papers Ltd have confirmed that they have not made any encumbrance, directly or indirectly, on the shares held by them in the company. This confirmation is in accordance with Regulation 31(4) of SEBI (SAST) Regulations, 2011. Furthermore, the promoters have confirmed that as of December 31, 2025, nil number of shares of the company are encumbered or pledged by them.</p><ul><li>Promoters of Shree Karthik Papers Ltd confirm no encumbrance on shares as of December 2025</li><li>Confirmation made in accordance with Regulation 31(4) of SEBI (SAST) Regulations, 2011</li><li>No shares of the company encumbered or pledged by promoters as of December 31, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d4e51968-dadd-44cd-9e74-711b615a2140.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHREE KARTHIK PAPERS LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KOTAKBANK] Kotak Mahindra Bank Appoints Mr. Anup Kumar Saha as Whole-time Director and Senior Management Personnel</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KOTAK+MAHINDRA+BANK+LTD.&title=Kotak+Mahindra+Bank+Appoints+Mr.+Anup+Kumar+Saha+as+Whole-time+Director+and+Senior+Management+Personnel&newsId=5b46d401-bb3d-4dc6-9b1d-50122c0ecd27&token=NWI0NmQ0MDEtYmIz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b46d401-bb3d-4dc6-9b1d-50122c0ecd27</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 03:38:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd. has appointed Mr. Anup Kumar Saha as an Additional Director and a Whole-time Director (Executive Director) for a period of three years. The appointment will take effect from the date of receipt of all necessary approvals from the Reserve Bank of India or any other regulatory/statutory authority. Mr. Saha has also been appointed as Whole-time Director (Designate) and Senior Management Personnel from January 12, 2026, till his appointment as Whole-time Director takes effect. He will also be a Key Managerial Personnel of the Bank once his appointment as Whole-time Director takes effect.</p><ul><li>Mr. Anup Kumar Saha appointed as Additional Director and Whole-time Director (Executive Director) of Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd.</li><li>Appointment is for a period of three years, subject to regulatory approvals.</li><li>Mr. Saha also appointed as Whole-time Director (Designate) and Senior Management Personnel from January 12, 2026.</li><li>Mr. Saha will be a Key Managerial Personnel once his appointment as Whole-time Director takes effect.</li><li>Mr. Saha has over 32 years of professional experience in financial services.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/71cfe8e7-51df-4861-85c9-18fb85217648.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KOTAK MAHINDRA BANK LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TANFACIND] Tanfac Industries Signs Long Term Supply Contract with Japanese Customer for Fluorinated Chemicals</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TANFAC+INDUSTRIES+LTD.-%24&title=Tanfac+Industries+Signs+Long+Term+Supply+Contract+with+Japanese+Customer+for+Fluorinated+Chemicals&newsId=52a3d7ed-7c82-4561-83bd-03a0d14b425a&token=NTJhM2Q3ZWQtN2M4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">52a3d7ed-7c82-4561-83bd-03a0d14b425a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 03:37:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Tanfac Industries Limited has entered into a long term supply contract with a Japanese customer for fluorinated chemicals. The contract covers the supply of 7,500 metric tonnes per annum with an estimated value of 2337.5 crore per year and an aggregate contract value of approximately 2,362 crore over a seven year period. The agreement will be effective from 1 January 2027 and provides long term revenue visibility backed by committed volumes. This contract strengthens the Company&apos;s domestic and export portfolio, enhances earnings predictability, and reinforces its position as a reliable supplier in the global fluorinated chemicals market.</p><ul><li>Long term supply contract with a Japanese customer for fluorinated chemicals.</li><li>Supply of 7,500 metric tonnes per annum with an estimated value of 2337.5 crore per year.</li><li>Aggregate contract value of approximately 2,362 crore over a seven year period.</li><li>Effective from 1 January 2027.</li><li>Strengthens the Company&apos;s domestic and export portfolio and reinforces its position in the global fluorinated chemicals market.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/44b43d7f-09da-439f-80bc-41fa1093d8d8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TANFAC INDUSTRIES LTD.-$ | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SEAMECLTD] Seamec Ltd&apos;s Vessel &apos;SEAMEC PALADIN&apos; Off-hired for Statutory Drydocking</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SEAMEC+LTD.&title=Seamec+Ltd%27s+Vessel+%27SEAMEC+PALADIN%27+Off-hired+for+Statutory+Drydocking&newsId=0f2bf628-cf8c-4a34-bbf0-7974bc30b60a&token=MGYyYmY2MjgtY2Y4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f2bf628-cf8c-4a34-bbf0-7974bc30b60a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 03:32:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Seamec Ltd has announced that its vessel, &apos;SEAMEC PALADIN&apos;, has been temporarily off-hired for statutory drydocking. The off-hiring took effect from 10 January 2026 at 16:00 hrs and is expected to last for around 70 days. The decision was made after completion of formalities.</p><ul><li>Seamec Ltd&apos;s vessel &apos;SEAMEC PALADIN&apos; is off-hired for drydocking</li><li>The off-hiring is expected to last for around 70 days</li><li>The decision was made after completion of formalities</li><li>The vessel was off-hired with effect from 10 January 2026 at 16:00 hrs</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/481d2aa5-4bad-4e92-975d-73620b142632.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SEAMEC LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TANFACIND] TANFAC Industries Ltd. Secures Rs. 2,362.5 Crores Contract with Japanese Customer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TANFAC+INDUSTRIES+LTD.-%24&title=TANFAC+Industries+Ltd.+Secures+Rs.+2%2C362.5+Crores+Contract+with+Japanese+Customer&newsId=a68922c2-3a78-44fd-a882-3d286d41c01b&token=YTY4OTIyYzItM2E3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a68922c2-3a78-44fd-a882-3d286d41c01b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 03:24:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>TANFAC Industries Ltd. has signed a significant contract with a Japanese customer for the supply of 7,500 MT of Fluorinated Chemicals per annum, estimated to be worth Rs. 337.5 Crores annually. The contract, which is part of the company&apos;s normal course of business, has a duration of 7 years, starting from 1st January 2027, and is expected to generate a total of Rs. 2,362.5 Crores over its term, excluding GST.</p><ul><li>Contract value: Rs. 337.5 Crores per annum, totaling to Rs. 2,362.5 Crores over 7 years</li><li>Supply of 7,500 MT of Fluorinated Chemicals per annum</li><li>7-year contract duration starting from 1st January 2027</li><li>Awarded in the normal course of business</li><li>Contract signed with a Japanese customer</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/791cf2d8-4441-4327-88a4-afc1b0fad2ca.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TANFAC INDUSTRIES LTD.-$ | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MANINDS] Man Industries Receives New Orders Worth Approx. Rs. 550 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MAN+INDUSTRIES+%28INDIA%29+LTD.-%24&title=Man+Industries+Receives+New+Orders+Worth+Approx.+Rs.+550+Crores&newsId=e9ba038c-f48e-47ec-9a8a-2f8127983407&token=ZTliYTAzOGMtZjQ4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9ba038c-f48e-47ec-9a8a-2f8127983407</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 03:24:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Man Industries (India) Ltd. has announced that it has received new orders for approximately Rs. 550 crores. The orders are expected to be delivered within 6 months, contributing to the total unexecuted order book of approximately Rs. 4600 crores. This development highlights the robust business environment and the trust of customers in the company&apos;s technological and executional capabilities.</p><ul><li>Man Industries receives new orders worth approximately Rs. 550 crores</li><li>Orders are expected to be delivered within 6 months</li><li>Total unexecuted order book stands at approximately Rs. 4600 crores</li><li>Reflects the robust business environment</li><li>Showcases the trust of customers in the company&apos;s capabilities</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/94563e99-a1cc-4579-815d-c51185437d74.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MAN INDUSTRIES (INDIA) LTD.-$ | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BIOCON] Biocon Pharma&apos;s Subsidiary Receives U.S. FDA Approval for Everolimus Tablets</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BIOCON+LTD.&title=Biocon+Pharma%27s+Subsidiary+Receives+U.S.+FDA+Approval+for+Everolimus+Tablets&newsId=3743a973-ebf6-4aeb-9c5d-653a9c1f4aaa&token=Mzc0M2E5NzMtZWJm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3743a973-ebf6-4aeb-9c5d-653a9c1f4aaa</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 03:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>USFDA</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Biocon Pharma Limited, a wholly owned subsidiary of Biocon Ltd, has received approval from the U.S. Food and Drug Administration (U.S. FDA) for its ANDA for Everolimus Tablets for Oral Suspension in 2 mg, 3 mg and 5 mg strengths. The tablets are indicated for the treatment of adult and pediatric patients aged 1 year and older with Tuberous Sclerosis Complex (TSC) who have Subependymal Giant Cell Astrocytoma (SEGA) and for the adjunctive treatment of adult and pediatric patients aged 2 years and older with TSC-associated partial-onset seizures. This approval strengthens Biocon’s portfolio of vertically integrated drug products.</p><ul><li>Biocon Pharma&apos;s subsidiary receives U.S. FDA approval for Everolimus Tablets for Oral Suspension in 2 mg, 3 mg and 5 mg strengths</li><li>The tablets are indicated for the treatment of adult and pediatric patients aged 1 year and older with Tuberous Sclerosis Complex (TSC) who have Subependymal Giant Cell Astrocytoma (SEGA)</li><li>The tablets are also indicated for the adjunctive treatment of adult and pediatric patients aged 2 years and older with TSC-associated partial-onset seizures</li><li>This approval strengthens Biocon’s portfolio of vertically integrated drug products in the U.S. market</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/79513d53-5e55-4bbc-969f-04033d0f3b9f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BIOCON LTD. | Category: USFDA</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHAKTIPUMP] Shakti Pumps India Ltd. Receives Letter of Award for 16,780 Standalone Off-Grid DC Solar Photovoltaic Water Pumping Systems</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHAKTI+PUMPS+%28INDIA%29+LTD.-%24&title=Shakti+Pumps+India+Ltd.+Receives+Letter+of+Award+for+16%2C780+Standalone+Off-Grid+DC+Solar+Photovoltaic+Water+Pumping+Systems&newsId=2cd6abb9-6c38-4b50-b754-48dc145fef52&token=MmNkNmFiYjktNmMz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2cd6abb9-6c38-4b50-b754-48dc145fef52</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 03:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Shakti Pumps India Ltd. has announced that it has received a Letter of Award from Karnataka Renewable Energy Development Limited for 16,780 Standalone Off-Grid DC Solar Photovoltaic Water Pumping Systems. The total value of the pumps is around Rs. 654.03 Crores (inclusive of GST). The order includes design, manufacture, supply, transport, installation, testing, and commissioning of the systems. The time period for the order is on or before 31.03.2026.</p><ul><li>Shakti Pumps India Ltd. received a Letter of Award from Karnataka Renewable Energy Development Limited</li><li>The award is for 16,780 Standalone Off-Grid DC Solar Photovoltaic Water Pumping Systems</li><li>The total value of the pumps is around Rs. 654.03 Crores (inclusive of GST)</li><li>The order includes design, manufacture, supply, transport, installation, testing, and commissioning</li><li>The time period for the order is on or before 31.03.2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f51b6866-9048-465a-a7fc-383182baa7db.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHAKTI PUMPS (INDIA) LTD.-$ | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>