<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 01:42:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[IRMENERGY] IRM Energy Ltd Announces Q3 &amp; 9M FY2025 Financial Results with New Director Appointment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IRM+Energy+Ltd&title=IRM+Energy+Ltd+Announces+Q3+%26+9M+FY2025+Financial+Results+with+New+Director+Appointment&newsId=e02170d7-6fde-41d1-a3c0-c2bd6b19e9aa&token=ZTAyMTcwZDctNmZk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e02170d7-6fde-41d1-a3c0-c2bd6b19e9aa</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:01:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>IRM Energy Ltd has announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s Board of Directors approved the results, which were prepared in accordance with the provisions of Regulation 33 of the SEBI Listing Regulations. The Board also approved the appointment of Mr. Vivek Vishwas Wathodkar as an Additional Independent Director and Independent Director for a period of 5 years, subject to member approval. The financial results showed a consolidated net loss of Rs. 8.07 million and Rs. 21.03 million for the quarter and year to date period, respectively.</p><ul><li>Unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 and 9M FY2025 approved</li><li>New Additional Independent Director appointed (Mr. Vivek Vishwas Wathodkar)</li><li>Consolidated net loss of Rs. 8.07 million for the quarter and Rs. 21.03 million year to date</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Wathodkar subject to member approval</li><li>Financial results prepared according to Regulation 33 of SEBI Listing Regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6d25e8c4-7970-43ae-96c8-7451e4f921e3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IRM Energy Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CENTRUM] Centrum Capital&apos;s Subsidiary, Centrum Housing Finance, Receives RBI Approval for Change in Control</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CENTRUM+CAPITAL+LTD.&title=Centrum+Capital%27s+Subsidiary%2C+Centrum+Housing+Finance%2C+Receives+RBI+Approval+for+Change+in+Control&newsId=6cd41d47-6ad1-421a-b87a-fd07288c2ce7&token=NmNkNDFkNDctNmFk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6cd41d47-6ad1-421a-b87a-fd07288c2ce7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Centrum Capital Ltd has announced that its subsidiary, Centrum Housing Finance Limited (CHFL), has received approval from the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) for the proposed change in control and acquisition of the Company’s stake in CHFL by Weaver Services Private Limited. This approval marks a significant step towards the closure of the transaction, which is subject to the fulfilment of other conditions precedent specified in the Share Purchase Agreement (SPA).</p><ul><li>Centrum Housing Finance Limited (CHFL) has received approval from the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) for the proposed change in control</li><li>The approval is a significant step towards the closure of the transaction</li><li>The transaction is subject to the fulfilment of other conditions precedent specified in the Share Purchase Agreement (SPA)</li><li>Centrum Capital Ltd had entered into a Share Purchase Agreement (SPA) for the transfer of its entire stake in CHFL to Weaver Services Private Limited</li><li>The proposed acquisition is subject to requisite statutory, regulatory and corporate approvals</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3e46ca52-2a41-4bad-a5cb-78f7eb6a0690.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CENTRUM CAPITAL LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IRMENERGY] IRM Energy Ltd Updates Key Managerial Personnel Details</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IRM+Energy+Ltd&title=IRM+Energy+Ltd+Updates+Key+Managerial+Personnel+Details&newsId=7984df93-7f06-4d07-8662-c03b613508df&token=Nzk4NGRmOTMtN2Yw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7984df93-7f06-4d07-8662-c03b613508df</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>IRM Energy Ltd has updated the details of its Key Managerial Personnel who have been authorized by the Board of Directors for determining materiality of any event or information and for the purpose of making disclosure to the Stock Exchange(s) under Regulation 30 of SEBI Listing Regulations. The new appointments include Mr. Amitabha Banerjee as Whole Time Director, Mr. Manoj Kumar Sharma as Chief Executive Officer (CEO), Mr. Arun Kumar Saluru as Chief Financial Officer (CFO), and Mr. Akshit Soni as Company Secretary &amp; Compliance Officer. The company is requested to take this information on record.</p><ul><li>IRM Energy Ltd updates Key Managerial Personnel details</li><li>Mr. Amitabha Banerjee appointed as Whole Time Director</li><li>Mr. Manoj Kumar Sharma appointed as Chief Executive Officer (CEO)</li><li>Mr. Arun Kumar Saluru appointed as Chief Financial Officer (CFO)</li><li>Mr. Akshit Soni appointed as Company Secretary &amp; Compliance Officer</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/10a56691-d8fa-4aa8-9f31-71a0014347d0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IRM Energy Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[APOLLOFI] Apollo Finvest India Ltd Announces Q3 Results for 2025, Profit After Tax at 16.54%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=APOLLO+FINVEST+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Apollo+Finvest+India+Ltd+Announces+Q3+Results+for+2025%2C+Profit+After+Tax+at+16.54%25&newsId=7f0f6230-0f9d-4388-bb90-3819bd41c490&token=N2YwZjYyMzAtMGY5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7f0f6230-0f9d-4388-bb90-3819bd41c490</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Apollo Finvest India Ltd has announced its financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s profit before tax stands at INR XX.XX Lakhs and profit after tax is INR XX.XX Lakhs, representing a growth of 3.1% and 15.76% respectively. The earnings per equity share (of 210 each) are INR 4.67 for basic and INR 4.67 for diluted. The financial results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Profit before tax for the quarter is INR XX.XX Lakhs</li><li>Profit after tax for the quarter is INR XX.XX Lakhs</li><li>Earnings per equity share (of 210 each) are INR 4.67 for basic and INR 4.67 for diluted</li><li>The financial results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors</li><li>The company has accounted for the estimated incremental impact of the New Labour Codes as Employee benefits expenses amounting to INR 9.47 Lakhs</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e4f7a076-f424-4321-8bec-382427e4db58.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: APOLLO FINVEST (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAVINFOCO] Magnus Steel and Infra Corrigendum: Change in Post-Issue Shareholding of Proposed Allottee Ms. Arti Anjaria</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SAVANT+INFOCOMM+LTD.&title=Magnus+Steel+and+Infra+Corrigendum%3A+Change+in+Post-Issue+Shareholding+of+Proposed+Allottee+Ms.+Arti+Anjaria&newsId=5c6b4cdb-70d6-4365-881e-1561c40256e0&token=NWM2YjRjZGItNzBk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c6b4cdb-70d6-4365-881e-1561c40256e0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Magnus Steel and Infra Ltd has issued a corrigendum to the Notice of the Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) dated January 15, 2026. The corrigendum is to inform the Shareholders of a change in the Explanatory Statement regarding the percentage of post-issue shareholding of the proposed allottee Ms. Arti Anjaria. The proposed allotment of equity shares to Ms. Arti Anjaria will now result in a 10.33% post preferential allotment shareholding instead of the previously stated 11.11%. This change is due to an inadvertent error in the original Explanatory Statement. The corrigendum forms an integral part of the Notice of EGM and is also available on the Company&apos;s website and BSE Limited website.</p><ul><li>Magnus Steel and Infra Ltd has issued a corrigendum to the Notice of the Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) dated January 15, 2026.</li><li>The corrigendum is to inform the Shareholders of a change in the Explanatory Statement regarding the percentage of post-issue shareholding of the proposed allottee Ms. Arti Anjaria.</li><li>The proposed allotment of equity shares to Ms. Arti Anjaria will now result in a 10.33% post preferential allotment shareholding instead of the previously stated 11.11%.</li><li>This change is due to an inadvertent error in the original Explanatory Statement.</li><li>The corrigendum forms an integral part of the Notice of EGM and is also available on the Company&apos;s website and BSE Limited website.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d84572d9-6bb8-4f4c-b924-d9823f5e0a19.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SAVANT INFOCOMM LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CSL] Continental Securities Ltd Receives Disclosure from Promoter Group Vachi Commercial LLP under SEBI(PIT) Regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Continental+Securities+Ltd&title=Continental+Securities+Ltd+Receives+Disclosure+from+Promoter+Group+Vachi+Commercial+LLP+under+SEBI%28PIT%29+Regulations&newsId=5a4e43b8-610e-4d27-848e-f7cc2ac3c187&token=NWE0ZTQzYjgtNjEw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a4e43b8-610e-4d27-848e-f7cc2ac3c187</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Continental Securities Ltd has received disclosures from VACHI COMMERCIAL LLP, Promoter Group of the Company under Regulation 7(2) of SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015. The disclosure includes Form C under Regulation 7(2) read with Regulation 6(2) of the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015. Vachi Commercial LLP has subscribed to 17,00,000 Convertible Warrants and 10,00,000 Equity Shares of face value Rs. 2.00 each have been allotted upon exercise/conversion of 10,00,000 Convertible Warrants to Equity Shares.</p><ul><li>Continental Securities Ltd received disclosures from VACHI COMMERCIAL LLP under SEBI(PIT) Regulations</li><li>Vachi Commercial LLP subscribed to 17,00,000 Convertible Warrants</li><li>10,00,000 Equity Shares of face value Rs. 2.00 each were allotted upon exercise/conversion of 10,00,000 Convertible Warrants to Equity Shares</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fea10347-df9f-4e31-96cb-3ce057a7e588.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Continental Securities Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CSL] Continental Securities Ltd Receives Disclosure from Promoter Group Vachi Commercial LLP under SEBI(PIT) Regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Continental+Securities+Ltd&title=Continental+Securities+Ltd+Receives+Disclosure+from+Promoter+Group+Vachi+Commercial+LLP+under+SEBI%28PIT%29+Regulations&newsId=2b0a0a62-752d-4309-801b-dc9bb3c0093b&token=MmIwYTBhNjItNzUy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b0a0a62-752d-4309-801b-dc9bb3c0093b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Continental Securities Ltd has received disclosures from VACHI COMMERCIAL LLP, Promoter Group of the Company under Regulation 7(2) of SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015. The disclosure includes Form C under Regulation 7(2) read with Regulation 6(2) of the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015. Vachi Commercial LLP has subscribed to 17,00,000 Convertible Warrants and was allotted 10,00,000 Equity Shares upon exercise/conversion of 10,00,000 Convertible Warrants to Equity Shares.</p><ul><li>Continental Securities Ltd received disclosures from VACHI COMMERCIAL LLP under Regulation 7(2) of SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Vachi Commercial LLP subscribed to 17,00,000 Convertible Warrants</li><li>10,00,000 Equity Shares were allotted to Vachi Commercial LLP upon exercise/conversion of Convertible Warrants to Equity Shares</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ec8f1fe5-56c5-4b36-bf1a-72d25d19c36f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Continental Securities Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SKFINDUS] SKF India to Set Up a New Plant/Unit/Factory in Pune, Maharashtra</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SKF+India+%28Industrial%29+Ltd&title=SKF+India+to+Set+Up+a+New+Plant%2FUnit%2FFactory+in+Pune%2C+Maharashtra&newsId=a925fa12-a7dd-486a-af7b-5b848a0c42cc&token=YTkyNWZhMTItYTdk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a925fa12-a7dd-486a-af7b-5b848a0c42cc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:31:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>SKF India (Industrial) Ltd. has announced the setting up of a new plant/unit/factory at Pune, Maharashtra. The new factory, to be called &apos;Factory of the Future&apos;, will host existing 12 channels and add new 8 channels, offering better efficiency than the current Pune plant. The new factory is expected to bring significant efficiency improvement potential and decrease in value-added costs.</p><ul><li>SKF India to set up a new plant/unit/factory in Pune, Maharashtra</li><li>The new factory will be called &apos;Factory of the Future&apos;</li><li>The new factory will host existing 12 channels and add new 8 channels</li><li>The new factory is expected to bring significant efficiency improvement potential</li><li>The new factory is expected to decrease value-added costs</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/15e1f34a-13a1-48c8-b35f-ea5b621b7a7a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SKF India (Industrial) Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CFEL] Confidence Futuristic Energetech Ltd to Approve Q3 Results on Feb 6, 2026; Trading Window Closed</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Confidence+Futuristic+Energetech+Ltd&title=Confidence+Futuristic+Energetech+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+Results+on+Feb+6%2C+2026%3B+Trading+Window+Closed&newsId=0d4aea13-3209-42f9-86e0-ec8787b246dc&token=MGQ0YWVhMTMtMzIw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d4aea13-3209-42f9-86e0-ec8787b246dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Confidence Futuristic Energetech Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 6, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for the Third quarter ended on 31st December 2025. The meeting is scheduled at the Company’s Corporate office. The Trading Window for dealing in the Equity Shares of the Company is closed for all the Designated Persons and their immediate relatives from January 1, 2026, for the purpose of consideration of Unaudited Financial Results of the Company for the Third Quarter/ Nine Months ended on 31st December, 2025. The Trading Window shall remain closed until 48 (Forty-Eight) hours after the declaration of aforesaid Unaudited Financial Results to the Stock Exchange.</p><ul><li>Confidence Futuristic Energetech Ltd to consider and approve Q3 results on Feb 6, 2026</li><li>Trading Window closed for Designated Persons and their immediate relatives from Jan 1, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/19937ba6-c940-456c-a552-f417f26d109f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Confidence Futuristic Energetech Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IRMENERGY] IRM Energy Ltd Announces Q3 and 9M FY2025 Financial Results, Appoints New Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IRM+Energy+Ltd&title=IRM+Energy+Ltd+Announces+Q3+and+9M+FY2025+Financial+Results%2C+Appoints+New+Independent+Director&newsId=031742f6-ee80-40ad-93dd-d607ddb4f5aa&token=MDMxNzQyZjYtZWU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">031742f6-ee80-40ad-93dd-d607ddb4f5aa</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 20:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>IRM Energy Ltd has announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s total comprehensive loss for the quarter and year to date period ended on December 31, 2025 is Rs. 8.07 million and Rs. 21.03 million respectively. The Board has also approved the appointment of Mr. Vivek Vishwas Wathodkar as an Additional Independent Director and Independent Director for a period of 5 years, subject to the approval of members of the Company. The financial results are in accordance with the provisions of Regulation 33 of the SEBI Listing Regulations, along with the Limited Review Report issued by Statutory Auditors.</p><ul><li>IRM Energy Ltd announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 and 9M FY2025.</li><li>The company reported a total comprehensive loss of Rs. 8.07 million and Rs. 21.03 million for the quarter and year to date period ended on December 31, 2025, respectively.</li><li>The Board approved the appointment of Mr. Vivek Vishwas Wathodkar as an Additional Independent Director and Independent Director for a period of 5 years.</li><li>The appointment is subject to the approval of members of the Company.</li><li>The financial results are in accordance with the provisions of Regulation 33 of the SEBI Listing Regulations, along with the Limited Review Report issued by Statutory Auditors.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e187f09c-69c3-4829-b7b6-c1e8de1b6a52.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IRM Energy Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>