<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 04:10:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[AURIONPRO] Aurionpro wins major CSB bank mandate, expands presence in India&apos;s banking sector</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AURIONPRO+SOLUTIONS+LTD.&title=Aurionpro+wins+major+CSB+bank+mandate%2C+expands+presence+in+India%27s+banking+sector&newsId=d8c23e8e-0b04-4f10-997d-f85a4f32101e&token=ZDhjMjNlOGUtMGIw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d8c23e8e-0b04-4f10-997d-f85a4f32101e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 04:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Aurionpro Solutions, a global leader in banking technology, has won a significant mandate to implement its next-generation cash management platform for CSB Bank, a leading private sector bank in India. This multi-year, multi-million-dollar engagement includes software licensing, full implementation, and an extended annual maintenance contract (AMC). The cash management solution is a key component of Aurionpro’s comprehensive, AI-native transaction banking platform, designed to transform and elevate the banking experience for the bank’s corporate customers. This win adds to Aurionpro’s recent projects with several major public sector banks and solidifies its position as a trusted partner among leading banks in India and globally, delivering scalable, future-ready corporate banking solutions.</p><ul><li>Aurionpro wins a major mandate from CSB Bank for cash management solution</li><li>Multi-year, multi-million-dollar engagement includes software licensing, full implementation, and AMC</li><li>Aurionpro’s cash management solution is a key component of its comprehensive, AI-native transaction banking platform</li><li>Win adds to Aurionpro’s recent projects with several major public sector banks</li><li>Aurionpro is a trusted partner among leading banks in India and globally, delivering scalable, future-ready corporate banking solutions</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0f001d8d-b639-49fa-8664-4d8c4fbd60bd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AURIONPRO SOLUTIONS LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SYNGENE] Syngene International Extends Long-term Research Collaboration with Bristol Myers Squibb until 2035</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Syngene+International+Ltd&title=Syngene+International+Extends+Long-term+Research+Collaboration+with+Bristol+Myers+Squibb+until+2035&newsId=49c23522-25cc-434d-b183-e07d1c15984a&token=NDljMjM1MjItMjVj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">49c23522-25cc-434d-b183-e07d1c15984a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 04:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Syngene International, a global contract research, development, and manufacturing organization (CRDMO), has announced the extension of its strategic collaboration with Bristol Myers Squibb through 2035. The expanded agreement broadens the scope of integrated services across the drug development lifecycle, including discovery, translational sciences, pharmaceutical development and manufacturing, clinical trials, data and information technology services. This collaboration marks the next phase of growth for Syngene, reinforcing its position as a strategic partner delivering integrated, end-to-end scientific and manufacturing solutions. The collaboration began in 1998 and has evolved into a major strategic R&amp;D site for Bristol Myers Squibb, contributing to discovery, preclinical development, and patent filings across therapeutic areas.</p><ul><li>Syngene International extends its long-term research collaboration with Bristol Myers Squibb until 2035</li><li>The expanded agreement broadens the scope of integrated services across the drug development lifecycle</li><li>The collaboration began in 1998 and has evolved into a major strategic R&amp;D site for Bristol Myers Squibb</li><li>The Biocon Bristol Myers Squibb Research and Development Center (BBRC) contributes to discovery, preclinical development, and patent filings across therapeutic areas</li><li>The BBRC houses around 700 Syngene scientists working as an extension of Bristol Myers Squibb’s global research organization</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/53786865-f22a-4d7f-a3a3-1e330e535563.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Syngene International Ltd | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DESCO] Desco Infratech Enters CBG Sector with Shri Green Agro Energies Acquisition</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Desco+Infratech+Ltd&title=Desco+Infratech+Enters+CBG+Sector+with+Shri+Green+Agro+Energies+Acquisition&newsId=710c0625-b191-4c8c-80d4-17c057e99b7e&token=NzEwYzA2MjUtYjE5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">710c0625-b191-4c8c-80d4-17c057e99b7e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 04:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Desco Infratech Limited (&apos;DESCO&apos;) has announced its strategic acquisition of Shri Green Agro Energies Private Limited (SGAEPL), marking its entry into the Compressed Biogas (CBG) segment. This acquisition provides DESCO with an advanced-stage CBG project, enabling accelerated market entry and significantly reducing development and execution risks. The plant benefits from secured long-term feedstock supply arrangements, established infrastructure, and key land, statutory, and regulatory approvals. This acquisition is a significant milestone in DESCO&apos;s clean energy roadmap, strengthening its sustainable energy portfolio.</p><ul><li>Desco Infratech Limited acquires Shri Green Agro Energies Private Limited, marking its entry into the Compressed Biogas (CBG) segment.</li><li>The acquisition provides DESCO with an advanced-stage CBG project, enabling accelerated market entry and significantly reducing development and execution risks.</li><li>The plant benefits from secured long-term feedstock supply arrangements, established infrastructure, and key land, statutory, and regulatory approvals.</li><li>This acquisition is a significant milestone in DESCO&apos;s clean energy roadmap, strengthening its sustainable energy portfolio.</li><li>Desco Infratech Limited is a diversified infrastructure EPC and O&amp;M company engaged in City Gas Distribution, Water Pipeline, and Power Transmission projects across India.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/58531e2e-9ee4-4835-8c63-f921a8b9943d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Desco Infratech Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IXIGO] ixigo to Announce Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025 on January 22, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Le+Travenues+Technology+Ltd&title=ixigo+to+Announce+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025+on+January+22%2C+2026&newsId=718c43bf-5fa1-47ae-a757-f6b47b6a1c61&token=NzE4YzQzYmYtNWZh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">718c43bf-5fa1-47ae-a757-f6b47b6a1c61</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 04:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Le Travenues Technology Ltd (ixigo) has announced that it will be announcing its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, on January 22, 2026. The earnings conference call will be held at 05:00 P.M. (IST) on the same day. The financial results will be available on ixigo’s website and on the websites of National Stock Exchange of India Limited and BSE Limited.</p><ul><li>ixigo to announce financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, on January 22, 2026</li><li>The earnings conference call will be held at 05:00 P.M. (IST) on January 22, 2026</li><li>Results will be available around 04:45 P.M. (IST) on January 22, 2026 at ixigo’s website https://www.ixigo.com and on the websites of National Stock Exchange of India Limited and BSE Limited at www.nseindia.com and www.bseindia.com</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/18bef978-38ef-43e1-a75f-f7a393ad68e8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Le Travenues Technology Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ACMESOLAR] ACME Solar Elevates Yogesh Sanklecha as Head of Business Development and Senior Management Personnel</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ACME+Solar+Holdings+Ltd&title=ACME+Solar+Elevates+Yogesh+Sanklecha+as+Head+of+Business+Development+and+Senior+Management+Personnel&newsId=0d649db4-27d5-457f-afe5-1c427d8479a0&token=MGQ2NDlkYjQtMjdk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d649db4-27d5-457f-afe5-1c427d8479a0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 03:34:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>ACME Solar Holdings Ltd has elevated Yogesh Kumar Sanklecha as Head of Business Development and designated him as Senior Management Personnel. He has been associated with the ACME Group for over 25 years and has played a pivotal role in shaping the organisation’s growth journey. In his new role, Yogesh is expected to be a key enabler in advancing ACME Solar’s ambitious growth charter to reach 10GW by 2030, while continuing to be responsible for end-to-end stakeholder management from bidding through to project commissioning.</p><ul><li>Yogesh Kumar Sanklecha elevated as Head of Business Development and Senior Management Personnel at ACME Solar</li><li>Sanklecha has been associated with ACME Group for over 25 years and has held several leadership positions</li><li>He has played a pivotal role in shaping ACME&apos;s growth journey and has spearheaded multiple strategic initiatives</li><li>Expected to advance ACME Solar’s ambitious growth charter to reach 10GW by 2030</li><li>Responsible for end-to-end stakeholder management from bidding through to project commissioning</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5bf593b1-9127-402d-99be-e1ae22ea707d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ACME Solar Holdings Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ACMESOLAR] ACME Solar Commissions Additional 12 MW Wind Power Project in Gujarat</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ACME+Solar+Holdings+Ltd&title=ACME+Solar+Commissions+Additional+12+MW+Wind+Power+Project+in+Gujarat&newsId=ca0f70d1-4a85-482b-b83e-3f2b0f3b722c&token=Y2EwZjcwZDEtNGE4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ca0f70d1-4a85-482b-b83e-3f2b0f3b722c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 03:28:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>ACME Solar Holdings Limited, through its subsidiary ACME Eco Clean Energy Pvt Ltd, has commissioned an additional 12 MW of a wind power project located in Surendranagar, Gujarat. This brings the project&apos;s total operational capacity to 68 MW out of the total 100 MW being commissioned in phases. The project is financed through Power Finance Corporation (PFC) and constructed using SANY&apos;s 4 MW turbines. The power generated will be sold through a 25-year Power Purchase Agreement with Gujarat Urja Vikas Nigam Limited.</p><ul><li>ACME Solar commissions additional 12 MW of wind power project in Gujarat</li><li>Total operational capacity now stands at 68 MW out of 100 MW</li><li>Financed through Power Finance Corporation (PFC)</li><li>Constructed using SANY&apos;s 4 MW turbines</li><li>Power to be sold through a 25-year PPA with Gujarat Urja Vikas Nigam Limited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0d2338f3-5e08-426f-b05f-53ca583a5a59.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ACME Solar Holdings Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VPRPL] Vishnu Prakash R Punglia Ltd Reports Robust Order Book of Approximately ₹5,000 Crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vishnu+Prakash+R+Punglia+Ltd&title=Vishnu+Prakash+R+Punglia+Ltd+Reports+Robust+Order+Book+of+Approximately+%E2%82%B95%2C000+Crore&newsId=3223170f-53b8-4b91-a7eb-2f65b247f4f1&token=MzIyMzE3MGYtNTNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3223170f-53b8-4b91-a7eb-2f65b247f4f1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 03:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Vishnu Prakash R Punglia Limited, an ISO 9001: 2015 Certified Company, has reported a robust order book of approximately ₹5,000 crore, providing strong revenue visibility. The Company has already achieved a turnover of approximately ₹570 crore in the first half of the financial year and expects to deliver improved performance in the second half. The diversified nature of the order book ensures stability and reduces dependency on any single sector. The Company is currently challenging the termination of the Jaipur—Sawai Madhopur Doubling Project in the Hon’ble High Court of Rajasthan, Jaipur.</p><ul><li>Robust order book of approximately ₹5,000 crore</li><li>Achieved a turnover of approximately ₹570 crore in the first half of the financial year</li><li>Expects improved performance in the second half</li><li>Diversified order book ensures stability and reduces dependency on any single sector</li><li>Challenging the termination of the Jaipur—Sawai Madhopur Doubling Project in the Hon’ble High Court of Rajasthan, Jaipur</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dbbf3422-cde0-4a30-b051-585b4ea995e4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vishnu Prakash R Punglia Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AXISCADES] AXISCADES secures 100 Cr Defence Radar Subsystem Contract, bolstering high-margin Embedded Systems Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Axiscades+Technologies+Ltd&title=AXISCADES+secures+100+Cr+Defence+Radar+Subsystem+Contract%2C+bolstering+high-margin+Embedded+Systems+Growth&newsId=f6534a47-c8bc-495f-884d-03651a115f54&token=ZjY1MzRhNDctYzhi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6534a47-c8bc-495f-884d-03651a115f54</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 01:04:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>AXISCADES Technologies Limited, a chip to product company and a pioneer in Aerospace, Defence, Electronics, Semiconductor and Artificial Intelligence applications, announced that its subsidiary Mistral Solutions has secured a contract worth around 100 Crores from the LLTR Ashwini programme. This programme is India’s indigenous Low-Level Transportable Radar system developed by DRDO and BEL. The contract is for the supply of Signal and Data Processing Units (SDPU), including associated spares, with deliveries over 2 years for steady revenue visibility. This win reflects Mistral’s continued commitment to supporting India’s defence indigenisation initiatives and contributing critical technologies to next-generation military systems. It also positions Mistral to capture the expanding DRDO/BEL pipeline in indigenous defence electronics.</p><ul><li>Around 100 Crores contract for state-of-the-art Signal and Data Processing Units (SDPU) and associated spares</li><li>Deliveries over 2 years for steady revenue visibility</li><li>Critical role in enhancing low-altitude surveillance against UAVs, helicopters, and fighter jets</li><li>Liquid-cooled SDPU meets extreme operational demands, showcasing proprietary expertise in embedded computing for next-gen radar platforms</li><li>Positions Mistral to capture expanding DRDO/BEL pipeline in indigenous defence electronics</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3362371a-e714-463f-8208-7f471e43928f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Axiscades Technologies Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AXISCADES] Axiscades Technologies&apos; Subsidiary Secures Supply Order from Bharat Electronics Ltd for Signal and Data Processing Units</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Axiscades+Technologies+Ltd&title=Axiscades+Technologies%27+Subsidiary+Secures+Supply+Order+from+Bharat+Electronics+Ltd+for+Signal+and+Data+Processing+Units&newsId=90940940-dd47-41e8-ada9-45589a54a5e3&token=OTA5NDA5NDAtZGQ0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90940940-dd47-41e8-ada9-45589a54a5e3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 00:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Axiscades Technologies Ltd announced that its subsidiary, Mistral Solutions Private Limited, has secured a supply order from Bharat Electronics Ltd (BEL), Ministry of Defence, for supply of Signal and Data Processing Units along with associated spares. The order is worth approximately 100 Crores INR and is to be executed over a period of two years.</p><ul><li>Axiscades Technologies&apos; subsidiary, Mistral Solutions Private Limited, has secured a supply order from Bharat Electronics Ltd (BEL), Ministry of Defence.</li><li>The order is for the supply of Signal and Data Processing Units along with associated spares.</li><li>The estimated value of the order is 100 Crores INR.</li><li>The order is to be executed over a period of two years.</li><li>Bharat Electronics Ltd (BEL) is a domestic entity.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/22447165-67df-4e75-a7c3-650971ed5855.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Axiscades Technologies Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WAKEFIT] Wakefit Innovations Ltd. Announces Amendments to Memorandum and Articles of Association</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Wakefit+Innovations+Ltd&title=Wakefit+Innovations+Ltd.+Announces+Amendments+to+Memorandum+and+Articles+of+Association&newsId=730798a8-6284-4fde-8607-f8cb78aa9113&token=NzMwNzk4YTgtNjI4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">730798a8-6284-4fde-8607-f8cb78aa9113</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 00:02:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Wakefit Innovations Ltd. has announced amendments to its Memorandum and Articles of Association. The amendments include reclassification of authorized share capital, alteration to the Capital Clause, approval for upside arrangement under the Shareholders’ Agreement, and amendment in the Articles of Association. The reclassification of authorized share capital will result in the conversion of compulsorily convertible preference shares into equity shares. The upside arrangement under the Shareholders’ Agreement has been approved, which relates to the right of promoters to receive upside sharing from investors. The Articles of Association have been amended to insert a new article relating to the right to upside arrangement. These amendments are subject to approval from shareholders as required under SEBI regulations.</p><ul><li>Reclassification of authorized share capital and alteration to the Capital Clause of the Memorandum of Association</li><li>Approval for the upside arrangement under the Shareholders’ Agreement</li><li>Amendment in the Articles of Association</li><li>Subject to approval from shareholders as required under SEBI regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/32ce02fc-4da4-4e6b-baf0-31a3d0fb4bda.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Wakefit Innovations Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>