<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:32:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[CAPPL] Caplin Steriles Gets USFDA Approval for Desmopressin Acetate Injection</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CAPLIN+POINT+LABORATORIES+LTD.&title=Caplin+Steriles+Gets+USFDA+Approval+for+Desmopressin+Acetate+Injection&newsId=05f4e399-1585-4b90-bd59-a3008ba2e782&token=MDVmNGUzOTktMTU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05f4e399-1585-4b90-bd59-a3008ba2e782</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>USFDA</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Caplin Steriles Limited, a subsidiary of Caplin Point Laboratories Limited, has received final approval from the USFDA for its Abbreviated New Drug Application (ANDA) Desmopressin Acetate Injection USP, 4 mcg/mL single-dose vials and 40 mcg/10 mL (4 mcg/mL) multiple-dose vials. This is a generic therapeutic equivalent version of the Reference Listed Drug (RLD) DDAVP (desmopressin acetate) Injection, 4 mcg/mL of Nordic Pharma Inc. The injection is used to treat conditions like haemophilia A, von Willebrand disease, and central diabetes insipidus. According to IQVIA™, the US sales for this injection were approximately $26 million for the 12-month period ending December 2025.</p><ul><li>Caplin Steriles Limited received final approval from the USFDA for Desmopressin Acetate Injection USP</li><li>The injection is a generic therapeutic equivalent version of the Reference Listed Drug (RLD) DDAVP</li><li>The injection is used to treat conditions like haemophilia A, von Willebrand disease, and central diabetes insipidus</li><li>According to IQVIA™, the US sales for this injection were approximately $26 million for the 12-month period ending December 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/112b9297-da70-4cdd-9334-17462629ad22.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CAPLIN POINT LABORATORIES LTD. | Category: USFDA</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[OVAL] Oval Projects Engineering Ltd: No Deviations from Objects in IPO Proceeds Utilization as of December 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Oval+Projects+Engineering+Ltd&title=Oval+Projects+Engineering+Ltd%3A+No+Deviations+from+Objects+in+IPO+Proceeds+Utilization+as+of+December+2025&newsId=d0b9c31e-aa19-4141-af30-104ca3e2a785&token=ZDBiOWMzMWUtYWEx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d0b9c31e-aa19-4141-af30-104ca3e2a785</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Infomerics Valuation and Rating Limited, the Monitoring Agency for Oval Projects Engineering Ltd&apos;s Initial Public Offering (IPO), has submitted a report highlighting the utilization of the issue proceeds for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The report indicates no deviations from the objects for which the funds were raised, and the range of deviation is nil.</p><ul><li>Oval Projects Engineering Ltd&apos;s IPO proceeds utilized in accordance with the objects, as of December 31, 2025</li><li>No deviations from the intended objects found in the monitoring agency report</li><li>Infomerics Valuation and Rating Limited, a SEBI registered and RBI accredited credit rating agency, is the monitoring agency for the IPO</li><li>The IPO, which raised Rs. 46.74 crores, was fully subscribed, and the company has allotted 54,99,200 Equity Shares to the applicants</li><li>Infomerics Ratings does not have any direct/indirect interest in or relationship with the issuer, promoters, directors, or management</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a09c63bc-02b9-427a-abb4-7314a5d54575.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Oval Projects Engineering Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SOUTHWEST] South West Pinnacle Exploration Ltd Secures INR 307 Crore Exploration Services Contract</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=South+West+Pinnacle+Exploration+Ltd&title=South+West+Pinnacle+Exploration+Ltd+Secures+INR+307+Crore+Exploration+Services+Contract&newsId=b29734ba-52dd-4400-99fa-ea02d4168500&token=YjI5NzM0YmEtNTJk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b29734ba-52dd-4400-99fa-ea02d4168500</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>South West Pinnacle Exploration Limited (SWPE) has signed a long-term exploration services contract with M/s Hind Metal Exploration Services Pvt Ltd., a wholly owned subsidiary of M/s Hindustan Zinc Limited. The contract, valued at approximately INR 307 Crore, is the largest ever single order bagged by the company and is expected to start generating significant additional revenue from the first quarter of FY 2026-27. The contract will be executed over a period of four years after mobilization.</p><ul><li>SWPE signed an exploration services contract with M/s Hind Metal Exploration Services Pvt Ltd., a wholly owned subsidiary of M/s Hindustan Zinc Limited.</li><li>The contract is valued at approximately INR 307 Crore.</li><li>The contract is the largest ever single order for SWPE and is expected to start generating significant additional revenue from the first quarter of FY 2026-27.</li><li>The contract will be executed over a period of four years after mobilization.</li><li>M/s Hind Metal Exploration Services Pvt Ltd. is a wholly owned subsidiary of M/s Hindustan Zinc Limited.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7471fb66-8dcc-4899-b872-d4c1eee34862.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: South West Pinnacle Exploration Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ICICIBANK] ICICI Bank to Purchase Up to 2.0% Additional Shareholding in ICICI Prudential Life Insurance</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ICICI+BANK+LTD.&title=ICICI+Bank+to+Purchase+Up+to+2.0%25+Additional+Shareholding+in+ICICI+Prudential+Life+Insurance&newsId=7197894f-986e-46ce-9a29-96dc8ec2c21c&token=NzE5Nzg5NGYtOTg2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7197894f-986e-46ce-9a29-96dc8ec2c21c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of ICICI Bank Limited approved the purchase of up to 2.0% additional shareholding in its subsidiary, ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company Limited. This purchase is primarily towards maintaining the Bank’s majority shareholding in the event of exercise of stock-based compensation of ICICI Life. The decision is subject to receipt of requisite approvals.</p><ul><li>ICICI Bank to purchase up to 2.0% additional shareholding in ICICI Prudential Life Insurance</li><li>Purchase aimed at maintaining the Bank’s majority shareholding in the subsidiary</li><li>Subject to receipt of necessary approvals</li><li>Move made in anticipation of exercise of stock-based compensation of ICICI Life</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bf4127ab-b1ff-44ec-86b0-97fe164a313f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ICICI BANK LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ICICIBANK] ICICI Bank to Purchase Up to 2.0% Additional Shareholding in ICICI Prudential Life Insurance</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ICICI+BANK+LTD.&title=ICICI+Bank+to+Purchase+Up+to+2.0%25+Additional+Shareholding+in+ICICI+Prudential+Life+Insurance&newsId=87fbd304-2378-4a96-8f6d-0d2f69ee57cc&token=ODdmYmQzMDQtMjM3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">87fbd304-2378-4a96-8f6d-0d2f69ee57cc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of ICICI Bank Limited approved the purchase of up to 2.0% additional shareholding in its subsidiary, ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company Limited. This purchase is primarily towards maintaining the Bank’s majority shareholding in the event of exercise of stock-based compensation of ICICI Life. The decision is subject to receipt of necessary approvals.</p><ul><li>ICICI Bank to purchase up to 2.0% additional shareholding in ICICI Prudential Life Insurance</li><li>Purchase aimed at maintaining the Bank’s majority shareholding</li><li>Subject to approval from relevant authorities</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/76183d68-40e9-4868-aa08-edb40d72cdb0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ICICI BANK LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VRFILMS] VR Films &amp; Studios Ltd&apos;s Independent Director&apos;s Meeting Review</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=V+R+Films+%26+Studios+Ltd&title=VR+Films+%26+Studios+Ltd%27s+Independent+Director%27s+Meeting+Review&newsId=df69aad4-1910-489a-9e3e-05d14344dc28&token=ZGY2OWFhZDQtMTkx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df69aad4-1910-489a-9e3e-05d14344dc28</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>VR Films &amp; Studios Ltd held a separate meeting of its Independent Director on February 28, 2026, to review the performance of Non-Independent Directors, the Board as a whole, the Chairperson of the Company, and assess the quality, quantity, and timeliness of information flow between the Company management and the Board. The meeting commenced at 10:30 A.M. and concluded at 11:30 A.M.</p><ul><li>Review of the performance of Non-Independent Directors and the Board as a Whole</li><li>Assessment of the Chairperson&apos;s performance</li><li>Evaluation of information flow between the Company management and the Board</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6dbba74c-b80a-4edb-9a83-5b89b7ea1841.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: V R Films & Studios Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZYDUSLIFE] Zydus Lifesciences Ltd Receives Final Approvals from USFDA for Ivermectin and Dapsone Tablets</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Zydus+Lifesciences+Ltd&title=Zydus+Lifesciences+Ltd+Receives+Final+Approvals+from+USFDA+for+Ivermectin+and+Dapsone+Tablets&newsId=795460bf-98fe-4b2b-a007-af607f717766&token=Nzk1NDYwYmYtOThm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">795460bf-98fe-4b2b-a007-af607f717766</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:02:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>USFDA</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Zydus Lifesciences Limited has received final approvals from the USFDA for Ivermectin Tablets USP, 3 mg and Dapsone Tablets USP, 25 mg and 100 mg. Ivermectin Tablets USP, 3 mg, are prescription anti-parasitic medications primarily indicated for treating parasitic worm infections in humans, specifically intestinal strongyloidiasis and onchocerciasis. Ivermectin tablets will be manufactured at the group’s formulation manufacturing facility at SEZ, Ahmedabad and distributed by Viona Pharmaceuticals Inc. Ivermectin Tablets USP, 3 mg had annual sales of USD 14.8 mn. Dapsone Tablets USP, 25 mg and 100 mg are indicated for the treatment of leprosy (all forms, including multibacillary and paucibacillary) and dermatitis herpetiformis. It acts as an anti-infective and antibacterial agent and is used to control skin lesions in dermatitis herpetiformis and for leprosy. Dapsone tablets will be manufactured at the group’s formulation manufacturing facility at SEZ-II, Ahmedabad and distributed by Viona Pharmaceuticals Inc. Dapsone Tablets USP, 25 mg and 100 mg had annual sales of USD 8.4 mn in the United States. The group now has 434 approvals and has so far filed 505 ANDAs since the commencement of the filing process in FY 2003-04.</p><ul><li>Zydus Lifesciences Ltd receives final approvals from USFDA for Ivermectin Tablets USP, 3 mg and Dapsone Tablets USP, 25 mg and 100 mg</li><li>Ivermectin Tablets USP, 3 mg are indicated for treating parasitic worm infections in humans</li><li>Dapsone Tablets USP, 25 mg and 100 mg are indicated for the treatment of leprosy and dermatitis herpetiformis</li><li>Ivermectin Tablets USP, 3 mg had annual sales of USD 14.8 mn and Dapsone Tablets USP, 25 mg and 100 mg had annual sales of USD 8.4 mn in the United States</li><li>Zydus Lifesciences Ltd now has 434 approvals and has so far filed 505 ANDAs since the commencement of the filing process in FY 2003-04</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b8eafbfa-7ecf-4903-8c8a-fb7746228678.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Zydus Lifesciences Ltd | Category: USFDA</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GANONPRO] Ganon Products Ltd Announces Resignation of Mr. Madanlal Goyal as Chairman and Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ganon+Products+Ltd&title=Ganon+Products+Ltd+Announces+Resignation+of+Mr.+Madanlal+Goyal+as+Chairman+and+Director&newsId=9a1ea0ef-5edc-41e2-bef3-5eee94b0d95e&token=OWExZWEwZWYtNWVk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a1ea0ef-5edc-41e2-bef3-5eee94b0d95e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ganon Products Ltd announced the resignation of Mr. Madanlal Goyal as Chairman and Director of the company with effect from the close of business hours on 27th February, 2026. The resignation is due to personal reasons and other professional commitments. There are no material reasons for his resignation other than those mentioned in the resignation letter. The company has filed the necessary e-forms with the Registrar of Companies and will intimate the Stock Exchanges as required under Regulation 30 of SEBI (LODR) Regulations.</p><ul><li>Mr. Madanlal Goyal has resigned from the position of Chairman and Director of Ganon Products Ltd.</li><li>The resignation is due to personal reasons and other professional commitments.</li><li>The resignation is effective from the close of business hours on 27th February, 2026.</li><li>The company has filed the necessary e-forms with the Registrar of Companies.</li><li>The company will intimate the Stock Exchanges as required under Regulation 30 of SEBI (LODR) Regulations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0249af80-299c-4023-b234-978ffedea76f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ganon Products Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GANONPRO] Ganon Products Ltd: Chairman Madanlal Goyal Resigns from Board</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ganon+Products+Ltd&title=Ganon+Products+Ltd%3A+Chairman+Madanlal+Goyal+Resigns+from+Board&newsId=7c1b08f8-d0de-4b06-9c52-8170ea16f10f&token=N2MxYjA4ZjgtZDBk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c1b08f8-d0de-4b06-9c52-8170ea16f10f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ganon Products Ltd announced the resignation of Mr. Madanlal Goyal as Chairman and Director of the Company, effective from 27th February, 2026. The decision was made during a Board Meeting held on the same day. Mr. Goyal cited personal reasons and other professional commitments as the reasons for his resignation. The Company expressed gratitude for his contributions and wished him well in his future endeavors.</p><ul><li>Mr. Madanlal Goyal has resigned from his positions as Chairman and Director of Ganon Products Ltd.</li><li>The resignation is effective from the close of business hours on 27th February, 2026.</li><li>Mr. Goyal cited personal reasons and other professional commitments as the reasons for his resignation.</li><li>The resignation was approved during a Board Meeting held on 28th February, 2026.</li><li>The Company expressed gratitude for Mr. Goyal&apos;s contributions and wished him well in his future endeavors.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8454e52c-9b3c-414d-93c6-3cfb6bf50dbe.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ganon Products Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZPRBHSTE] Prabhu Steel Industries Ltd. Boosts Loan, Investment Limits; Ups Non-Executive Director&apos;s Remuneration</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PRABHU+STEEL+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Prabhu+Steel+Industries+Ltd.+Boosts+Loan%2C+Investment+Limits%3B+Ups+Non-Executive+Director%27s+Remuneration&newsId=002d55c9-c9d5-452d-b9c6-c5d55b8791dc&token=MDAyZDU1YzktYzlk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">002d55c9-c9d5-452d-b9c6-c5d55b8791dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 06:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Prabhu Steel Industries Ltd. held a Board of Directors meeting on February 28, 2026, where they approved several key items. The Board recommended a special resolution to increase loan and investment limits under Section 186 of the Companies Act, 2013. They also approved a revision in remuneration for Mr. Harish Agrawal, a Non-Executive Non-Independent Director, to 15 Lakhs per annum, effective from the financial year 2025-26, pending shareholder approval in the Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EOGM). The EOGM is scheduled for March 24, 2026, at 9:00 A.M., at Plot No 158 Small Factory Area Bagadganj Nagpur 440008. The Board also approved the calendar of events for the EOGM, set the cut-off date for voting rights, and appointed M/S Jaymin Modi &amp; Co as the scrutinizer for the EOGM.</p><ul><li>Prabhu Steel Industries Ltd. recommends increasing loan and investment limits</li><li>Company approves remuneration revision for Non-Executive Non-Independent Director</li><li>Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EOGM) scheduled for March 24, 2026</li><li>Calendar of events for EOGM approved</li><li>M/S Jaymin Modi &amp; Co appointed as EOGM scrutinizer</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d2d4f458-34cf-4f0b-9325-b5cf43b7d11b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PRABHU STEEL INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>