<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 01:17:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[KCDGROUP] KCD Industries India Ltd: Resignation of Statutory Auditor and Secretarial Auditor</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KCD+Industries+India+Ltd&title=KCD+Industries+India+Ltd%3A+Resignation+of+Statutory+Auditor+and+Secretarial+Auditor&newsId=035e5962-0b12-48c8-8a64-90f4697ad581&token=MDM1ZTU5NjItMGIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">035e5962-0b12-48c8-8a64-90f4697ad581</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Auditor</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>KCD Industries India Ltd has informed about the resignation of its Statutory Auditor, M/s J. Singh &amp; Associates, Chartered Accountants, and Secretarial Auditor, M/s Deepak Patil &amp; Co., Practicing Company Secretary, with immediate effect. The resignation is due to the resignation of a key partner in the auditing firm and acute staff constraints. The company will take necessary steps to fill the vacancy caused due to resignation by way of appointment of new Statutory Auditors and Secretarial Auditor.</p><ul><li>Resignation of Statutory Auditor, M/s J. Singh &amp; Associates, Chartered Accountants</li><li>Resignation of Secretarial Auditor, M/s Deepak Patil &amp; Co., Practicing Company Secretary</li><li>Resignation due to resignation of a key partner and acute staff constraints</li><li>Company to appoint new Statutory Auditors and Secretarial Auditor</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/465d1ac3-c646-48d0-834e-e2e64cbe2fd5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KCD Industries India Ltd | Category: Auditor</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADANIPORTS] Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone Ltd Clarifies on Legal Summons Report</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADANI+PORTS+AND+SPECIAL+ECONOMIC+ZONE+LTD.&title=Adani+Ports+and+Special+Economic+Zone+Ltd+Clarifies+on+Legal+Summons+Report&newsId=2bdc9b70-e094-4da4-a65a-cf4cb48df347&token=MmJkYzliNzAtZTA5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2bdc9b70-e094-4da4-a65a-cf4cb48df347</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone Ltd has clarified a media report published on January 23, 2026, regarding a legal summons served to Gautam and Sagar Adani. The company confirmed that there are no allegations made against it in these proceedings and it is not a party to them. The report does not trigger any disclosure requirements under the SEBI Listing Regulations.</p><ul><li>Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone Ltd has clarified a media report regarding a legal summons served to Gautam and Sagar Adani.</li><li>The company confirmed that it is not a party to these proceedings and there are no allegations made against it.</li><li>The content of the report does not trigger any disclosure requirements under the SEBI Listing Regulations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d962d29e-4cb7-41d6-8fc4-74ffc9369626.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADANI PORTS AND SPECIAL ECONOMIC ZONE LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADANIENT] Adani Enterprises Responds to Media Reports on US Regulator&apos;s Legal Summons</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADANI+ENTERPRISES+LTD.&title=Adani+Enterprises+Responds+to+Media+Reports+on+US+Regulator%27s+Legal+Summons&newsId=54af54ce-9d64-4a69-9b9c-c8b4a81f528b&token=NTRhZjU0Y2UtOWQ2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54af54ce-9d64-4a69-9b9c-c8b4a81f528b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Adani Enterprises Ltd has issued a clarification in response to media reports published on January 23, 2026, regarding a US regulator seeking measures to serve legal summons to Gautam and Sagar Adani. The company, not being a party to these proceedings and there being no allegations made against it, stated that the content of the press report does not trigger any disclosure requirements under Regulation 30 read with Schedule III of SEBI Listing Regulations.</p><ul><li>Adani Enterprises has responded to media reports regarding a US regulator seeking legal summons for Gautam and Sagar Adani.</li><li>The company is not a party to these proceedings and there are no allegations made against it.</li><li>The content of the press report does not require any disclosure under SEBI Listing Regulations.</li><li>The clarification was provided in response to queries from the Stock Exchanges.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/aa6a6bc3-d7f6-4a01-8fe6-7db280ea5dae.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADANI ENTERPRISES LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADANITRANS] Adani Energy Solutions Ltd: No Allegations or Disclosure Requirements in US Regulator Proceedings</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Adani+Transmission+Ltd&title=Adani+Energy+Solutions+Ltd%3A+No+Allegations+or+Disclosure+Requirements+in+US+Regulator+Proceedings&newsId=ebf5f365-1954-48d6-892b-b6dd1c83f00f&token=ZWJmNWYzNjUtMTk1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ebf5f365-1954-48d6-892b-b6dd1c83f00f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Adani Energy Solutions Ltd has clarified a media report titled &apos;US regulator seeking measures to serve Gautam, Sagar Adani legal summons, Bloomberg reports&apos; published on January 23, 2026. The company stated that there are no allegations against them in these proceedings, and they are not a party to them. The content of the report does not trigger any disclosure requirements under SEBI Listing Regulations. This clarification was provided in response to a query from the Stock Exchanges regarding a news item appearing in media/publication on November 21, 2024.</p><ul><li>Adani Energy Solutions Ltd has clarified a media report titled &apos;US regulator seeking measures to serve Gautam, Sagar Adani legal summons, Bloomberg reports&apos;</li><li>The company stated that they are not a party to the proceedings and there are no allegations against them</li><li>The content of the report does not trigger any disclosure requirements under SEBI Listing Regulations</li><li>This clarification was provided in response to a query from the Stock Exchanges on November 21, 2024</li><li>Adani Energy Solutions Ltd is not involved in any legal proceedings with the US regulator</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/04b1889e-4773-4a5b-b81c-b3ac73db4443.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Adani Transmission Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ATGL] Adani Total Gas Ltd Clarifies on Media Reports of Legal Proceedings</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Adani+Total+Gas+Ltd&title=Adani+Total+Gas+Ltd+Clarifies+on+Media+Reports+of+Legal+Proceedings&newsId=2a0b3a2c-c42b-427e-908d-c05fa6d6ab68&token=MmEwYjNhMmMtYzQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a0b3a2c-c42b-427e-908d-c05fa6d6ab68</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Adani Total Gas Ltd has clarified a media report titled &apos;US regulator seeking measures to serve Gautam, Sagar Adani legal summons, Bloomberg reports&apos; published on January 23, 2026. The company stated that there are no allegations against it in these proceedings, and it is not a party to them. The report does not trigger any disclosure requirements under Regulation 30 read with Schedule III of SEBI Listing Regulations.</p><ul><li>Adani Total Gas Ltd has clarified a media report titled &apos;US regulator seeking measures to serve Gautam, Sagar Adani legal summons, Bloomberg reports&apos;</li><li>The company stated that it is not a party to these proceedings and there are no allegations against it</li><li>The report does not trigger any disclosure requirements under SEBI Listing Regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bcae4b5e-dc47-4384-b0d7-1f8ddf05e573.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Adani Total Gas Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KCDGROUP] KCD Industries India Ltd: Statutory and Secretarial Auditor Resignations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KCD+Industries+India+Ltd&title=KCD+Industries+India+Ltd%3A+Statutory+and+Secretarial+Auditor+Resignations&newsId=83d4e22c-f6d7-4a43-8859-d97ed5f7eefd&token=ODNkNGUyMmMtZjZk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">83d4e22c-f6d7-4a43-8859-d97ed5f7eefd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 00:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Auditor</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>KCD Industries India Ltd has announced the resignation of its Statutory Auditor, M/s J. Singh &amp; Associates, Chartered Accountants, and the Secretarial Auditor, M/s Deepak Patil &amp; Co., Practicing Company Secretary, with immediate effect. The Statutory Auditor cited the resignation of a key partner and acute staff constraints as the reasons for their resignation. The Secretarial Auditor resigned due to other commitments and acute staff constraints. The company will take necessary steps to fill the casual vacancies caused due to resignation by way of appointment of new Statutory Auditors and Secretarial Auditor in their upcoming meetings.</p><ul><li>Statutory Auditor M/s J. Singh &amp; Associates, Chartered Accountants, has resigned due to the resignation of a key partner and acute staff constraints.</li><li>Secretarial Auditor M/s Deepak Patil &amp; Co. has resigned due to other commitments and acute staff constraints.</li><li>The company will appoint new Statutory Auditors and Secretarial Auditor to fill the casual vacancies.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d8ed9405-e573-4bfe-8ac4-504665f24649.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KCD Industries India Ltd | Category: Auditor</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADANIGREEN] Adani Green Energy Provides Clarification on SEC Fraud Case Allegations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Adani+Green+Energy+Ltd&title=Adani+Green+Energy+Provides+Clarification+on+SEC+Fraud+Case+Allegations&newsId=be99fb0f-f8e4-4e85-90f0-da16e76f7930&token=YmU5OWZiMGYtZjhl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be99fb0f-f8e4-4e85-90f0-da16e76f7930</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:46:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Adani Green Energy Ltd has provided a clarification on a news item regarding a civil complaint brought by the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) against Mr. Gautam Adani and Mr. Sagar Adani. The company is not a party to these proceedings, and no charges have been brought against it. The SEC proceedings are civil in nature, and there are no charges of bribery or corruption against the defendants. The content of the Press Report does not trigger any disclosure requirements under Regulation 30 read with Schedule Ill of SEBI Listing Regulations and has no adverse impact on the business or operations of the company.</p><ul><li>Adani Green Energy Ltd provides clarification on a civil complaint by the SEC against its directors.</li><li>The company is not a party to the SEC proceedings and no charges have been brought against it.</li><li>The SEC proceedings are civil in nature, with no charges of bribery or corruption against the defendants.</li><li>The Press Report does not trigger any disclosure requirements under SEBI Listing Regulations.</li><li>There is no adverse impact on the business or operations of Adani Green Energy Ltd.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e5bfb845-1efc-4f56-a0e9-77dc1fa6a66b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Adani Green Energy Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADANIGREEN] Adani Green Energy Clarifies on SEC Proceedings Against Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Adani+Green+Energy+Ltd&title=Adani+Green+Energy+Clarifies+on+SEC+Proceedings+Against+Directors&newsId=5d4ed8c1-d97b-4be3-8c92-e203b6350020&token=NWQ0ZWQ4YzEtZDk3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d4ed8c1-d97b-4be3-8c92-e203b6350020</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:45:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Adani Green Energy Ltd has issued a clarification regarding a media report on the SEC seeking alternate means of service of summons and complaint upon its directors, Mr. Gautam Adani and Mr. Sagar Adani. The company is not a party to these proceedings and no charges have been brought against it. The proceedings are civil in nature and there are no charges of bribery or corruption against the defendants. The press report does not have any adverse impact on the business or operations of the company.</p><ul><li>Adani Green Energy Ltd has issued a clarification on a media report related to SEC proceedings against its directors.</li><li>The company is not a party to these proceedings and no charges have been brought against it.</li><li>The SEC proceedings are civil in nature and there are no charges of bribery or corruption against the defendants.</li><li>The press report does not have any adverse impact on the business or operations of the company.</li><li>The SEC made an application for alternate means of service of summons and complaint upon the defendants on January 21, 2026 (New York time) / January 22, 2026 (India time).</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/70053139-f451-4272-92fb-abc2bca8c561.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Adani Green Energy Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NIITMTS] NIIT USA Inc. Approves Additional Equity Investment of USD 300,000 in NIIT Brazil LTDA</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NIIT+Learning+Systems+Ltd&title=NIIT+USA+Inc.+Approves+Additional+Equity+Investment+of+USD+300%2C000+in+NIIT+Brazil+LTDA&newsId=2f702727-74da-43cf-80b5-79fd89abbf77&token=MmY3MDI3MjctNzRk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2f702727-74da-43cf-80b5-79fd89abbf77</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>NIIT USA Inc., a wholly owned subsidiary of NIIT Learning Systems Limited, has approved an additional equity investment of up to USD 300,000 in its wholly owned subsidiary, NIIT Brazil LTDA. The decision was made during a board meeting on January 23, 2026, to meet NIIT Brazil&apos;s funds requirement for growth and working capital. The existing capital of NIIT Brazil is USD 200,000 (Brazilian Real 1,093,000). The proposed equity investments are subject to applicable regulatory and customary approvals. The decision is not expected to have a material impact on the consolidated financials of the Company. NIIT Brazil will continue to remain a wholly owned subsidiary of NIIT USA and a step-down subsidiary of the Company.</p><ul><li>NIIT USA Inc. approved an additional equity investment of up to USD 300,000 in NIIT Brazil LTDA</li><li>The decision was made to meet NIIT Brazil&apos;s funds requirement for growth and working capital</li><li>NIIT Brazil&apos;s existing capital is USD 200,000 (Brazilian Real 1,093,000)</li><li>The proposed equity investments are subject to applicable regulatory and customary approvals</li><li>The decision is not expected to have a material impact on the consolidated financials of the Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6416e7cc-161c-4101-83bf-18895c85c13d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NIIT Learning Systems Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GOCOLORS] Go Fashion (India) Ltd to Approve Q3 &amp; Year-to-Date Unaudited Financial Results on Jan 29, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Go+Fashion+%28India%29+Ltd&title=Go+Fashion+%28India%29+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+%26+Year-to-Date+Unaudited+Financial+Results+on+Jan+29%2C+2026&newsId=19c21765-b438-4220-843c-aa9e7a157eab&token=MTljMjE3NjUtYjQz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19c21765-b438-4220-843c-aa9e7a157eab</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:45:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Go Fashion (India) Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 29, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and year to date ended December 31, 2025. This is in accordance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations &amp; Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Go Fashion (India) Ltd to hold a Board Meeting on January 29, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and year-to-date ended December 31, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0e265ad7-9be0-48f2-ae32-1ebabf74e3f3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Go Fashion (India) Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>