<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 18:59:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[PARKHOTELS] Apeejay Surrendra Park Hotels and Ambuja Neotia Launch The Park Unizen on EM Bypass in Kolkata</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Apeejay+Surrendra+Park+Hotels+Ltd&title=Apeejay+Surrendra+Park+Hotels+and+Ambuja+Neotia+Launch+The+Park+Unizen+on+EM+Bypass+in+Kolkata&newsId=516b10c5-2e83-4d9c-9c45-657527a64269&token=NTE2YjEwYzUtMmU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">516b10c5-2e83-4d9c-9c45-657527a64269</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Apeejay Surrendra Park Hotels and Ambuja Neotia have jointly announced the launch of The Park Unizen, a hospitality-integrated development of serviced residences on EM Bypass in Kolkata. The project comprises 69 serviced residences and is positioned alongside the upcoming THE Park Hotel. The collaboration aims to strengthen the corridor’s emergence as a mixed-use lifestyle destination. The project is designed by global architecture firm Gensler and interiors of the common area and club have been designed by Bobby Mukherrji Architects. The development also features an elevated wellness terrace with a panoramic pool and curated leisure spaces. The upcoming THE Park Hotel, also designed by Gensler, is envisioned as a vibrant destination for the city, offering curated banquet and event spaces, signature dining experiences, dynamic nightlife venues, and dedicated wellness and leisure facilities.</p><ul><li>Apeejay Surrendra Park Hotels and Ambuja Neotia collaborate to launch The Park Unizen on EM Bypass in Kolkata.</li><li>The project comprises 69 serviced residences and is designed by global architecture firm Gensler.</li><li>The development also features an elevated wellness terrace with a panoramic pool and curated leisure spaces.</li><li>The upcoming THE Park Hotel is designed by Gensler and offers curated banquet and event spaces, signature dining experiences, dynamic nightlife venues, and dedicated wellness and leisure facilities.</li><li>The collaboration aims to strengthen the corridor’s emergence as a mixed-use lifestyle destination.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/77eca387-ecfd-479e-9d64-e5090e13c1dd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Apeejay Surrendra Park Hotels Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KPEL] K.P. Energy Ltd Secures LoA for 40.8 MW Wind-Solar Hybrid Power Project in Gujarat</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=K.P.+Energy+Ltd&title=K.P.+Energy+Ltd+Secures+LoA+for+40.8+MW+Wind-Solar+Hybrid+Power+Project+in+Gujarat&newsId=6b524ad1-d40a-4152-980a-c550123a8d69&token=NmI1MjRhZDEtZDQw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6b524ad1-d40a-4152-980a-c550123a8d69</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:42:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>K.P. Energy Limited has received a Letter of Award (LoA) from Enerparc Energy Private Limited for the development of a 40.8 MW Wind-Solar Hybrid Power Project in Gujarat. The project, which comprises approximately 20.2 MW of wind capacity and 20.6 MWp of solar capacity, has been awarded on a complete turnkey basis. This includes supply, installation and commissioning of the project, development of evacuation infrastructure, facilitation of grid connectivity, and obtaining requisite statutory and regulatory approvals.</p><ul><li>K.P. Energy Limited has secured a Letter of Award (LoA) for a 40.8 MW Wind-Solar Hybrid Power Project in Gujarat.</li><li>The project comprises approximately 20.2 MW of wind capacity and 20.6 MWp of solar capacity.</li><li>The project has been awarded on a complete turnkey basis, including supply, installation, commissioning, and development of evacuation infrastructure.</li><li>This award strengthens K.P. Energy&apos;s position as an integrated renewable energy solutions provider.</li><li>The project is expected to enhance K.P. Energy&apos;s execution pipeline in the wind-solar hybrid segment.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f8c54fc5-cab4-4653-adc1-37b01a5decb4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: K.P. Energy Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SANSERA] Sansera Engineering Ltd Incorporates Wholly Owned Subsidiary Nichidai Sansera Private Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sansera+Engineering+Ltd&title=Sansera+Engineering+Ltd+Incorporates+Wholly+Owned+Subsidiary+Nichidai+Sansera+Private+Limited&newsId=261924da-7b39-4d7c-a73e-bec79c589c98&token=MjYxOTI0ZGEtN2Iz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">261924da-7b39-4d7c-a73e-bec79c589c98</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:37:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sansera Engineering Ltd has announced the incorporation of Nichidai Sansera Private Limited as a wholly owned subsidiary. The joint venture company, registered with the Registrar of Companies, Karnataka, was incorporated on February 25, 2026, following the execution of a Joint Venture Agreement between Nichidai Corporation and Sansera Engineering Limited. The infusion of funds by Nichidai Corporation and the Company into Nichidai Sansera Private Limited will be undertaken in due course, leading to the allotment of shares in the ratio of 60:40 respectively.</p><ul><li>Sansera Engineering Ltd incorporates Nichidai Sansera Private Limited as a wholly owned subsidiary</li><li>Nichidai Sansera Private Limited registered with the Registrar of Companies, Karnataka</li><li>Infusion of funds by Nichidai Corporation and Sansera Engineering Limited into Nichidai Sansera Private Limited to be undertaken</li><li>Shares to be allotted in the ratio of 60:40 following the infusion of funds</li><li>Information made available on the website of Sansera Engineering Ltd</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f9ea3eb5-a0a1-4ca0-a784-afb35bf34f7d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sansera Engineering Ltd | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RVNL] Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd Receives LOA from NMDC for Development of Township in Kirandul, Chhattisgarh</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Rail+Vikas+Nigam+Ltd&title=Rail+Vikas+Nigam+Ltd+Receives+LOA+from+NMDC+for+Development+of+Township+in+Kirandul%2C+Chhattisgarh&newsId=fa80519d-6e73-406f-8bd9-0ea65a7a5ead&token=ZmE4MDUxOWQtNmU3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa80519d-6e73-406f-8bd9-0ea65a7a5ead</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd has announced that it has received a Letter of Acceptance (LOA) from National Mineral Development Corporation (NMDC) for the development of a township in Kirandul, Chhattisgarh. The project cost is Rs. 371.69 Crore and is expected to be completed in 21 months. This is a normal course of business for the company and does not involve any related party transactions.</p><ul><li>Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd has received an LOA from NMDC for a township development project in Kirandul, Chhattisgarh.</li><li>The project cost is Rs. 371.69 Crore and is expected to be completed in 21 months.</li><li>This project is in the normal course of business for the company.</li><li>The project does not involve any related party transactions.</li><li>The announcement was made in compliance with Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e8233a45-25ce-416f-906e-99ca5814d3a5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RVNL] Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd Receives LOA from NMDC for Construction of Residential Tower in Kirandul, Chhattisgarh</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Rail+Vikas+Nigam+Ltd&title=Rail+Vikas+Nigam+Ltd+Receives+LOA+from+NMDC+for+Construction+of+Residential+Tower+in+Kirandul%2C+Chhattisgarh&newsId=cff1e603-6101-422a-8e36-712b973ddba4&token=Y2ZmMWU2MDMtNjEw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cff1e603-6101-422a-8e36-712b973ddba4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd (RVNL) has announced that it has received a Letter of Acceptance (LOA) from National Mineral Development Corporation (NMDC) for the construction of a residential tower in Kirandul, Chhattisgarh. The project cost is Rs. 284.52 Crore (Rupees Two Hundred Eighty Four Crore and Fifty Two Lakhs Only) and the time period for execution is 16 months. This project is in the normal course of business of the Company.</p><ul><li>RVNL received LOA from NMDC for the construction of a residential tower in Kirandul, Chhattisgarh.</li><li>The project cost is Rs. 284.52 Crore and the execution time is 16 months.</li><li>This project is in the normal course of business of the Company.</li><li>NMDC is a domestic entity and the order has been awarded at &apos;arm’s length&apos;</li><li>RVNL is a Government of India Enterprise</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bce2f852-06c7-4487-9739-af5c2771bb14.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SASTASUNDR] Sastasundar Healthbuddy Limited to Sell 4.68% Stake to Envision India Fund for Rs. 49,99,99,528.86</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sastasundar+Ventures+Ltd&title=Sastasundar+Healthbuddy+Limited+to+Sell+4.68%25+Stake+to+Envision+India+Fund+for+Rs.+49%2C99%2C99%2C528.86&newsId=ed83aea1-ef37-4af0-a0da-1bd44bf5d06d&token=ZWQ4M2FlYTEtZWYz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed83aea1-ef37-4af0-a0da-1bd44bf5d06d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:11:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Sastasundar Healthbuddy Limited (SHBL), a material subsidiary of Health X Platform Limited (formerly known as Sastasundar Ventures Limited), has executed a Share Purchase Agreement (SPA) with Mitsubishi Corporation (Seller) and Envision India Fund (Buyer). The Buyer will acquire 10,13,766 (Ten Lakh Thirteen Thousand Seven Hundred Sixty Six) Equity Shares, representing 4.68% of the total issued and paid-up share capital of SHBL, at a price of Rs. 493.21 per share. The total consideration for this transaction is Rs. 49,99,99,528.86, subject to the satisfaction of agreed terms and conditions. Post-acquisition, the Seller will cease to be a shareholder of SHBL.</p><ul><li>Sastasundar Healthbuddy Limited to sell 4.68% stake to Envision India Fund</li><li>Transaction value at Rs. 49,99,99,528.86</li><li>Share Purchase Agreement executed with Mitsubishi Corporation as Seller</li><li>Price per share at Rs. 493.21</li><li>Completion of acquisition will result in Seller ceasing to be a shareholder of SHBL</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/641554c3-abe4-42f8-8048-7058d1957714.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sastasundar Ventures Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDIQUBE] Indiqube Spaces Ltd Announces Resignation of Company Secretary, Compliance Officer, and General Manager — Workspace Planning</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Indiqube+Spaces+Ltd&title=Indiqube+Spaces+Ltd+Announces+Resignation+of+Company+Secretary%2C+Compliance+Officer%2C+and+General+Manager+%E2%80%94+Workspace+Planning&newsId=e28a79c7-b579-49a5-927d-79ff72b67a81&token=ZTI4YTc5YzctYjU3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e28a79c7-b579-49a5-927d-79ff72b67a81</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 17:01:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indiqube Spaces Ltd has informed the Exchange about the resignation of Mr. Pranav Ayanath Kuttiyat, the Company Secretary and Compliance Officer, and Ms. Bhavna Srivastava, the General Manager — Workspace Planning. Both have resigned to accept new opportunities that align with their long-term career goals. The resignations will take effect from the close of business hours on February 25, 2026. The company has also revised the list of authorized persons for determining the materiality of information or events for disclosure to the Stock Exchange(s).</p><ul><li>Indiqube Spaces Ltd announces the resignation of Mr. Pranav Ayanath Kuttiyat, the Company Secretary and Compliance Officer.</li><li>Ms. Bhavna Srivastava, the General Manager — Workspace Planning, also tenders her resignation.</li><li>Both resignations are to accept new opportunities that align with their long-term career goals.</li><li>The resignations will take effect from the close of business hours on February 25, 2026.</li><li>The company has revised the list of authorized persons for determining the materiality of information or events for disclosure.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5cfcd9e1-b7cf-4c4d-a0fc-0cb1201e358e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Indiqube Spaces Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RELINFRA] Reliance Infrastructure: INR 516 Crore Plus Interest Expected from Mumbai Metro One Joint Venture</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RELIANCE+INFRASTRUCTURE+LTD.&title=Reliance+Infrastructure%3A+INR+516+Crore+Plus+Interest+Expected+from+Mumbai+Metro+One+Joint+Venture&newsId=11047576-959f-4d5e-8e63-07a539cc0777&token=MTEwNDc1NzYtOTU5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11047576-959f-4d5e-8e63-07a539cc0777</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Reliance Infrastructure Ltd. has announced that the Hon’ble Bombay High Court has pronounced its judgment on the Section 34 Petition filed by Mumbai Metropolitan Region Development Authority (MMRDA) challenging the arbitral award in favour of Mumbai Metro One Private Limited (MMOPL), a joint venture between the Company and MMRDA. The judgment partially upholds the award, directing that after computation, the amount payable to MMOPL be released after a period of 8 weeks. The estimated amount to be received by MMOPL is INR 516 crore plus interest from the date of the award dated August 29, 2023. MMOPL is currently reviewing the judgment and will take further steps as legally advised.</p><ul><li>Bombay High Court pronounces judgment on Section 34 Petition</li><li>Award in favour of Mumbai Metro One Private Limited partially upheld</li><li>Estimated INR 516 crore plus interest to be received by MMOPL</li><li>MMOPL conducting a detailed review of the judgment</li><li>Further steps to be taken as legally advised</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7e91512c-f900-4f8b-a0a7-8ff074eed9f1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RELIANCE INFRASTRUCTURE LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WELCORP] Welspun Corp Ltd Incorporates Wholly Owned Subsidiary in UAE</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Welspun+Corp+Limited&title=Welspun+Corp+Ltd+Incorporates+Wholly+Owned+Subsidiary+in+UAE&newsId=decd0158-441b-4743-8cb8-3825dce9f388&token=ZGVjZDAxNTgtNDQx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">decd0158-441b-4743-8cb8-3825dce9f388</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Welspun Corp Ltd has incorporated a wholly owned subsidiary, Welspun International FZCO (WIFZCQ), in Free Trade Zone, United Arab Emirates (UAE). The subsidiary will handle global marketing for all Welspun products and carry out the business of trading of any of the products and raw materials in which the parent company and its subsidiaries transact. The company has received the Certificate of Incorporation / licence from the relevant DMCC authority.</p><ul><li>Welspun Corp Ltd has incorporated a wholly owned subsidiary, Welspun International FZCO (WIFZCQ), in Free Trade Zone, United Arab Emirates (UAE).</li><li>WIFZCQ will handle global marketing for all Welspun products and carry out the business of trading of any of the products and raw materials in which the parent company and its subsidiaries transact.</li><li>The company has received the Certificate of Incorporation / licence from the relevant DMCC authority.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/aa80159d-ed76-4dc3-8bcf-42d633b0f9ca.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Welspun Corp Limited | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KRN] KRN Heat Exchanger And Refrigeration Ltd: Significant Price Movement Market-Driven, No Pending Disclosures</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KRN+Heat+Exchanger+And+Refrigeration+Ltd&title=KRN+Heat+Exchanger+And+Refrigeration+Ltd%3A+Significant+Price+Movement+Market-Driven%2C+No+Pending+Disclosures&newsId=c0868c31-63d6-4cc1-a6f1-ad5dcc3ba05a&token=YzA4NjhjMzEtNjNk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c0868c31-63d6-4cc1-a6f1-ad5dcc3ba05a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 16:47:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>KRN Heat Exchanger And Refrigeration Ltd has clarified a significant movement in their equity share price, stating that it is purely market-driven. The company has made all necessary disclosures as per Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, and there are no pending announcements or price-sensitive information that could influence the share price or volume behavior.</p><ul><li>Significant price movement in KRN Heat Exchanger And Refrigeration Ltd&apos;s equity shares is market-driven.</li><li>The company has made all necessary disclosures as per SEBI regulations.</li><li>No pending announcements or price-sensitive information that could influence the share price or volume behavior.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f260fcc5-d063-414e-ba58-15b79499854d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KRN Heat Exchanger And Refrigeration Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>