<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:56:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[LLFICL] Leading Leasing Finance And Investment Company Ltd to Consider Various Significant Matters in Upcoming Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Leading+Leasing+Finance+And+Investment+Company+Ltd&title=Leading+Leasing+Finance+And+Investment+Company+Ltd+to+Consider+Various+Significant+Matters+in+Upcoming+Board+Meeting&newsId=414459ae-c055-412a-a860-218fa44f5a7c&token=NDE0NDU5YWUtYzA1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">414459ae-c055-412a-a860-218fa44f5a7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:55:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Leading Leasing Finance And Investment Company Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 16, 2026, to consider several important matters. The agenda includes an increase in the company&apos;s authorized share capital, amendments to loan agreements with non-promoter group, conversion of loan into equity shares, and other items with the chairperson&apos;s permission. The meeting&apos;s decisions will be made available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>The Board of Directors of Leading Leasing Finance And Investment Company Ltd will meet on February 16, 2026</li><li>The agenda includes an increase in the company&apos;s authorized share capital</li><li>Amendments to loan agreements with non-promoter group will be considered</li><li>Conversion of loan into equity shares is also on the agenda</li><li>The meeting&apos;s decisions will be made available on the company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/11b42e87-b315-4527-b21f-8d50f3c8729c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Leading Leasing Finance And Investment Company Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PMTELELIN] P.M. Telelinnks Ltd to Approve Q4 2025 Financial Results in February 2026 Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=P.M.TELELINNKS+LTD.&title=P.M.+Telelinnks+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+2025+Financial+Results+in+February+2026+Board+Meeting&newsId=4504cbb5-7012-41ba-b670-9b9db64d4025&token=NDUwNGNiYjUtNzAx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4504cbb5-7012-41ba-b670-9b9db64d4025</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:54:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>P.M. Telelinnks Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 14th February 2026 to consider and approve the unaudited Financial Results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The meeting will also take note of the Limited Review Report for the same quarter and the Certificate of Managing Director &amp; Chief Financial Officer. Other matters will also be discussed.</p><ul><li>P.M. Telelinnks Ltd to consider and approve Q4 2025 financial results</li><li>Board meeting scheduled on 14th February 2026</li><li>Limited Review Report for Q4 2025 to be taken note of</li><li>Certificate of Managing Director &amp; Chief Financial Officer for Q4 2025 to be considered</li><li>Other matters to be discussed in the meeting</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/de819fc3-5391-4754-aa60-c421111d5ca2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: P.M.TELELINNKS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SIYARAM] Siyaram Recycling Secures Order Worth Rs. 3,405,267.60 from Usha International</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Siyaram+Recycling+Industries+Ltd&title=Siyaram+Recycling+Secures+Order+Worth+Rs.+3%2C405%2C267.60+from+Usha+International&newsId=f23599be-e4aa-466a-bbc0-9879d5313e3e&token=ZjIzNTk5YmUtZTRh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f23599be-e4aa-466a-bbc0-9879d5313e3e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:53:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Siyaram Recycling Industries Ltd has secured a significant order from Usha International Limited for various products. The total order is worth Rs. 3,405,267.60. The order includes FRONT CONNECTOR BRASS-HNC, Chuck Nut, Tank connector with hole &amp; Cover w/o Nut, Tank connector with hole w/o Chuck Nut and Water Inlet / Outlet Connector. The order is to be executed within 6 months and does not fall under related party transactions.</p><ul><li>Siyaram Recycling secures order from Usha International</li><li>Order worth Rs. 3,405,267.60</li><li>Includes various products like FRONT CONNECTOR BRASS-HNC, Chuck Nut, etc.</li><li>To be executed within 6 months</li><li>Does not fall under related party transactions</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bb6a569a-5cb2-4ed5-b967-45d4cef617b0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Siyaram Recycling Industries Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[APLAB] Aplab Ltd: Release of Pledge on 25,00,000 Equity Shares by Promoter Mrs. Amrita Prabhakar Deodhar</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=APLAB+LTD.-%24&title=Aplab+Ltd%3A+Release+of+Pledge+on+25%2C00%2C000+Equity+Shares+by+Promoter+Mrs.+Amrita+Prabhakar+Deodhar&newsId=adc7571a-4c30-481b-a1e2-afd81e362832&token=YWRjNzU3MWEtNGMz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">adc7571a-4c30-481b-a1e2-afd81e362832</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Pledge</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Exchange has received a disclosure under Regulation 31(1) and 31(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011 from Aplab Ltd. The disclosure pertains to the release of pledge on 25,00,000 equity shares of Aplab Limited by Mrs. Amrita Prabhakar Deodhar. This release of encumbrance is in accordance with Regulation 31(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</p><ul><li>Mrs. Amrita Prabhakar Deodhar, a promoter and director of Aplab Ltd., has released a pledge on 25,00,000 equity shares.</li><li>This release of pledge is in accordance with Regulation 31(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</li><li>The total fully paid equity share capital of the Company is 84,97,511 shares.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1C84032A_BE1F_4DD7_9B22_E6F88C2E93F1_122121.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: APLAB LTD.-$ | Category: Pledge</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RELCHEMQ] Reliance Chemotex Industries Ltd. Approves Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended on December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RELIANCE+CHEMOTEX+INDUSTRIES+LTD.-%24&title=Reliance+Chemotex+Industries+Ltd.+Approves+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+on+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=8ea61fcb-c043-4f9e-9ab4-36e6db0fc09b&token=OGVhNjFmY2ItYzA0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ea61fcb-c043-4f9e-9ab4-36e6db0fc09b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Reliance Chemotex Industries Ltd. has approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue and net profit have been affected by various factors including changes in inventories, employee benefits expense, finance cost, depreciation and amortization expenses, power &amp; fuel, and other expenses. The company has recognized one-time liabilities of Rs 3,09,804/- in the financial result for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025 due to the implementation of new labour codes. The company does not have any subsidiary, associates, or joint ventures as of 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s primary business segment is Yarn.</p><ul><li>Unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025 approved.</li><li>Recognition of one-time liabilities of Rs 3,09,804/- due to the implementation of new labour codes.</li><li>The company&apos;s primary business segment is Yarn.</li><li>No subsidiary, associates, or joint ventures as of 31st December 2025.</li><li>The financial results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/60a43fab-fabf-4b33-8ca6-946effe6515a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RELIANCE CHEMOTEX INDUSTRIES LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ACTIVE] Active Clothing Co Ltd. Issues Corrigendum for Extraordinary General Meeting on 26.02.2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Active+Clothing+Co+Ltd&title=Active+Clothing+Co+Ltd.+Issues+Corrigendum+for+Extraordinary+General+Meeting+on+26.02.2026&newsId=c3ce2362-3877-4ceb-8247-5b2b643d449e&token=YzNjZTIzNjItMzg3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c3ce2362-3877-4ceb-8247-5b2b643d449e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:47:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Active Clothing Co Ltd. has issued a corrigendum to the notice of the Extraordinary General Meeting (EGM) scheduled for 26th February 2026. The corrigendum includes amendments and clarifications related to the preferential issue of convertible warrants. The Company had filed an application with BSE Limited for in-principle approval and has been directed to rectify and provide additional details. The corrigendum notifies these changes and provides updated information about the status of allottees and the percentage of post-preferential issue capital that may be held by the allottees.</p><ul><li>Active Clothing Co Ltd. issues corrigendum for EGM on 26.02.2026</li><li>Amendments and clarifications related to preferential issue of convertible warrants</li><li>Company directed by BSE to rectify and provide additional details</li><li>Updated information about the status of allottees</li><li>Details about the percentage of post-preferential issue capital held by allottees</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/19cccd98-5087-4aab-adec-f146d26bd5d9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Active Clothing Co Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SIYARAM] Siyaram Recycling Secures Rs. 1,88,53,332 Order from Charbhuja Impex</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Siyaram+Recycling+Industries+Ltd&title=Siyaram+Recycling+Secures+Rs.+1%2C88%2C53%2C332+Order+from+Charbhuja+Impex&newsId=e6f1ce99-477e-4301-b7d3-5b760cbcf4cd&token=ZTZmMWNlOTktNDc3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e6f1ce99-477e-4301-b7d3-5b760cbcf4cd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:44:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Siyaram Recycling Industries Ltd has secured a significant order from Charbhuja Impex for Brass Scrap Honey as per ISRI. The total worth of the order is Rs. 1,88,53,332.00. The order is a domestic fixed cost contract to be executed within 6 months.</p><ul><li>Order from Charbhuja Impex worth Rs. 1,88,53,332</li><li>Domestic fixed cost contract</li><li>Execution time period: Within 6 months</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0df0d48f-bc87-44e1-a4dc-116284bb6de4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Siyaram Recycling Industries Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BIRLACOT] Birla Cotsyn (India) Ltd to Approve Un-audited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Birla+Cotsyn+%28India%29+Ltd&title=Birla+Cotsyn+%28India%29+Ltd+to+Approve+Un-audited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=b735f4eb-6814-40bb-88b5-8f92c5ea21a5&token=YjczNWY0ZWItNjgx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b735f4eb-6814-40bb-88b5-8f92c5ea21a5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Birla Cotsyn (India) Ltd has scheduled a Board of Directors meeting on February 14, 2026, to consider and approve the Un-audited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will also approve the Limited Review Reports. The trading window for dealing in the equity shares of the company will be closed for all designated persons and their immediate relatives from January 01, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of the Un-audited Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Birla Cotsyn (India) Ltd to approve Un-audited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the equity shares of the company to be closed for all designated persons and their immediate relatives from January 01, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of Un-audited Financial Results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2da81acb-4b56-48f4-8e04-1a0547ac684e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Birla Cotsyn (India) Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GORANIN] Gorani Industries Clarifies Price Movement Unrelated to Company Disclosures</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GORANI+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Gorani+Industries+Clarifies+Price+Movement+Unrelated+to+Company+Disclosures&newsId=f05838fd-da81-482a-b0da-ee1a5c3c6d29&token=ZjA1ODM4ZmQtZGE4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f05838fd-da81-482a-b0da-ee1a5c3c6d29</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gorani Industries Limited has submitted a clarification regarding the movement in the price of their security. The company stated that all necessary disclosures have been made in accordance with Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, and there is no pending price sensitive information. The movement in the share price is attributed to market conditions.</p><ul><li>Gorani Industries has clarified the price movement of their security.</li><li>The company has made all necessary disclosures as per Regulation 30 of SEBI regulations.</li><li>No price sensitive information is pending from the company.</li><li>The movement in the share price is due to market conditions.</li><li>The clarification is submitted in response to a BSE e-mail dated February 10, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0880d04f-d6a4-44b8-819c-f2a8346ca656.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GORANI INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RGL] Renaissance Global Ltd Appoints Merlin Capital Advisors as Investor Relations Agency</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Renaissance+Global+Ltd&title=Renaissance+Global+Ltd+Appoints+Merlin+Capital+Advisors+as+Investor+Relations+Agency&newsId=2b045209-b4e9-44d7-8fa9-e2539d82dc17&token=MmIwNDUyMDktYjRl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b045209-b4e9-44d7-8fa9-e2539d82dc17</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:39:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Renaissance Global Ltd has appointed Merlin Capital Advisors as its Investor Relations Agency to provide Investor and Public Relations Advisory Services. This appointment is aimed at strengthening investor communication, enhancing transparency, and improving the Company’s visibility in the capital markets. The necessary disclosure in terms of Para A of Part A of Schedule III of Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015 has been made.</p><ul><li>Renaissance Global Ltd has appointed Merlin Capital Advisors as its Investor Relations Agency.</li><li>The purpose of the agreement is to provide Investor and Public Relations Advisory Services.</li><li>The appointment is aimed at strengthening investor communication, enhancing transparency, and improving the Company’s visibility in the capital markets.</li><li>The necessary disclosure has been made in accordance with SEBI regulations.</li><li>Merlin Capital Advisors has been designated a special email ID for all investor-related queries, concerns, or requests.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f66d6210-9a83-4860-832a-816fe03254a9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Renaissance Global Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>