<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 21:18:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ORCHASP] Orchasp Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Orchasp+Ltd&title=Orchasp+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=e23e683f-8364-4455-abe9-4626b7c3e90e&token=ZTIzZTY4M2YtODM2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e23e683f-8364-4455-abe9-4626b7c3e90e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 17:41:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Orchasp Ltd, with the BSE Scrip Code 532271 and NSE Symbol ORCHASP, has announced a board meeting scheduled for 10/02/2026. The meeting aims to consider and approve the unaudited financial results (consolidated and standalone) for the quarter and nine months ended 31** December 2025, along with the limited review report issued by M/s JMT &amp; Associates. The meeting will also approve/ratify related party transactions and consider any other matter with the permission of the board.</p><ul><li>Orchasp Ltd scheduled a board meeting for 10/02/2026 to approve Q3 and nine months financial results for 2025.</li><li>The company will consider and approve unaudited financial results (consolidated and standalone) for the quarter and nine months ended 31** December 2025.</li><li>The limited review report for the aforementioned period is issued by M/s JMT &amp; Associates.</li><li>Orchasp Ltd will approve/ratify related party transactions during the meeting.</li><li>The board will consider any other matter with the required permissions.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/643ca147-de35-44e3-8198-910760308571.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Orchasp Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INFY*] Infosys Faces USD 11,041.03 Penalty from California&apos;s State Unemployment Department</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INFOSYS+LTD.&title=Infosys+Faces+USD+11%2C041.03+Penalty+from+California%27s+State+Unemployment+Department&newsId=2cc88b2a-9d06-413f-ae24-7bc4f480c721&token=MmNjODhiMmEtOWQw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2cc88b2a-9d06-413f-ae24-7bc4f480c721</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 17:41:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Infosys Ltd. has received communication regarding the collection of a penalty from the State Unemployment Department, California. The penalty, amounting to USD 11,041.03, was levied due to late payment of State Unemployment Insurance for Q4FY25. The company confirmed that there is no material impact on its financials, operations, or other activities due to this penalty.</p><ul><li>Infosys has been penalized by the State Unemployment Department, California for late payment of State Unemployment Insurance for Q4FY25.</li><li>The total penalty amount is USD 11,041.03.</li><li>The company confirmed that there is no material impact on its financials, operations, or other activities due to this penalty.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2b4ba835-799b-49e5-8053-5a186d754c7b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INFOSYS LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GOKEX] Gokaldas Exports Q3FY26 Total Income Holds Steady Despite US Tariff Impact</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GOKALDAS+EXPORTS+LTD.&title=Gokaldas+Exports+Q3FY26+Total+Income+Holds+Steady+Despite+US+Tariff+Impact&newsId=5e18fcd3-aa09-4227-899d-87b6e05b6418&token=NWUxOGZjZDMtYWEw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5e18fcd3-aa09-4227-899d-87b6e05b6418</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 17:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Gokaldas Exports registered a total income of Rs. 998 crores in Q3FY26, holding steady YoY. The India operation maintained its growth momentum of 8% YoY, while the African business improved sequentially. The company reported an EBIDTA of Rs. 96 crores with margins at 9.7% in Q3FY26. Despite the US tariff impact, productivity gains, strong order book, and better cost management helped in absorbing the impact.</p><ul><li>Gokaldas Exports registered a total income of Rs. 998 crores in Q3FY26, holding steady YoY.</li><li>India operation delivered a growth of 8% YoY, while apparel export from India remained flat.</li><li>AGOA uncertainty and supply chain delays impacted Africa business, but improved sequentially.</li><li>The company reported an EBIDTA of Rs. 96 crores with margins at 9.7% in Q3FY26.</li><li>Productivity gains, strong order book, and better cost management helped in absorbing the US tariff impact.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b81746c6-336a-401e-9f32-1eaa6a6ce2b6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GOKALDAS EXPORTS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NTPC] NTPC Ltd Transfers Coal Mines to NTPC Mining Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NTPC+LTD.&title=NTPC+Ltd+Transfers+Coal+Mines+to+NTPC+Mining+Limited&newsId=7a43f003-d629-47af-89e2-ede43c693829&token=N2E0M2YwMDMtZDYy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7a43f003-d629-47af-89e2-ede43c693829</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 17:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In a recent development, NTPC Ltd has transferred the coal mining business of two of its mines to its wholly owned subsidiary, NTPC Mining Limited (NML). The Dulanga Coal Mine located in Distt. Sundergarh, Odisha and the Talaipalli Coal Mine in Distt. Raigarh, Chhattisgarh have been transferred to NML with effect from 31st January 2026. This move is a part of the phased transfer of coal mining business from NTPC to NML.</p><ul><li>NTPC Ltd transfers coal mining business of Dulanga Coal Mine, Odisha and Talaipalli Coal Mine, Chhattisgarh to NTPC Mining Limited.</li><li>The transfer is effective from 31st January 2026.</li><li>This transfer is a part of the phased transfer of coal mining business from NTPC to NTPC Mining Limited.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/440a46f8-dfa8-4542-9d6e-f049913c3c9b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NTPC LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[OLPCL] Olympic Cards Ltd Defaults on Loan Repayment to HDFC Bank</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=OLYMPIC+CARDS+LTD.&title=Olympic+Cards+Ltd+Defaults+on+Loan+Repayment+to+HDFC+Bank&newsId=12e93316-7d6a-4099-a5e1-b8a96bf49c51&token=MTJlOTMzMTYtN2Q2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12e93316-7d6a-4099-a5e1-b8a96bf49c51</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 17:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Olympic Cards Ltd, script code 534190, has disclosed a default on a loan from HDFC Bank Ltd. The default occurred on 31st December 2025, with a current default amount of Rs. 0.1517 Cr (Rs.15,17,273/-). The total outstanding borrowings from banks/financial institutions are Rs. 9.28 Cr, and the total financial indebtedness of the company, including short-term and long-term debt, is Rs. 12.23 Cr as of 30th September 2025.</p><ul><li>Olympic Cards Ltd has defaulted on a loan from HDFC Bank Ltd.</li><li>The default occurred on 31st December 2025 with a current default amount of Rs. 0.1517 Cr.</li><li>The total outstanding borrowings from banks/financial institutions are Rs. 9.28 Cr.</li><li>The total financial indebtedness of the company is Rs. 12.23 Cr as of 30th September 2025.</li><li>The loan was a secured facility with an interest rate of 11.05% and a tenure of 120 months.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b6740140-445f-40f9-83e3-70ae34226793.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: OLYMPIC CARDS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SRMENERGY] SRM Energy Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results on Feb 07, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SRM+ENERGY+LTD.&title=SRM+Energy+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+on+Feb+07%2C+2026&newsId=ca78c74d-8dd6-44fd-affb-ca1914dde8a0&token=Y2E3OGM3NGQtOGRk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ca78c74d-8dd6-44fd-affb-ca1914dde8a0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 17:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SRM Energy Ltd has informed the BSE that the Board of Directors will meet on February 07, 2026, to consider and approve the draft Un-Audited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The meeting will be conducted through video conferencing and will also cover other matters deemed fit by the Board. The trading window for dealing in securities of the company has been closed from January 01, 2026, and will remain closed till February 09, 2026, in accordance with the Code of Conduct under the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>SRM Energy Ltd to consider and approve draft Un-Audited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended on December 31, 2025</li><li>Meeting scheduled on February 07, 2026, through video conferencing</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities closed from January 01, 2026, to February 09, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/330bc832-7f50-465f-9b5d-415018aa084b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SRM ENERGY LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SIRCA] Sirca Paints India Ltd Confirms No Deviation in Utilization of Preferential Issue Proceeds as of Q4 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sirca+Paints+India+Ltd&title=Sirca+Paints+India+Ltd+Confirms+No+Deviation+in+Utilization+of+Preferential+Issue+Proceeds+as+of+Q4+2025&newsId=ee9c10dd-2080-4e62-9559-85005789dfaf&token=ZWU5YzEwZGQtMjA4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee9c10dd-2080-4e62-9559-85005789dfaf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 17:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sirca Paints India Ltd has released a statement confirming that there is no deviation or variation in the use of proceeds raised through Preferential Issue from the objects stated in the Letter of Offer. The confirmation is for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company has raised 75,29,28000 Rs. through the Preferential Issue. The objects for which the funds have been raised include New Capex for Sirca Welcome and Wembley Manufacturing Facilities, Extension of Distribution Channel and Brand Promotion, Working Capital, and General Corporate Purpose.</p><ul><li>Sirca Paints India Ltd confirms no deviation in utilization of Preferential Issue proceeds</li><li>Raised 75,29,28000 Rs. through Preferential Issue</li><li>Funds utilized for New Capex, Extension of Distribution Channel, Working Capital, and General Corporate Purpose</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b1cc659d-c2cc-4f15-acaf-7bb6524eafd5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sirca Paints India Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DITCO] Decorous Investment &amp; Trading Co Ltd to Approve Q3 Financial Results on Feb 9, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Decorous+Investment+%26+Trading+Co+Ltd&title=Decorous+Investment+%26+Trading+Co+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+Financial+Results+on+Feb+9%2C+2026&newsId=90dcdad0-aba9-429c-a05a-8555efccdf7d&token=OTBkY2RhZDAtYWJh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90dcdad0-aba9-429c-a05a-8555efccdf7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 17:11:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Decorous Investment &amp; Trading Co Ltd has announced a Board of Directors meeting on February 9, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited quarterly and nine months financial results for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025. The trading window for all insiders will be closed from January 1, 2026, to February 15, 2026. The meeting will also discuss any other matter with the permission of the Chair.</p><ul><li>Decorous Investment &amp; Trading Co Ltd to approve Q3 financial results on Feb 9, 2026</li><li>Trading window for insiders to be closed from Jan 1, 2026, to Feb 15, 2026</li><li>Meeting to discuss any other matter with the permission of the Chair</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cfd21a9c-d78d-4de1-a30b-99b9de0d9dd2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Decorous Investment & Trading Co Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GPIL] Godawari Power and Ispat Ltd Receives Environmental Clearance for Ari Dongri Iron Ore Mines Expansion</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GODAWARI+POWER+%26+ISPAT+LTD.&title=Godawari+Power+and+Ispat+Ltd+Receives+Environmental+Clearance+for+Ari+Dongri+Iron+Ore+Mines+Expansion&newsId=9c980683-f042-4559-8185-9533811110e1&token=OWM5ODA2ODMtZjA0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c980683-f042-4559-8185-9533811110e1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Godawari Power and Ispat Ltd has received the Environmental Clearance from the Ministry of Environment, Forest and Climate Change for the expansion of Ari Dongri Iron Ore Mines. The expansion is from the existing capacity of 2.35 MTPA to 6 MTPA, with an increase in mining lease area from 138.96 Ha to 213.01 Ha. This clearance was received on 31.01.2026, in continuation to the company&apos;s earlier intimation dated 10.10.2025, 13.11.2025 and 07.01.2026.</p><ul><li>Godawari Power and Ispat Ltd has received Environmental Clearance for the expansion of Ari Dongri Iron Ore Mines.</li><li>The expansion is from the existing capacity of 2.35 MTPA to 6 MTPA.</li><li>The mining lease area will increase from 138.96 Ha to 213.01 Ha.</li><li>The clearance was received on 31.01.2026.</li><li>This is in line with the company&apos;s earlier intimation dated 10.10.2025, 13.11.2025 and 07.01.2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1bdb5406-a9ef-404c-8561-b7bb3a56be1a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GODAWARI POWER & ISPAT LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SERIND] SER Industries Ltd Company Secretary Mr. Ronak Jain Resigns Effective Jan 31, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SER+Industries+Ltd&title=SER+Industries+Ltd+Company+Secretary+Mr.+Ronak+Jain+Resigns+Effective+Jan+31%2C+2026&newsId=463632fa-f2b2-4457-b9f3-a6bd322e71ed&token=NDYzNjMyZmEtZjJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">463632fa-f2b2-4457-b9f3-a6bd322e71ed</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Auditor</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SER Industries Ltd has announced the resignation of its Company Secretary, Mr. Ronak Jain, who has tendered his resignation to pursue an alternate career opportunity outside the Organization. Mr. Jain will be relieved from his responsibilities with effect from close of business hours on 31st January 2026. The company is in the process of identifying/hiring a suitable candidate for the said position.</p><ul><li>Mr. Ronak Jain resigns from the position of Company Secretary at SER Industries Ltd.</li><li>Resignation is to pursue an alternate career opportunity outside the Organization.</li><li>Mr. Jain will be relieved from his responsibilities on 31st January 2026.</li><li>The company is in the process of identifying/hiring a new Company Secretary.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e5c7f19f-8ad8-4237-befc-7f4370d8df44.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SER Industries Ltd | Category: Auditor</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>