<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:41:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ALLSEC] Alldigi Tech Ltd May Declare Interim Dividend for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ALLSEC+TECHNOLOGIES+LTD.&title=Alldigi+Tech+Ltd+May+Declare+Interim+Dividend+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=6d5df0c2-377c-4817-a14a-68fd5d2c5edb&token=NmQ1ZGYwYzItMzc3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d5df0c2-377c-4817-a14a-68fd5d2c5edb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Alldigi Tech Ltd has informed the BSE that their Board of Directors will meet on 27/01/2026 to consider the declaration of interim dividend, if any, for the financial year 2025-26. This announcement comes in addition to the previously scheduled meeting to consider the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results of the Company for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. This disclosure is in accordance with Regulation 29(1) of Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The information is also available on the Company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Alldigi Tech Ltd&apos;s Board of Directors to meet on 27/01/2026</li><li>Board to consider declaration of interim dividend for FY 2025-26</li><li>Meeting also to consider unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Disclosure is in accordance with Regulation 29(1) of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Information available on the Company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/417c38ff-d8f3-46f9-a7ae-71c2d2a0362e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ALLSEC TECHNOLOGIES LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KEI] KEI Industries Declares Interim Dividend of Rs. 4.50 and Approves Voluntary Delisting from Calcutta Stock Exchange</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KEI+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=KEI+Industries+Declares+Interim+Dividend+of+Rs.+4.50+and+Approves+Voluntary+Delisting+from+Calcutta+Stock+Exchange&newsId=71165683-42bc-480c-8dd8-72d8a40b1a4f&token=NzExNjU2ODMtNDJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71165683-42bc-480c-8dd8-72d8a40b1a4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>KEI Industries Ltd. has declared an interim dividend of Rs. 4.50 per equity share and approved the voluntary delisting of its equity shares from The Calcutta Stock Exchange Limited (CSE). The company&apos;s standalone and consolidated un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025 have been approved. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at Rs. 29,547.04 crore for the quarter and Rs. 97,358.77 crore for the nine months ended 31st December 2025. The board also approved the reconstitution of the Risk Management Committee.</p><ul><li>Declaration of interim dividend of Rs. 4.50 per equity share</li><li>Approval of voluntary delisting from Calcutta Stock Exchange</li><li>Approval of standalone and consolidated un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025</li><li>Revenue from operations stands at Rs. 29,547.04 crore for the quarter and Rs. 97,358.77 crore for the nine months ended 31st December 2025</li><li>Reconstitution of the Risk Management Committee</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/80da1f88-8a68-47b8-b9a8-e58a4f90f176.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KEI INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RICHUNV] Rich Universe Network Ltd to Approve Q4 2025 Unaudited Financial Results on Jan 30, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RICH+UNIVERSE+NETWORK+LTD.&title=Rich+Universe+Network+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+2025+Unaudited+Financial+Results+on+Jan+30%2C+2026&newsId=143e9309-e70b-4cf9-be0e-6c20821a9876&token=MTQzZTkzMDktZTcw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">143e9309-e70b-4cf9-be0e-6c20821a9876</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rich Universe Network Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 30, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025. The meeting will be held at the company&apos;s registered office in Kanpur. In compliance with the SEBI regulations, the trading window for dealing in the securities of the company for all designated persons, including insiders, is closed from January 1, 2026, and will reopen 48 hours after the results are published.</p><ul><li>Rich Universe Network Ltd to approve Q4 2025 unaudited financial results on Jan 30, 2026</li><li>Meeting scheduled at the company&apos;s registered office in Kanpur</li><li>Trading window for designated persons closed from Jan 1, 2026, as per SEBI regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b908ef14-faaf-4a14-88fe-b76f1a6d042e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RICH UNIVERSE NETWORK LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KEI] KEI Industries Ltd. Declares Interim Dividend of Rs. 4.50, Approves Voluntary Delisting from Calcutta Stock Exchange</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KEI+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=KEI+Industries+Ltd.+Declares+Interim+Dividend+of+Rs.+4.50%2C+Approves+Voluntary+Delisting+from+Calcutta+Stock+Exchange&newsId=5cf4f0bb-8771-4873-9fd4-1fb4bb962836&token=NWNmNGYwYmItODc3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5cf4f0bb-8771-4873-9fd4-1fb4bb962836</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:33:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>KEI Industries Ltd. has approved an interim dividend of Rs. 4.50 per equity share and the voluntary delisting of its equity shares from The Calcutta Stock Exchange Limited. The decision was made at the board meeting held on January 21, 2026. The company also reported its standalone and consolidated un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025.</p><ul><li>KEI Industries Ltd. declares an interim dividend of Rs. 4.50 per equity share.</li><li>The company approves the voluntary delisting of its equity shares from The Calcutta Stock Exchange Limited.</li><li>The board approves the standalone and consolidated un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/681a70a4-3ac1-4be1-a836-d98302619d51.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KEI INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHILGRAVQ] Shilp Gravures Ltd. Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025, Reports Profit Before Tax of Rs. 12.69 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHILP+GRAVURES+LTD.-%24&title=Shilp+Gravures+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Reports+Profit+Before+Tax+of+Rs.+12.69+Crores&newsId=c34a62bd-8c67-4560-91ea-5587dd8e1df6&token=YzM0YTYyYmQtOGM2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c34a62bd-8c67-4560-91ea-5587dd8e1df6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:33:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shilp Gravures Ltd. has announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December 2025. The company reported a profit before tax of Rs. 12.69 Crores for the nine months period. The results were approved in a Board Meeting on 21st January 2026. The company operates in three segments: manufacture of Gravure rollers, power generation, and others. The financial results are available on the company&apos;s website and the stock exchange websites.</p><ul><li>Profit before tax of Rs. 12.69 Crores for the nine months ended on 31st December 2025</li><li>Financial results approved in a Board Meeting on 21st January 2026</li><li>Three operating segments: manufacture of Gravure rollers, power generation, and others</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/44b07e04-ae61-4140-8c09-eeebb5b00a9a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHILP GRAVURES LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SERA] Sera Investments &amp; Finance India Ltd Announces Q3 2025 Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sera+Investments+%26+Finance+India+Ltd&title=Sera+Investments+%26+Finance+India+Ltd+Announces+Q3+2025+Financial+Results&newsId=53d40173-6ab7-48b6-8c4f-7d5061824aab&token=NTNkNDAxNzMtNmFi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53d40173-6ab7-48b6-8c4f-7d5061824aab</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sera Investments &amp; Finance India Ltd has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations (net of taxes) stands at 252,191 Lakhs, with a net profit after tax from business operations of 200,313 Lakhs. The company is registered as a Non-Banking Financial Company (NBFC) and has recorded the unrealized profit of its investment in Sri Adhikari Brothers Television Network Ltd as OCI adjustments.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations (net of taxes) for Q3 2025 is 252,191 Lakhs</li><li>Net profit after tax from business operations for Q3 2025 is 200,313 Lakhs</li><li>Company is registered as a Non-Banking Financial Company (NBFC)</li><li>Unrealized profit of the investment in Sri Adhikari Brothers Television Network Ltd has been recorded as OCI adjustments</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5de4be55-5428-4b36-b473-8d65a738aba3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sera Investments & Finance India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DCMSHRIRAM] DCM Shriram Ltd. Delivers Resilient Q3 Performance with 13% Revenue Increase, Driven by Chemicals Expansion and Agri Businesses</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DCM+Shriram+Limited&title=DCM+Shriram+Ltd.+Delivers+Resilient+Q3+Performance+with+13%25+Revenue+Increase%2C+Driven+by+Chemicals+Expansion+and+Agri+Businesses&newsId=779ac736-135b-4128-89b5-9ce9ad7e38d6&token=Nzc5YWM3MzYtMTM1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">779ac736-135b-4128-89b5-9ce9ad7e38d6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:32:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>DCM Shriram Ltd. announced financial results for the quarter ending December 31, 2025 (Q3 FY26), demonstrating business resilience and delivering long-term value to stakeholders. The company witnessed revenue increase across all major business lines, including Chemicals, Sugar and Ethanol, Fenesta Building Systems, and Shriram Farm Solutions. Net revenues stood at Rs 3,811 crore with PBDIT at Rs 560 crore and PAT of Rs 213 crore. Despite an exceptional charge of Rs 55 crore under new labour codes, the company announced a dividend of Rs 56.14 crores during this quarter.</p><ul><li>Consolidated net revenue rose 13% to Rs 3,811 crore for Q3 FY26</li><li>Healthy performance in Sugar &amp; Ethanol, with higher sugar prices and better volumes</li><li>Volume-led growth in Chemicals, with newer projects contributing significantly</li><li>Shriram Farm Solutions reported 7% revenue growth to X756 crore</li><li>DCM Shriram Limited committed to pursuing growth and investing in scaling up core operations and adjacent businesses</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8dff848c-7ecf-4850-906f-d60d225efc32.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DCM Shriram Limited | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ROLEXRINGS] Rolex Rings Ltd Receives No Objection Letter for Promoter Reclassification</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Rolex+Rings+Ltd&title=Rolex+Rings+Ltd+Receives+No+Objection+Letter+for+Promoter+Reclassification&newsId=1dcd19bc-1ae9-4fe2-8f2a-da9e96ccceaf&token=MWRjZDE5YmMtMWFl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1dcd19bc-1ae9-4fe2-8f2a-da9e96ccceaf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rolex Rings Ltd has received a No Objection Letter from BSE and NSE for the reclassification of Mr. Hemal Paresh Madeka and Mr. Sanjay Bhagwanji Bole from ‘Promoter/Promoter Group’ category to ‘Public’ category. The reclassification applies to 30,90,000 shares held by the outgoing promoter group shareholders, reducing their shareholding to 1.13%. The approval letter from the stock exchanges is available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Rolex Rings Ltd receives No Objection Letter from BSE and NSE for promoter reclassification</li><li>Mr. Hemal Paresh Madeka and Mr. Sanjay Bhagwanji Bole reclassified from ‘Promoter/Promoter Group’ to ‘Public’ category</li><li>30,90,000 shares held by the outgoing promoter group shareholders reclassified</li><li>Shareholding of Mr. Hemal Paresh Madeka and Mr. Sanjay Bhagwanji Bole reduced to 1.13%</li><li>Approval letter available on the company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/64391492-20a4-49e8-9ceb-206ee75262e6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Rolex Rings Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TRAVELS] Travels &amp; Rentals Ltd Approves Rights Issue of Equity Shares Aggregating to ₹ 16,80,40,275</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Travels+%26+Rentals+Ltd&title=Travels+%26+Rentals+Ltd+Approves+Rights+Issue+of+Equity+Shares+Aggregating+to+%E2%82%B9+16%2C80%2C40%2C275&newsId=124785e4-cf6f-4174-9b5a-9d7acabb3feb&token=MTI0Nzg1ZTQtY2Y2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">124785e4-cf6f-4174-9b5a-9d7acabb3feb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Travels &amp; Rentals Ltd has approved the issue of equity shares on a rights basis to eligible shareholders. The rights issue is for an amount aggregating up to ¥1,700/- Lakhs, or approximately ₹ 16,80,40,275. The record date for determining the shareholders eligible to apply for the equity shares is January 28, 2026. The issue opening date is February 5, 2026, and the issue closing date is March 6, 2026. The rights entitlement ratio is 1:1, and the rights issue price is ₹ 15 per fully paid-up rights equity share. The company will have the right to extend the issue period.</p><ul><li>Travels &amp; Rentals Ltd approves rights issue of equity shares worth ₹ 16,80,40,275</li><li>Rights issue price set at ₹ 15 per fully paid-up rights equity share</li><li>Record date set as January 28, 2026, for determining eligible shareholders</li><li>Issue opening date is February 5, 2026, and issue closing date is March 6, 2026</li><li>Company reserves the right to extend the issue period</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2910210e-0593-48b4-9ca8-626e044e3d5a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Travels & Rentals Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FISCHER] Fischer Medical Ventures Transfers Shares in Foreign Subsidiary for Administrative Efficiency</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=FISCHER+CHEMIC+LTD.&title=Fischer+Medical+Ventures+Transfers+Shares+in+Foreign+Subsidiary+for+Administrative+Efficiency&newsId=8e7c14fa-2c6a-40c6-9ec7-84243d5a2602&token=OGU3YzE0ZmEtMmM2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8e7c14fa-2c6a-40c6-9ec7-84243d5a2602</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 12:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Fischer Medical Ventures Limited has announced that its Executive Business Committee has approved the transfer of shares held by the Company in its foreign subsidiary, PellucidCare Health Innovations Pte Ltd, to FlynnCare Health Innovations Private Limited. This transfer is part of an internal group reorganization aimed at enhancing administrative and operational efficiency. The ultimate ownership, control, management, and economic interest of the Company in the foreign subsidiary remain unchanged. The transaction, being between the Holding Company and its wholly owned subsidiary, does not have a material impact on the consolidated financials of the Company.</p><ul><li>Fischer Medical Ventures is transferring shares in its foreign subsidiary, PellucidCare Health Innovations Pte Ltd, to FlynnCare Health Innovations Private Limited.</li><li>The transfer is part of an internal group reorganization for administrative and operational efficiency.</li><li>The ultimate ownership, control, management, and economic interest of the Company in the foreign subsidiary remain unchanged.</li><li>The transaction does not have a material impact on the consolidated financials of the Company.</li><li>The disclosure is made in compliance with the applicable provisions of Regulation 30 of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cc38f40f-de69-4f2e-b27d-f2ccc00afa10.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: FISCHER CHEMIC LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>