<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:28:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[OFSS] Oracle Financial Services Software Reports Q3 Fiscal Year 2026 Results: Revenue at Rs. 1,966 Crore, up 15% YoY</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ORACLE+FINANCIAL+SERVICES+SOFTWARE+LTD.&title=Oracle+Financial+Services+Software+Reports+Q3+Fiscal+Year+2026+Results%3A+Revenue+at+Rs.+1%2C966+Crore%2C+up+15%25+YoY&newsId=3e4512d5-ce04-453c-9dbb-40c511b665c9&token=M2U0NTEyZDUtY2Uw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e4512d5-ce04-453c-9dbb-40c511b665c9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:21:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Oracle Financial Services Software Limited, a majority-owned subsidiary of Oracle, announced results for the quarter and nine-months ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a 15% YoY growth in revenue for the quarter, which stood at Rs. 1,966 Crore. The net income for the quarter was Rs. 610 Crore, up 13% YoY. The company&apos;s products business posted revenue of Rs. 1,774 Crore, up 14%, and the services business posted revenue of Rs. 192 Crore, up 25%. The net profit margin for the quarter was 31% despite the effect of new labour code-related accruals.</p><ul><li>Revenue for the quarter at Rs. 1,966 Crore, up 15% YoY</li><li>Net income of Rs. 610 Crore, up 13% YoY</li><li>Products business posted revenue of Rs. 1,774 Crore, up 14%</li><li>Services business posted revenue of Rs. 192 Crore, up 25%</li><li>Net profit margin for the quarter was 31%</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/36a9432b-4c4b-4acb-8fec-31897daec393.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ORACLE FINANCIAL SERVICES SOFTWARE LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MOTHERSON] Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd Issues INR 250 Crores Commercial Paper</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Samvardhana+Motherson+International+Ltd&title=Samvardhana+Motherson+International+Ltd+Issues+INR+250+Crores+Commercial+Paper&newsId=d0c35f03-22a2-4c14-9de2-b8797bd5ef39&token=ZDBjMzVmMDMtMjJh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d0c35f03-22a2-4c14-9de2-b8797bd5ef39</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Samvardhana Motherson International Limited has announced the listing of Commercial Paper worth INR 250 crores on BSE Limited. The Commercial Paper has a face value of Rs. 500,000/- each and is unsecured. The tenure of the Commercial Paper is 50 days with a maturity date of 11-03-2026. The coupon/interest rate is 6.35% and the interest is charged upfront. The payment of principal will be made on maturity. The Company&apos;s registered office is in Mumbai, Maharashtra.</p><ul><li>Samvardhana Motherson International Limited issues Commercial Paper worth INR 250 crores.</li><li>The Commercial Paper is listed on BSE Limited.</li><li>The tenure of the Commercial Paper is 50 days with a maturity date of 11-03-2026.</li><li>The coupon/interest rate is 6.35% and the interest is charged upfront.</li><li>The payment of principal will be made on maturity.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3355a294-16af-466d-a92b-e64c8fddc92d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ANANTRAJ] Anant Raj Ltd. Reports QIP Proceeds Utilization for Q4 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Anant+Raj+Limited-%24&title=Anant+Raj+Ltd.+Reports+QIP+Proceeds+Utilization+for+Q4+2025&newsId=46fb9b22-35b0-4780-97f2-ee273ff1f28a&token=NDZmYjliMjItMzVi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">46fb9b22-35b0-4780-97f2-ee273ff1f28a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Anant Raj Ltd. has released the Monitoring Agency Report for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, regarding the utilization of proceeds from the Qualified Institutions Placement (QIP). The report, prepared by Infomerics Valuation and Rating Limited, confirms that the company has adhered to the objects of the QIP issue without any deviations. The report is available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Anant Raj Ltd. has fully utilized the QIP proceeds for the intended objectives without any deviations.</li><li>The Monitoring Agency Report confirms the company&apos;s adherence to the QIP regulations.</li><li>The report is prepared by the SEBI-registered, RBI-accredited, and NSIC-empaneled credit rating agency Infomerics Valuation and Rating Limited.</li><li>The report is available on the company&apos;s website for public access.</li><li>This report is a testament to Anant Raj Ltd.&apos;s transparency and commitment to regulatory compliance.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/17457864-2fa0-4dd8-a5a8-b813838ff735.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Anant Raj Limited-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WAAREEENER] Waaree Energies Ltd Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025, Reports Profit Before Tax of ₹ 1,634.65 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Waaree+Energies+Ltd&title=Waaree+Energies+Ltd+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Reports+Profit+Before+Tax+of+%E2%82%B9+1%2C634.65+Crores&newsId=81b1c225-e064-4ab8-aef2-578f7bf6611d&token=ODFiMWMyMjUtZTA2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">81b1c225-e064-4ab8-aef2-578f7bf6611d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Waaree Energies Ltd, a leading solar photovoltaic module manufacturer, announced its unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a profit before tax of ₹ 1,634.65 crores. The results were approved in a Board Meeting on January 21, 2026. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stood at ₹ 12,764.55 crores for the quarter and ₹ 35,399.33 crores for the nine months period. The total expenses for the quarter were ₹ 11,345.78 crores and ₹ 33,758.77 for the nine months period. The company also reported a net profit for the period of ₹ 1,535.94 crores. The company&apos;s other comprehensive income items for the period were ₹ 1,339.87 crores.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter stood at ₹ 12,764.55 crores</li><li>Profit before tax for the quarter was ₹ 1,634.65 crores</li><li>Net profit for the period was ₹ 1,535.94 crores</li><li>Other comprehensive income items for the period were ₹ 1,339.87 crores</li><li>Company has recognized a provision of ₹ 294.78 crores in relation to liabilities related to a CBP investigation</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/04a53de3-58b7-4046-a1f3-b34ea4ea6886.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Waaree Energies Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PNBHOUSING] PNB Housing Finance Q3 &amp; 9M FY2025-26: Retail Loan Asset Grew by 16% YoY to INR 81,931 Crore; Net Profit Increased by 7.7% YoY to INR 520 Crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PNB+Housing+Finance+Ltd&title=PNB+Housing+Finance+Q3+%26+9M+FY2025-26%3A+Retail+Loan+Asset+Grew+by+16%25+YoY+to+INR+81%2C931+Crore%3B+Net+Profit+Increased+by+7.7%25+YoY+to+INR+520+Crore&newsId=e7fab5c9-e476-4962-a2d8-a8979ae182dc&token=ZTdmYWI1YzktZTQ3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e7fab5c9-e476-4962-a2d8-a8979ae182dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:01:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>The Board of Directors of PNB Housing Finance Limited approved the Consolidated Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The Retail Loan Asset grew by 16% YoY to INR 81,931 crore, which is 99.7% of the Total Loan Asset. The Affordable and Emerging Markets segment grew by 31% YoY and contributes 39% to the Retail Loan Asset. Net profit increased by 7.7% YoY and declined by 10.5% QoQ to INR 520 crore. Pre-provision Operating profit grew by 8.4% YoY and declined by 2.9% QoQ to Rs 628 crore. Gross NPA stood at 1.04% as on 31st Dec 2025 as compared to 1.19 % as on 31st Dec 2024. Capital Risk Adequacy Ratio stood at 29.46% as on 31st Dec 2025.</p><ul><li>Retail Loan Asset grew by 16% YoY to INR 81,931 crore</li><li>Affordable and Emerging Markets segment grew by 31% YoY</li><li>Net profit increased by 7.7% YoY to INR 520 crore</li><li>Pre-provision Operating profit grew by 8.4% YoY</li><li>Capital Risk Adequacy Ratio stood at 29.46% as on 31st Dec 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8c8e7da0-8bf8-442e-803c-ae70dafe8a69.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PNB Housing Finance Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SYSTMTXC] Systematix Corporate Services Ltd: Board Approves Q3 Results, Appoints New Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SYSTEMATIX+CORPORATE+SERVICES+LTD.&title=Systematix+Corporate+Services+Ltd%3A+Board+Approves+Q3+Results%2C+Appoints+New+Independent+Director&newsId=55b6c48f-4707-49bc-a4c5-1638a53bef61&token=NTViNmM0OGYtNDcw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55b6c48f-4707-49bc-a4c5-1638a53bef61</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Systematix Corporate Services Ltd approved the standalone and consolidated unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company also announced the resignation of Mr. Sampath Kumar Kangeyam Venkatakrishnan as Non-Executive Independent Director and the appointment of Mr. Vijaykumar Gautam as an Additional Non-Executive Independent Director.</p><ul><li>Board approved Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025 financial results</li><li>Resignation of Mr. Sampath Kumar Kangeyam Venkatakrishnan as Non-Executive Independent Director</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Vijaykumar Gautam as Additional Non-Executive Independent Director</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d73bb773-1964-4d4b-b3f4-5e25fb05fea9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SYSTEMATIX CORPORATE SERVICES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WAAREEENER] Waaree Energies Ltd. Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025 with Net Profit and Tax Expense Details</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Waaree+Energies+Ltd&title=Waaree+Energies+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025+with+Net+Profit+and+Tax+Expense+Details&newsId=eae2e6c1-5137-4fad-8ab7-ddf1c37ffeaa&token=ZWFlMmU2YzEtNTEz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eae2e6c1-5137-4fad-8ab7-ddf1c37ffeaa</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:53:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Waaree Energies Ltd. announced the outcome of its Board meeting held on January 21, 2026, which considered and approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company reported revenue from operations of ₹ 12,764.55 crores and ₹ 453,91 crores for the quarter and nine months respectively. Total income stood at ₹ 3,184.20 crores and ₹ 15,39,933 crores for the same periods. The company&apos;s expenses include cost of materials consumed, purchases of stock-in-trade, employee benefits, and finance costs among others. The net profit for the quarter and nine months amounted to ₹ 1,010.01 crores and ₹ 1,619.89 crores respectively. The company also reported a tax expense of ₹ 294.78 crores and ₹ 1,339.87 crores for the quarter and nine months respectively. The equity share capital is ₹ 287.64 crores. The company&apos;s earnings per equity share for the quarter and nine months are not annualised.</p><ul><li>Waaree Energies Ltd. announced the unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The company reported revenue from operations of ₹ 12,764.55 crores for the quarter and ₹ 453,91 crores for the nine months period.</li><li>The net profit for the quarter and nine months amounted to ₹ 1,010.01 crores and ₹ 1,619.89 crores respectively.</li><li>The company reported a tax expense of ₹ 294.78 crores and ₹ 1,339.87 crores for the quarter and nine months respectively.</li><li>Waaree Energies Ltd. has an equity share capital of ₹ 287.64 crores.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7a8e3bf6-d492-41ed-ade2-266867c0d304.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Waaree Energies Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DISAQ] Disa India Ltd Appoints Mr. Muralidharan Angadu Mohanakrishnan as Additional and Non-Executive Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DISA+INDIA+LTD.&title=Disa+India+Ltd+Appoints+Mr.+Muralidharan+Angadu+Mohanakrishnan+as+Additional+and+Non-Executive+Independent+Director&newsId=6ce1ac74-6b10-4182-844e-aa8c42c3bee7&token=NmNlMWFjNzQtNmIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ce1ac74-6b10-4182-844e-aa8c42c3bee7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:52:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Disa India Ltd has announced the appointment of Mr. Muralidharan Angadu Mohanakrishnan as Additional and Non-Executive Independent Director. The appointment was approved by the Board of Directors at their meeting held on January 21, 2026. Mr. Mohanakrishnan, a seasoned leader in the construction equipment industry, has over 35 years of global experience and has held senior leadership positions in various companies. He will serve as a Director from January 28, 2026, to May 19, 2030, subject to the approval of shareholders.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Muralidharan Angadu Mohanakrishnan as Additional and Non-Executive Independent Director</li><li>Mr. Mohanakrishnan&apos;s extensive experience in the construction equipment industry</li><li>His appointment is subject to the approval of shareholders</li><li>He will serve as a Director from January 28, 2026, to May 19, 2030</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e3c98c63-0473-4a09-a2af-c59a1478d0f2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DISA INDIA LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GET&amp;D] GE Vernova T&amp;D India Ltd to Approve Q3 and Half-Yearly Results for FY 2025-2026 on Jan 28, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GE+T%26D+India+Ltd&title=GE+Vernova+T%26D+India+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Half-Yearly+Results+for+FY+2025-2026+on+Jan+28%2C+2026&newsId=6df86624-e086-4fb5-993b-2ec0ab6a048f&token=NmRmODY2MjQtZTA4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6df86624-e086-4fb5-993b-2ec0ab6a048f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:51:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>GE Vernova T&amp;D India Ltd has announced a Board meeting on January 28, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter and period ended December 31, 2025. The meeting is in compliance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The company will communicate the financial results once they are approved and taken on record by the Board. The trading window for dealing in securities of the company has been closed from January 1, 2026, to January 30, 2026, as per the Code of Conduct to Regulate, Monitor and Report Trading in Securities of the Company.</p><ul><li>GE Vernova T&amp;D India Ltd to consider and approve un-audited financial results for Q3 and half-yearly results for FY 2025-2026 on Jan 28, 2026.</li><li>The meeting is in compliance with Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li><li>The company will communicate the financial results once they are approved and taken on record by the Board.</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities of the company has been closed from Jan 1, 2026, to Jan 30, 2026.</li><li>The announcement is in accordance with the Code of Conduct to Regulate, Monitor and Report Trading in Securities of the Company.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2311eaa0-b26c-45ab-9171-8837153e5882.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GE T&D India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DISAQ] Disa India Ltd Appoints Mr. Muralidharan Angadu Mohanakrishnan as Additional and Non-Executive Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DISA+INDIA+LTD.&title=Disa+India+Ltd+Appoints+Mr.+Muralidharan+Angadu+Mohanakrishnan+as+Additional+and+Non-Executive+Independent+Director&newsId=7ba9611c-779e-4e66-a4f3-0fed92f95209&token=N2JhOTYxMWMtNzc5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ba9611c-779e-4e66-a4f3-0fed92f95209</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:51:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Disa India Ltd has approved the appointment of Mr. Muralidharan Angadu Mohanakrishnan as Additional and Non-Executive Independent Director, effective from January 28, 2026, until May 19, 2030, subject to shareholder approval. Mr. Mohanakrishnan is a seasoned leader in the construction equipment industry with over 35 years of global experience. He has held senior leadership positions at Volvo Group Singapore and Volvo Construction Equipment India, among others. He retired from full-time work in December 2024 and currently works as a consultant with the Indian Foundation for Quality Management.</p><ul><li>Mr. Muralidharan Angadu Mohanakrishnan appointed as Additional and Non-Executive Independent Director of Disa India Ltd.</li><li>Mr. Mohanakrishnan has over 35 years of global experience in the construction equipment industry.</li><li>He has held senior leadership positions at Volvo Group Singapore and Volvo Construction Equipment India.</li><li>Mr. Mohanakrishnan retired from full-time work in December 2024 and currently works as a consultant.</li><li>His appointment is subject to shareholder approval.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/561a37eb-7c99-462d-906a-e047726a255b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DISA INDIA LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>