<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:00:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[INRADIA] India Radiators Ltd. Announces Equity Shareholders Meeting for Scheme of Amalgamation on March 13, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDIA+RADIATORS+LTD.&title=India+Radiators+Ltd.+Announces+Equity+Shareholders+Meeting+for+Scheme+of+Amalgamation+on+March+13%2C+2026&newsId=97a19d15-ef7b-4990-b3eb-c2d53f80856e&token=OTdhMTlkMTUtZWY3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97a19d15-ef7b-4990-b3eb-c2d53f80856e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>India Radiators Ltd. has announced a meeting of equity shareholders to be held on March 13, 2026, at 10.00 A.M. (IST) through video conference and/or other audio and visual means. The meeting is convened as per the directions of the Hon’ble National Company Law Tribunal (Court — I), Chennai Bench in the matter of the Scheme of Amalgamation with Mercantile Ventures Limited. The notice of the meeting, explanatory statement, and accompanying documents are available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>India Radiators Ltd. and Mercantile Ventures Limited are planning a Scheme of Amalgamation.</li><li>The meeting is convened as per the directions of the Hon’ble National Company Law Tribunal (Court — I), Chennai Bench.</li><li>The meeting will be held through video conference and/or other audio and visual means.</li><li>The notice of the meeting, explanatory statement, and accompanying documents are available on the company&apos;s website.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d8b360b5-8f7a-49a8-93cb-26d820298ecc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDIA RADIATORS LTD. | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RSYSTEMINT] R Systems Reports Robust FY2025 Performance with 17.8% YoY Growth in Normalized EBITDA</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=R+Systems+International+Limited&title=R+Systems+Reports+Robust+FY2025+Performance+with+17.8%25+YoY+Growth+in+Normalized+EBITDA&newsId=4163a7d9-c086-48bd-a203-c74210559f87&token=NDE2M2E3ZDktYzA4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4163a7d9-c086-48bd-a203-c74210559f87</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>R Systems International Limited, a leading digital product engineering company, reported a robust financial performance for the year ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s consolidated revenue was Rs. 19,582 mn (US$ 224.8 mn), representing a YoY growth of 12.4% in INR terms and 8.0% in US$ terms. The Adj. EBITDA was Rs. 3,427 mn (US$ 39.3 mn), reflecting a YoY growth of 17.8%. The Adj. net profit after taxes was Rs. 1,936 mn (US$ 22.2 mn), indicating a YoY growth of 24.6%. The company also reported a YoY growth of 27.0% in Adj. EBITDA and 27.4% in Adj. net profit after taxes for the quarter ended December 31, 2025.</p><ul><li>Revenue of Rs. 19,582 mn (US$ 224.8 mn) with a YoY growth of 12.4% in INR terms and 8.0% in US$ terms</li><li>Adj. EBITDA of Rs. 3,427 mn (US$ 39.3 mn) i.e. 17.5%</li><li>Adj. Net profit after taxes of Rs. 1,936 mn (US$ 22.2 mn) with a YoY growth of 24.6%</li><li>Q4 revenue of Rs 555 crores and an EBITDA margin of 18.3%</li><li>Successful completion of the acquisition of Novigo Solutions, enhancing capabilities in automation and Agentic AI</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/87c95ae5-521f-4a7e-a618-dcecf66475af.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: R Systems International Limited | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RSYSTEMINT] R Systems International Ltd Approves Audited Financial Results for FY2025, Including Acquisition of Novigo Solutions</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=R+Systems+International+Limited&title=R+Systems+International+Ltd+Approves+Audited+Financial+Results+for+FY2025%2C+Including+Acquisition+of+Novigo+Solutions&newsId=09a85036-d6fe-430c-ad91-b2f42e50d425&token=MDlhODUwMzYtZDZm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09a85036-d6fe-430c-ad91-b2f42e50d425</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>R Systems International Ltd has approved the audited financial results for the year ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a profit before tax of INR 3,958.46 million and a profit for the year of INR 1,861.96 million. The Board also approved the acquisition of 100% equity shares of Novigo Solutions Private Limited for a total consideration of INR 5,923.88 million.</p><ul><li>R Systems International Ltd reported a profit before tax of INR 3,958.46 million for the year ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The company reported a profit for the year of INR 1,861.96 million.</li><li>The Board approved the acquisition of 100% equity shares of Novigo Solutions Private Limited for a total consideration of INR 5,923.88 million.</li><li>The acquisition was partially funded through the issuance of rated, listed, unsecured, senior, redeemable non-convertible debentures (NCDs) amounting to INR 2,750.00 million.</li><li>The transaction for sale of land, building and certain other assets located at Parent’s Noida office was concluded during the year, resulting in a profit of INR 435.95 million.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/31241b10-65f7-4fa6-989a-c5d40138b617.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: R Systems International Limited | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HARISH] Harish Textile Engineers Ltd. to Raise Funds via Preferential Issue of Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Harish+Textile+Engineers+Ltd&title=Harish+Textile+Engineers+Ltd.+to+Raise+Funds+via+Preferential+Issue+of+Equity+Shares&newsId=0e8d6615-c3ec-4586-aee8-f9bdf2310f28&token=MGU4ZDY2MTUtYzNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e8d6615-c3ec-4586-aee8-f9bdf2310f28</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:42:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Harish Textile Engineers Ltd. has decided to raise funds by issuing up to 21,23,800 fully paid-up equity shares at an issue price of Rs. 64/- per share, including a securities premium of Rs. 54/-. The preferential issue will be made to proposed allottees belonging to the Promoter and Non-Promoter Category, for a total amount of Rs. 13,59,23,200. The decision is subject to the approval of the shareholders of the Company and other regulatory authorities.</p><ul><li>Harish Textile Engineers Ltd. to raise funds via preferential issue of equity shares</li><li>Issuance of up to 21,23,800 equity shares at an issue price of Rs. 64/- per share</li><li>Including a securities premium of Rs. 54/- per share</li><li>Total fundraising of Rs. 13,59,23,200</li><li>Subject to approval of shareholders and regulatory authorities</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9ace23ae-5103-443e-9a7d-78047d8e486a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Harish Textile Engineers Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RSYSTEMINT] R Systems International Ltd Approves Audited Financial Results for FY2025, Including Acquisition of Novigo Solutions</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=R+Systems+International+Limited&title=R+Systems+International+Ltd+Approves+Audited+Financial+Results+for+FY2025%2C+Including+Acquisition+of+Novigo+Solutions&newsId=d366184e-03b3-43e3-a0c6-2862355967f9&token=ZDM2NjE4NGUtMDNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d366184e-03b3-43e3-a0c6-2862355967f9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:41:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>R Systems International Ltd has approved the audited financial results for the year ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a profit of INR 1,861.96 million and a total income of INR 20,118.18 million. The Board also approved the acquisition of 100% equity shares of Novigo Solutions Private Limited for a total consideration of INR 5,923.88 million, which includes the fair value of compulsory convertible redeemable preference shares (CCPS) valued at INR 1,923.88 million.</p><ul><li>R Systems International Ltd approved the audited financial results for FY2025</li><li>The company reported a profit of INR 1,861.96 million</li><li>Total income for FY2025 stood at INR 20,118.18 million</li><li>The Board approved the acquisition of 100% equity shares of Novigo Solutions Private Limited</li><li>The total consideration for the acquisition was INR 5,923.88 million</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8bb33ec0-a2be-400e-8a1e-e58ed278e718.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: R Systems International Limited | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[OMANSH] Omansh Enterprises Ltd to Approve Q4 Results and Director Fees in February 2026 Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Omansh+Enterprises+Ltd&title=Omansh+Enterprises+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+Results+and+Director+Fees+in+February+2026+Board+Meeting&newsId=019b88c0-636f-47eb-b142-514680e521b8&token=MDE5Yjg4YzAtNjM2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">019b88c0-636f-47eb-b142-514680e521b8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Omansh Enterprises Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 14th February 2026 to consider and approve several matters. These include the un-audited financial results for the quarter ended on 31st December 2025, sitting fees for Non-Executive/Independent Directors, and a review of actions taken since the last meeting. The meeting will also adhere to the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations 2015, with the trading window for dealing in securities of the Company closed for Insiders from 1st January 2026.</p><ul><li>Omansh Enterprises Ltd to approve Q4 results for 2025 in February 2026</li><li>Board meeting scheduled on 14th February 2026 to consider Q4 results</li><li>Sitting fees for Non-Executive/Independent Directors to be approved</li><li>Trading window for Insiders closed from 1st January 2026</li><li>Adherence to SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/75999f2b-cc37-4e38-8e09-ecd925e45666.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Omansh Enterprises Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MEGASOFT] Sigma Advanced Systems Acquires 51% Stake in AS Strategic Private Limited for INR 20 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MEGASOFT+LTD.&title=Sigma+Advanced+Systems+Acquires+51%25+Stake+in+AS+Strategic+Private+Limited+for+INR+20+Crores&newsId=02384627-0a33-4d84-bb20-25d9591d4c13&token=MDIzODQ2MjctMGEz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02384627-0a33-4d84-bb20-25d9591d4c13</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Sigma Advanced Systems Ltd has signed a Share Purchase Agreement to acquire 51% Stake in AS Strategic Private Limited, a Delhi based Defence and Space focused company. The acquisition is a key step in Sigma building a globally embedded aerospace and defence platform, providing access to established joint ventures with major European Aerospace &amp; Defence OEMs. The acquisition will not fall within related party transaction(s) and the promoter / promoter group / group companies do not have any interest in the entity being acquired. The consideration for the acquisition is INR 20 crores in cash. The acquisition is expected to be completed within 4 to 6 weeks. AS Strategic reported a turnover of Rs. 608 lacs for the twelve-month period ending March 2025, Rs. 141 lacs for the twelve-month period ending March 2024, and Rs. 2 lacs for the twelve-month period ending March 2023.</p><ul><li>Sigma Advanced Systems to acquire 51% Stake in AS Strategic Private Limited</li><li>Acquisition consideration is INR 20 crores in cash</li><li>Acquisition to be completed within 4 to 6 weeks</li><li>AS Strategic reported a turnover of Rs. 608 lacs for the twelve-month period ending March 2025</li><li>Acquisition will provide access to established joint ventures with major European Aerospace &amp; Defence OEMs</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3aaa8d37-765d-4199-8f3e-6c8e2a9cdcf3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MEGASOFT LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TREJHARA] Trejhara Solutions Ltd Allots 6,11,112 Equity Shares and 68,97,000 Convertible Warrants in Preferential Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Trejhara+Solutions+Ltd&title=Trejhara+Solutions+Ltd+Allots+6%2C11%2C112+Equity+Shares+and+68%2C97%2C000+Convertible+Warrants+in+Preferential+Issue&newsId=5717b5fe-a4db-46ec-95f3-6f9f12903d95&token=NTcxN2I1ZmUtYTRk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5717b5fe-a4db-46ec-95f3-6f9f12903d95</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Trejhara Solutions Ltd has allotted 6,11,112 equity shares and 68,97,000 convertible warrants on a preferential basis to various allottees. The equity shares were offered at a price of Rs. 216 per share, while the warrants were offered at a price of Rs. 216, with Rs. 54 paid upfront as the warrant subscription price. The allotment was approved by the Allotment committee of the Board of Directors of the Company. The equity shares will rank pari-passu with the existing equity shares of the Company. The size of the preferential issue stands reduced to Rs. 162.18 Crore from the earlier proposed Rs. 185.94 Crore.</p><ul><li>Trejhara Solutions Ltd allots 6,11,112 equity shares and 68,97,000 convertible warrants on a preferential basis.</li><li>The equity shares were offered at a price of Rs. 216 per share and the warrants at a price of Rs. 216 with Rs. 54 paid upfront as the warrant subscription price.</li><li>The allotment was approved by the Allotment committee of the Board of Directors of the Company.</li><li>The equity shares will rank pari-passu with the existing equity shares of the Company.</li><li>The size of the preferential issue stands reduced to Rs. 162.18 Crore from the earlier proposed Rs. 185.94 Crore.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4a387db7-da84-4f2c-9985-1df50d439f76.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Trejhara Solutions Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CHORDIA] Chordia Food Products Ltd. Reports Q3 and Nine Months Unaudited Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CHORDIA+FOOD+PRODUCTS+LTD.&title=Chordia+Food+Products+Ltd.+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=57fa182b-c02d-42d7-bf15-6b3fb86e85e9&token=NTdmYTE4MmItYzAy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57fa182b-c02d-42d7-bf15-6b3fb86e85e9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:20:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Chordia Food Products Ltd. announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s total income for the quarter is Rs. 134.95 Lakhs and for the nine months is Rs. 319.33 Lakhs. The profit before tax for the quarter is Rs. 23.70 Lakhs and for the nine months is Rs. 14.44 Lakhs. The earnings per equity share (basic) for the quarter is Rs. 0.41 and for the nine months is Rs. 0.27. The company has reported its segment results for the Food Division and Food - Infrastructure Division.</p><ul><li>Total income for the quarter is Rs. 134.95 Lakhs and for the nine months is Rs. 319.33 Lakhs.</li><li>Profit before tax for the quarter is Rs. 23.70 Lakhs and for the nine months is Rs. 14.44 Lakhs.</li><li>Earnings per equity share (basic) for the quarter is Rs. 0.41 and for the nine months is Rs. 0.27.</li><li>The company has reported its segment results for the Food Division and Food - Infrastructure Division.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bbca5800-4eeb-4d46-9b2b-8ff2f4bfbe14.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CHORDIA FOOD PRODUCTS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MODINSU] Modern Insulators Ltd. Approves Q3 &amp; 9M Results for FY2025-26, Re-appoints Internal Auditor</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MODERN+INSULATORS+LTD.&title=Modern+Insulators+Ltd.+Approves+Q3+%26+9M+Results+for+FY2025-26%2C+Re-appoints+Internal+Auditor&newsId=73e2436b-1511-49d1-a0e3-53523f177a0d&token=NzNlMjQzNmItMTUx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73e2436b-1511-49d1-a0e3-53523f177a0d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 17:12:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Modern Insulators Ltd. announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s Board of Directors approved the results in a meeting on 10th February 2026. M/s S. Garg &amp; Co., Chartered Accountants have been re-appointed as the internal auditor for the financial year 2026-27. The company is also addressing certain regulatory and procedural requirements following a court order.</p><ul><li>Modern Insulators Ltd. announced Q3 &amp; 9M results for FY2025-26.</li><li>The Board of Directors approved the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results.</li><li>M/s S. Garg &amp; Co., Chartered Accountants re-appointed as internal auditor for FY2026-27.</li><li>Company is working on certain regulatory and procedural requirements following a court order.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/13bee43f-e435-4275-a9f8-5c710f62f750.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MODERN INSULATORS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>