<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 23:04:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[KBSINDIA] KBS India Ltd Reports Q3 Results for FY2025-26, Profit Before Tax Increases</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KBS+INDIA+LIMITED&title=KBS+India+Ltd+Reports+Q3+Results+for+FY2025-26%2C+Profit+Before+Tax+Increases&newsId=2707a9ad-536f-4a57-a80f-cf3f89b18339&token=MjcwN2E5YWQtNTM2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2707a9ad-536f-4a57-a80f-cf3f89b18339</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:34:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>KBS India Ltd, a shares and stock broking company, has reported its unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s profit before tax has increased compared to the previous year. However, there are certain matters that require attention, such as the non-provision of gratuity liability for employees and outstanding loans to a former subsidiary, KBS Capital Management Singapore Pte Ltd, which has been struck off.</p><ul><li>Profit before tax has increased compared to the previous year.</li><li>Gratuity liability for employees is not provided for as required by Ind AS 19 on &apos;Employee Benefits&apos;.</li><li>Long-term loan and current account balance amounting to Rs. 16,65,40,533/- and Rs. 8,02,444/- respectively are outstanding and receivable from KBS Capital Management Singapore Pte Ltd.</li><li>The company&apos;s operations are focused on shares and stock broking.</li><li>The unaudited financial results have been reviewed by the Audit committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b9f87321-a014-4707-aaf8-8e93a6078abe.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KBS INDIA LIMITED | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STDSHOE] Standard Shoe Sole And Mould (India) Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results on Feb 13, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=STANDARD+SHOE+SOLE+AND+MOULD+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Standard+Shoe+Sole+And+Mould+%28India%29+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+on+Feb+13%2C+2026&newsId=8ebb76a8-0167-4e38-86b7-9cbd57421de9&token=OGViYjc2YTgtMDE2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ebb76a8-0167-4e38-86b7-9cbd57421de9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:51:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Standard Shoe Sole And Mould (India) Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 13, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting is scheduled in accordance with Regulation 33 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The company has also announced that the trading window for dealing with shares/securities of the company has been closed for designated persons as per the company&apos;s insider trading code and will reopen after 48 hours from the announcement of the financial results.</p><ul><li>Standard Shoe Sole And Mould (India) Ltd to consider and approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended 31 December 2025.</li><li>Trading window closed for designated persons as per the company&apos;s insider trading code.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b1058bc4-1981-4ac7-92e3-70bac9c25a24.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: STANDARD SHOE SOLE AND MOULD (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AKASHDEEP] Kalyan Capitals Ltd to Approve Un-audited Financial Results on Feb 12, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Akashdeep+Metal+Industries+Ltd&title=Kalyan+Capitals+Ltd+to+Approve+Un-audited+Financial+Results+on+Feb+12%2C+2026&newsId=d11dacb2-7cc3-4768-8172-07c94b5d97e9&token=ZDExZGFjYjItN2Nj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d11dacb2-7cc3-4768-8172-07c94b5d97e9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:51:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kalyan Capitals Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 12, 2026, to consider and approve the Un-audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for designated persons, their immediate relatives, and other connected persons will be closed till the conclusion of 48 hours after the declaration of the Un-audited Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Kalyan Capitals Ltd to consider and approve Un-audited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>Trading window to be closed for all designated persons, their immediate relatives, and other connected persons till the conclusion of 48 hours after the declaration of Un-audited Financial Results.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0cf6d1df-5cd5-4fba-ba6d-217ba6157900.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Akashdeep Metal Industries Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CITYONLINE] City Online Services Ltd to Approve Q3 2025 Financial Results on Feb 13, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=City+Online+Services+Ltd&title=City+Online+Services+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+2025+Financial+Results+on+Feb+13%2C+2026&newsId=810288f6-abe7-4f11-b85f-83622617f998&token=ODEwMjg4ZjYtYWJl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">810288f6-abe7-4f11-b85f-83622617f998</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:51:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>City Online Services Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 13, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will take place at the company&apos;s registered office at 3.00 P.M. The company has also informed the exchange that the trading window for dealing in securities of the company by the designated persons, their immediate relatives and all connected persons covered under the company’s Code of Conduct will be closed from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of the results.</p><ul><li>City Online Services Ltd to consider and approve un-audited financial results for Q3 2025</li><li>Board meeting scheduled on February 13, 2026</li><li>Trading window for designated persons to be closed from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0797afb2-f158-4386-9025-e5a3ccba92df.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: City Online Services Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ROUTE] Route Mobile Q3 FY26 Results: Revenue at Rs. 1,107.06 crore, PAT at Rs. 102.56 crore; Leadership Update with Rajdipkumar Gupta as Managing Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Route+Mobile+Ltd&title=Route+Mobile+Q3+FY26+Results%3A+Revenue+at+Rs.+1%2C107.06+crore%2C+PAT+at+Rs.+102.56+crore%3B+Leadership+Update+with+Rajdipkumar+Gupta+as+Managing+Director&newsId=64248b2c-2b67-4f67-ad92-d51c65b906ff&token=NjQyNDhiMmMtMmI2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">64248b2c-2b67-4f67-ad92-d51c65b906ff</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Route Mobile Limited, a leading cloud communication platform service provider, has announced its financial results for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025, alongside a leadership transition. The company reported a revenue from operations of Rs. 1,107.06 crore and a PAT of Rs. 102.56 crore for Q3 FY26. The company&apos;s Profit Before Tax stands at Rs. 135.21 crore as against Rs. 106.95 crore in Q3FY25. The Board of Directors has re-designated Mr. Rajdipkumar Gupta as the Managing Director of the Company, effective February 9, 2026, upon his ceding the role of Chief Executive Officer. Mr. Tushar Agnihotri has been elevated to the role of Chief Executive Officer and KMP, effective February 9, 2026.</p><ul><li>Q3 FY26 Revenue from operations stands at Rs. 1,107.06 crore</li><li>PAT stands at Rs. 102.56 crore for Q3 FY26</li><li>Profit Before Tax stands at Rs. 135.21 crore for Q3 FY26</li><li>Rajdipkumar Gupta re-designated as Managing Director, Tushar Agnihotri as Chief Executive Officer</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a9755495-a989-4ccf-94ea-44b2648d2555.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Route Mobile Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TEXRAIL] Texmaco Rail &amp; Engineering Limited Announces Q3 FY26 Financial Results: Revenue of 21,042 crore, EBITDA of 2,102 crore, and PAT of 242 crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TEXMACO+RAIL+%26+ENGINEERING+LTD.&title=Texmaco+Rail+%26+Engineering+Limited+Announces+Q3+FY26+Financial+Results%3A+Revenue+of+21%2C042+crore%2C+EBITDA+of+2%2C102+crore%2C+and+PAT+of+242+crore&newsId=f5299404-2fac-430b-b6f2-6b8a0f1de78f&token=ZjUyOTk0MDQtMmZh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f5299404-2fac-430b-b6f2-6b8a0f1de78f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Texmaco Rail &amp; Engineering Limited, a leading manufacturer of freight wagons and provider of rail and infrastructure solutions, announced its unaudited consolidated financial results for the quarter ended 31 December 2025 (Q3 FY26). The company reported revenue of 21,042 crore, EBITDA of 2,102 crore with a margin of 9.6%, and PAT of 242 crore. Despite transient supply-side constraints and export headwinds, operational discipline and cost control supported margin stability. The company remains focused on disciplined execution, selective bidding, and expanding its addressable market through mobility and technology-led initiatives, supported by a strong policy and investment environment.</p><ul><li>Revenue of 21,042 crore in Q3 FY26</li><li>EBITDA of 2,102 crore with a margin of 9.6%</li><li>Profit After Tax of 242 crore</li><li>Operational challenges in wagon manufacturing and export-oriented businesses</li><li>Multiple orders across rail electrification, freight mobility, and metro rail infrastructure</li><li>Commissioned a 10 MW solar power installation at Urla Foundry in Raipur</li><li>Converted one high-tension furnace from LDO to LPG at Belgharia Foundry in Kolkata</li><li>CRISIL upgraded Texmaco’s ESG rating from 50 to 51, placing it in the ‘Adequate’ risk category</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fa852ad4-c1bb-4d52-b5a9-9597df7b65f5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TEXMACO RAIL & ENGINEERING LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ROUTE] Route Mobile Declares 3rd Interim Dividend of Rs. 3/- per Share for FY 2025-26 and Appoints New CEO</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Route+Mobile+Ltd&title=Route+Mobile+Declares+3rd+Interim+Dividend+of+Rs.+3%2F-+per+Share+for+FY+2025-26+and+Appoints+New+CEO&newsId=6650a07e-c340-4430-ab77-a99e05e97f85&token=NjY1MGEwN2UtYzM0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6650a07e-c340-4430-ab77-a99e05e97f85</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:11:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Route Mobile Ltd. has approved a 3rd interim dividend of Rs. 3/- per share for the Financial Year 2025-26. The record date for the dividend is February 13, 2026. The company has also approved the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. Additionally, the Board has noted the lapse of 1,500 stock options and approved the re-designation of Mr. Rajdipkumar Gupta as Managing Director and the appointment of Mr. Tushar Agnihotri as Chief Executive Officer and Key Managerial Personnel.</p><ul><li>Route Mobile declares 3rd interim dividend of Rs. 3/- per share for FY 2025-26</li><li>Unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results approved for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>1,500 stock options granted under Route Mobile ESOP Plan 2021 have lapsed</li><li>Mr. Rajdipkumar Gupta re-designated as Managing Director</li><li>Mr. Tushar Agnihotri appointed as Chief Executive Officer and Key Managerial Personnel</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d0dd89bd-7558-47f7-bb3d-554c4e4a04b0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Route Mobile Ltd | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PADMALAYAT] Padmalaya Telefilms Ltd to Approve Q3 Financial Results on February 14, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PADMALAYA+TELEFILMS+LTD.&title=Padmalaya+Telefilms+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+Financial+Results+on+February+14%2C+2026&newsId=f921a7ba-ce29-4139-8c24-51dda7e8d082&token=ZjkyMWE3YmEtY2Uy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f921a7ba-ce29-4139-8c24-51dda7e8d082</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:11:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Padmalaya Telefilms Ltd has informed the BSE that a Board Meeting is scheduled on February 14, 2026, to consider and approve the Intimation and authenticate the quarterly Un-audited financial results of the Company for the Third quarter ended on 31st December 2025. This is in accordance with Regulation 33 &amp; 29 (1) a) of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosures Requirements) Regulations 2015.</p><ul><li>Padmalaya Telefilms Ltd scheduled a Board Meeting on February 14, 2026, to discuss and approve Q3 financial results.</li><li>The meeting will be held at the Registered Office of the Company.</li><li>The financial results to be discussed are for the quarter ended on 31st December 2025.</li><li>The meeting is in accordance with Regulation 33 &amp; 29 (1) a) of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosures Requirements) Regulations 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2a836869-9c28-4189-81a3-81c069f85d62.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PADMALAYA TELEFILMS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AFFORDABLE] Affordable Robotic &amp; Automation Ltd to Increase Authorized Share Capital and Raise Funds via Preferential Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Affordable+Robotic+%26+Automation+Ltd&title=Affordable+Robotic+%26+Automation+Ltd+to+Increase+Authorized+Share+Capital+and+Raise+Funds+via+Preferential+Issue&newsId=8749a587-1234-4185-ac6a-651fef34b383&token=ODc0OWE1ODctMTIz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8749a587-1234-4185-ac6a-651fef34b383</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Affordable Robotic &amp; Automation Ltd has announced a Board of Directors meeting on 18/02/2026 to consider increasing the authorized share capital and amending the Memorandum of Association. The company also plans to raise funds through a preferential issue of Equity Shares to identified persons, subject to members&apos; and regulatory approvals. An Extraordinary General Meeting or postal ballot process may be conducted to seek member approval.</p><ul><li>Affordable Robotic &amp; Automation Ltd to consider increasing authorized share capital</li><li>Company to amend Memorandum of Association</li><li>Preferential issue of Equity Shares to identified persons proposed</li><li>Funds raising subject to members&apos; and regulatory approvals</li><li>Extraordinary General Meeting or postal ballot process may be held for member approval</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4708e3a8-20f0-4dd0-a0be-8beeeef96e76.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Affordable Robotic & Automation Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INERTIAST] Director Resigns from Banganga Paper Industries Ltd.</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INERTIA+STEEL+LTD.&title=Director+Resigns+from+Banganga+Paper+Industries+Ltd.&newsId=75cbbc08-1246-4bcb-be03-d0654c847ace&token=NzVjYmJjMDgtMTI0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75cbbc08-1246-4bcb-be03-d0654c847ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:04:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Banganga Paper Industries Ltd. has announced the resignation of Mr. Chetan Karbhari Dhatrak from his position as Director. The resignation is voluntary and due to personal reasons. There are no other material reasons or circumstances connected with the resignation. Mr. Dhatrak expressed his gratitude for the opportunity to serve on the Board and confirmed no claims or dues outstanding against the Company.</p><ul><li>Mr. Chetan Karbhari Dhatrak resigns from the position of Director at Banganga Paper Industries Ltd.</li><li>The resignation is voluntary and due to personal reasons.</li><li>No other material reasons or circumstances connected with the resignation.</li><li>Mr. Dhatrak expressed gratitude for the opportunity to serve on the Board.</li><li>No claims or dues outstanding against the Company.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fc0f9f66-04b1-4d2b-bec2-1b156c410946.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INERTIA STEEL LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>