<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 06:29:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[VAIBHAVGBL] Vaibhav Global Ltd Subsidiary Receives US$ 2.76 Million Grant Under ERC Scheme</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vaibhav+Global+Ltd&title=Vaibhav+Global+Ltd+Subsidiary+Receives+US%24+2.76+Million+Grant+Under+ERC+Scheme&newsId=5ce8d13d-fdce-4a15-86c4-2e96d2e4ddc3&token=NWNlOGQxM2QtZmRj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ce8d13d-fdce-4a15-86c4-2e96d2e4ddc3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 06:29:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SHOPLC Global Inc., USA, a step-down subsidiary of Vaibhav Global Ltd, has received a grant amounting to US$ 2.76 million (net of expenses) under the Employee Retention Credit (ERC) Scheme. The grant was provided by the Internal Revenue Service, Department of the Treasury, United States of America, pursuant to the Coronavirus Aid, Relief and Economic Security Act (the “CARES Act”). The subsidiary is currently evaluating the appropriate accounting and financial treatment of the aforesaid grant and its impact, if any, on the consolidated financial statements of the Company.</p><ul><li>SHOPLC Global Inc., USA, a step-down subsidiary of Vaibhav Global Ltd, received a grant of US$ 2.76 million under the ERC Scheme.</li><li>The grant was provided by the Internal Revenue Service, Department of the Treasury, United States of America, pursuant to the CARES Act.</li><li>The subsidiary is evaluating the appropriate accounting and financial treatment of the grant.</li><li>The impact of the grant on the consolidated financial statements of the Company is being assessed.</li><li>The grant was received to mitigate the adverse economic impact of the COVID-19 pandemic.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/378404d7-9c07-4387-8071-70bb61e1860b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vaibhav Global Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RETAGGIO] Retaggio Industries Ltd. Approves Allotment of 53,04,000 Convertible Equity Warrants</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Retaggio+Industries+Ltd&title=Retaggio+Industries+Ltd.+Approves+Allotment+of+53%2C04%2C000+Convertible+Equity+Warrants&newsId=7c52404b-41a2-493b-b8bb-7d95df4ae8f0&token=N2M1MjQwNGItNDFh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c52404b-41a2-493b-b8bb-7d95df4ae8f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 06:29:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Retaggio Industries Ltd. has approved the allotment of 53,04,000 (Fifty-Three Lakhs Four Thousand) Convertible Equity Warrants at an issue price of Rs. 26/- per warrant. The Company has received 25% of the issue price, i.e. Rs. 6.50/- per warrant, amounting to Rs. 3,44, 76,000/-. The Warrants are convertible into Equity Shares, aggregating to Rs. 13,79,04,000/- (Rupees Thirteen Crores Seventy-Nine Lakhs Four Thousand only). The allotment is made on a preferential basis and In Principle Approval has been granted by BSE Limited.</p><ul><li>Retaggio Industries Ltd. approves allotment of 53,04,000 Convertible Equity Warrants</li><li>The warrants are issued at an issue price of Rs. 26/- per warrant</li><li>The Company has received 25% of the issue price, i.e. Rs. 6.50/- per warrant</li><li>The warrants are convertible into Equity Shares aggregating to Rs. 13,79,04,000/-</li><li>In Principle Approval has been granted by BSE Limited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/99ef90d3-97b9-4814-a7ad-ad90174b4ab0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Retaggio Industries Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MCLOUD] Magellanic Cloud&apos;s Subsidiary, Provigil Surveillance, Wins Contract from Central Railway&apos;s Nagpur Division</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Magellanic+Cloud+Ltd&title=Magellanic+Cloud%27s+Subsidiary%2C+Provigil+Surveillance%2C+Wins+Contract+from+Central+Railway%27s+Nagpur+Division&newsId=dc4bdb41-ce83-4ddb-af00-23ca0c27aead&token=ZGM0YmRiNDEtY2U4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc4bdb41-ce83-4ddb-af00-23ca0c27aead</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 06:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Magellanic Cloud Ltd&apos;s wholly owned subsidiary, Provigil Surveillance Limited, has been awarded a Letter of Acceptance (LoA) from Central Railway, Nagpur Division (NGP Division). The mandate involves the comprehensive supply, installation, testing, commissioning, and maintenance of CCTV surveillance systems at manned, non-interlocked Level Crossing (LC) gates within the Narkher-Chandur Bazar section of the Nagpur Division. The project, valued at approximately ₹ 3.61 crores, encompasses the deployment of RDSO-compliant Full HD IP CCTV cameras, network video recorders (NVRs), power and communication infrastructure, complete system integration, and associated civil and electrical works.</p><ul><li>Magellanic Cloud&apos;s subsidiary, Provigil Surveillance, has been awarded a contract worth approximately ₹ 3.61 crores from Central Railway&apos;s Nagpur Division.</li><li>The project involves the deployment of RDSO-compliant Full HD IP CCTV cameras, network video recorders (NVRs), power and communication infrastructure, and associated civil and electrical works.</li><li>The contract is a strong endorsement of the company’s ability to manage complex, high-reliability safety systems in sensitive environments.</li><li>The order/contract does not fall within the purview of related party transaction.</li><li>The project is to be completed within 9 months.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0f83db29-80c0-4b5d-bb78-153eb5f725a4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Magellanic Cloud Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[QUICKHEAL] Quick Heal Technologies Ltd Receives Request for Reclassification from Promoter Group to Public Category</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Quick+Heal+Technologies+Ltd&title=Quick+Heal+Technologies+Ltd+Receives+Request+for+Reclassification+from+Promoter+Group+to+Public+Category&newsId=66388ff6-39c5-4ccd-8598-de9494d7929c&token=NjYzODhmZjYtMzlj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66388ff6-39c5-4ccd-8598-de9494d7929c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 06:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Quick Heal Technologies Ltd has received a request from Gagan Bharari Enterprises LLP, a member of the Promoter Group, for reclassification as a Public shareholder. Gagan Bharari Enterprises LLP currently holds zero equity shares, amounting to 0% of the total shareholding of the Company. The request is due to be considered in the upcoming Board meeting. Gagan Bharari Enterprises LLP has confirmed that they are not associated with the business or management of the Company and do not have any rights to appoint Directors or control the management or policy decisions of the Company.</p><ul><li>Quick Heal Technologies Ltd received a request for reclassification from Promoter Group to Public category.</li><li>Request submitted by Gagan Bharari Enterprises LLP, which holds zero equity shares in the Company.</li><li>Gagan Bharari Enterprises LLP is not associated with the business or management of the Company.</li><li>The request will be considered in the upcoming Board meeting.</li><li>Gagan Bharari Enterprises LLP confirms they do not have rights to appoint Directors or control Company&apos;s management.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6f248db7-8b1d-440e-8726-8949857f1c11.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Quick Heal Technologies Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHANTIGOLD] Shanti Gold International Announces 4,000 kg Capacity Expansion to Cater Future Increase in Demand</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shanti+Gold+International+Ltd&title=Shanti+Gold+International+Announces+4%2C000+kg+Capacity+Expansion+to+Cater+Future+Increase+in+Demand&newsId=376b58f1-3c13-430f-99e1-6574ec6235ba&token=Mzc2YjU4ZjEtM2Mx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">376b58f1-3c13-430f-99e1-6574ec6235ba</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 06:24:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Shanti Gold International Limited, a leading gold jewellery manufacturer, has announced a proposed expansion of its manufacturing facility. The expansion aims to address the increasing demand from organised jewellery retailers across the country and support the Company’s expanding portfolio of long-term retail partnerships. Upon completion, the Company’s manufacturing capacity is expected to increase by approximately 4,000 kgs per annum.</p><ul><li>The capacity expansion aims to cater to the growing demand across key product segments.</li><li>The proposed capacity utilization will increase by 4,000 kg per annum.</li><li>The investment required for the expansion is approximately Rs. 8.50 crore.</li><li>The expansion is strategically aligned with the ongoing structural shift towards organised jewellery retail.</li><li>The expanded facility will strengthen the company&apos;s ability to service leading retail chains with consistent quality, timely delivery, and customised designs at scale.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6833b585-3590-494c-8882-5ec11a9a204d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shanti Gold International Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GOKULAGRO] Gokul Agro Resources Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on Feb 5, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Gokul+Agro+Resources+Ltd&title=Gokul+Agro+Resources+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+Feb+5%2C+2026&newsId=c679357f-a293-4851-89a6-0bf3694767c2&token=YzY3OTM1N2YtYTI5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c679357f-a293-4851-89a6-0bf3694767c2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 06:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gokul Agro Resources Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 5, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The meeting will also discuss other businesses of the Company. The Trading Window closure period will end after 48 hours after the results are made public.</p><ul><li>Gokul Agro Resources Ltd to approve Q3 and nine months financial results on Feb 5, 2026</li><li>The meeting will also discuss other businesses of the Company</li><li>Trading Window closure period will end after 48 hours after the results are made public</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/59d995e8-3a67-46ea-8708-d7dd4d5fbdf5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Gokul Agro Resources Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JPASSOCIAT] Jaiprakash Associates Ltd Re-lodges Transfer Requests of Physical Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JAIPRAKASH+ASSOCIATES+LTD.&title=Jaiprakash+Associates+Ltd+Re-lodges+Transfer+Requests+of+Physical+Shares&newsId=00a09c9f-f24b-480b-809a-adabf687e786&token=MDBhMDljOWYtZjI0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00a09c9f-f24b-480b-809a-adabf687e786</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 06:20:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jaiprakash Associates Ltd, in accordance with SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97 dated 2nd July 2025, has released a report from the Registrar and Share Transfer Agent, M/s Alankit Assignments Limited, on the re-lodgement of transfer requests for physical shares as of 31st December 2025. The report indicates that no requests were rejected during the month, and the average time taken for processing requests was not specified in the text.</p><ul><li>Jaiprakash Associates Ltd complies with SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97</li><li>Report received from Registrar and Share Transfer Agent, M/s Alankit Assignments Limited</li><li>No requests rejected during the month of December 2025</li><li>Average time taken for processing requests not specified</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/60c7a0f7-b49a-4b1e-a155-fb1a8432afa4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JAIPRAKASH ASSOCIATES LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CARTRADE] CarTrade Tech Ltd. to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on January 28, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CarTrade+Tech+Ltd&title=CarTrade+Tech+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+January+28%2C+2026&newsId=84515516-5b40-4da0-afdc-a353854317bd&token=ODQ1MTU1MTYtNWI0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">84515516-5b40-4da0-afdc-a353854317bd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 06:19:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>CarTrade Tech Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 28, 2026, to consider and approve the Standalone and Consolidated Unaudited Financial Results for the third quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. This meeting is pursuant to Regulation 29(1) of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company was closed for all designated persons from January 01, 2026, and will remain closed till 48 hours after the declaration of the Financial Results by the Company.</p><ul><li>CarTrade Tech Ltd. to consider and approve Q3 and nine months financial results for 2025</li><li>Meeting of the Board of Directors scheduled on January 28, 2026</li><li>Pursuant to Regulation 29(1) of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities closed for all designated persons from January 01, 2026</li><li>Trading window to remain closed till 48 hours after the declaration of financial results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dff71b6b-8f0d-47d1-8a0e-8a2c1d2cba57.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CarTrade Tech Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SATIN] Satin Creditcare Network Ltd to Approve Q3 and 9M Financial Results on Jan 28, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Satin+Creditcare+Network+Ltd&title=Satin+Creditcare+Network+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+9M+Financial+Results+on+Jan+28%2C+2026&newsId=9b7ee75f-ea31-46f8-b966-ed8cc95a8f96&token=OWI3ZWU3NWYtZWEz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b7ee75f-ea31-46f8-b966-ed8cc95a8f96</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 06:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Satin Creditcare Network Ltd has announced a Board of Directors meeting on January 28, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results (Standalone and Consolidated) for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in securities of the company will remain closed till 48 hours after the declaration of Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Satin Creditcare Network Ltd scheduled a Board of Directors meeting on January 28, 2026</li><li>The meeting aims to consider and approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and 9M ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities of the company will be closed till 48 hours after the declaration of Financial Results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fe2465e0-0700-4922-a720-66dae4b4bcd9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Satin Creditcare Network Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RETAGGIO] Retaggio Industries Ltd Approves Allotment of 53,04,000 Convertible Equity Warrants</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Retaggio+Industries+Ltd&title=Retaggio+Industries+Ltd+Approves+Allotment+of+53%2C04%2C000+Convertible+Equity+Warrants&newsId=4d4fdac5-10c8-4000-8043-9d7b8a5b4a80&token=NGQ0ZmRhYzUtMTBj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d4fdac5-10c8-4000-8043-9d7b8a5b4a80</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 06:13:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Retaggio Industries Ltd has approved the allotment of 53,04,000 Convertible Equity Warrants at an issue price of Rs. 26/- per warrant. The company has received 25% of the issue price, i.e. Rs. 6.50/- per warrant, amounting to Rs. 3,44,76,000/-. The warrants are convertible into Equity Shares, aggregating to Rs. 13,79,04,000/-. The allotment is in accordance with the applicable provisions of the Companies Act, 2013 and SEBI (ICDR) Regulations, 2018. The equity shares to be allotted on exercise of the warrants will rank pari passu with the existing Equity Shares of the Company in all respects.</p><ul><li>Retaggio Industries Ltd approves allotment of 53,04,000 Convertible Equity Warrants</li><li>The issue price of the warrants is Rs. 26/- per warrant</li><li>The company has received Rs. 3,44,76,000/- towards subscription of the warrants</li><li>The warrants are convertible into Equity Shares aggregating to Rs. 13,79,04,000/-</li><li>The equity shares to be allotted on exercise of the warrants will rank pari passu with the existing Equity Shares of the Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8a3b8da7-1c8c-4d6e-85b4-567960ba89d3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Retaggio Industries Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>