<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 06:30:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[MOSCHIP] Moschip Technologies Ltd Schedules Board Meeting for January 2026 to Approve Q3 Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Moschip+Technologies+Ltd&title=Moschip+Technologies+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+for+January+2026+to+Approve+Q3+Results&newsId=9e04e83c-b674-4fa6-a0d1-522bcda0aa10&token=OWUwNGU4M2MtYjY3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e04e83c-b674-4fa6-a0d1-522bcda0aa10</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 06:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Moschip Technologies Ltd has informed the BSE that its Board of Directors will meet on 31st January 2026 to consider and approve the next Board Meeting. The agenda includes the review and approval of the un-audited financial results (Standalone &amp; Consolidated) for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. In accordance with the Companies Code of Conduct, the trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company will be closed from 1st January 2026 till 48 hours after the conclusion of the Board Meeting.</p><ul><li>Moschip Technologies Ltd scheduled a Board Meeting for 31st January 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the next Board Meeting</li><li>The agenda includes the review and approval of Q3 FY2025-26 financial results</li><li>The trading window for dealing in the company&apos;s securities will be closed from 1st January 2026 till 48 hours after the Board Meeting</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fca55041-c984-4c2f-b777-f54befff2c4a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Moschip Technologies Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RAYMONDLSL] Raymond Lifestyle Ltd Appoints New Chief Financial Officer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Raymond+Lifestyle+Ltd&title=Raymond+Lifestyle+Ltd+Appoints+New+Chief+Financial+Officer&newsId=38c61613-836a-423a-a451-6dc577ce56ae&token=MzhjNjE2MTMtODM2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">38c61613-836a-423a-a451-6dc577ce56ae</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 06:26:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Raymond Lifestyle Ltd has appointed Mr. Prasad Ellatch Chathuar as the Chief Financial Officer and Key Managerial Personnel of the Company, replacing Mr. Vishal Raigagla who served as the Interim CFO since October 29, 2025. Mr. Chathuar brings 28 years of experience in the Consumer Industry and has previously worked with Bajaj Electricals Limited, Voltas Limited, and Emami Paper Mills Limited. He is a Cost Accountant, Chartered Accountant, and has an Executive Certification Program in Finance from Harvard University.</p><ul><li>Raymond Lifestyle Ltd has appointed Mr. Prasad Ellatch Chathuar as the Chief Financial Officer and Key Managerial Personnel.</li><li>Mr. Vishal Raigagla, the Interim CFO, will cease to hold the position from January 27, 2026.</li><li>Mr. Chathuar has 28 years of experience in the Consumer Industry.</li><li>He has previously worked with Bajaj Electricals Limited, Voltas Limited, and Emami Paper Mills Limited.</li><li>Mr. Chathuar is a Cost Accountant, Chartered Accountant, and has an Executive Certification Program in Finance from Harvard University.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/207fc963-166c-448b-8223-f1e9d0048bf2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Raymond Lifestyle Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MEP] MEP Infrastructure Developers Ltd. holds 21st Meeting of Committee of Creditors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MEP+Infrastructure+Developers+Ltd&title=MEP+Infrastructure+Developers+Ltd.+holds+21st+Meeting+of+Committee+of+Creditors&newsId=9034eb58-07de-4f5d-95bd-d2bae66f38a9&token=OTAzNGViNTgtMDdk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9034eb58-07de-4f5d-95bd-d2bae66f38a9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 06:25:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pursuant to the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015 and in accordance with the requirements of sub-clause 16(g) of Clause A of Part A of Schedule III of the LODR, MEP Infrastructure Developers Ltd. held the 21st Meeting of Committee of Creditors on Friday, 23rd January, 2026. The meeting was held in accordance with the Hon’ble NCLT Order dated 28th March, 2024.</p><ul><li>The meeting was held in accordance with the Hon’ble NCLT Order dated 28th March, 2024</li><li>This is the 21st Meeting of Committee of Creditors for MEP Infrastructure Developers Ltd.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4ef6d205-9aa0-4081-ad3e-852af568693d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MEP Infrastructure Developers Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KRISHNACAP] Krishna Capital Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q3 FY2025-26 Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Krishna+Capital+and+Securities+Ltd&title=Krishna+Capital+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+FY2025-26+Financial+Results&newsId=5230cd15-7953-474f-8423-de7fb298b6a9&token=NTIzMGNkMTUtNzk1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5230cd15-7953-474f-8423-de7fb298b6a9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 06:25:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Krishna Capital and Securities Ltd has informed the BSE that their Board of Directors will meet on February 12, 2026, to consider and approve the Standalone and Consolidated Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, in accordance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulation, 2015.</p><ul><li>Krishna Capital has scheduled a Board Meeting on February 12, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the Q3 FY2025-26 financial results</li><li>The results are for the quarter ended December 31, 2025</li><li>The announcement is in accordance with SEBI&apos;s Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements Regulation, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0d8627c4-5484-4649-96af-9b2819f30196.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Krishna Capital and Securities Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHIPWAVES] Shipwaves Online Ltd Appoints Scrutinizers for Postal Ballot through E-voting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shipwaves+Online+Ltd&title=Shipwaves+Online+Ltd+Appoints+Scrutinizers+for+Postal+Ballot+through+E-voting&newsId=5ec3daef-296d-49ce-b057-83f271db4c1c&token=NWVjM2RhZWYtMjk2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ec3daef-296d-49ce-b057-83f271db4c1c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 06:24:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In a recent Board Meeting held on 27th January 2026, the Board of Directors of Shipwaves Online Ltd considered and approved the Notice of Postal Ballot and the calendar of events. The company has appointed Mr. Chethan Nayak K and Mrs. Ujala Rani of Chethan Nayak &amp; Associates, Practicing Company Secretaries, as scrutinizers for conducting the Postal Ballot through E-voting process. The meeting, which commenced at 11:15 a.m. and concluded at 11:30 a.m., will ensure a fair and transparent process.</p><ul><li>Board of Directors of Shipwaves Online Ltd approved the Notice of Postal Ballot and the calendar of events.</li><li>Mr. Chethan Nayak K and Mrs. Ujala Rani of Chethan Nayak &amp; Associates appointed as scrutinizers for the Postal Ballot through E-voting process.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a5f21c6a-f35d-49d5-8fde-53ef2f4acd43.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shipwaves Online Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RAYMONDLSL] Raymond Lifestyle Ltd. Approves Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Raymond+Lifestyle+Ltd&title=Raymond+Lifestyle+Ltd.+Approves+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=2e2931ae-a558-4b09-8b61-6ec6d51f1379&token=MmUyOTMxYWUtYTU1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e2931ae-a558-4b09-8b61-6ec6d51f1379</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 06:22:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Raymond Lifestyle Limited, a company based in Mumbai, India, has announced its unaudited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s Board of Directors approved the results in a meeting held on January 27, 2026. The results are in compliance with the Indian Accounting Standard 34 and other accounting principles generally accepted in India. The review was conducted by Walker Chandiok &amp; Co LLP, a registered chartered accountant firm.</p><ul><li>Raymond Lifestyle Ltd. has approved the unaudited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The results are in compliance with the Indian Accounting Standard 34 and other accounting principles generally accepted in India.</li><li>The review of the results was conducted by Walker Chandiok &amp; Co LLP, a registered chartered accountant firm.</li><li>The Board of Directors approved the results in a meeting held on January 27, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f2cbf283-859d-476d-972b-5400e935c4df.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Raymond Lifestyle Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DBEIL] Deepak Builders And Engineers India Ltd to Approve Un-audited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months of FY 2025-2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Deepak+Builders+and+Engineers+India+Ltd&title=Deepak+Builders+And+Engineers+India+Ltd+to+Approve+Un-audited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+of+FY+2025-2026&newsId=e468d1b1-9c75-4c5d-88cb-dd1da16740e6&token=ZTQ2OGQxYjEtOWM3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e468d1b1-9c75-4c5d-88cb-dd1da16740e6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 06:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Deepak Builders And Engineers India Ltd has informed BSE that the meeting of the Board of Directors of the Company is scheduled on 13/02/2026. The Board will inter alia consider and approve the un-audited financial results (Standalone) for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company will remain closed for all the Directors, Key Managerial Persons, Designated Persons of the Company and their immediate relatives as prescribed in the Schedule B of the Regulations from January 01, 2026 till 48 hours after the declaration of the un-audited financial results of the Company for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</p><ul><li>Deepak Builders And Engineers India Ltd to consider and approve un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company will remain closed from January 01, 2026 till 48 hours after the declaration of the un-audited financial results.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/89443ee3-1e50-496c-8e44-76c3d8306738.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Deepak Builders and Engineers India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[63MOONS] 63 Moons Technologies Ltd Launches Upgraded Trading Engine for Metropolitan Stock Exchange</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=63+Moons+Technologies+Ltd&title=63+Moons+Technologies+Ltd+Launches+Upgraded+Trading+Engine+for+Metropolitan+Stock+Exchange&newsId=6a96dd7f-23df-480e-aded-35af6852df71&token=NmE5NmRkN2YtMjNk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a96dd7f-23df-480e-aded-35af6852df71</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 06:19:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Pursuant to the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015, Metropolitan Stock Exchange of India Limited (MSE) is launching trading in the Equity Cash Segment with an upgraded trading engine provided by 63 moons technologies limited. This is similar to the technology services model that 63 moons has provided to MCX since 2003. The new engine is expected to enhance the trading experience and efficiency at MSE.</p><ul><li>63 Moons Technologies Ltd provides upgraded trading engine to Metropolitan Stock Exchange</li><li>The new engine is similar to the technology services model provided to MCX since 2003</li><li>Launch of the new engine is expected to improve trading experience and efficiency at MSE</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c21dc80b-c80a-47c0-aa23-9d54afc2c856.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: 63 Moons Technologies Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MEDICO] Medico Remedies Secures INR 37 Crores Government Supply Order from Uttar Pradesh Medical Supplies Corporation Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Medico+Remedies+Ltd&title=Medico+Remedies+Secures+INR+37+Crores+Government+Supply+Order+from+Uttar+Pradesh+Medical+Supplies+Corporation+Limited&newsId=48eb1731-9729-48e4-a564-f2cd7ed28cde&token=NDhlYjE3MzEtOTcy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48eb1731-9729-48e4-a564-f2cd7ed28cde</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 06:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Medico Remedies Limited has announced that it has secured a government supply order worth INR 37,17,62,439/- (Rupees Thirty Seven Crores Seventeen Lakhs Sixty Two Thousand Four Hundred Thirty Nine) from Uttar Pradesh Medical Supplies Corporation Limited. The order is for the supply of multiple drugs to the corporation. The supply period will last till 31/10/2026. The order has been awarded by a domestic entity, and the company will supply the drugs from its factory located at 7, 8 &amp; 9, Dewan &amp; Sons Udyog Nagar, Lokmanya Nagar, Palghar (W), Dist. Palghar - 401 404, Maharashtra.</p><ul><li>Medico Remedies secures government supply order worth INR 37 Crores</li><li>Order for the supply of multiple drugs to Uttar Pradesh Medical Supplies Corporation Limited</li><li>Supply period to last till 31/10/2026</li><li>Order awarded by a domestic entity</li><li>Supply from factory located at Palghar, Maharashtra</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d147e001-0a55-404e-a531-2f095ed25d1f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Medico Remedies Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NATPLAS] National Plastic Industries Ltd Re-lodges Share Transfer Requests During Special Window Period in November 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NATIONAL+PLASTIC+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=National+Plastic+Industries+Ltd+Re-lodges+Share+Transfer+Requests+During+Special+Window+Period+in+November+2025&newsId=a7ef9461-cfc5-4ae4-aed0-2b6dd0f4682d&token=YTdlZjk0NjEtY2Zj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a7ef9461-cfc5-4ae4-aed0-2b6dd0f4682d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 06:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>National Plastic Industries Ltd has provided a status report on the re-lodgment of physical share transfer requests received and processed during the special window period in November 2025, as per the SEBI Circular dated July 2, 2025. The report indicates that there were no requests, processing, approvals, or rejections in November 2025. The data is sourced from the Company&apos;s RTA.</p><ul><li>National Plastic Industries Ltd shares transfer requests re-lodged during the special window period in November 2025</li><li>No share transfer requests, processing, approvals, or rejections found in November 2025</li><li>Report based on information from the Company&apos;s RTA</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/baa5b123-5b46-41e9-9768-6c3c2351067f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NATIONAL PLASTIC INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>