<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:55:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[BCONCEPTS] Brand Concepts Limited Reports No Deviation in Utilization of Funds Raised Through Warrants Convertible into Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Brand+Concepts+Ltd&title=Brand+Concepts+Limited+Reports+No+Deviation+in+Utilization+of+Funds+Raised+Through+Warrants+Convertible+into+Equity+Shares&newsId=4978f7f9-a7ab-4361-9511-0b93079f785d&token=NDk3OGY3ZjktYTdh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4978f7f9-a7ab-4361-9511-0b93079f785d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:54:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Brand Concepts Limited has informed the exchange about the statement of deviation and variation with respect to funds raised through warrants convertible into equity shares. The company has confirmed no deviation or variation in the utilization of proceeds raised through issuance of warrants to the promoter group of the company on a preferential basis for the quarter ended 31st December 2025.</p><ul><li>Brand Concepts Limited raised 4,99,89,500 Rs. through preferential issue of convertible warrants.</li><li>The company has confirmed no deviation or variation in the utilization of funds for the quarter ended 31st December 2025.</li><li>The funds were raised for capital expansion, manufacturing facility, brand building, and acquiring new brands.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/abd567bd-8cb1-41b6-ab99-3bf82bfe8f9a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Brand Concepts Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CRESSAN] Cressanda Railway Solutions Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CRESSANDA+SOLUTIONS+LTD.&title=Cressanda+Railway+Solutions+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=ad686ba8-31e5-4655-9094-8fa8c0956fc3&token=YWQ2ODZiYTgtMzFl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad686ba8-31e5-4655-9094-8fa8c0956fc3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:54:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cressanda Railway Solutions Ltd has reported its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The total income from operations for the quarter is 142.61 lakhs, while the net profit for the period before tax, after exceptional and/or extraordinary items, is -443.90 lakhs. The total comprehensive income for the period is -443.90 lakhs. The equity share capital is 4227.35 lakhs. The earnings per share for continuing and discontinued operations is not annualised for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, and is -1.00 for both basic and diluted.</p><ul><li>Cressanda Railway Solutions Ltd has reported its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The total income from operations for the quarter is 142.61 lakhs.</li><li>The net profit for the period before tax, after exceptional and/or extraordinary items, is -443.90 lakhs.</li><li>The total comprehensive income for the period is -443.90 lakhs.</li><li>The equity share capital is 4227.35 lakhs.</li><li>The earnings per share for continuing and discontinued operations is not annualised for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, and is -1.00 for both basic and diluted.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/12da4573-0a85-474d-8a79-c0aa706faff8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CRESSANDA SOLUTIONS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAGRSOY-B] Signature Green Corporation Ltd Approves Q3 &amp; Nine Months Ended Dec 2025 Financial Results in Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SAGAR+SOYA+PRODUCTS+LTD.&title=Signature+Green+Corporation+Ltd+Approves+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Ended+Dec+2025+Financial+Results+in+Board+Meeting&newsId=10004cf6-9418-44be-931c-3db5d424c905&token=MTAwMDRjZjYtOTQx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">10004cf6-9418-44be-931c-3db5d424c905</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Signature Green Corporation Ltd, formerly known as Sagar Soya Products Limited, held a Board Meeting on 13th February 2026. The Board approved the un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company has also acquired 60.19% equity shares of Arvind Foods Limited, making it a subsidiary. The company&apos;s operation consists of only one segment, and there are no outstanding defaults on loans and debt securities.</p><ul><li>Signature Green Corporation Ltd approved the un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025.</li><li>The company has acquired 60.19% equity shares of Arvind Foods Limited, making it a subsidiary.</li><li>Arvind Foods Limited&apos;s financial results have been consolidated to the extent of the Company’s shareholding.</li><li>The company&apos;s operation consists of only one segment.</li><li>There are no outstanding defaults on loans and debt securities.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5d5350fc-892f-4587-9b69-180439e8501f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SAGAR SOYA PRODUCTS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADIEXRE] Trustedge Capital Ltd Confirms No Deviation in Use of Rights Issue Proceeds</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADINATH+EXIM+RESOURCES+LTD.&title=Trustedge+Capital+Ltd+Confirms+No+Deviation+in+Use+of+Rights+Issue+Proceeds&newsId=b5e2790b-4a63-4a19-98a0-78c8e5b88add&token=YjVlMjc5MGItNGE2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5e2790b-4a63-4a19-98a0-78c8e5b88add</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:52:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Trustedge Capital Ltd, formerly known as Adinath Exim Resources Limited, has confirmed in a statement that there was no deviation or variation in the use of proceeds of funds raised through Rights Issue of Equity Shares for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025. The company raised Rs. 2699.54 lakhs and received the same amount on application. A statement of deviation or variation, if any, for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, is enclosed in the prescribed format as Annexure - A. The information is also available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Trustedge Capital Ltd confirms no deviation in use of Rights Issue proceeds</li><li>Raised Rs. 2699.54 lakhs through Rights Issue of Equity Shares</li><li>Received the same amount on application</li><li>Statement of deviation or variation available on the company&apos;s website</li><li>Formerly known as Adinath Exim Resources Limited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8c2450e9-89de-42b7-a4df-f71e4d1e4947.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADINATH EXIM RESOURCES LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BRISK] Brisk Technovision Declares Interim Dividend of ₹ 1.40 Per Share</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Brisk+Technovision+Ltd&title=Brisk+Technovision+Declares+Interim+Dividend+of+%E2%82%B9+1.40+Per+Share&newsId=57a20e43-d4e8-4c08-bfd2-57039249e5bc&token=NTdhMjBlNDMtZDRl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57a20e43-d4e8-4c08-bfd2-57039249e5bc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Brisk Technovision Ltd has declared an interim dividend of ₹ 1.40 per equity share of ₹ 10 each, leading to a total outflow of ₹ 28,00,000. The record date for the purpose of declaration and payment of Interim Dividend is February 19, 2026. The Board Meeting of the Company commenced on 10:30 am (IST) and concluded at 11:44 am (IST).</p><ul><li>Brisk Technovision Ltd declares an interim dividend of ₹ 1.40 per equity share</li><li>Total outflow of ₹ 28,00,000 for the dividend</li><li>Record date for dividend payment is February 19, 2026</li><li>Board Meeting commenced at 10:30 am (IST) and concluded at 11:44 am (IST)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6fa9b0fe-4352-4e57-a8d0-eca63cac4bd6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Brisk Technovision Ltd | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LOOKS] Looks Health Services Ltd. Board Meeting Approves Reclassifications, Office Shift, and Postal Ballot</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Looks+Health+Services+Limited&title=Looks+Health+Services+Ltd.+Board+Meeting+Approves+Reclassifications%2C+Office+Shift%2C+and+Postal+Ballot&newsId=d6ac822d-d399-4451-b7cc-ed07e9c07c54&token=ZDZhYzgyMmQtZDM5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6ac822d-d399-4451-b7cc-ed07e9c07c54</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:49:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In a Board Meeting held on February 13, 2026, Looks Health Services Ltd. approved several key decisions. The meeting, which started at 10.00 AM and concluded at 11.45 AM, saw the Board consider and approve a Postal Ballot through remote e-voting from February 14, 2026, to March 15, 2026. The Ballot includes the reclassification of Mr. Pritesh Doshi and Maxgainz Finserve Private Limited from &apos;Promoter and Promoter Group&apos; to &apos;Public&apos; category. The Board also approved the shifting of the company&apos;s Registered Office from Mumbai, Maharashtra to Ahmedabad, Gujarat, subject to necessary approvals. VKM &amp; Associates were appointed as Scrutinizers for the Postal Ballot process.</p><ul><li>Approval of Postal Ballot through remote e-voting from February 14, 2026, to March 15, 2026</li><li>Reclassification of Mr. Pritesh Doshi from &apos;Promoter and Promoter Group&apos; to &apos;Public&apos; category</li><li>Reclassification of Maxgainz Finserve Private Limited from &apos;Promoter and Promoter Group&apos; to &apos;Public&apos; category</li><li>Proposed shifting of the company&apos;s Registered Office from Mumbai, Maharashtra to Ahmedabad, Gujarat</li><li>Appointment of VKM &amp; Associates as Scrutinizers for the Postal Ballot process</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/31d139f8-9c92-4a7b-bebf-5975edc44d39.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Looks Health Services Limited | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[THOMASCOOK] Sterling Launches Sterling Saryu Ayodhya, Its Second Hotel in the Holy City</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=THOMAS+COOK+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Sterling+Launches+Sterling+Saryu+Ayodhya%2C+Its+Second+Hotel+in+the+Holy+City&newsId=bdb1e168-2b37-4dff-bdd7-65ff716b2177&token=YmRiMWUxNjgtMmIz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bdb1e168-2b37-4dff-bdd7-65ff716b2177</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Sterling Holiday Resorts, a subsidiary of Thomas Cook (India) Limited, has announced the opening of Sterling Saryu Ayodhya, its second resort in Ayodhya. The launch aligns with Sterling&apos;s strategy to build high-intent travel circuits in India&apos;s heritage and pilgrimage destinations. The new resort offers comfortable accommodations, easy access to key temples and ghats, and a restful retreat for faith-led journeys. Located near key regional hubs, Sterling Saryu Ayodhya also serves as a convenient base for extended heritage journeys across North India.</p><ul><li>Sterling Holiday Resorts launches Sterling Saryu Ayodhya, its second resort in Ayodhya.</li><li>The launch aligns with Sterling&apos;s strategy to build high-intent travel circuits in India&apos;s heritage and pilgrimage destinations.</li><li>The resort offers comfortable accommodations, easy access to key temples and ghats, and a restful retreat for faith-led journeys.</li><li>Sterling Saryu Ayodhya is located near key regional hubs, making it a convenient base for extended heritage journeys across North India.</li><li>The new resort is part of Sterling&apos;s commitment to serve travellers with comfort, calm, and reliability in spiritual destinations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f7ea5403-3259-49a3-bd77-4102b7191d0c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: THOMAS COOK (INDIA) LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHISHIND] Shish Industries Submits Revised Financial Results with UDIN for Q4 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shish+Industries+Ltd&title=Shish+Industries+Submits+Revised+Financial+Results+with+UDIN+for+Q4+2025&newsId=8beb9927-dfbb-45d5-a129-8fbdce5d5a67&token=OGJlYjk5MjctZGZi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8beb9927-dfbb-45d5-a129-8fbdce5d5a67</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:48:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shish Industries Ltd. has resubmitted the financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025, including the Consolidated Limited Review Report and Statement of Deviation with UDIN. The company had previously submitted these documents without UDIN due to technical issues with the ICAI UDIN portal. The financial results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Shish Industries resubmits Q4 2025 financial results with UDIN</li><li>Previously submitted documents did not include UDIN due to technical issues</li><li>Financial results reviewed by Audit Committee and approved by Board of Directors</li><li>UDIN now included in Consolidated Limited Review Report and Statement of Deviation</li><li>Submission part of company&apos;s commitment to transparency and regulatory compliance</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/29e8acd3-2abd-4f14-84c7-c952da4c0a97.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shish Industries Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TRABI] Transgene Biotek Ltd Approves Unaudited Consolidated &amp; Stand-alone Financial Results for Q3 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TRANSGENE+BIOTEK+LTD.&title=Transgene+Biotek+Ltd+Approves+Unaudited+Consolidated+%26+Stand-alone+Financial+Results+for+Q3+2025&newsId=e01d4c0a-648e-4e88-a77a-9467e5c476ed&token=ZTAxZDRjMGEtNjQ4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e01d4c0a-648e-4e88-a77a-9467e5c476ed</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Transgene Biotek Ltd has approved the unaudited Consolidated &amp; Stand-alone Financial Results for the quarter ended 31.12.2025. The company&apos;s financial results have been prepared in accordance with the Indian Accounting Standards (IND-AS) as per Companies (Indian Accounting Standards) Rules, 2015. The Limited Review Report on the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results of the Company for the quarter ended 31.12.2025 has also been approved.</p><ul><li>Transgene Biotek Ltd has approved the unaudited Consolidated &amp; Stand-alone Financial Results for Q3 2025.</li><li>The financial results have been prepared in accordance with the Indian Accounting Standards (IND-AS) as per Companies (Indian Accounting Standards) Rules, 2015.</li><li>Limited Review Report on the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results of the Company for the quarter ended 31.12.2025 has been approved.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8ede8d89-e990-417d-8045-7fab89ef74f0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TRANSGENE BIOTEK LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BCONCEPTS] Brand Concepts Ltd. Announces Q3 &amp; Nine Months Results for Dec 2025 with Profit of Rs. 1,242.19 Lakhs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Brand+Concepts+Ltd&title=Brand+Concepts+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Results+for+Dec+2025+with+Profit+of+Rs.+1%2C242.19+Lakhs&newsId=8c8679cf-47be-46ec-954c-820d73c5e2d9&token=OGM4Njc5Y2YtNDdi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c8679cf-47be-46ec-954c-820d73c5e2d9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:43:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Brand Concepts Ltd. has announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December 2025. The company reported a net profit of Rs. 1,242.19 lakhs for the nine-month period. The Board of Directors has approved these results in compliance with the relevant regulations. The company operates in the &apos;Travel Gear and related accessories&apos; segment and has recently issued warrants to promoters. A change in depreciation method and the impact of new labour codes have been accounted for in the financial results.</p><ul><li>Net profit of Rs. 1,242.19 lakhs for the nine months ended on 31st December 2025.</li><li>Unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results approved by the Board of Directors.</li><li>Issuance of warrants to promoters and operation in the &apos;Travel Gear and related accessories&apos; segment.</li><li>Change in depreciation method from Written Down Value (WDV) to Straight Line Method (SLM).</li><li>Accounting for incremental liability of Rs. 76.28 lakhs for employee benefits as per the New Labour Codes.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/85213614-a9f7-4f68-a508-2f4d4b0e858a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Brand Concepts Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>