<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:45:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SUDEEPPHRM] Sudeep Pharma&apos;s Vice President of Sales &amp; Supply Chain, John Garcia, Resigns</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sudeep+Pharma+Ltd&title=Sudeep+Pharma%27s+Vice+President+of+Sales+%26+Supply+Chain%2C+John+Garcia%2C+Resigns&newsId=297ed097-273f-4e18-89f8-ff9743b94ec0&token=Mjk3ZWQwOTctMjcz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">297ed097-273f-4e18-89f8-ff9743b94ec0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:42:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Auditor</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sudeep Pharma Ltd. has announced the resignation of Mr. John Garcia, Vice President of Sales &amp; Supply Chain at Sudeep Pharma USA Inc. Mr. Garcia has tendered his resignation with effect from the close of business hours on 6th February 2026. The resignation is due to his decision to pursue new challenges and opportunities.</p><ul><li>John Garcia, Vice President of Sales &amp; Supply Chain at Sudeep Pharma USA Inc, has resigned.</li><li>Mr. Garcia&apos;s last day will be 6th February 2026.</li><li>His decision to resign is to pursue new challenges and opportunities.</li><li>The company has made the necessary disclosures as required by the SEBI regulations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/53d896a6-6932-4e7a-a919-5746364f8d94.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sudeep Pharma Ltd | Category: Auditor</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CNCRD] Concord Control Systems Secures ₹ 2185.09 Crore KAVACH 4.0 Order from Indian Railways</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Concord+Control+Systems+Ltd&title=Concord+Control+Systems+Secures+%E2%82%B9+2185.09+Crore+KAVACH+4.0+Order+from+Indian+Railways&newsId=ce6062ab-1372-4e8d-935b-bc069f04e18c&token=Y2U2MDYyYWItMTM3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce6062ab-1372-4e8d-935b-bc069f04e18c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:37:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Concord Control Systems Limited, a leading manufacturer of embedded electronic systems and critical electronic solutions company, has secured a major order worth ₹ 2185.09 crore for the supply, installation, testing, and commissioning of KAVACH 4.0, an indigenous Automatic Train Protection (ATP) system. The order, awarded through Progota India Private Limited, an associate company of Concord Control Systems, is scheduled to be executed within the next 12 months. KAVACH 4.0 is designed to enhance rail safety by preventing collisions, over-speeding, and signal violations, integrating advanced digital technologies to strengthen operational efficiency and passenger safety across the railway network.</p><ul><li>Concord Control Systems secures ₹ 2185.09 crore order for KAVACH 4.0 from Indian Railways.</li><li>Order to be executed within the next 12 months through Progota India Private Limited.</li><li>KAVACH 4.0 is an indigenous Automatic Train Protection (ATP) system designed to enhance rail safety.</li><li>Advanced digital technologies integrated to strengthen operational efficiency and passenger safety.</li><li>Order represents a major step towards building a safer, more reliable rail network.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a9b0f53a-9e92-4e56-ba9f-b0bb51758191.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Concord Control Systems Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PRECAM] Precision Camshafts Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results on Feb 11, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Precision+Camshafts+Ltd&title=Precision+Camshafts+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+on+Feb+11%2C+2026&newsId=32391f8f-e425-4d5d-a99a-e5dc488cf0a6&token=MzIzOTFmOGYtZTQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32391f8f-e425-4d5d-a99a-e5dc488cf0a6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:33:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Precision Camshafts Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 11, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2026. The trading window for the company&apos;s designated persons and their immediate relatives has been closed from January 01, 2026, and will reopen 48 hours after the announcement of financial results. This information has been submitted to stock exchanges and posted on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Precision Camshafts Ltd to consider and approve Q3 and nine months results on Feb 11, 2026</li><li>Trading window closed for designated persons and their immediate relatives from Jan 01, 2026</li><li>Trading window to reopen 48 hours after financial results announcement</li><li>Information submitted to stock exchanges and posted on company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c76d971e-e8cd-4775-b456-55e1b3d11bb1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Precision Camshafts Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CNCRD] Concord Control Systems Ltd Bags Rs. 185.09 Crores Order of KAVACH 4.0 from Indian Railways</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Concord+Control+Systems+Ltd&title=Concord+Control+Systems+Ltd+Bags+Rs.+185.09+Crores+Order+of+KAVACH+4.0+from+Indian+Railways&newsId=8f765ae8-f304-4695-bca0-1ef48c56e94e&token=OGY3NjVhZTgtZjMw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f765ae8-f304-4695-bca0-1ef48c56e94e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Concord Control Systems Limited has been awarded an order by Indian Railways for the supply, installation, testing and commissioning of On-board KAVACH 4.0 Loco equipment through its associate company, Progota India Private Limited. The order is worth Rs. 185.09 Crores and needs to be executed within 12 months.</p><ul><li>Concord Control Systems Ltd has been awarded an order by Indian Railways for KAVACH 4.0</li><li>The order is worth Rs. 185.09 Crores</li><li>The order involves supply, installation, testing and commissioning of On-board KAVACH 4.0 Loco equipment</li><li>The order has been awarded to Concord Control Systems Ltd through its associate company, Progota India Private Limited</li><li>The order needs to be executed within 12 months</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/582dae81-1c55-42c1-a6f5-1cbd3da51868.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Concord Control Systems Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GRMOVER] GRM Overseas Reports Strong Q3FY26 Financial Results with 28.9% YoY Growth in Total Revenue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GRM+OVERSEAS+LTD.&title=GRM+Overseas+Reports+Strong+Q3FY26+Financial+Results+with+28.9%25+YoY+Growth+in+Total+Revenue&newsId=7f3ab4a8-0bc3-4fdd-8264-8cc82bbbbc1b&token=N2YzYWI0YTgtMGJj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7f3ab4a8-0bc3-4fdd-8264-8cc82bbbbc1b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:25:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>GRM Overseas Limited announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a 28.9% YoY growth in total revenue, reaching Rs. 492.6 Crores in Q3FY26. EBITDA grew by 34.1% YoY to Rs. 31.3 Crores, and PAT surged by 42.8% YoY to Rs. 19.3 Crores in Q3FY26. The domestic branded business crossed Rs. 200 Crores sales in a single quarter for the first time, registering a growth of 26% YoY. GRM Overseas completed a bonus issue in the ratio of 2:1, reflecting the Board&apos;s confidence in the company&apos;s long-term growth prospects.</p><ul><li>GRM Overseas reported a 28.9% YoY growth in total revenue in Q3FY26.</li><li>EBITDA grew by 34.1% YoY in Q3FY26.</li><li>PAT surged by 42.8% YoY in Q3FY26.</li><li>Domestic branded business crossed Rs. 200 Crores sales in a single quarter for the first time.</li><li>Company completed a bonus issue in the ratio of 2:1.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/773948c2-69ee-4788-bd38-444cbdc1652f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GRM OVERSEAS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[YASHO] Yasho Industries Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on February 12, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Yasho+Industries+Ltd&title=Yasho+Industries+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+February+12%2C+2026&newsId=597acb07-313b-4800-acc8-a9852299d1b0&token=NTk3YWNiMDctMzEz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">597acb07-313b-4800-acc8-a9852299d1b0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Yasho Industries Ltd has announced a Board of Directors meeting on February 12, 2026. The agenda includes the consideration and approval of standalone and consolidated unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in shares of the company will be closed from January 01, 2026, and will open after 48 hours of the declaration of financial results.</p><ul><li>Yasho Industries Ltd to approve Q3 and nine months financial results on February 12, 2026</li><li>Trading window for dealing in shares of the company to be closed from January 01, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d7c55c40-c879-4716-85ac-e9d94154e501.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Yasho Industries Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ABDL] ABD Maestro Debuts with Exclusive 34-Year-Old Single Malt &apos;The Collective&apos; Priced at 11 Lakhs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Allied+Blenders+and+Distillers+Ltd&title=ABD+Maestro+Debuts+with+Exclusive+34-Year-Old+Single+Malt+%27The+Collective%27+Priced+at+11+Lakhs&newsId=c7f673f9-1bca-4bbe-8738-ddef05778277&token=YzdmNjczZjktMWJj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7f673f9-1bca-4bbe-8738-ddef05778277</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 04:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>ABD Maestro Pvt. Ltd., a subsidiary of Allied Blenders &amp; Distillers, announced the debut of its ultra-grand &apos;The Collective&apos; Limited Editions in India, starting with a 34-year-old Speyside Single Malt. Distilled at Macallan Distillery in 1991, this rare expression is priced at 11 Lakhs for 700ML and is available for pre-orders now. The Collective promises to present the world’s most extraordinary spirits to the knowledgeable and discerning, starting with India.</p><ul><li>ABD Maestro debuts with &apos;The Collective&apos; Limited Editions, starting with a 34-year-old Speyside Single Malt.</li><li>Distilled at Macallan Distillery in 1991, this rare expression is priced at 11 Lakhs for 700ML.</li><li>The Collective promises to present the world’s most extraordinary spirits to the knowledgeable and discerning, starting with India.</li><li>Each release speaks as much to the collector or connoisseur and those who understand exclusivity as value in itself.</li><li>Available for pre-orders now.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9a16e6ea-9146-4135-bec5-708c7796ab44.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Allied Blenders and Distillers Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ACE] Action Construction Equipment Ltd Releases Q3FY26 Conference Call Audio Clip</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ACTION+CONSTRUCTION+EQUIPMENT+LTD.&title=Action+Construction+Equipment+Ltd+Releases+Q3FY26+Conference+Call+Audio+Clip&newsId=8447a361-3413-4d1b-aa27-8d81ba71d81d&token=ODQ0N2EzNjEtMzQx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8447a361-3413-4d1b-aa27-8d81ba71d81d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 03:58:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Action Construction Equipment Ltd has released the audio clip for its Q3FY-2026 Conference call meeting. The meeting was held on February 04, 2026, and the audio clip is now available for access. This disclosure is in accordance with Regulation 30 and 46 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Action Construction Equipment Ltd has released the audio clip for its Q3FY-2026 Conference call meeting.</li><li>The meeting was held on February 04, 2026.</li><li>The audio clip is now available for access.</li><li>Disclosure is in accordance with Regulation 30 and 46 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/12febb3e-ef33-4267-a166-fa9bef49a7ee.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ACTION CONSTRUCTION EQUIPMENT LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MITSU] Mitsu Chem Plast Limited Becomes Global Supplier to Arjohuntleigh Polska (Poland)</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Mitsu+Chem+Plast+Ltd&title=Mitsu+Chem+Plast+Limited+Becomes+Global+Supplier+to+Arjohuntleigh+Polska+%28Poland%29&newsId=3f77d410-bd7f-4441-9d94-e61f044fe00e&token=M2Y3N2Q0MTAtYmQ3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3f77d410-bd7f-4441-9d94-e61f044fe00e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 03:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Mitsu Chem Plast Limited, a leading Indian polymer solutions company, has entered into a Global Supplier Agreement with Arjohuntleigh Polska Sp. z 0.0., following a year-long validation Process and approvals. This agreement marks Mitsu Chem Plast Limited’s onboarding as a global supplier to the Arjo Group, one of the world’s Top 5 medical equipment companies. The partnership strengthens Mitsu’s presence in the global Furniture parts supply chain and enhances its brand visibility across international markets. It also creates long-term growth opportunities by expanding the Company’s hospital furniture parts portfolio and supporting export-led business growth.</p><ul><li>Mitsu Chem Plast Limited has become a Global Supplier to Arjohuntleigh Polska Sp. z 0.0., a top 5 medical equipment company.</li><li>The agreement reflects Mitsu’s strong manufacturing capabilities, professional approach, consistent quality, and compliance with international standards.</li><li>Mitsu will supply hospital furniture parts and other related plastic accessories to Arjohuntleigh Polska.</li><li>The partnership strengthens Mitsu’s presence in the global Furniture parts supply chain and enhances its brand visibility across international markets.</li><li>The engagement comes at a time of strengthening India-European Union trade relations, supported by the recently concluded India-EU trade agreement.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a07019a1-816f-426d-b3e7-ca74791dc10c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Mitsu Chem Plast Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STAR] Strides Pharma Inc receives USFDA closure report (EIR) for its formulations facility at Chestnut Ridge, New York</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Strides+Pharma+Science+Ltd&title=Strides+Pharma+Inc+receives+USFDA+closure+report+%28EIR%29+for+its+formulations+facility+at+Chestnut+Ridge%2C+New+York&newsId=fd039eb1-0e88-4b16-a5af-71d1b30fd60d&token=ZmQwMzllYjEtMGU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd039eb1-0e88-4b16-a5af-71d1b30fd60d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 03:26:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>USFDA</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Strides Pharma Science Limited announced that Strides Pharma Inc. (SPI), a step-down wholly owned subsidiary of the Company in the USA, has received the USFDA Inspection Closure Report (Establishment Inspection Report — EIR) for its Formulations Facility located at Chestnut Ridge, New York, USA. The Facility was inspected by the USFDA from December 17, 2025 to December 23, 2025 and the inspection covered current Good Manufacturing Practices (CGMP) and included a pre-approval inspection for Drug-Device Combination capabilities, covering the Company’s recent filing in Nasal Sprays domain. The USFDA has classified the inspection outcome as VAI (Voluntary Action Indicated). The Chestnut Ridge facility caters to the U.S. market and manufactures Liquids, Gels, Hormones, Modified Release products and Controlled Substances, supporting several current and future products for the U.S. market. The successful closure of this inspection including Device Combinations further strengthens the Company’s U.S. business and near term growth prospects.</p><ul><li>Strides Pharma Inc. (SPI) has received the USFDA Inspection Closure Report (Establishment Inspection Report — EIR) for its Formulations Facility located at Chestnut Ridge, New York, USA.</li><li>The inspection covered current Good Manufacturing Practices (CGMP) and included a pre-approval inspection for Drug-Device Combination capabilities.</li><li>The USFDA has classified the inspection outcome as VAI (Voluntary Action Indicated).</li><li>The Chestnut Ridge facility caters to the U.S. market and manufactures Liquids, Gels, Hormones, Modified Release products and Controlled Substances.</li><li>The successful closure of this inspection including Device Combinations further strengthens the Company’s U.S. business and near term growth prospects.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/258bbc32-e404-4002-894b-82ba273a4c59.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Strides Pharma Science Ltd | Category: USFDA</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>