<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 09:30:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SURAJEST] Suraj Estate Developers Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results on Jan 28, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Suraj+Estate+Developers+Ltd&title=Suraj+Estate+Developers+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+on+Jan+28%2C+2026&newsId=b92799dd-d557-475c-87c8-e35ef4feb4f2&token=YjkyNzk5ZGQtZDU1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b92799dd-d557-475c-87c8-e35ef4feb4f2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 09:29:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Suraj Estate Developers Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 28, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company has also complied with the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, and its Code of Conduct for Regulating, Monitoring and Reporting of Trading by Designated Person(s). The trading window for all Designated Persons, including insiders, was closed from January 1, 2026, and will remain closed till 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results.</p><ul><li>Suraj Estate Developers Ltd to consider and approve Q3 and nine months results on January 28, 2026</li><li>Trading window closed for Designated Persons from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4a6297fc-3f6e-4ede-9ade-0336f317598c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Suraj Estate Developers Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DCMSHRIRAM] DCM Shriram Ltd Reports Zero Re-lodgement Requests for Physical Shares in December 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DCM+Shriram+Limited&title=DCM+Shriram+Ltd+Reports+Zero+Re-lodgement+Requests+for+Physical+Shares+in+December+2025&newsId=3864ebbc-6e25-491f-b397-5d585e4fda5d&token=Mzg2NGViYmMtNmUy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3864ebbc-6e25-491f-b397-5d585e4fda5d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 09:27:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>DCM Shriram Ltd, in accordance with SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97, has released a report from MCS Share Transfer Agent Limited detailing the re-lodgement of transfer requests for physical shares from December 7, 2025, to December 31, 2025. The report indicates that there were no requests received, processed, approved, or rejected during this period.</p><ul><li>DCM Shriram Ltd reports zero re-lodgement requests for physical shares in December 2025.</li><li>The report was provided by MCS Share Transfer Agent Limited.</li><li>The data covers the period from December 7, 2025, to December 31, 2025.</li><li>No requests were received, processed, approved, or rejected during this time.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f510a4c3-4d06-4e82-b02a-75a5bc773f79.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DCM Shriram Limited | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[OSCARGLO] Oscar Global Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on 28th January, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=OSCAR+GLOBAL+LTD.&title=Oscar+Global+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+28th+January%2C+2026&newsId=5d42ce07-543d-4dc7-bcbe-2b493e888a42&token=NWQ0MmNlMDctNTQz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d42ce07-543d-4dc7-bcbe-2b493e888a42</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 09:26:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Oscar Global Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 28th January, 2026 to consider and approve the unaudited Financial Results of the Company for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. In line with the Company’s Code of Conduct for Regulating, Monitoring and Reporting of Trading by Insiders, the trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company will be closed from the close of business hours of 31st January, 2026 and will reopen on 1st February, 2026.</p><ul><li>Oscar Global Ltd to consider and approve unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December, 2025</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company to be closed from the close of business hours of 31st January, 2026 to 1st February, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cd3cfd02-65c7-41f9-8f7a-3132282a69b7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: OSCAR GLOBAL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MUKATPIP] Mukat Pipes Limited: No Price Sensitive Information, Share Price Movement Market Driven</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MUKAT+PIPES+LTD.-%24&title=Mukat+Pipes+Limited%3A+No+Price+Sensitive+Information%2C+Share+Price+Movement+Market+Driven&newsId=b6395ce1-c542-4413-9125-6afa0e787456&token=YjYzOTVjZTEtYzU0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6395ce1-c542-4413-9125-6afa0e787456</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 09:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mukat Pipes Limited has clarified that there is no undisclosed or price sensitive information that could affect the price or volume behavior of its shares. The company is in compliance with SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015 and has been promptly informing the Stock Exchange about all events and information that could impact its operation or performance. The movement in the company&apos;s share price is therefore purely market driven and not influenced by any internal factors.</p><ul><li>Mukat Pipes Limited has no undisclosed or price sensitive information</li><li>The company is in compliance with SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015</li><li>The movement in the company&apos;s share price is market driven</li><li>The company promptly informs the Stock Exchange about all material events/information/actions</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2881166d-84f4-4265-9261-b323e40c2dc8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MUKAT PIPES LTD.-$ | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AVIVA] Aviva Industries Ltd to Approve Un-audited Financial Results on Jan 28, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AVIVA+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Aviva+Industries+Ltd+to+Approve+Un-audited+Financial+Results+on+Jan+28%2C+2026&newsId=bebf90f9-7f9b-4c7a-9a4c-637ce44293a4&token=YmViZjkwZjktN2Y5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bebf90f9-7f9b-4c7a-9a4c-637ce44293a4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 09:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Aviva Industries Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 28, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the period ending December 31, 2025. The meeting will be held in compliance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Aviva Industries Ltd to hold a Board Meeting on January 28, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve un-audited financial results for the period ending December 31, 2025</li><li>The meeting is held in compliance with Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7f6b99b7-c618-4cc6-a945-a7ab2962a1bb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AVIVA INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PATELRMART] Patel Retail Ltd Secures Export Order Worth 25 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Patel+Retail+Ltd&title=Patel+Retail+Ltd+Secures+Export+Order+Worth+25+Crores&newsId=e81fc2e6-ae92-4175-8e0f-8102f9dd229f&token=ZTgxZmMyZTYtYWU5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e81fc2e6-ae92-4175-8e0f-8102f9dd229f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 09:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Patel Retail Limited has announced that it has bagged an export order worth 25 Crores. The order has been awarded by various clients including P &amp; B (Foods) Limited, Shahi Foods Spices LLC from UK, Italy, UAE, and Saudi Arabia. The order is for various products of Spices &amp; FMCG and is to be executed within 45 days. The broad consideration for the order is 25 Crores.</p><ul><li>Patel Retail Ltd has secured an export order worth 25 Crores</li><li>The order has been awarded by various clients including P &amp; B (Foods) Limited, Shahi Foods Spices LLC from UK, Italy, UAE, and Saudi Arabia</li><li>The order is for various products of Spices &amp; FMCG</li><li>The order is to be executed within 45 days</li><li>The broad consideration for the order is 25 Crores</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/57664a50-86cf-4df0-a934-35621876506c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Patel Retail Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GTIL] Gabion Technologies India Receives Product Approval for Mumbai-Ahmedabad High Speed Rail Project</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Gabion+Technologies+India+Ltd&title=Gabion+Technologies+India+Receives+Product+Approval+for+Mumbai-Ahmedabad+High+Speed+Rail+Project&newsId=eef5439d-e8c8-4321-baa5-4a639346c25c&token=ZWVmNTQzOWQtZThj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eef5439d-e8c8-4321-baa5-4a639346c25c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 09:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Gabion Technologies India Limited has received material approval for its product - Mechanically Woven, Double-Twisted, Hexagonal Wire Mesh for use in the Mumbai-Ahmedabad High Speed Rail (Bullet Train) Project. The approval was given by M E Testing Lab Pvt. Ltd. and ACE Test House, confirming compliance with the prescribed technical and performance parameters. This approval enables the Company to participate in the supply of the approved product for various construction and infrastructure requirements of the said project.</p><ul><li>Gabion Technologies India Limited has received material approval for its product - Mechanically Woven, Double-Twisted, Hexagonal Wire Mesh for use in the Mumbai-Ahmedabad High Speed Rail (Bullet Train) Project.</li><li>The product has been tested and approved by M E Testing Lab Pvt. Ltd. and ACE Test House, confirming compliance with the prescribed technical and performance parameters.</li><li>This approval enables the Company to participate in the supply of the approved product for various construction and infrastructure requirements of the said project.</li><li>The Mumbai-Ahmedabad High Speed Rail (MAHSR) Project is India’s first High Speed Rail corridor, connecting Mumbai (Maharashtra) with Ahmedabad (Gujarat).</li><li>Gabion Technologies India Limited is engaged in the manufacturing, supply, marketing, and installation of steel gabions and allied geotechnical and geosystem solutions.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/84c7dd9c-72dd-4451-beea-d2d91ff5617a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Gabion Technologies India Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GTIL] Gabion Technologies India Ltd. Bags Orders Worth Approx. Rs. 2,02,48,610 in Last Week</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Gabion+Technologies+India+Ltd&title=Gabion+Technologies+India+Ltd.+Bags+Orders+Worth+Approx.+Rs.+2%2C02%2C48%2C610+in+Last+Week&newsId=61c075ba-f887-4705-ba5d-1c9c9a885be9&token=NjFjMDc1YmEtZjg4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61c075ba-f887-4705-ba5d-1c9c9a885be9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 09:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Gabion Technologies India Ltd., a company listed on the BSE SME Exchange, has received multiple routine orders during the period from January 11, 2026 to January 17, 2026. The total order value, inclusive of applicable GST, is approximately Rs. 2,02,48,610. The orders are for supply and installation as per individual contract terms. The execution period for these orders varies. The company clarifies that these orders are routine and have been received in the normal course of business. Gabion Technologies India Ltd. is engaged in manufacturing, trading, design, and construction services relating to gabions, rockfall protection systems, geosynthetics, and other geotechnical solutions.</p><ul><li>Orders worth approximately Rs. 2,02,48,610 received</li><li>Orders received from various customers in the ordinary course of business</li><li>Orders are for supply and installation as per individual contract terms</li><li>Execution period varies as per individual contract terms</li><li>Gabion Technologies India Ltd. is engaged in manufacturing, trading, design, and construction services relating to gabions, rockfall protection systems, geosynthetics, and other geotechnical solutions</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7b69b466-85db-4dbb-90cf-c7fe30d4c200.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Gabion Technologies India Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BANARISUG] Bannari Amman Sugars Ltd. Addresses Discrepancies in Corporate Announcement Regarding TNPDCL Demand Notice</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BANNARI+AMMAN+SUGARS+LTD.&title=Bannari+Amman+Sugars+Ltd.+Addresses+Discrepancies+in+Corporate+Announcement+Regarding+TNPDCL+Demand+Notice&newsId=9078debd-d373-4c07-84a1-807b98128dfc&token=OTA3OGRlYmQtZDM3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9078debd-d373-4c07-84a1-807b98128dfc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 09:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bannari Amman Sugars Ltd. has submitted a revised disclosure to address discrepancies observed in their corporate announcement submitted to the exchange on 17 March 2025. The company received a demand notice from Tamilnadu Power Distribution Corporation Limited (TNPDCL) on 15 March 2025, after working hours, for an amount of Rs.8,69,15,567/- towards start-up powers provided by the TANGEDCO during the period from October, 2013 to July, 2017. The company is planning to discuss the errors in calculations and applicability of interest with the authorities and will update on the impact on financial, operation or other activities.</p><ul><li>Bannari Amman Sugars Ltd. addresses discrepancies in their corporate announcement.</li><li>Company received a demand notice from Tamilnadu Power Distribution Corporation Limited (TNPDCL) for Rs.8,69,15,567/-.</li><li>The demand notice was received after working hours on a Saturday.</li><li>Company submitted the intimation on the next working day.</li><li>Bannari Amman Sugars Ltd. plans to discuss errors in calculations and applicability of interest with the authorities.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/da216f5f-fcbc-4c2d-9670-376d3d5fa679.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BANNARI AMMAN SUGARS LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NEWGEN] Newgen Software Reports Revenue at Rs 1,122 cr in 9M FY’26, up 6% YoY; Profit after Tax at Rs 222 cr, up 7% YoY</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Newgen+Software+Technologies+Ltd&title=Newgen+Software+Reports+Revenue+at+Rs+1%2C122+cr+in+9M+FY%E2%80%9926%2C+up+6%25+YoY%3B+Profit+after+Tax+at+Rs+222+cr%2C+up+7%25+YoY&newsId=78a0f99d-7e14-4aab-9698-072f0e0ac729&token=NzhhMGY5OWQtN2Ux</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78a0f99d-7e14-4aab-9698-072f0e0ac729</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 09:09:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Newgen Software Technologies Ltd. announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company reported a revenue of Rs 1,122 crore, a 6% YoY growth. The Profit after Tax (adjusted) stood at Rs 222 crore, a 7% YoY increase. The company&apos;s Annuity revenue streams were at Rs 706 crores, with subscription revenues at Rs 382 crores, a 23% YoY growth. The company onboarded 34 new logos within the nine-month period. Newgen Software was recognized in various Gartner and Forrester reports.</p><ul><li>Revenue at Rs 1,122 cr in 9M FY’26, up 6% YoY</li><li>Profit after Tax (adjusted) at Rs 222 cr, up 7% YoY</li><li>Annuity revenue streams at Rs 706 crores</li><li>Subscription revenues at Rs 382 crores, a 23% YoY growth</li><li>Onboarded 34 new logos within the nine-month period</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b684047a-0eaf-4c2b-a95d-8598e4f73979.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Newgen Software Technologies Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>