<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:23:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[KEERTHI] Keerthi Industries Confirms Status of Share Transfer Requests Under SEBI Special Window</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KEERTHI+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Keerthi+Industries+Confirms+Status+of+Share+Transfer+Requests+Under+SEBI+Special+Window&newsId=5e5bc7a4-b396-4223-b9e9-1f25c9e58e7f&token=NWU1YmM3YTQtYjM5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5e5bc7a4-b396-4223-b9e9-1f25c9e58e7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:22:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Keerthi Industries Ltd. has provided an update on the status of share transfer requests received for the month ended 31st December 2025. This update comes in response to the SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97. The company has confirmed the processing and approval status of the requests. Additionally, Keerthi Industries has reminded shareholders to dematerialize their securities within 120 days of this letter, as per the SEBI Gazette Notification ne SEBI /LAD-NRO/GN/2022/66 dated January 24, 2022.</p><ul><li>Keerthi Industries provides update on share transfer requests under SEBI special window.</li><li>Company confirms processing and approval status of requests for December 2025.</li><li>Shareholders reminded to dematerialize securities within 120 days as per SEBI guidelines.</li><li>SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97 is the reference point for this update.</li><li>SEBI Gazette Notification ne SEBI /LAD-NRO/GN/2022/66 dated January 24, 2022, mandates securities to be issued in demat mode only.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4a6b90d6-b22f-4b5c-99ba-33d03d070d5a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KEERTHI INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HONASA] Honasa Consumer Ltd Completes Acquisition of Reginald Men Brand Owner BTM Ventures</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Honasa+Consumer+Ltd&title=Honasa+Consumer+Ltd+Completes+Acquisition+of+Reginald+Men+Brand+Owner+BTM+Ventures&newsId=1689d410-cf5b-403e-889e-a907d1e8e550&token=MTY4OWQ0MTAtY2Y1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1689d410-cf5b-403e-889e-a907d1e8e550</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:19:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Honasa Consumer Ltd has completed the acquisition of 95% of the issued and paid-up equity share capital of BTM Ventures Private Limited (BVPL), the company that owns and operates the men’s focused personal care products brand ‘Reginald Men’. The acquisition was done for an equity value of INR 197.96 Crores, which includes cash and cash equivalents of INR 12.71 Crores available on the books of BVPL as on the closing date. This makes BTM Ventures Private Limited a subsidiary of Honasa Consumer Ltd.</p><ul><li>Honasa Consumer Ltd completes 95% acquisition of BTM Ventures Private Limited</li><li>BTM Ventures Private Limited is the owner of the brand ‘Reginald Men’</li><li>The acquisition was done for an equity value of INR 197.96 Crores</li><li>The acquisition includes cash and cash equivalents of INR 12.71 Crores</li><li>BTM Ventures Private Limited becomes a subsidiary of Honasa Consumer Ltd</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2da0828a-e315-4768-a990-7a357fb1df28.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Honasa Consumer Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ACCELERATE] Acceleratebs India Ltd Approves USD 1 Million Investment in Wholly-Owned Subsidiary Accelerate Next Inc</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Acceleratebs+India+Ltd&title=Acceleratebs+India+Ltd+Approves+USD+1+Million+Investment+in+Wholly-Owned+Subsidiary+Accelerate+Next+Inc&newsId=3df23990-864c-4220-a145-6e69327b58b3&token=M2RmMjM5OTAtODY0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3df23990-864c-4220-a145-6e69327b58b3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Acceleratebs India Ltd announced the approval of a significant investment of up to USD 1,000,000 (United States Dollar One Million Only) in its wholly-owned subsidiary, Accelerate Next Inc, incorporated in Wyoming, United States of America. The investment will be made by subscribing to the equity shares of the subsidiary. Additionally, the Board of Directors has also approved granting a loan of up to USD 1,000,000 (United States Dollar One Million Only) to Accelerate Next Inc in one or more tranches at its discretion.</p><ul><li>Acceleratebs India Ltd to invest up to USD 1,000,000 in Accelerate Next Inc</li><li>Investment to be made by subscribing to equity shares of the subsidiary</li><li>Board approves granting a loan of up to USD 1,000,000 to Accelerate Next Inc</li><li>Loan to be granted in one or more tranches at the discretion of the Board</li><li>Accelerate Next Inc is a wholly-owned subsidiary of Acceleratebs India Ltd, incorporated in Wyoming, United States of America</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/980e1423-9dcb-4af4-b7df-2babcc46e367.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Acceleratebs India Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAFFRON] Saffron Industries Ltd. Re-Appoints Mr. Manoj Rameshwar Sinha as Whole-time Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Saffron+Industries+Limited&title=Saffron+Industries+Ltd.+Re-Appoints+Mr.+Manoj+Rameshwar+Sinha+as+Whole-time+Director&newsId=eb218dd9-f0bd-4d33-86b1-c6b6743d8323&token=ZWIyMThkZDktZjBi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eb218dd9-f0bd-4d33-86b1-c6b6743d8323</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Saffron Industries Ltd. has announced the re-appointment of Mr. Manoj Rameshwar Sinha as Whole-time Director for a period of three years, effective from January 06, 2026, subject to the approval of the Shareholders at the ensuing General Meeting. Mr. Sinha, a Commerce graduate, brings over 20 years of experience in property acquisition, development, and management. He has been instrumental in strategic leadership, market analysis, financial acumen, stakeholder relations, and driving innovation in sustainability. His re-appointment is based on the recommendations of the Nomination and Remuneration Committee and the approval of the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Re-appointment of Mr. Manoj Rameshwar Sinha as Whole-time Director</li><li>Re-appointment for a further period of three years</li><li>Mr. Sinha&apos;s extensive experience in property acquisition, development, and management</li><li>His role in strategic leadership, market analysis, and financial acumen</li><li>Subject to the approval of the Shareholders at the ensuing General Meeting</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6eb86cb4-bd32-49d5-b5a9-bf77a04fbb98.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Saffron Industries Limited | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAFFRON] Saffron Industries Ltd. Re-Appoints Mr. Manoj Rameshwar Sinha as Whole-time Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Saffron+Industries+Limited&title=Saffron+Industries+Ltd.+Re-Appoints+Mr.+Manoj+Rameshwar+Sinha+as+Whole-time+Director&newsId=49d5a0c7-eadb-4a67-a13b-218af78fe094&token=NDlkNWEwYzctZWFk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">49d5a0c7-eadb-4a67-a13b-218af78fe094</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Saffron Industries Ltd. has approved the re-appointment of Mr. Manoj Rameshwar Sinha as Whole-time Director for a period of three years, subject to the approval of the Shareholders at the ensuing General Meeting. Mr. Sinha, a Commerce graduate, has over 20 years of experience in property acquisition, development, and management. His key duties include scheduling, budgeting, quality assurance, team development, and coordinating with editorial, sales, and marketing.</p><ul><li>Re-appointment of Mr. Manoj Rameshwar Sinha as Whole-time Director for a further period of three years</li><li>Mr. Sinha is a Commerce graduate with over 20 years of experience in property acquisition, development, and management</li><li>His key duties include scheduling, budgeting, quality assurance, team development, and coordinating with editorial, sales, and marketing</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/46c97022-b2d2-4076-ace2-9a2021458ae4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Saffron Industries Limited | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UNIROYAL] Uniroyal Industries&apos; Promoter, Rashmi Mahajan, to Acquire 8.63% Shares via Gift from Son</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=UNIROYAL+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Uniroyal+Industries%27+Promoter%2C+Rashmi+Mahajan%2C+to+Acquire+8.63%25+Shares+via+Gift+from+Son&newsId=c99b9091-4d98-48f5-ae56-7e6b277a038e&token=Yzk5YjkwOTEtNGQ5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c99b9091-4d98-48f5-ae56-7e6b277a038e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Uniroyal Industries Ltd. has received disclosure from Mrs. Rashmi Mahajan, a promoter and part of the promoter group, intending to acquire 713475 equity shares from her son, Mr. Abhay Mahajan, also a part of the promoter group, through inter se transfer of shares on 10/01/2026. This being an inter se transfer amongst promoter group and immediate relative, it falls within the exception under regulation 10(1)(a)(i) and 10(1)(a)(ii). The transfer is in the nature of gift, and the aggregate holding of promoter and promoter group before and after the above inter se transfer of shares remains the same.</p><ul><li>Mrs. Rashmi Mahajan, a promoter of Uniroyal Industries Ltd., intends to acquire 713475 equity shares from her son, Mr. Abhay Mahajan, who is also a part of the promoter group.</li><li>The transfer of shares is by way of gift, and no consideration is being paid.</li><li>The proposed acquisition date is 10/01/2026.</li><li>The acquisition is exempt from making an open offer under SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</li><li>The acquirer, Mrs. Rashmi Mahajan, has complied with the necessary disclosure requirements in Regulation 10(5) of SEBI (SAST) Regulation, 2011.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5B68AF7F_3D40_46A4_8631_BBCCF236BBA3_143359.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: UNIROYAL INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UNIROYAL] Uniroyal Industries&apos; Promoter Rashmi Mahajan to Acquire 8.63% Shares from Son Abhay Mahajan by Gift</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=UNIROYAL+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Uniroyal+Industries%27+Promoter+Rashmi+Mahajan+to+Acquire+8.63%25+Shares+from+Son+Abhay+Mahajan+by+Gift&newsId=36d8688a-b848-4615-aee3-c03ca2124a96&token=MzZkODY4OGEtYjg0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">36d8688a-b848-4615-aee3-c03ca2124a96</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 09:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Uniroyal Industries Ltd&apos;s promoter, Rashmi Mahajan, intends to acquire 713475 equity shares from her son, Abhay Mahajan, through a gift. The transaction is exempt from making an open offer under the SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. The shares represent 8.63% of the company&apos;s share capital. The transaction is set to occur on 10/01/2026.</p><ul><li>Rashmi Mahajan to acquire 713475 equity shares from her son Abhay Mahajan.</li><li>The transaction is a gift, not subject to financial consideration.</li><li>The shares represent 8.63% of Uniroyal Industries&apos; share capital.</li><li>The transaction is exempt from making an open offer under SEBI regulations.</li><li>The proposed acquisition is set to occur on 10/01/2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/182E6850_280D_4131_BFE2_4A57D3F2A571_143240.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: UNIROYAL INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JRELTD] EbixCash, Lotus India Pay Launch Co-Branded Legend Card to Enhance Payment Experience</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Justride+Enterprises+Ltd&title=EbixCash%2C+Lotus+India+Pay+Launch+Co-Branded+Legend+Card+to+Enhance+Payment+Experience&newsId=0614cf53-46d6-40e4-9a4a-0023eb64b6bb&token=MDYxNGNmNTMtNDZk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0614cf53-46d6-40e4-9a4a-0023eb64b6bb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 08:56:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>EbixCash, the Indian flagship subsidiary of Eraaya Lifespaces Ltd, has partnered with Lotus India Pay to launch the Legend Card, a co-branded prepaid card. This strategic move strengthens EbixCash&apos;s prepaid and digital payments portfolio and enhances the shopping and lifestyle experience of Lotus India Pay customers. The Legend Card is designed to support point-of-sale transactions, e-commerce purchases, QR-based payments, and UPI-linked usage, enabling seamless cashless transactions. The card is made for today&apos;s digitally inclined customers who seek secure, convenient, and seamless payment solutions.</p><ul><li>EbixCash and Lotus India Pay partner to launch co-branded Legend Card</li><li>The card enhances the shopping and lifestyle experience of Lotus India Pay customers</li><li>Supports point-of-sale transactions, e-commerce purchases, QR-based payments, and UPI-linked usage</li><li>Designed for today&apos;s digitally inclined customers seeking secure, convenient, and seamless payment solutions</li><li>Part of EbixCash&apos;s ongoing product and partnership roadmap</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0fe8748b-2e2a-40c1-9061-2ad7b7711393.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Justride Enterprises Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JSTL] Jeevan Scientific Technology Ltd Receives Disclosure for Substantial Acquisition of Shares by Sushma Bangad, Shradha Bangad, Pranali Bangad, and Alpha Financials</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jeevan+Scientific+Technology+Ltd&title=Jeevan+Scientific+Technology+Ltd+Receives+Disclosure+for+Substantial+Acquisition+of+Shares+by+Sushma+Bangad%2C+Shradha+Bangad%2C+Pranali+Bangad%2C+and+Alpha+Financials&newsId=49874645-72ae-406e-a91e-aa792c1b9765&token=NDk4NzQ2NDUtNzJh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">49874645-72ae-406e-a91e-aa792c1b9765</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 08:52:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jeevan Scientific Technology Ltd has received a disclosure under Regulation 29(1) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. The disclosure is for the acquisition of shares by Sushma Bangad, Shradha Bangad, Pranali Bangad, and Alpha Financials. The acquisition was made through a preferential issue (Cash basis) on 02-01-2026. The total shares acquired amount to 15,00,000, which is 7.54% of the total diluted share/voting capital of the company.</p><ul><li>Acquisition of 15,00,000 shares by Sushma Bangad, Shradha Bangad, Pranali Bangad, and Alpha Financials</li><li>The acquisition was made through a preferential issue (Cash basis) on 02-01-2026</li><li>The total shares acquired represent 7.54% of the total diluted share/voting capital of the company</li><li>The acquisition does not involve any encumbrance or warrants/convertible securities</li><li>The total share capital/voting capital after the acquisition is Rs, 19,91,89,650 divided into 1,99,18,965 equit shares of Rs. 10/- each</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/522E5F2A_903C_47B0_BCBF_3D5656206A8D_141300.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jeevan Scientific Technology Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WEL] Sad Demise of Independent Director Mr. Jugal Kishore Chugh at Wonder Electricals Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Wonder+Electricals+Ltd&title=Sad+Demise+of+Independent+Director+Mr.+Jugal+Kishore+Chugh+at+Wonder+Electricals+Ltd&newsId=2dce74dd-96c2-481c-8481-f1c04de0f4f5&token=MmRjZTc0ZGQtOTZj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2dce74dd-96c2-481c-8481-f1c04de0f4f5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 08:47:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Wonder Electricals Ltd announced the demise of its Independent Director, Mr. Jugal Kishore Chugh (DIN: 01254901) on January 06, 2026. His unexpected death is considered an irreplaceable loss to the company. The board of directors and employees express their deepest sympathy, sorrow, and condolences to his family. The required disclosures as per the SEBI Listing Regulations are attached as Annexure-I.</p><ul><li>Demise of Independent Director Mr. Jugal Kishore Chugh</li><li>Wonder Electricals Ltd expresses deep sympathy and condolences to the family</li><li>Required disclosures attached as Annexure-I as per SEBI Listing Regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dc6f3d83-d304-496e-973d-f2a8cba4280e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Wonder Electricals Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>