<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:42:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[MEGASOFT] Sigma Advanced Systems Wins Rs. 100 Crore Order From Ministry of Defence</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MEGASOFT+LTD.&title=Sigma+Advanced+Systems+Wins+Rs.+100+Crore+Order+From+Ministry+of+Defence&newsId=af823f3c-bfaf-4bb4-a586-924371c75622&token=YWY4MjNmM2MtYmZh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">af823f3c-bfaf-4bb4-a586-924371c75622</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:42:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sigma Advanced Systems has secured fresh orders worth about Rs. 100 crore from the Ministry of Defence and associated defence PSUs. The contracts relate to ongoing strategic programmes across missile systems, naval platforms, and airborne applications, under which Sigma will supply built-to-spec systems, control electronics, and actuation solutions. The scope of work covers Surface-to-Air Missile (SAM) programmes, Anti-tank missile programmes, New Generation Anti-radiation missile programmes, and naval weapon systems.</p><ul><li>Sigma Advanced Systems has secured orders worth about Rs. 100 crore from the Ministry of Defence and associated defence PSUs.</li><li>The contracts relate to ongoing strategic programmes across missile systems, naval platforms, and airborne applications.</li><li>Sigma will supply built-to-spec systems, control electronics, and actuation solutions.</li><li>The scope of work covers Surface-to-Air Missile (SAM) programmes, Anti-tank missile programmes, New Generation Anti-radiation missile programmes, and naval weapon systems.</li><li>Sigma will execute these orders for leading defence public sector undertakings and research laboratories, including Bharat Dynamics Limited (BDL), Hindustan Aeronautics Limited (HAL), and the Defence Research and Development Organisation (DRDO) establishments.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f3381b42-9490-49fe-bac8-d1e04441f95f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MEGASOFT LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HEXT] Hexaware Technologies Ltd: Appointment of Alok Chandra Misra as Non-Executive Independent Director, Resignation of Vivek Sharma, and Reconstitution of Committees</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Hexaware+Technologies+Ltd&title=Hexaware+Technologies+Ltd%3A+Appointment+of+Alok+Chandra+Misra+as+Non-Executive+Independent+Director%2C+Resignation+of+Vivek+Sharma%2C+and+Reconstitution+of+Committees&newsId=add5775f-5c00-4278-81ab-d61099887863&token=YWRkNTc3NWYtNWMw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">add5775f-5c00-4278-81ab-d61099887863</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:28:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hexaware Technologies Ltd has announced the appointment of Alok Chandra Misra as an Additional Director in the capacity of Non-Executive Independent Director for a term of 3 years, starting from February 23, 2026. Mr. Misra is a seasoned professional with extensive experience in financial roles and as a public company CFO. He co-founded Guvrn, India&apos;s first curated board network, and has served as Operating Partner and Chief Operating Officer of India at General Atlantic. Furthermore, Mr. Vivek Sharma has resigned from his position as an Independent Director due to other professional commitments. The Board has also approved the reconstitution of committees, with Mr. Misra joining as a member of the Audit Committee, Nomination &amp; Remuneration Committee, Risk Management Committee, Environmental, Social &amp; Governance Committee, and Cybersecurity Committee.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Alok Chandra Misra as Non-Executive Independent Director</li><li>Resignation of Vivek Sharma from the position of Independent Director</li><li>Reconstitution of Committees of the Board</li><li>Alok Chandra Misra&apos;s extensive experience in financial roles and as a public company CFO</li><li>Vivek Sharma&apos;s resignation due to other professional commitments</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/197d6ee6-eb7a-4211-b8db-bddbd11da01a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Hexaware Technologies Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HEXT] Hexaware Technologies Ltd Announces Changes in Board of Directors and Committee Reconstitution</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Hexaware+Technologies+Ltd&title=Hexaware+Technologies+Ltd+Announces+Changes+in+Board+of+Directors+and+Committee+Reconstitution&newsId=875c220d-e244-45bc-988a-4ee84d821d41&token=ODc1YzIyMGQtZTI0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">875c220d-e244-45bc-988a-4ee84d821d41</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:22:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hexaware Technologies Ltd has announced changes in its Board of Directors, with the appointment of Mr. Alok Chandra Misra as an Additional Director in the capacity of Non-Executive Independent Director for a term of 3 years, and the resignation of Mr. Vivek Sharma due to other professional commitments. The company has also reconstituted its committees and appointed Mr. Shantanu Baruah for an additional role of North America — Hunting Head. The changes are in compliance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Alok Chandra Misra as an Additional Director in the capacity of Non-Executive Independent Director for a term of 3 years.</li><li>Resignation of Mr. Vivek Sharma due to other professional commitments.</li><li>Reconstitution of Committees of the Board with Mr. Alok Chandra Misra as a member of the Audit Committee, Nomination &amp; Remuneration Committee, Risk Management Committee, Environmental, Social &amp; Governance Committee, and Cybersecurity Committee.</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Shantanu Baruah for an additional role of North America — Hunting Head.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/752e1e0f-61cf-4bc7-800c-d1f6452d6756.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Hexaware Technologies Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HEXT] Hexaware Technologies Ltd: Appointment of Mr. Alok Chandra Misra as Non-Executive Independent Director and Resignation of Mr. Vivek Sharma</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Hexaware+Technologies+Ltd&title=Hexaware+Technologies+Ltd%3A+Appointment+of+Mr.+Alok+Chandra+Misra+as+Non-Executive+Independent+Director+and+Resignation+of+Mr.+Vivek+Sharma&newsId=7f010552-84fa-49f0-ace4-b1bbb0ab68a0&token=N2YwMTA1NTItODRm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7f010552-84fa-49f0-ace4-b1bbb0ab68a0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:22:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hexaware Technologies Ltd has announced the appointment of Mr. Alok Chandra Misra as an Additional Director in the capacity of Non-Executive Independent Director for a term of 3 years, subject to shareholder approval. Mr. Misra is a seasoned professional with extensive experience as a public company CFO and as an Operating Partner and Chief Operating Officer of India at General Atlantic. He also serves as a non-executive/independent director on the boards of various private and public companies. Simultaneously, Mr. Vivek Sharma has resigned from his position as an Independent Director due to other professional commitments. Mr. Sharma was a member of the Stakeholders Relationship Committee and Corporate Social Responsibility Committee, and his resignation will be effective from the close of business hours on February 23, 2026. The company has also announced the reconstitution of various committees of the Board and the appointment of Mr. Shantanu Baruah for an additional role of North America — Hunting Head.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Alok Chandra Misra as Non-Executive Independent Director</li><li>Resignation of Mr. Vivek Sharma due to other professional commitments</li><li>Reconstitution of various committees of the Board</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Shantanu Baruah for an additional role of North America — Hunting Head</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/535bfb8a-5ca4-425e-8655-20f7005c5a18.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Hexaware Technologies Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADITYA] Aditya Ispat Ltd Approves Slump Sale of Non-alloy Steel Business for INR 3,67,63,000</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADITYA+ISPAT+LTD.&title=Aditya+Ispat+Ltd+Approves+Slump+Sale+of+Non-alloy+Steel+Business+for+INR+3%2C67%2C63%2C000&newsId=cb49ad05-7df5-45b6-8f28-c80fa22762b2&token=Y2I0OWFkMDUtN2Rm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb49ad05-7df5-45b6-8f28-c80fa22762b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:22:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Sale</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Aditya Ispat Ltd announced the outcome of its board meeting held on February 23, 2026. The board approved the slump sale of the business of manufacturing and trading activity of Non-alloy steel of the company on a going concern basis at a lump sum consideration of INR 3,67,63,000. The sale will be effective from 01.03.2026, subject to the approval of the Members of the Company through postal ballot. The board also approved the appointment of M/s Ernst &amp; Young LLP as consultants for assistance in implementation of the BTA and appointed Mr. Manjeet Bucha as the Scrutinizer for the purposes of collating the Postal Ballot and remote e-voting data.</p><ul><li>Aditya Ispat Ltd approved the slump sale of its Non-alloy steel business for INR 3,67,63,000</li><li>The sale will be effective from 01.03.2026, subject to the approval of the Members of the Company through postal ballot</li><li>M/s Ernst &amp; Young LLP appointed as consultants for assistance in implementation of the BTA</li><li>Mr. Manjeet Bucha appointed as the Scrutinizer for the purposes of collating the Postal Ballot and remote e-voting data</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a5efd048-4d1c-41f9-8194-66c30b868dc8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADITYA ISPAT LTD. | Category: Sale</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADITYA] Aditya Ispat Ltd Approves Slump Sale of Non-alloy Steel Business to Promoter Group Company</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADITYA+ISPAT+LTD.&title=Aditya+Ispat+Ltd+Approves+Slump+Sale+of+Non-alloy+Steel+Business+to+Promoter+Group+Company&newsId=1353aef6-cba1-493f-9a4f-1450f1b9ddfe&token=MTM1M2FlZjYtY2Jh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1353aef6-cba1-493f-9a4f-1450f1b9ddfe</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:22:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Sale</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Aditya Ispat Ltd has approved the slump sale of its Non-alloy steel manufacturing and trading activity business to M/s. Jai Bapji Ispat Private Limited, a related party and promoter group company, for a lump sum consideration of INR 3,67,63,000. The decision was made at a board meeting held on 23rd February 2026, and is subject to approval by the members of the company through a postal ballot. The sale is expected to be completed by 31st March 2026. The board also approved the appointment of Ernst &amp; Young LLP as consultants for assistance in implementing the Business Transfer Agreement.</p><ul><li>Aditya Ispat Ltd approves slump sale of Non-alloy steel business</li><li>Sale to related party and promoter group company, M/s. Jai Bapji Ispat Private Limited</li><li>Lump sum consideration of INR 3,67,63,000</li><li>Subject to approval by members through postal ballot</li><li>Expected completion date: 31st March 2026</li><li>Ernst &amp; Young LLP appointed as consultants</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/37d344bb-edcb-4014-98d6-bc6cd1a21121.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADITYA ISPAT LTD. | Category: Sale</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[COVIDH] Covidh Technologies to Acquire 100% Equity Shareholding of iISERA Biological Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=COVIDH+TECHNOLOGIES+LIMITED&title=Covidh+Technologies+to+Acquire+100%25+Equity+Shareholding+of+iISERA+Biological+Limited&newsId=bdbcedfc-f57a-4119-80a6-ec561f8e7613&token=YmRiY2VkZmMtZjU3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bdbcedfc-f57a-4119-80a6-ec561f8e7613</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:21:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Covidh Technologies Ltd. has executed a non-binding Letter of Intent (LOI) with iISERA Biological Limited for the proposed acquisition of 100% equity shareholding. The proposed acquisition is subject to various conditions including execution of definitive agreements, completion of satisfactory due diligence, and necessary approvals. Upon completion, iISERA Biological Limited will become a wholly owned subsidiary of Covidh Technologies Ltd.</p><ul><li>Covidh Technologies Ltd. has executed a non-binding LOI with iISERA Biological Limited for the proposed acquisition of 100% equity shareholding.</li><li>The proposed acquisition is subject to various conditions including execution of definitive agreements, completion of satisfactory due diligence, and necessary approvals.</li><li>Upon completion, iISERA Biological Limited will become a wholly owned subsidiary of Covidh Technologies Ltd.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/204d60da-97e1-4290-b4e6-e6e6e2a52cb7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: COVIDH TECHNOLOGIES LIMITED | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KOCL] Kome-On Communication Ltd. Approves Q1 2022-2023 Unaudited Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kome-On+Communication+Ltd&title=Kome-On+Communication+Ltd.+Approves+Q1+2022-2023+Unaudited+Financial+Results&newsId=6b61051b-6afe-44ae-b5f7-2f9d1aec6013&token=NmI2MTA1MWItNmFm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6b61051b-6afe-44ae-b5f7-2f9d1aec6013</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Kome-On Communication Ltd. announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter ended on 30th June, 2022. The company&apos;s revenue and profitability showed a positive trend. The Board of Directors approved these results in their meeting held on 23rd February, 2026. The Statutory Auditor carried out a limited review of the financial results and found no qualification in the review report.</p><ul><li>Kome-On Communication Ltd. announced its unaudited financial results for Q1 2022-2023.</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue and profitability showed a positive trend.</li><li>The Board of Directors approved these results in their meeting held on 23rd February, 2026.</li><li>The Statutory Auditor carried out a limited review of the financial results.</li><li>No qualification was found in the review report.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/599724c8-0275-4a17-9d28-25fbc1f23799.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kome-On Communication Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AARNAV] Aarnav Fashions Secures Listing Approval from National Stock Exchange</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Aarnav+Fashions+Ltd&title=Aarnav+Fashions+Secures+Listing+Approval+from+National+Stock+Exchange&newsId=e256d68b-21e5-4495-bb1c-c179570b6b47&token=ZTI1NmQ2OGItMjFl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e256d68b-21e5-4495-bb1c-c179570b6b47</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:11:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Aarnav Fashions Ltd. has received approval for listing and trading of its 4,22,38,628 equity shares with a face value of Rs. 10/- each from the National Stock Exchange of India Limited (NSE). The approval was granted on February 23, 2026, and the shares will be listed and traded on the NSE from February 25, 2026, under the symbol ‘AARNAV’. This listing is expected to improve trading liquidity, attract a wider base of investors, and reinforce the company&apos;s brand presence.</p><ul><li>Aarnav Fashions receives approval for listing and trading of 4,22,38,628 equity shares from NSE.</li><li>The shares will be listed and traded on the NSE from February 25, 2026, under the symbol ‘AARNAV’.</li><li>This listing is expected to improve trading liquidity and attract a wider base of investors.</li><li>The company&apos;s brand presence will be reinforced across both premier stock exchanges.</li><li>This development marks a key milestone in the company&apos;s growth journey.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b028be32-4120-48f4-bab7-123aa279b539.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Aarnav Fashions Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IDFCFIRSTB] IDFC First Bank Ltd Clarifies Price Movement Not Due to De-Empanelment but Fraud Identification</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IDFC+First+Bank+Ltd&title=IDFC+First+Bank+Ltd+Clarifies+Price+Movement+Not+Due+to+De-Empanelment+but+Fraud+Identification&newsId=a807a254-22ef-48eb-be82-54151a2fdb68&token=YTgwN2EyNTQtMjJl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a807a254-22ef-48eb-be82-54151a2fdb68</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 15:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Fraud Identification</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>IDFC First Bank Ltd has clarified that the recent price movement in its securities is not due to de-empanelment but rather the identification and disclosure of a fraud. The bank followed due process, informing the Special Committee of the Board, Audit Committee, Board, police authorities, and relevant regulatory bodies. A forensic audit was also initiated with KPMG.</p><ul><li>IDFC First Bank Ltd clarifies price movement not due to de-empanelment but fraud identification</li><li>Bank followed due process, informing relevant authorities and initiating a forensic audit with KPMG</li><li>Fraud identified and disclosed to the exchanges on February 21, 2026</li><li>Bank believes trading movement is a result of the disclosures made to the exchanges</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c7b65281-2cfa-4981-bb79-866ab5b5b3ec.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IDFC First Bank Ltd | Category: Fraud Identification</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>