<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:28:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[BARONINF] Baron Infotech Ltd Announces Sixteenth Meeting of Committee of Creditors on January 9, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BARON+INFOTECH+LTD.&title=Baron+Infotech+Ltd+Announces+Sixteenth+Meeting+of+Committee+of+Creditors+on+January+9%2C+2026&newsId=4ddbe18f-2ab6-4409-9855-b29471e0c541&token=NGRkYmUxOGYtMmFi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4ddbe18f-2ab6-4409-9855-b29471e0c541</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Baron Infotech Limited, under Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP), has announced that the Sixteenth meeting of the Committee of Creditors (CoC) will be held on Friday, January 9, 2026, at 11.30 am. The meeting will be conducted in accordance with the Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015 (LODR) and sub-clause 16(g) of Clause A of Part A of Schedule II of LODR. The company has requested the General Manager of BSE Limited to take note of this information.</p><ul><li>Baron Infotech Ltd is under Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP).</li><li>Sixteenth meeting of the Committee of Creditors (CoC) has been scheduled for January 9, 2026.</li><li>The meeting will be held at 11.30 am.</li><li>The meeting is in accordance with Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015 (LODR) and sub-clause 16(g) of Clause A of Part A of Schedule II of LODR.</li><li>Company has informed the General Manager of BSE Limited about the meeting.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ef919b92-72f3-4cef-986c-0822231031fe.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BARON INFOTECH LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GENESIS] Padmanaban Krishnamoorthy Acquires Shares in Genesis Ibrc India Ltd via Open Offer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Genesis+Ibrc+India+Ltd&title=Padmanaban+Krishnamoorthy+Acquires+Shares+in+Genesis+Ibrc+India+Ltd+via+Open+Offer&newsId=8cd55dd5-38a9-4607-8506-108d430dd1aa&token=OGNkNTVkZDUtMzhh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8cd55dd5-38a9-4607-8506-108d430dd1aa</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:10:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Padmanaban Krishnamoorthy has acquired shares in Genesis Ibrc India Ltd through an open offer. The acquisition was made on 16th December 2025, with the shares being transferred to Krishnamoorthy. The total paid-up share capital of the company remains at Rs 13,00,00,000/-, comprising of 1,30,00,000 fully paid equity shares of Rs 10 each. This acquisition increases Krishnamoorthy&apos;s share in the company to 6.92% from the previous 0%.</p><ul><li>Padmanaban Krishnamoorthy acquires shares in Genesis Ibrc India Ltd through an open offer.</li><li>The acquisition was made on 16th December 2025, with the shares being transferred to Krishnamoorthy.</li><li>The total paid-up share capital of the company remains at Rs 13,00,000/-, comprising of 1,30,00,000 fully paid equity shares of Rs 10 each.</li><li>This acquisition increases Krishnamoorthy&apos;s share in the company to 6.92% from the previous 0%.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/39AC74AF_E506_43EC_9F6D_52942C1C559B_113532.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Genesis Ibrc India Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MODINATUR] Modi Naturals Ltd: Transfer Request of Physical Shares Re-lodged Under Special Window in December 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Modi+Naturals+Limited&title=Modi+Naturals+Ltd%3A+Transfer+Request+of+Physical+Shares+Re-lodged+Under+Special+Window+in+December+2025&newsId=f54510f9-3b1a-47f4-bc39-07237cafb597&token=ZjU0NTEwZjktM2Ix</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f54510f9-3b1a-47f4-bc39-07237cafb597</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Modi Naturals Ltd has released a report on the transfer requests of physical shares that were re-lodged for transfer cum demat for the month ended December 2025. The report, in compliance with SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97 dated July 2, 2025, was provided by the company&apos;s Registrar and Transfer Agent, Skyline Financial Services Private Limited. The report includes the tabular details of re-lodgement under the special window for the securities received and processed in December 2025. The average time taken for the approval of the requests in December 2025 was also provided.</p><ul><li>Modi Naturals Ltd releases report on transfer requests of physical shares for December 2025</li><li>Report provided by the company&apos;s Registrar and Transfer Agent, Skyline Financial Services Private Limited</li><li>Includes tabular details of re-lodgement under the special window for the securities received and processed in December 2025</li><li>Provides the average time taken for the approval of the requests in December 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/947ac782-3fb8-43e8-b16b-cfbfee052b44.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Modi Naturals Limited | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IOC] Indian Oil Corporation Ltd: Shri S G Venkatesh Leaves Senior Management for Subsidiary Board</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDIAN+OIL+CORPORATION+LTD.&title=Indian+Oil+Corporation+Ltd%3A+Shri+S+G+Venkatesh+Leaves+Senior+Management+for+Subsidiary+Board&newsId=387533dc-622b-406b-b50d-7c588cea6506&token=Mzg3NTMzZGMtNjIy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">387533dc-622b-406b-b50d-7c588cea6506</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:07:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indian Oil Corporation Ltd announced a change in its senior management personnel. Shri S G Venkatesh, Executive Director (Petrochemicals), Business Development Group, ceased to be a Senior Management Personnel of IndianOil on 5th January 2026. This change is due to his appointment as Director (Technical) on the Board of Chennai Petroleum Corporation Limited, a subsidiary of Indian Oil Corporation Limited.</p><ul><li>Shri S G Venkatesh, Executive Director (Petrochemicals), Business Development Group, has left his position in Indian Oil Corporation Ltd.</li><li>His departure is due to his appointment as Director (Technical) on the Board of Chennai Petroleum Corporation Limited.</li><li>This change is in accordance with the Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations 2015.</li><li>Indian Oil Corporation Ltd is a subsidiary of Chennai Petroleum Corporation Limited.</li><li>The change is effective from 5th January 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8cd29fc3-be44-493a-a3ce-6ffc96d89436.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDIAN OIL CORPORATION LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KTKBANK] Karnataka Bank Appoints New Company Secretary and Compliance Officer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KARNATAKA+BANK+LTD.&title=Karnataka+Bank+Appoints+New+Company+Secretary+and+Compliance+Officer&newsId=f836c627-e715-4e47-a89e-fdf1e340e78b&token=ZjgzNmM2MjctZTcx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f836c627-e715-4e47-a89e-fdf1e340e78b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Karnataka Bank Ltd. has appointed Mr. Sham K as the Company Secretary and Compliance Officer with effect from February 27, 2023. The bank also confirmed that M/s. Integrated Registry Management Services Private Limited is their Registrar and Share Transfer Agent (RTA). This disclosure is in accordance with the continuous disclosure norms relating to the provisions of Regulations 6 (1) and 7 (1) of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Mr. Sham K appointed as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer</li><li>M/s. Integrated Registry Management Services Private Limited is the Registrar and Share Transfer Agent (RTA)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e24990b2-671e-45b6-bae7-a7d20701b8f3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KARNATAKA BANK LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TAALENT] TAAL Enterprises Ltd Declares 2nd Interim Dividend of 350% for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TAAL+Enterprises+Ltd&title=TAAL+Enterprises+Ltd+Declares+2nd+Interim+Dividend+of+350%25+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=0e7df500-1f7b-40ee-b8d8-eb69f53facfb&token=MGU3ZGY1MDAtMWY3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e7df500-1f7b-40ee-b8d8-eb69f53facfb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 05:59:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>TAAL Enterprises Ltd, in accordance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, has declared a 2nd Interim Dividend for the Financial Year 2025-26. The dividend is set at X35/- (i.e. 350%) per equity share of face value X10/- each. The total amount to be distributed is Rs. 10,90,71,970/. This is in addition to the interim dividends declared earlier in the financial year, amounting to 20,25,62,230/. The Record Date for the payment of this dividend is January 16, 2026, and the payment is expected to be made to eligible shareholders on or before February 05, 2026.</p><ul><li>TAAL Enterprises Ltd declares 2nd Interim Dividend for FY 2025-26</li><li>Dividend amount set at X35/- per equity share</li><li>Total amount to be distributed is Rs. 10,90,71,970/</li><li>Record Date for dividend payment is January 16, 2026</li><li>Payment expected to be made to eligible shareholders by February 05, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c1634a73-89fa-4a14-b2cb-f6efcfea5823.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TAAL Enterprises Ltd | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SITAENT] Sita Enterprises Ltd: No Price-Sensitive Information Disclosed, Movement Market-Driven</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SITA+ENTERPRISES+LTD.&title=Sita+Enterprises+Ltd%3A+No+Price-Sensitive+Information+Disclosed%2C+Movement+Market-Driven&newsId=d7c1086a-9c92-4025-a12b-4dffa98133a6&token=ZDdjMTA4NmEtOWM5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7c1086a-9c92-4025-a12b-4dffa98133a6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 05:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sita Enterprises Ltd has issued a clarification letter stating that there is no undisclosed information that could influence the price or volume behavior of its equity shares. The movement in the share price is attributed to general market conditions and investor perception. The company assures prompt disclosure of any material events or information as required by the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Sita Enterprises Ltd has clarified that there is no undisclosed price-sensitive information.</li><li>The movement in the company&apos;s share price is market-driven, attributable to general market conditions and investor perception.</li><li>The company assures prompt disclosure of any material events or information as per SEBI regulations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5ac4ffe1-975f-4c6d-854d-30b28d03ed92.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SITA ENTERPRISES LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TAALENT] TAAL Enterprises Ltd Declares 2nd Interim Dividend of 350% for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TAAL+Enterprises+Ltd&title=TAAL+Enterprises+Ltd+Declares+2nd+Interim+Dividend+of+350%25+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=f05e8662-1f22-4e66-888c-1d1fc913f18b&token=ZjA1ZTg2NjItMWYy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f05e8662-1f22-4e66-888c-1d1fc913f18b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 05:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>TAAL Enterprises Ltd, in accordance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, has declared a 2nd Interim Dividend of 350% (i.e. Rs. 10,90,71,970/) per equity share for the Financial Year 2025-26. This is in addition to the interim dividends declared earlier in the same financial year, which totaled to Rs. 20,25,62,230/. The Record Date for the payment of this dividend is January 16, 2026, and the dividend will be paid to eligible shareholders on or before February 05, 2026.</p><ul><li>TAAL Enterprises Ltd declares 2nd Interim Dividend of 350% for FY 2025-26</li><li>The dividend amounts to Rs. 10,90,71,970/</li><li>Total interim dividends for FY 2025-26 amount to Rs. 20,25,62,230/</li><li>Record Date for dividend payment is January 16, 2026</li><li>Dividend to be paid to eligible shareholders on or before February 05, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8fb3828d-7a00-430f-b9f8-33eb9afae887.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TAAL Enterprises Ltd | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NAVKARCORP] Navkar Corporation Ltd to Consider and Approve Q4 2025 Financial Results on January 13, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Navkar+Corporation+Ltd&title=Navkar+Corporation+Ltd+to+Consider+and+Approve+Q4+2025+Financial+Results+on+January+13%2C+2026&newsId=ba93be58-1429-4e57-ba0d-6bcb2f2ec891&token=YmE5M2JlNTgtMTQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba93be58-1429-4e57-ba0d-6bcb2f2ec891</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 05:53:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Navkar Corporation Ltd has informed the BSE that their Board of Directors will meet on January 13, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will also address any other business with the permission of the Chair. In accordance with SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015 and the company&apos;s internal code, the trading window for dealing in the securities of the company for designated persons has been closed from January 01, 2026 till 48 hours after the results are made public.</p><ul><li>Navkar Corporation Ltd to consider and approve Q4 2025 financial results on January 13, 2026.</li><li>Trading window for designated persons closed from January 01, 2026 till 48 hours after results are made public.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a3aba5c0-3d89-44e2-b839-1cc7d19d19c2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Navkar Corporation Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BHEL] Bharat Heavy Electricals Ltd Board Meeting on 19/01/2026 to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Quarter Ended 31st December, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BHARAT+HEAVY+ELECTRICALS+LTD.&title=Bharat+Heavy+Electricals+Ltd+Board+Meeting+on+19%2F01%2F2026+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Quarter+Ended+31st+December%2C+2025&newsId=d6f48b98-8c8f-4fa7-b105-c4fb238aa773&token=ZDZmNDhiOTgtOGM4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6f48b98-8c8f-4fa7-b105-c4fb238aa773</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 05:52:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bharat Heavy Electricals Ltd (BHEL) has informed the BSE that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on 19th January, 2026. The meeting will consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results of BHEL for the quarter ended 31st December, 2025. In accordance with Regulation 29 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations &amp; Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, a notice has been issued. The trading window for designated persons will remain closed until 21st January, 2026. The company&apos;s registered office is at BHEL HOUSE, Siri Fort, New Delhi - 110049.</p><ul><li>BHEL board meeting scheduled on 19th January, 2026</li><li>Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter ended 31st December, 2025 to be approved</li><li>Trading window for designated persons to remain closed until 21st January, 2026</li><li>Meeting in accordance with Regulation 29 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations &amp; Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>BHEL&apos;s registered office at BHEL HOUSE, Siri Fort, New Delhi - 110049</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/359868db-d559-41ac-9b5f-9955579d4ea9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BHARAT HEAVY ELECTRICALS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>