<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 04:01:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[LT] L&amp;T Wins Large Order for Hydrocarbon Onshore Business from Petronet LNG</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LARSEN+%26+TOUBRO+LTD.&title=L%26T+Wins+Large+Order+for+Hydrocarbon+Onshore+Business+from+Petronet+LNG&newsId=dabab839-c2de-4450-8952-842b7813064d&token=ZGFiYWI4MzktYzJk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dabab839-c2de-4450-8952-842b7813064d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 03:58:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Larsen &amp; Toubro Limited (L&amp;T) has won a large order from Petronet LNG, a joint venture promoted by four leading PSUs, for engineering, procurement, construction and commissioning of a Liquefied Natural Gas (LNG)/Ethane double-wall storage tank and a Propane double-wall storage tank at the Dahej Petrochemical Complex in Gujarat. The scope also includes Ethane and Propane handling and despatch facilities to support the Propane Dehydrogenation and Polypropylene plant. This project is part of India’s first petrochemical complex integrating cold energy utilisation from an LNG terminal and is expected to contribute towards bridging the domestic polypropylene demand-supply gap. The order reflects the industry’s enduring confidence in L&amp;T’s proven ability to deliver projects within stringent timelines, while maintaining an unwavering commitment to excellence, safety and quality.</p><ul><li>L&amp;T’s Hydrocarbon Onshore business vertical has won a large order from Petronet LNG.</li><li>The project comprises engineering, procurement, construction and commissioning of a Liquefied Natural Gas (LNG)/Ethane double-wall storage tank and a Propane double-wall storage tank.</li><li>The project is part of India’s first petrochemical complex integrating cold energy utilisation from an LNG terminal.</li><li>The order reflects the industry’s enduring confidence in L&amp;T’s proven ability to deliver projects within stringent timelines.</li><li>The project aligns with Government of India’s Aatmanirbhar Bharat initiative by strengthening indigenous petrochemical manufacturing capacity.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/797e0395-c564-444e-8946-383c03500ef7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LARSEN & TOUBRO LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RELTD] Ravindra Energy Q3 Business Update: 187 MW Renewable Energy Generation, 55 Vehicles Sold, INR 296 Crore Financial Assistance Sanctioned</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ravindra+Energy+Ltd&title=Ravindra+Energy+Q3+Business+Update%3A+187+MW+Renewable+Energy+Generation%2C+55+Vehicles+Sold%2C+INR+296+Crore+Financial+Assistance+Sanctioned&newsId=fa0becaf-3c8d-4ef5-af14-5379a350f6d5&token=ZmEwYmVjYWYtM2M4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa0becaf-3c8d-4ef5-af14-5379a350f6d5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 03:37:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Ravindra Energy Ltd has announced its business update for the 3rd quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s Renewable Energy Generation business has reported an operating capacity of 187 MW DC. The Agri Feeder Projects in Karnataka have generated as per the target, and the Rooftop projects and Wind asset have also contributed 6 MW. The Mukhya Mantri Saurya Krishi Vahini Yojana (MSKVY) Phase 1 projects have been fully commissioned, and generation income is as per the target. The company is also constructing 60 MW DC under MSKVY Phase 2, expected to be commissioned before March 26. The Renewable Energy Generation business has 235 MW DC under development/pipeline. The Energy in Motion business has sold 55 vehicles in Q3 and has 8 swap stations expected to be commissioned by March 26. The company has also received financial assistance in the form of various credit facilities of INR 296 Crore and a hedge facility of INR 32 Crore from YES Bank Limited.</p><ul><li>Renewable Energy Generation business reports 187 MW DC operating capacity</li><li>Agri Feeder Projects in Karnataka generate as per target</li><li>MSKVY Phase 1 projects fully commissioned, generation income as per target</li><li>235 MW DC under development/pipeline</li><li>Energy in Motion business sells 55 vehicles in Q3, 8 swap stations expected by March 26</li><li>INR 296 Crore financial assistance sanctioned from YES Bank Limited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7616a70e-d697-4282-b03e-f0a462f51119.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ravindra Energy Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ANDHRAPET] Andhra Petrochemicals Ltd. to Approve Q3 Results on Feb 4, 2026; Trading Window Closed</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ANDHRA+PETROCHEMICALS+LTD.&title=Andhra+Petrochemicals+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q3+Results+on+Feb+4%2C+2026%3B+Trading+Window+Closed&newsId=e168fcce-d4c8-49ae-b82a-27280bb98582&token=ZTE2OGZjY2UtZDRj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e168fcce-d4c8-49ae-b82a-27280bb98582</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 03:21:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Andhra Petrochemicals Ltd. has announced that a Board Meeting will be held on February 4, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months period ended 31st December 2025. The trading window for dealing in the Equity Shares of the Company is closed from January 1, 2026, to February 6, 2026, in connection with the aforesaid Board Meeting.</p><ul><li>Andhra Petrochemicals Ltd. to hold a Board Meeting on February 4, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months period ended 31st December 2025</li><li>Trading Window for dealing in the Equity Shares of the Company is closed from January 1, 2026, to February 6, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2d329e19-6aa7-4895-96b5-d4e327b2ed84.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ANDHRA PETROCHEMICALS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NECLIFE] Nectar Lifesciences Completes Buyback of 3 Crore Equity Shares at INR 27 Each</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NECTAR+LIFESCIENCES+LTD.&title=Nectar+Lifesciences+Completes+Buyback+of+3+Crore+Equity+Shares+at+INR+27+Each&newsId=c3ae72be-107f-449f-9b6e-921c8b2755e8&token=YzNhZTcyYmUtMTA3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c3ae72be-107f-449f-9b6e-921c8b2755e8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 02:42:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Buyback</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Nectar Lifesciences Ltd has completed its buyback of 3,00,00,000 (Three Crore Only) fully paid-up Equity Shares of face value of INR 1/- each at a price of INR 27/- per Equity Share. The buyback was implemented through the Tender Offer route and was completed on January 13, 2026. The total amount utilized in the buyback was INR 81,00,00,000/- (Indian Rupees Eighty One Crore Only), excluding Transaction Cost.</p><ul><li>Nectar Lifesciences completes buyback of 3 Crore Equity Shares</li><li>Buyback implemented through Tender Offer route</li><li>Buyback price: INR 27/- per Equity Share</li><li>Total amount utilized: INR 81,00,00,000/-</li><li>Completion date: January 13, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1E818F4D-8CB4-438B-9618-7024E69BB43F-081023.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NECTAR LIFESCIENCES LTD. | Category: Buyback</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHREDIGCEM] Shree Digvijay Cement Open Offer Extended to January 19, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHREE+DIGVIJAY+CEMENT+CO.LTD.-%24&title=Shree+Digvijay+Cement+Open+Offer+Extended+to+January+19%2C+2026&newsId=45b467a3-b3c5-4af1-adb3-c2c5e76d86c6&token=NDViNDY3YTMtYjNj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">45b467a3-b3c5-4af1-adb3-c2c5e76d86c6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 02:36:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Open Offer</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Axis Capital Ltd, the Manager to the Offer, has announced an extension of the Tendering Period for the Open Offer of Shree Digvijay Cement Company Ltd. The Offer, initially proposed to close on January 16, 2026, will now close on January 19, 2026. This extension is due to a trading holiday declared on account of the municipal corporation elections in Maharashtra on January 15, 2026. The Public Notice has been published in various newspapers.</p><ul><li>Shree Digvijay Cement Open Offer extended to January 19, 2026</li><li>Extension due to a trading holiday on account of municipal corporation elections in Maharashtra</li><li>Public Notice published in various newspapers</li><li>Axis Capital Ltd is the Manager to the Offer</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/60F40400-F657-4EBA-8AFF-390E7BB308D5-080243.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHREE DIGVIJAY CEMENT CO.LTD.-$ | Category: Open Offer</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SMARTWORKS] Smartworks Coworking Spaces Ltd Enters Public Markets, Maintains Leadership Momentum</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Smartworks+Coworking+Spaces+Ltd&title=Smartworks+Coworking+Spaces+Ltd+Enters+Public+Markets%2C+Maintains+Leadership+Momentum&newsId=9cb6c498-4f91-4118-9763-44669e17e317&token=OWNiNmM0OTgtNGY5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9cb6c498-4f91-4118-9763-44669e17e317</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 02:10:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Smartworks Coworking Spaces Ltd, a leading provider of enterprise workspace infrastructure, has entered the public markets, reflecting years of disciplined execution and a focus on building at national scale. The company operates at the intersection of flexibility and infrastructure, serving long-term demand through large, fully managed campuses. Over the past year, Smartworks has maintained leadership momentum, strengthened its footprint, improved demand visibility, and deepened relationships with large enterprises. The company&apos;s growth is increasingly visible and pre-sold, driven by demand pull rather than speculative supply. As the platform scales, every incremental square foot improves economics, reinforcing the self-sustaining nature of the model. Smartworks is now moving from growth funding to growth monetisation, supported by a maturing portfolio, expanding multi-city client relationships, and an ecosystem designed for multi-decade relevance.</p><ul><li>Smartworks Coworking Spaces Ltd enters public markets</li><li>Maintained leadership momentum while strengthening footprint</li><li>Growing share of growth from existing enterprise clients</li><li>Increasingly visible and pre-sold growth</li><li>Moving from growth funding to growth monetisation</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f980e073-773b-47f6-b0bf-dea78338eb21.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Smartworks Coworking Spaces Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDUSTOWER] Indus Towers Ltd Establishes Subsidiaries in Nigeria and Zambia</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Indus+Towers+Ltd&title=Indus+Towers+Ltd+Establishes+Subsidiaries+in+Nigeria+and+Zambia&newsId=de032edd-10ab-42bd-ad66-2c02ff95835a&token=ZGUwMzJlZGQtMTBh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de032edd-10ab-42bd-ad66-2c02ff95835a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indus Towers Limited has announced the incorporation of step-down subsidiaries in Nigeria and Zambia. Indus Towers Management FZE and Indus Towers Investment FZE, wholly owned subsidiaries of Indus Towers Limited, have incorporated Indus Towers Nigeria Limited and Indus Towers Infra Zambia Limited, respectively. The new entities will carry on the business of establishing, erecting, installing, operating, managing, and maintaining telecommunication towers, masts, poles, antennas, and other related infrastructure for telecommunication, broadcasting, or wireless communication purposes.</p><ul><li>Indus Towers Limited has incorporated step-down subsidiaries in Nigeria and Zambia.</li><li>The new entities will be involved in the business of establishing, erecting, installing, operating, managing, and maintaining telecommunication towers.</li><li>The contribution to initial share capital will be made in cash at face value.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8174fda2-4ed3-46f1-b811-a487f6008ba3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Indus Towers Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KDDL] KDDL Ltd Subsidiary&apos;s Name Changed to Kamla Business Services Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KDDL+LTD.-%24&title=KDDL+Ltd+Subsidiary%27s+Name+Changed+to+Kamla+Business+Services+Limited&newsId=85c2bfc5-83b6-4dba-9293-4e26a4a7efa8&token=ODVjMmJmYzUtODNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85c2bfc5-83b6-4dba-9293-4e26a4a7efa8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>KDDL Ltd has announced that the name of its subsidiary company, previously known as &apos;Kamla Tesio Dials Limited&apos;, has been changed to &apos;Kamla Business Services Limited&apos; with effect from 14th January, 2026. This change has been approved by the Ministry of Corporate Affairs (MCA).</p><ul><li>KDDL Ltd&apos;s subsidiary company name changed to Kamla Business Services Limited</li><li>Change effective from 14th January, 2026</li><li>Approval received from the Ministry of Corporate Affairs (MCA)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1988450a-8ab5-4098-9055-ed9f97570a2e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KDDL LTD.-$ | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MAJESAUT] Majestic Auto Ltd Receives Order Modifying GST Demand from ₹ 9,56,04,387 to ₹ 3,39,238</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MAJESTIC+AUTO+LTD.-%24&title=Majestic+Auto+Ltd+Receives+Order+Modifying+GST+Demand+from+%E2%82%B9+9%2C56%2C04%2C387+to+%E2%82%B9+3%2C39%2C238&newsId=81d7ad19-d132-4561-a8e2-b2dbbddf9222&token=ODFkN2FkMTktZDEz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">81d7ad19-d132-4561-a8e2-b2dbbddf9222</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Majestic Auto Ltd has received an order from the Additional Commissioner Grade-II Appeal, GST Appellate Authority, Gautam Budha Nagar, Uttar Pradesh, modifying the earlier GST demand of ₹ 9,56,04,387 to ₹ 3,39,238. The order was passed pursuant to an appeal filed by the company on December 30, 2023, against an order of Deputy Commissioner (GST) that raised a demand of ₹ 956.04 Lakhs on the company in December 2023 for the financial year 2017-18. The appeal has been accepted by the Appellate Authority, and the demand has been modified to ₹ 3,39,238. The contingent liability appearing in the Notes to Accounts of the company on this account will stand extinguished. The other expenses will increase by ₹ 3,39,238, and the Profit before tax &amp; Profit after tax will reduce by the same amount during the current financial year 2025-26. No finding of deliberate violation has been recorded by the Appellate Authority.</p><ul><li>Majestic Auto Ltd receives order modifying GST demand from ₹ 9,56,04,387 to ₹ 3,39,238</li><li>Order passed pursuant to an appeal filed by the company on December 30, 2023</li><li>No finding of deliberate violation recorded by the Appellate Authority</li><li>Contingent liability appearing in the Notes to Accounts of the company to be extinguished</li><li>Other expenses to increase by ₹ 3,39,238 and Profit before tax &amp; Profit after tax to reduce by the same amount during the current financial year 2025-26</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3946677e-43e8-4def-a9cc-fd33c470676e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MAJESTIC AUTO LTD.-$ | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUNPHARMA] Sun Pharma Announces the Availability of UNLOXCYT™ (cosibelimab-ipdl) for Advanced Cutaneous Squamous Cell Carcinoma (aCSCC)</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SUN+PHARMACEUTICAL+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Sun+Pharma+Announces+the+Availability+of+UNLOXCYT%E2%84%A2+%28cosibelimab-ipdl%29+for+Advanced+Cutaneous+Squamous+Cell+Carcinoma+%28aCSCC%29&newsId=ba86a9eb-cb40-4d88-af07-066b4fac5430&token=YmE4NmE5ZWItY2I0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba86a9eb-cb40-4d88-af07-066b4fac5430</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Limited has announced the availability of UNLOXCYT™ (cosibelimab-ipdl) for the treatment of adults in the U.S. with metastatic cutaneous squamous cell carcinoma (mCSCC) or locally advanced CSCC (laCSCC) who are not candidates for curative surgery or curative radiation. UNLOXCYT offers a balanced treatment approach with long-term data confirming durable efficacy and a proven tolerability profile. It has a multifaceted mechanism of action that helps restore the adaptive immune response and engages the innate immune system while preserving PD-L2 signaling.</p><ul><li>Sun Pharma announces the availability of UNLOXCYT™ (cosibelimab-ipdl) for the treatment of adults with metastatic cutaneous squamous cell carcinoma (mCSCC) or locally advanced CSCC (laCSCC) who are not candidates for curative surgery or curative radiation.</li><li>UNLOXCYT offers a balanced treatment approach with long-term data confirming durable efficacy and a proven tolerability profile.</li><li>UNLOXCYT has a multifaceted mechanism of action that helps restore the adaptive immune response and engages the innate immune system while preserving PD-L2 signaling.</li><li>UNLOXCYT is now available in the U.S. for healthcare professionals to prescribe.</li><li>Sun Pharma is committed to ensuring access from day one with the UNLOXCYT SUPPORT™ patient access and affordability program.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/08817f40-0386-46c4-8c55-9556e2e44513.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SUN PHARMACEUTICAL INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>