<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 04:45:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[PREMIERPOL] Manvi Goenka Acquires and Disposes of Premier Polyfilm Limited Shares Through Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PREMIER+POLYFILM+LTD.&title=Manvi+Goenka+Acquires+and+Disposes+of+Premier+Polyfilm+Limited+Shares+Through+Open+Market&newsId=821972a3-8e83-4497-9102-0769484fd84c&token=ODIxOTcyYTMtOGU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">821972a3-8e83-4497-9102-0769484fd84c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 04:42:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Manvi Goenka, an immediate relative of Premier Polyfilm Limited promoters, has acquired and disposed of equity shares of the company through the open market. The total number of shares acquired is 3,000, which is 0.003% of the total shareholding of the company. The shares were purchased on 30th January 2026 and disposed of on 29th and 30th January 2026. The total diluted share capital of the company is 2,09,48,495 Equity Shares of Rs. 5/- after the said acquisition.</p><ul><li>Manvi Goenka, an immediate relative of Premier Polyfilm Limited promoters, has acquired and disposed of equity shares of the company through the open market.</li><li>The total number of shares acquired is 3,000, which is 0.003% of the total shareholding of the company.</li><li>The shares were purchased on 30th January 2026 and disposed of on 29th and 30th January 2026.</li><li>The total diluted share capital of the company is 2,09,48,495 Equity Shares of Rs. 5/- after the said acquisition.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/E6ECE4EC_FBE3_4B98_B3AD_27B09722B3DD_095207.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PREMIER POLYFILM LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ORIENTBELL] Mahendra K. Daga Acquires Shares in Orient Bell Ltd. as Per SEBI Regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ORIENT+BELL+LIMITED-%24&title=Mahendra+K.+Daga+Acquires+Shares+in+Orient+Bell+Ltd.+as+Per+SEBI+Regulations&newsId=c4716ff2-5b83-44a9-843f-fe6455ab8648&token=YzQ3MTZmZjItNWI4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4716ff2-5b83-44a9-843f-fe6455ab8648</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 04:39:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mahendra K. Daga, a prominent figure, has disclosed his shareholding in Orient Bell Ltd. under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. The disclosure was made in the promoter &amp; promoter’s group or PAC(s) category. The acquisition details indicate that Mr. Daga held 44.308% shares before the acquisition, which increased to 55.8% after the acquisition. The acquisition took place through the open market on 30th January 2026. The total equity share capital and total voting capital of the TC before and after the acquisition have also been provided.</p><ul><li>Mahendra K. Daga acquires shares in Orient Bell Ltd.</li><li>Acquisition made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</li><li>Acquisition details: Pre-acquisition - 44.308%, Post-acquisition - 55.8%.</li><li>Acquisition took place through the open market.</li><li>Details of equity share capital and total voting capital of the TC before and after the acquisition provided.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/60F5E325_CA3E_4CEA_AEF0_A8B3F5908AC4_100727.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ORIENT BELL LIMITED-$ | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BRAHMINFRA] Brahmaputra Infrastructure Ltd Receives New Order of Rs. 62.03 Crores from Water Resource Department Assam</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BRAHMAPUTRA+INFRASTRUCTURE+LTD.&title=Brahmaputra+Infrastructure+Ltd+Receives+New+Order+of+Rs.+62.03+Crores+from+Water+Resource+Department+Assam&newsId=2e512cf3-f7b2-4f7c-8315-85777c8cc134&token=MmU1MTJjZjMtZjdi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e512cf3-f7b2-4f7c-8315-85777c8cc134</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 04:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Brahmaputra Infrastructure Ltd has received a new order from the Water Resource Department Assam for the procurement of works for underwater riverbank protection works (Section 1) and above water riverbank protection works (Section 2) in Jorhat subproject (Sivasagar, Jorhat and Golaghat Districts), Package No. W-AF-03-RP-JH, Lot 1 under ADB&apos;s Climate Resilient Brahmaputra Integrated Flood and Riverbank Erosion Risk Management Project in Assam. The total amount of the order is Rs. 62.03 Crores.</p><ul><li>Brahmaputra Infrastructure Ltd has received a new order from the Water Resource Department Assam.</li><li>The order is for the procurement of works for underwater riverbank protection works (Section 1) and above water riverbank protection works (Section 2) in Jorhat subproject.</li><li>The total amount of the order is Rs. 62.03 Crores.</li><li>The order is under ADB&apos;s Climate Resilient Brahmaputra Integrated Flood and Riverbank Erosion Risk Management Project in Assam.</li><li>The order is awarded in the name of GHV Infra Projects - BIL (JV)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fb429af4-6c7c-4232-bfee-99e230ff4040.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BRAHMAPUTRA INFRASTRUCTURE LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MRO-TEK] Umiya Holding Pvt Ltd Acquires Shares in Umiya Buildcon Ltd, Increasing Holding to 37.84%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MRO-TEK+Realty+Ltd&title=Umiya+Holding+Pvt+Ltd+Acquires+Shares+in+Umiya+Buildcon+Ltd%2C+Increasing+Holding+to+37.84%25&newsId=89fc413e-a3c6-4ab4-87ac-4b975de608e5&token=ODlmYzQxM2UtYTNj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">89fc413e-a3c6-4ab4-87ac-4b975de608e5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 04:35:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Umiya Holding Pvt Ltd has acquired shares in Umiya Buildcon Ltd (formerly MRO-TEK Realty Limited), increasing its holding to 37.84%. The acquisition was made through the open market. The total number of shares carrying voting rights acquired is 70,77,716. This acquisition is in compliance with the SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</p><ul><li>Umiya Holding Pvt Ltd has acquired shares in Umiya Buildcon Ltd, increasing its holding to 37.84%</li><li>The acquisition was made through the open market</li><li>The total number of shares carrying voting rights acquired is 70,77,716</li><li>The acquisition is in compliance with the SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011</li><li>Umiya Buildcon Limited (formerly MRO-TEK Realty Limited) is the target company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/55E47538_0B84_437F_97CA_E81E813AE041_100345.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MRO-TEK Realty Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GTIL] Madhusudan Sarda, Promoter and Managing Director of Gabion Technologies India Ltd, Acquires Shares Worth 41.448%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Gabion+Technologies+India+Ltd&title=Madhusudan+Sarda%2C+Promoter+and+Managing+Director+of+Gabion+Technologies+India+Ltd%2C+Acquires+Shares+Worth+41.448%25&newsId=6f9d5d83-5122-40e8-8b7c-b38b2558b38a&token=NmY5ZDVkODMtNTEy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f9d5d83-5122-40e8-8b7c-b38b2558b38a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 04:35:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Madhusudan Sarda, Promoter and Managing Director of Gabion Technologies India Ltd, has acquired shares worth 41.448% through open market purchase on 1st February 2026. This acquisition is in compliance with Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeover) Regulations, 2011 &amp; Regulation 7(2) of the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Madhusudan Sarda, Promoter and Managing Director of Gabion Technologies India Ltd, acquires shares worth 41.448%</li><li>Shares acquired through open market purchase on 1st February 2026</li><li>Acquisition complies with Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeover) Regulations, 2011 &amp; Regulation 7(2) of the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/967DCC9B_CE9C_4890_8815_37320788B3B5_100059.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Gabion Technologies India Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PREMIERPOL] Premier Polyfilm Ltd Receives Disclosure from Promoter Group Company D L Millar &amp; Co Ltd under SEBI Regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PREMIER+POLYFILM+LTD.&title=Premier+Polyfilm+Ltd+Receives+Disclosure+from+Promoter+Group+Company+D+L+Millar+%26+Co+Ltd+under+SEBI+Regulations&newsId=72841cbc-0ccc-4f97-b55b-929428732b38&token=NzI4NDFjYmMtMGNj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72841cbc-0ccc-4f97-b55b-929428732b38</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 04:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Premier Polyfilm Ltd has received a disclosure from its promoter group company, D L Millar &amp; Co Ltd, under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. D L Millar &amp; Co Ltd has acquired 24,648 equity shares, which is 0.03% of the total shareholding of Premier Polyfilm Ltd, through the open market on 1st February 2026.</p><ul><li>Premier Polyfilm Ltd has received a disclosure from its promoter group company, D L Millar &amp; Co Ltd, under SEBI regulations.</li><li>D L Millar &amp; Co Ltd has acquired 24,648 equity shares, which is 0.03% of the total shareholding of Premier Polyfilm Ltd.</li><li>The acquisition has been made through the open market on 1st February 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/FDA1F85F_6AF7_4D23_9BB3_89B7375EC60B_095801.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PREMIER POLYFILM LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[REPCOHOME] Bandhan Mutual Fund Acquires 27,000 Shares of Repco Home Finance, Increasing Holding to 7.0355%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=REPCO+HOME+FINANCE+LTD.&title=Bandhan+Mutual+Fund+Acquires+27%2C000+Shares+of+Repco+Home+Finance%2C+Increasing+Holding+to+7.0355%25&newsId=cf701c53-267c-46c5-aa49-2908128a8246&token=Y2Y3MDFjNTMtMjY3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cf701c53-267c-46c5-aa49-2908128a8246</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 04:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bandhan Mutual Fund has acquired 27,000 equity shares of Repco Home Finance Limited on January 29, 2026, through its schemes. This acquisition has increased Bandhan Mutual Fund&apos;s holding in the company from 5.0132% to 7.0355%.</p><ul><li>Bandhan Mutual Fund acquired 27,000 equity shares of Repco Home Finance Limited on January 29, 2026.</li><li>This acquisition increased Bandhan Mutual Fund&apos;s holding in the company from 5.0132% to 7.0355%.</li><li>The acquisition was made through Bandhan Mutual Fund&apos;s schemes.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6CA89DCB_AD17_4DF2_AE37_7055573262E1_095918.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: REPCO HOME FINANCE LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PREMIERPOL] Premier Polyfilm Ltd: DL Millar &amp; Co Ltd Acquires and Sells Shares Through Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PREMIER+POLYFILM+LTD.&title=Premier+Polyfilm+Ltd%3A+DL+Millar+%26+Co+Ltd+Acquires+and+Sells+Shares+Through+Open+Market&newsId=9b6bd8ed-590a-469e-8d09-de51278a6b2e&token=OWI2YmQ4ZWQtNTkw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b6bd8ed-590a-469e-8d09-de51278a6b2e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 04:28:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>DL Millar &amp; Co Ltd, a promoter group company of Premier Polyfilm Limited, has acquired and sold equity shares of Premier Polyfilm Limited through the open market. The transaction took place on 1st February 2026, where DL Millar &amp; Co Ltd acquired 24,648 shares, which is 0.03% of the total shareholding of the target company.</p><ul><li>DL Millar &amp; Co Ltd, a promoter group company of Premier Polyfilm Limited, has acquired and sold shares of the target company through the open market.</li><li>The transaction took place on 1st February 2026.</li><li>DL Millar &amp; Co Ltd acquired 24,648 shares, which is 0.03% of the total shareholding of the target company.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/CEB13F32_DD58_4B36_A1FB_E6D70F1E6667_095653.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PREMIER POLYFILM LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EPIC] EPIC Energy Collaborates with REFNIC for Lithium-ion Battery Recycling and Second-life Battery Initiatives</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=EPIC+ENERGY+LTD.-%24&title=EPIC+Energy+Collaborates+with+REFNIC+for+Lithium-ion+Battery+Recycling+and+Second-life+Battery+Initiatives&newsId=5067b0b5-a8eb-4081-92aa-5998ffa7ff29&token=NTA2N2IwYjUtYThl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5067b0b5-a8eb-4081-92aa-5998ffa7ff29</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 04:28:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>EPIC Energy Limited has entered into a collaboration with REFNIC, a brand operated by Zetrance Technology Private Limited, for the development of its lithium-ion battery recycling and second-life battery initiatives through its Special Purpose Vehicle, Swachchha Urja Nirman LLP (SUN LLP). The collaboration includes the design, engineering, integration, installation, and commissioning of a lithium-ion battery shredding facility and a second-life battery assembly plant with an installed processing capacity of approximately 10 MWh per month. The proposed facilities are intended to support the responsible recycling, repurposing, and value recovery of end-of-life lithium-ion batteries, in alignment with EPIC Energy’s long-term strategy focused on sustainable energy systems and circular-economy solutions.</p><ul><li>EPIC Energy has entered into a collaboration with REFNIC for the development of its lithium-ion battery recycling and second-life battery initiatives.</li><li>The collaboration includes the design, engineering, integration, installation, and commissioning of a lithium-ion battery shredding facility and a second-life battery assembly plant.</li><li>The proposed facilities have an installed processing capacity of approximately 10 MWh per month.</li><li>The collaboration is in line with EPIC Energy’s long-term strategy focused on sustainable energy systems and circular-economy solutions.</li><li>The first facility is proposed to be set up at Wada, Maharashtra, with a lithium-ion battery shredding capacity of approximately 500 kilograms per hour of black-mass production and a second-life battery assembly capacity of approximately 10 MWh per month.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/28703c22-0173-434c-a283-db886cc995a5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: EPIC ENERGY LTD.-$ | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TUNITEX] Niraj Shah Acquires 13,06,31,000 Equity Shares of Tuni Textile Mills Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TUNI+TEXTILE+MILLS+LTD.&title=Niraj+Shah+Acquires+13%2C06%2C31%2C000+Equity+Shares+of+Tuni+Textile+Mills+Ltd&newsId=b52717d3-c6c5-4764-ad3c-fd66047d3307&token=YjUyNzE3ZDMtYzZj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b52717d3-c6c5-4764-ad3c-fd66047d3307</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 04:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Exchange has received a disclosure under Regulation 29(1) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011 from Niraj Shah. The disclosure is regarding the acquisition of 13,06,31,000 Equity Shares of Tuni Textile Mills Ltd. The acquisition was made before the acquisition set of Rel and after the acquisition set of Be. The total voting capital of the company will be 26,12,62,000 Equity Shares after the acquisition.</p><ul><li>Niraj Shah acquires 13,06,31,000 Equity Shares of Tuni Textile Mills Ltd</li><li>The acquisition was made before the acquisition set of Rel and after the acquisition set of Be</li><li>The total voting capital of the company will be 26,12,62,000 Equity Shares after the acquisition</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/EC03D1A6_3F24_46C0_B987_20280BAB18A4_095350.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TUNI TEXTILE MILLS LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>