<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 04:00:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[AVANTEL] Avantel Ltd Receives Purchase Order Worth Rs.11.19 Cr from NewSpace India Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AVANTEL+LTD.&title=Avantel+Ltd+Receives+Purchase+Order+Worth+Rs.11.19+Cr+from+NewSpace+India+Limited&newsId=65e37a07-642c-4c12-adcc-81843e84ba09&token=NjVlMzdhMDctNjQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65e37a07-642c-4c12-adcc-81843e84ba09</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 03:54:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Avantel Ltd has announced the receipt of a purchase order worth Rs.11.19 Crores (Excl. Taxes) from M/s. NewSpace India Limited. The order is for the Supply, Installation and Commissioning of Devices for Xponders. The order is to be executed by July 2026.</p><ul><li>Avantel Ltd has received a purchase order worth Rs.11.19 Crores from M/s. NewSpace India Limited.</li><li>The order is for the Supply, Installation and Commissioning of Devices for Xponders.</li><li>The order is to be executed by July 2026.</li><li>The announcement was made in line with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3467baad-864a-469b-b898-d47543124f6b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AVANTEL LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NUCLEUS] Nucleus Software Celebrates 25 Years of Partnership &amp; Innovation in Japan, Reaffirms Long-Term Commitment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NUCLEUS+SOFTWARE+EXPORTS+LTD.&title=Nucleus+Software+Celebrates+25+Years+of+Partnership+%26+Innovation+in+Japan%2C+Reaffirms+Long-Term+Commitment&newsId=fd8c2e65-ae85-4417-9530-34a5664cf00d&token=ZmQ4YzJlNjUtYWU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd8c2e65-ae85-4417-9530-34a5664cf00d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 03:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Partnership</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Nucleus Software Japan K.K. celebrated 25 years of partnership and innovation in Japan with a distinguished gathering at Imperial Hotel, Tokyo. The event was enriched by the presence of several distinguished leaders from Japan’s financial ecosystem. Speakers included Masamoto Yashiro, Former Chairman &amp; CEO of Shinsei Bank, and Akio Isowa, Senior Managing Executive Officer &amp; Group CDIO of SMBC Group. The evening also featured a fireside discussion on ‘SBI Shinsei Bank Transformation Journey &amp; What Lies Ahead.’ Nucleus Software expressed gratitude to partners and guests, reaffirming its dedication to supporting Japan with platforms engineered for stability, security, and long-term value.</p><ul><li>Nucleus Software Japan K.K. marks 25 years of partnership and innovation in Japan.</li><li>The celebration was held at Imperial Hotel, Tokyo with distinguished leaders from Japan’s financial ecosystem.</li><li>Speakers included Masamoto Yashiro, Former Chairman &amp; CEO of Shinsei Bank, and Akio Isowa, Senior Managing Executive Officer &amp; Group CDIO of SMBC Group.</li><li>A fireside discussion was held on ‘SBI Shinsei Bank Transformation Journey &amp; What Lies Ahead.’</li><li>Nucleus Software reaffirmed its dedication to supporting Japan with platforms engineered for stability, security, and long-term value.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dede8d78-6a2e-4dd2-b8c4-857021c9245d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NUCLEUS SOFTWARE EXPORTS LTD. | Category: Partnership</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GRANULES] Granules Pharmaceuticals Receives FDA Tentative Approval for Generic Amphetamine Extended-Release Tablets with 180-Day Exclusivity</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GRANULES+INDIA+LTD.-%24&title=Granules+Pharmaceuticals+Receives+FDA+Tentative+Approval+for+Generic+Amphetamine+Extended-Release+Tablets+with+180-Day+Exclusivity&newsId=e368fee4-f44e-48f5-86e0-808483389830&token=ZTM2OGZlZTQtZjQ0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e368fee4-f44e-48f5-86e0-808483389830</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 03:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Granules Pharmaceuticals, Inc., a subsidiary of Granules India Limited, has received Tentative Approval (TA) from the U.S. Food and Drug Administration (FDA) for its Abbreviated New Drug Application (ANDA) for generic Amphetamine Extended-Release Tablets in strengths of 5 mg, 10 mg, 15 mg, and 20 mg. The product is indicated for the treatment of Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD) and has an estimated market size of approximately USD 41 million. The Granules ANDA has been determined to be eligible for 180-day exclusivity by the FDA, reinforcing its growing capabilities in developing and commercializing complex and differentiated generic products for the U.S. market.</p><ul><li>Granules Pharmaceuticals, Inc. receives Tentative Approval from the FDA for generic Amphetamine Extended-Release Tablets.</li><li>The product is indicated for the treatment of Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD) and has an estimated market size of approximately USD 41 million.</li><li>The Granules ANDA has been determined to be eligible for 180-day exclusivity by the FDA.</li><li>This approval marks the second consecutive approval from Granules’ subsidiary within a period of a few weeks.</li><li>The achievement highlights Granules’ expanding capabilities in complex formulation development and regulatory execution.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/54f0aa08-3245-444b-81ee-ebf6eeff547f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GRANULES INDIA LTD.-$ | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ANGELONE] Angel One Ltd Reports Strong Q3 FY26 and December 2025 Business Update</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Angel+One+Ltd&title=Angel+One+Ltd+Reports+Strong+Q3+FY26+and+December+2025+Business+Update&newsId=709a448d-5e08-4384-b70b-261ac544dea8&token=NzA5YTQ0OGQtNWUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">709a448d-5e08-4384-b70b-261ac544dea8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 02:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Angel One Ltd, a leading financial services company, has reported its business updates for December 2025 and Q3 FY26. The company has seen a gradual growth across various parameters such as client acquisitions, executed orders, and average client funding book. The total number of trading days for Q3 FY26 was 61, with a client base of 35.71 million. The gross client acquisition for the quarter was 1.75 million, and the average client funding book stood at INR 58.58 billion. The number of orders executed during the quarter was 380.07 million, with an average daily orders count of 6.23 million. The unique MF SIPs registered were 2,321.22 thousand. The company&apos;s ADTO based on notional turnover for overall, F&amp;O, and cash segments showed a significant increase. The retail turnover market share based on option premium turnover for overall equity and F&amp;O also saw an increase. The company has been focusing on making its offerings broad-based and client-centric.</p><ul><li>Q3 FY26 and December 2025 business updates reported by Angel One Ltd</li><li>Gradual growth in client acquisitions, executed orders, and average client funding book</li><li>61 number of trading days in Q3 FY26 with a client base of 35.71 million</li><li>1.75 million gross client acquisition and INR 58.58 billion average client funding book in Q3 FY26</li><li>380.07 million orders executed in Q3 FY26 with an average daily orders count of 6.23 million</li><li>2,321.22 thousand unique MF SIPs registered</li><li>Significant increase in ADTO based on notional turnover for overall, F&amp;O, and cash segments</li><li>Increase in retail turnover market share based on option premium turnover for overall equity and F&amp;O</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d0bfed95-38dc-46f2-8df5-3e0ef018b298.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Angel One Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LEMONTREE] Warburg Pincus-Lemon Tree Hotels Stake Acquisition Report Denied by Lemon Tree</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Lemon+Tree+Hotels+Ltd&title=Warburg+Pincus-Lemon+Tree+Hotels+Stake+Acquisition+Report+Denied+by+Lemon+Tree&newsId=ac6cfbc2-ab7b-4a71-b57f-d32c044257ba&token=YWM2Y2ZiYzItYWI3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac6cfbc2-ab7b-4a71-b57f-d32c044257ba</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 00:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Lemon Tree Hotels Ltd has denied the news report published on www.moneycontrol.com dated January 7, 2026, captioned &apos;Warburg Pincus may acquire stake in Lemon Tree Hotels, reports CNBC-TV18; shares up 5%&apos;. The company clarified that no negotiations, discussions, agreements, or proposals are ongoing or have been approved in relation to any acquisition by Warburg Pincus of shares of Lemon Tree Hotels Limited. The company also stated that they have complied with the applicable disclosure requirements under Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, and as on date, there is no information, event, or decision in relation to the Company requiring mandatory disclosure under the LODR Regulations and applicable SEBI circulars which has not been disclosed to the stock exchanges.</p><ul><li>Lemon Tree Hotels denied the media report regarding Warburg Pincus acquiring stake in the company.</li><li>No negotiations, discussions, agreements, or proposals are ongoing or have been approved between Lemon Tree Hotels and Warburg Pincus.</li><li>The company has complied with the applicable disclosure requirements under Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li><li>There is no information, event, or decision in relation to the Company requiring mandatory disclosure under the LODR Regulations and applicable SEBI circulars which has not been disclosed to the stock exchanges.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1e8882fb-e8d7-45c3-9b6f-6704ac4d6912.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Lemon Tree Hotels Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MCX] SEBI Approves MD&amp;CEO Appointment for Multi Commodity Exchange Subsidiary</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MULTI+COMMODITY+EXCHANGE+OF+INDIA+LTD.&title=SEBI+Approves+MD%26CEO+Appointment+for+Multi+Commodity+Exchange+Subsidiary&newsId=32be8188-356b-4420-bf30-1e7bc4233e54&token=MzJiZTgxODgtMzU2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32be8188-356b-4420-bf30-1e7bc4233e54</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 00:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Multi Commodity Exchange Clearing Corporation Limited (MCXCCL), a wholly owned subsidiary of Multi Commodity Exchange of India Ltd, has received regulatory approval from SEBI for the appointment of Mr. Rishi Nathany as the Managing Director and CEO of MCXCCL. The appointment is subject to Mr. Nathany accepting the offer and obtaining approval from the shareholders of MCXCCL.</p><ul><li>SEBI approves MD&amp;CEO appointment for Multi Commodity Exchange subsidiary</li><li>Mr. Rishi Nathany to be the Managing Director and CEO of MCXCCL</li><li>Appointment subject to acceptance of offer and shareholder approval</li><li>MCXCCL is a wholly owned subsidiary of Multi Commodity Exchange of India Ltd</li><li>Regulatory approval received on January 7, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/11dee815-35ff-4b0b-aaf8-acf79f942a4a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MULTI COMMODITY EXCHANGE OF INDIA LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AVG] AVG Logistics Enters Liquid Logistics Through Train, Aiming to Enhance Safe and Reliable Chemical Transportation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AVG+Logistics+Ltd&title=AVG+Logistics+Enters+Liquid+Logistics+Through+Train%2C+Aiming+to+Enhance+Safe+and+Reliable+Chemical+Transportation&newsId=3560fda2-d3be-41be-a9ef-28c93fd9f9ac&token=MzU2MGZkYTItZDNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3560fda2-d3be-41be-a9ef-28c93fd9f9ac</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 20:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>AVG Logistics Ltd. has launched the transportation of liquid cargo using high-grade ISO tanks on trains, starting from January 07, 2026. This new venture is expected to generate an annual revenue of approximately Rs. 22-24 crore. The company has partnered with Central Warehousing Corporation for the long-term lease of its flatbed train and will offer cost-efficient, environmentally sustainable, and time-bound movement of liquid cargo. This initiative aligns with AVG Logistics’ focus on sustainability and operational efficiency.</p><ul><li>AVG Logistics launched a new business vertical for liquid cargo transportation using high-grade ISO tanks on trains.</li><li>The new venture is expected to generate an annual revenue of approximately Rs. 22-24 crore.</li><li>The company has partnered with Central Warehousing Corporation for the long-term lease of its flatbed train.</li><li>This initiative aims to offer cost-efficient, environmentally sustainable, and time-bound movement of liquid cargo.</li><li>The launch aligns with AVG Logistics’ focus on sustainability and operational efficiency.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3fd43065-d588-47dd-bcb6-43fa153cca0b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AVG Logistics Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RELHOME] Reliance Home Finance Reschedules CoC Meeting, Umesh Balaram Sonkar Appointed as Resolution Professional</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Reliance+Home+Finance+Ltd&title=Reliance+Home+Finance+Reschedules+CoC+Meeting%2C+Umesh+Balaram+Sonkar+Appointed+as+Resolution+Professional&newsId=c14fb477-143d-495f-9c5e-55078bad0e51&token=YzE0ZmI0NzctMTQz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c14fb477-143d-495f-9c5e-55078bad0e51</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:21:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Reliance Home Finance Ltd. has rescheduled the 5th Meeting of the Committee of Creditors (CoC) to January 8, 2026, at 11:30 A.M. (IST) through Video Conferencing. The meeting was initially scheduled for January 7, 2026. Umesh Balaram Sonkar has been appointed as the Resolution Professional in the matter of Reliance Home Finance Limited under Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP).</p><ul><li>Reliance Home Finance Ltd. reschedules the 5th Meeting of the Committee of Creditors (CoC) to January 8, 2026</li><li>The meeting was initially scheduled for January 7, 2026, and will now be held through Video Conferencing</li><li>Umesh Balaram Sonkar appointed as the Resolution Professional in the matter of Reliance Home Finance Limited under CIRP</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f9c87a19-cfb0-4569-8650-124e547e9ad2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Reliance Home Finance Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MOTHERSON] Samvardhana Motherson International Completes Joint Venture with Egtronics Co. Ltd.</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Samvardhana+Motherson+International+Ltd&title=Samvardhana+Motherson+International+Completes+Joint+Venture+with+Egtronics+Co.+Ltd.&newsId=d16ebafa-ff4e-448b-8933-fe6ca4424a47&token=ZDE2ZWJhZmEtZmY0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d16ebafa-ff4e-448b-8933-fe6ca4424a47</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:11:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Samvardhana Motherson International Limited has completed the formation of a joint venture with Egtronics Co. Ltd., a South Korean company. This joint venture, established on January 07, 2026, is designed to design, develop, manufacture, and assemble clean mobility related vehicle electronics. The product portfolio includes DC-DC converters, auxiliary inverters, traction inverters, on-board chargers, power distribution units, or a combination of these for application in automobile and other industries. The equity shareholding of Motherson Egtronics Electronics Solutions Limited, the wholly owned subsidiary of the Company, is held by the Company and Egtronics in the ratio of 51% and 49%, respectively.</p><ul><li>Samvardhana Motherson International Limited has completed a joint venture with Egtronics Co. Ltd.</li><li>The joint venture is established to design, develop, manufacture, and assemble clean mobility related vehicle electronics.</li><li>The product portfolio includes DC-DC converters, auxiliary inverters, traction inverters, on-board chargers, power distribution units, or a combination of these.</li><li>The joint venture is applicable for automobile and other industries.</li><li>The equity shareholding of Motherson Egtronics Electronics Solutions Limited is held by the Company and Egtronics in the ratio of 51% and 49%, respectively.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c5394faa-4962-4b90-9ba9-cbee7a845386.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADORMUL] Thrive Future Habitats Ltd. Confirms Relodgement of Transfer of Physical Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADOR+MULTIPRODUCTS+LTD.&title=Thrive+Future+Habitats+Ltd.+Confirms+Relodgement+of+Transfer+of+Physical+Shares&newsId=47d6500b-6229-4d3d-af5a-2b068e55279d&token=NDdkNjUwMGItNjIy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47d6500b-6229-4d3d-af5a-2b068e55279d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Thrive Future Habitats Ltd. has published a notice on its website to inform shareholders about the relodgement of transfer requests for physical shares. The notice was published in accordance with SEBI Circular SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97. The company received no requests for the relodgement of shares for transfer cum demat for the six-month period from July 07, 2025, till January 06, 2026. The company&apos;s Registrar and Share Transfer Agent, BgSE Financials Limited, also confirmed no requests were received, processed, approved, or rejected during this period.</p><ul><li>Thrive Future Habitats Ltd. publishes notice for relodgement of transfer requests for physical shares.</li><li>Notice published in accordance with SEBI Circular SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97.</li><li>No requests received, processed, approved, or rejected for the six-month period from July 07, 2025, till January 06, 2026.</li><li>Confirmation from the company&apos;s Registrar and Share Transfer Agent, BgSE Financials Limited.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ec03e65b-4962-4a29-8a6b-d17f67bc7a80.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADOR MULTIPRODUCTS LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>