<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:47:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[GODREJPROP] Godrej Properties Sells Over INR 1,000 Crore Worth of Plots at Panipat Project Launch</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Godrej+Properties+Ltd&title=Godrej+Properties+Sells+Over+INR+1%2C000+Crore+Worth+of+Plots+at+Panipat+Project+Launch&newsId=47a065d0-5557-47c9-b629-e874d95b58dd&token=NDdhMDY1ZDAtNTU1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47a065d0-5557-47c9-b629-e874d95b58dd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 01:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Godrej Properties Limited (GPL), a leading real estate developer in India, announced that it has sold plots worth over INR 1,000 crore at the launch of its premium plotted development, Evora Estate, in Panipat. The company has sold over 600 plots, spanning around 8 lakh square feet of saleable area since its launch in December 2025. This is GPL&apos;s first project in Panipat and its most successful ever plotted development launch by value of sales achieved. The project, located on NH 44A, spans 43 acres and features a refined Mediterranean theme, complete with a luxurious clubhouse and premium lifestyle amenities.</p><ul><li>Godrej Properties sells plots worth over INR 1,000 crore at the launch of Evora Estate in Panipat.</li><li>Over 600 plots sold, spanning around 8 lakh square feet of saleable area since December 2025.</li><li>Evora Estate is Godrej Properties&apos; first project in Panipat and its most successful plotted development launch by value of sales achieved.</li><li>The project is strategically located on NH 44A and spans 43 acres with a refined Mediterranean theme.</li><li>The project marks Godrej Properties&apos; fourth addition to its portfolio of residential plotted townships in North India.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/54a89e15-0574-4681-a7fc-354c9ab4837a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Godrej Properties Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PAYTM*] One 97 Communications Ltd. Receives Compounding Order from RBI Under FEMA with No Material Impact</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=One+97+Communications+Ltd&title=One+97+Communications+Ltd.+Receives+Compounding+Order+from+RBI+Under+FEMA+with+No+Material+Impact&newsId=50312b0d-2e79-4c24-80e3-8965f134e314&token=NTAzMTJiMGQtMmU3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50312b0d-2e79-4c24-80e3-8965f134e314</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>One 97 Communications Ltd. has received a compounding order from the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) under the Foreign Exchange Management Act, 1999 (FEMA). The order, dated February 02, 2026, pertains to certain investments made in Little Internet Private Limited by Little Internet Singapore Pte Ltd. The RBI has imposed a compounding fee of INR 18.76 lakhs (Indian Rupees Eighteen Lakhs Seventy-Six Thousand). The Company is in the process of making the payment for the compounding fee, pursuant to which this item shall stand disposed. This compounding has no material impact on the Company’s financials or operations.</p><ul><li>One 97 Communications Ltd. received a compounding order from the RBI under FEMA.</li><li>The order pertains to certain investments made in Little Internet Private Limited by Little Internet Singapore Pte Ltd.</li><li>The RBI has imposed a compounding fee of INR 18.76 lakhs.</li><li>The Company is in the process of making the payment for the compounding fee.</li><li>This compounding has no material impact on the Company’s financials or operations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f04e70e1-2720-463a-95e1-3f4d1efaa963.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: One 97 Communications Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TEJNAKSH] Tejnaksh Healthcare Ltd to Approve Q3 Results on Feb 7, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Tejnaksh+Healthcare+Ltd&title=Tejnaksh+Healthcare+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+Results+on+Feb+7%2C+2026&newsId=3fb40c5e-dac4-4080-9e89-a981f58db109&token=M2ZiNDBjNWUtZGFj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3fb40c5e-dac4-4080-9e89-a981f58db109</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 19:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tejnaksh Healthcare Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 7, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will be held at Shivprasad Harihar Singh Compound, Jogeshwari East, Mumbai. The trading window for dealing in the shares of the company was closed on December 28, 2025, and will remain closed until 48 hours after the declaration of the un-audited financial results.</p><ul><li>Tejnaksh Healthcare Ltd to approve Q3 results on Feb 7, 2026</li><li>The meeting will be held at Shivprasad Harihar Singh Compound, Jogeshwari East, Mumbai</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the shares of the company was closed on Dec 28, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a20a2494-783a-4b44-a065-db7613fbc9c2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Tejnaksh Healthcare Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HEMIPROP] Hemisphere Properties India Ltd: Union of India vs. Tata Communications Ltd. Case Disposed, Hemisphere Properties India Limited vs. P. Venkata Rao Second Appeal Allowed</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Hemisphere+Properties+India+Ltd&title=Hemisphere+Properties+India+Ltd%3A+Union+of+India+vs.+Tata+Communications+Ltd.+Case+Disposed%2C+Hemisphere+Properties+India+Limited+vs.+P.+Venkata+Rao+Second+Appeal+Allowed&newsId=090dc7eb-d81f-40dd-8551-d15e76a0815a&token=MDkwZGM3ZWItZDgx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">090dc7eb-d81f-40dd-8551-d15e76a0815a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pursuant to Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, Hemisphere Properties India Ltd. informs about the disposed case bearing LAC No. 04-2014 renumbered as LAC No. 19-2016 titled Union of India &amp; Others vs. Tata Communications Ltd. The case pertains to compensation payable by Delhi Metro Rail Corporation Limited in respect of the land situated at Greater Kailash, New Delhi. Additionally, the company announces that the case bearing Second Appeal No. 935/2024 titled Hemisphere Properties India Limited vs. P. Venkata Rao has been allowed by the Hon’ble High Court of Madras vide order dated 29.01.2025. The detailed order is awaited.</p><ul><li>Case bearing LAC No. 04-2014 renumbered as LAC No. 19-2016 titled Union of India &amp; Others vs. Tata Communications Ltd. disposed of by District Court of Saket, Delhi</li><li>Compensation payable by Delhi Metro Rail Corporation Limited in respect of the land situated at Greater Kailash, New Delhi</li><li>Second Appeal No. 935/2024 titled Hemisphere Properties India Limited vs. P. Venkata Rao allowed by the Hon’ble High Court of Madras</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/093a0442-3fc0-4a2e-90f3-aa62fa8feab5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Hemisphere Properties India Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MALUPAPER] Malu Paper Mills Ltd to Approve Q4 2025 Financial Results on February 11, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MALU+PAPER+MILLS+LTD.&title=Malu+Paper+Mills+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+2025+Financial+Results+on+February+11%2C+2026&newsId=eaba4625-3981-4343-8a23-e5212f348d3b&token=ZWFiYTQ2MjUtMzk4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eaba4625-3981-4343-8a23-e5212f348d3b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:31:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Malu Paper Mills Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 11, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025. The meeting will also take on record the Limited Review report for the same quarter. The trading window for dealing in the company&apos;s shares has been closed for all Designated Persons and their immediate relatives from January 1, 2026, till the end of 48 hours after the conclusion of the Board Meeting.</p><ul><li>Malu Paper Mills Ltd to approve Q4 2025 financial results on February 11, 2026</li><li>The meeting will also take on record the Limited Review report for Q4 2025</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the company&apos;s shares is closed from January 1, 2026, till the end of 48 hours after the Board Meeting</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/95bab617-99ee-459a-be82-41d1e525fc51.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MALU PAPER MILLS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHRIPISTON] Shriram Pistons &amp; Rings Ltd. Announces Q3 Results, Interim Dividend, NCD Issuance, and Name Change</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shriram+Pistons+%26+Rings+Ltd&title=Shriram+Pistons+%26+Rings+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+Results%2C+Interim+Dividend%2C+NCD+Issuance%2C+and+Name+Change&newsId=018a2c40-8a7e-4148-addb-924abf8c5500&token=MDE4YTJjNDAtOGE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">018a2c40-8a7e-4148-addb-924abf8c5500</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shriram Pistons &amp; Rings Ltd. announced its un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a profit before tax of Rs. 2,035 Million for the quarter. The Board approved an interim dividend of Rs. 5/- per share (50%) for the financial year 2025-26. Additionally, the company will issue 100,000 secured, rated, listed, and redeemable non-convertible debentures (NCDs) having a face value of Rs. 100,000/- each. The company also announced a change of name to &apos;SPR Auto Technologies Limited&apos;, subject to approvals. The Board also approved alterations to the Object clause and adoption of a new set of Memorandum of Association (MOA) and Articles of Association (AOA) of the Company.</p><ul><li>Q3 standalone and consolidated financial results announced</li><li>Profit before tax reported at Rs. 2,035 Million</li><li>Interim dividend of Rs. 5/- per share approved</li><li>Issuance of 100,000 secured NCDs approved</li><li>Change of name to &apos;SPR Auto Technologies Limited&apos; announced</li><li>Alteration of Object clause and adoption of new MOA and AOA approved</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9bd40117-c8e8-4ab8-8ff4-c87cbd868f1f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shriram Pistons & Rings Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VENTIVE] Ventive Hospitality Ltd Reports KPIs for FY2025: Revenue from Operations Increases by 235.73% YoY</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ventive+Hospitality+Ltd&title=Ventive+Hospitality+Ltd+Reports+KPIs+for+FY2025%3A+Revenue+from+Operations+Increases+by+235.73%25+YoY&newsId=878bd8d3-6356-4e08-bee9-8cfa0465fb21&token=ODc4YmQ4ZDMtNjM1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">878bd8d3-6356-4e08-bee9-8cfa0465fb21</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:21:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Ventive Hospitality Ltd has released its Key Performance Indicators (KPIs) for the financial year ended March 31, 2025. The company reported a significant increase in total income and revenue from operations. The revenue from food and beverages also saw a growth. The EBITDA and profit for the year also increased. The company has also reported an increase in net borrowings and a decrease in total equity. The average room rate and occupancy have also increased, leading to a growth in RevPAR.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations increased by 235.73% YoY</li><li>Total income grew by 238.08% YoY</li><li>EBITDA increased by 175.70% YoY</li><li>Profit for the year increased to INR 483.07 million from a loss of INR 667.46 million in the previous year</li><li>Average room rate and occupancy increased, leading to a growth in RevPAR</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e4b69416-2a05-48e4-a8b9-6ea4d2495a0e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ventive Hospitality Ltd | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UCIL] Unifinz Capital India Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Discuss Fundraising Proposal</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Unifinz+Capital+India+Ltd&title=Unifinz+Capital+India+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Discuss+Fundraising+Proposal&newsId=fdd44020-7c14-4da2-9925-677fa81ff41d&token=ZmRkNDQwMjAtN2Mx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fdd44020-7c14-4da2-9925-677fa81ff41d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Unifinz Capital India Ltd has announced a board meeting on February 5, 2026, to consider and approve a fundraising proposal. The company plans to raise funds through various modes such as rights issue, preferential allotment, qualified institutions placement, private placement, or through any other permissible mode. The fundraising may involve the issuance of equity shares, convertible securities, warrants, or debt securities, subject to regulatory approvals.</p><ul><li>Unifinz Capital India Ltd has scheduled a board meeting on February 5, 2026, to discuss a fundraising proposal.</li><li>The company plans to raise funds through various modes including rights issue, preferential allotment, and private placement.</li><li>The fundraising may involve the issuance of equity shares, convertible securities, warrants, or debt securities.</li><li>The proposal is subject to regulatory approvals as may be required.</li><li>The trading window for dealing in the equity shares of the Company has been closed for all Designated Persons, Directors, Key Managerial Personnel and their immediate relatives.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4fed7912-1daf-4b04-b16a-8a0a720c8510.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Unifinz Capital India Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SILICON] Silicon Valley Infotech Ltd Approves Scheme of Capital Reduction and E-Voting Facility</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SILICON+VALLEY+INFOTECH+LTD.&title=Silicon+Valley+Infotech+Ltd+Approves+Scheme+of+Capital+Reduction+and+E-Voting+Facility&newsId=7ae34507-26e0-4d8e-b6ec-2627d05d37fe&token=N2FlMzQ1MDctMjZl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ae34507-26e0-4d8e-b6ec-2627d05d37fe</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Silicon Valley Infotech Ltd has approved the convening of an extraordinary general meeting (EGM) on March 9, 2026, to consider and approve the Scheme of Reduction of Capital between the company and its shareholders under Section 66 of the Companies Act, 2013. The company has also provided the facility for e-voting on all resolutions for members holding shares either in physical or electronic form as on the cut-off date, i.e., March 2, 2026. The remote e-voting will commence at 9:00 a.m. on March 6, 2026, and end at 5:00 p.m. on March 8, 2026.</p><ul><li>Board approved Scheme of Reduction of Capital between the company and its shareholders</li><li>Convening of an extraordinary general meeting (EGM) on March 9, 2026</li><li>E-voting facility provided for members holding shares in physical or electronic form</li><li>Remote e-voting to commence on March 6, 2026, and end on March 8, 2026</li><li>Cut-off date set as March 2, 2026, for members to be eligible for e-voting</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0f53618a-6025-40c6-bf29-35b7feda1744.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SILICON VALLEY INFOTECH LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HCLTECH] HCL Technologies to Participate in Three Investor Conferences in February 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HCL+TECHNOLOGIES+LTD.&title=HCL+Technologies+to+Participate+in+Three+Investor+Conferences+in+February+2026&newsId=3b4bae61-e9f8-4639-87ce-71ccbd31e4f3&token=M2I0YmFlNjEtZTlm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b4bae61-e9f8-4639-87ce-71ccbd31e4f3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:14:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>HCL Technologies Ltd has announced its participation in three investor conferences in February 2026. The conferences include Nuvama India Conference 2026 in Mumbai (Feb 3-11), Shoring up Self-Reliance Nuvama in Mumbai (Feb 28-26), and IIFL’s 17th Enterprising India Global Investors’ Conference in Mumbai (Feb 24-26). The company&apos;s executives are expected to meet with investors individually during these events, but no unpublished price sensitive information will be shared.</p><ul><li>HCL Technologies to participate in Nuvama India Conference 2026 in Mumbai from Feb 3-11, 2026</li><li>Company executives to participate in Shoring up Self-Reliance Nuvama in Mumbai on Feb 28-26, 2026</li><li>HCL Technologies to attend IIFL’s 17th Enterprising India Global Investors’ Conference in Mumbai from Feb 24-26, 2026</li><li>One-on-one meetings with investors expected during the conferences</li><li>No unpublished price sensitive information to be shared during the events</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8e28e9e4-2889-4621-9be1-85c8c3d1658c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HCL TECHNOLOGIES LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>