<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:14:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[PARKHOSPS] Park Medi World Ltd Acquires Krishna Super-speciality Hospital for INR 40 Cr.</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Park+Medi+World+Ltd&title=Park+Medi+World+Ltd+Acquires+Krishna+Super-speciality+Hospital+for+INR+40+Cr.&newsId=3180ef1e-5d94-4ec4-b408-15b5baac64ff&token=MzE4MGVmMWUtNWQ5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3180ef1e-5d94-4ec4-b408-15b5baac64ff</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Park Medi World Limited has approved the acquisition of Krishna Super-speciality Hospital, a 250-bedded facility with 70 ICU beds, modular operation theatres, and automated laboratories. The hospital is owned by Mahip Hospitals Private Limited and is strategically positioned in Bathinda, serving as a vital healthcare hub. Park Medi World Limited has been managing operations since July 2025 and has now acquired 100% shareholding. This acquisition will increase Park Group&apos;s hospital capacity and strengthen its infrastructure, supporting its plan to reach a total of 5,260 beds by March 2028.</p><ul><li>Park Medi World Ltd acquires Krishna Super-speciality Hospital for INR 40 Cr.</li><li>Krishna Super-speciality Hospital is a 250-bedded facility with 70 ICU beds and advanced diagnostics.</li><li>The hospital is strategically positioned in Bathinda and serves as a vital healthcare hub.</li><li>Park Medi World Ltd has been managing operations since July 2025 and has now acquired 100% shareholding.</li><li>This acquisition will increase Park Group&apos;s hospital capacity and strengthen its infrastructure.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/48015121-3237-435f-99c8-6426e3d2b6ef.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Park Medi World Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ALPHAIND] Alphalogic Industries Ltd: Promoters Acquire Shares &amp; Convertible Warrants via Preferential Allotment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Alphalogic+Industries+Ltd&title=Alphalogic+Industries+Ltd%3A+Promoters+Acquire+Shares+%26+Convertible+Warrants+via+Preferential+Allotment&newsId=e3faa78e-9b4d-449e-8fae-dd37a0c9dc53&token=ZTNmYWE3OGUtOWI0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3faa78e-9b4d-449e-8fae-dd37a0c9dc53</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Alphalogic Industries Ltd has announced that promoters have acquired shares and convertible warrants through preferential allotment. The total number of equity shares acquired by Alphalogic Techsys Limited, a promoter, is 52,14,528, and 3,000 by Alphalogic, another promoter. The total number of convertible warrants acquired by Alphalogic Techsys Limited is 81,90,000, and 3,00,000 by Alphalogic. The warrants have a conversion price of Rs. 28/- per warrant, and the allotment date is 01.01.2026. The company secretary and compliance officer, Aayushi Khandelwal, has made the disclosure.</p><ul><li>Alphalogic Industries Ltd promoters acquire shares and convertible warrants</li><li>Acquisition through preferential allotment</li><li>Alphalogic Techsys Limited acquires 52,14,528 equity shares and 81,90,000 warrants</li><li>Alphalogic acquires 3,000 equity shares and 3,00,000 warrants</li><li>Conversion price of Rs. 28/- per warrant</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e22c87f3-a7cd-4c70-9680-c0183d430f02.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Alphalogic Industries Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MAHABANK] Bank of Maharashtra Reports 17.24% Y-o-Y Growth in Total Business as of 31.12.2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BANK+OF+MAHARASHTRA&title=Bank+of+Maharashtra+Reports+17.24%25+Y-o-Y+Growth+in+Total+Business+as+of+31.12.2025&newsId=3aa0ff30-57ee-4557-8565-989360e924a3&token=M2FhMGZmMzAtNTdl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3aa0ff30-57ee-4557-8565-989360e924a3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 03:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Bank of Maharashtra has disclosed its provisional business figures as of 31.12.2025. The total business stands at 5,95,171 crores, showing a growth of 17.24% compared to the previous year. Total deposits have increased by 15.30% to 3,21,695 crores. CASA deposits have also seen a rise of 15.93% to 1,59,397 crores. The CASA percentage is now at 49.55%, an increase of 27bps. Corporate advances, both domestic and global, are subject to review.</p><ul><li>Total business growth of 17.24%</li><li>Total deposits increased by 15.30%</li><li>CASA deposits rose by 15.93%</li><li>CASA percentage now at 49.55%</li><li>Corporate advances to be reviewed</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/67560789-1e4b-4c93-a576-7773394f11ab.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BANK OF MAHARASHTRA | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MINID] Mini Diamonds India Ltd Receives USD 1.85 Million Export Order for Lab Grown Polished Diamonds</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MINI+DIAMONDS+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Mini+Diamonds+India+Ltd+Receives+USD+1.85+Million+Export+Order+for+Lab+Grown+Polished+Diamonds&newsId=79fa2729-f4f8-466a-adce-cc4df021af08&token=NzlmYTI3MjktZjRm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79fa2729-f4f8-466a-adce-cc4df021af08</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 03:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Mini Diamonds India Ltd (MDIL) has received an export order valued at USD 1.85 million (approximately INR 16,65,00,000) for the supply of lab-grown diamonds to a prominent overseas client from Hong Kong. This order is expected to strengthen the company’s export momentum and international order pipeline, reflecting continued demand from overseas buyers and reinforcing MDIL’s ability to convert repeat enquiries into executable business across export markets. The order aligns with MDIL’s strategy to deepen its presence in priority markets through disciplined execution, product consistency, and customer continuity.</p><ul><li>MDIL received an export order worth USD 1.85 million for lab-grown diamonds from a Hong Kong-based client.</li><li>The order is expected to strengthen the company’s export momentum and international order pipeline.</li><li>This deal reflects continued demand from overseas buyers and reinforces MDIL’s ability to convert repeat enquiries into executable business across export markets.</li><li>The order aligns with MDIL’s strategy to deepen its presence in priority markets through disciplined execution, product consistency, and customer continuity.</li><li>MDIL is focused on strengthening operational readiness to service repeat orders, improving turnaround efficiency, and building a sustainable overseas order book.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fe14def7-46d8-406b-945c-fe82a969e903.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MINI DIAMONDS (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MAGANTR] Magnanimous Trade &amp; Finance Ltd Announces 23:1 Bonus Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MAGNANIMOUS+TRADE+%26+FINANCE+LTD.&title=Magnanimous+Trade+%26+Finance+Ltd+Announces+23%3A1+Bonus+Issue&newsId=22150796-d4d7-4f90-bc60-98cf4a16857d&token=MjIxNTA3OTYtZDRk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">22150796-d4d7-4f90-bc60-98cf4a16857d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 03:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Bonus</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Magnanimous Trade &amp; Finance Ltd announced the allotment of 2,18,83,764 fully paid-up bonus equity shares of Rs. 10/- each in the ratio 23:1 to the shareholders of the Company as on the record date i.e. Friday, 2\</p><ul><li>Magnanimous Trade &amp; Finance Ltd announced a 23:1 bonus issue</li><li>2,18,83,764 bonus equity shares of Rs. 10/- each were approved for allotment</li><li>The bonus shares will rank pari-passu with the existing shares</li><li>The bonus shares will carry the same rights as the existing shares</li><li>The bonus shares will be credited to the beneficiary accounts in due course</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a98e77eb-fd45-44f8-80f0-758448df58db.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MAGNANIMOUS TRADE & FINANCE LTD. | Category: Bonus</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[METROPOLIS] Metropolis Healthcare Ltd Reports 26% Y-o-Y Revenue Growth in Q3FY26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Metropolis+Healthcare+Ltd&title=Metropolis+Healthcare+Ltd+Reports+26%25+Y-o-Y+Revenue+Growth+in+Q3FY26&newsId=b4488611-d201-45f3-8af0-f96b897317a4&token=YjQ0ODg2MTEtZDIw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4488611-d201-45f3-8af0-f96b897317a4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 03:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Metropolis Healthcare Ltd has reported a 26% year-on-year consolidated revenue growth in Q3FY26, driven by sustained momentum in preventive and wellness health check-ups under TruHealth and a strong increase in specialty testing volumes across both B2C and B2B channels. The integration of all acquisitions is progressing well, with synergies delivering operational efficiencies and strengthening operating leverage. The TruHealth Wellness and Specialty segments recorded Y-o-Y growth of ~35% and ~33%, respectively. The standalone revenues grew by approx. 15% Y-o-Y, largely on account of increased patient and test volumes and a favorable shift in product mix and realizations.</p><ul><li>26% Y-o-Y consolidated revenue growth including revenues from Core Diagnostics, Scientific Pathology, Agra, Dr. Ahuja’s Pathology &amp; Imaging Center, Dehradun and Dr. RS Patil’s Ambika Pathology Laboratory, Kolhapur.</li><li>Integration of acquisitions progressing well with operational efficiencies and strengthening operating leverage.</li><li>TruHealth Wellness and Specialty segments recorded Y-o-Y growth of ~35% and ~33%, respectively.</li><li>Standalone revenues grew by approx. 15% Y-o-Y, largely on account of increased patient and test volumes and a favorable shift in product mix and realizations.</li><li>EBITDA margins for the quarter recorded year-on-year expansion, despite Q3 being a seasonally weaker period for the diagnostic industry.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/18a7a581-69ff-42eb-a7b2-e55fa6a49e59.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Metropolis Healthcare Ltd | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PIRAMALFIN] CRISIL Assigns AA+/Stable Rating to Piramal Finance Limited&apos;s Non-Convertible Debentures and Bank Debt</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Piramal+Finance+Ltd&title=CRISIL+Assigns+AA%2B%2FStable+Rating+to+Piramal+Finance+Limited%27s+Non-Convertible+Debentures+and+Bank+Debt&newsId=f2287ca0-6c8d-435f-9e9f-07d13dbcc902&token=ZjIyODdjYTAtNmM4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f2287ca0-6c8d-435f-9e9f-07d13dbcc902</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 03:20:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>CRISIL has assigned a long-term rating of AA+/Stable to Piramal Finance Limited (Piramal Finance), marking a key milestone in the company’s multi-year transformation into a scaled, diversified retail-focused lender. The rating reflects sustained improvements in asset quality, a granular retail loan book, strengthening profitability metrics, robust capitalisation, and a conservative liquidity position. The company has also made significant investments in technology and digital infrastructure, enhancing underwriting precision, early risk identification, and scalable execution across its lending businesses.</p><ul><li>CRISIL assigns AA+/Stable rating to Piramal Finance Limited&apos;s Non Convertible Debentures and Bank Debt</li><li>Rating reflects sustained improvements in asset quality, a granular retail loan book, strengthening profitability metrics, robust capitalisation, and a conservative liquidity position</li><li>Company has made significant investments in technology and digital infrastructure</li><li>Total outstanding borrowings of approximately ~Rs. 75,000 Cr.</li><li>Company is among the fastest-growing large NBFCs, with AUM growing at a 40% CAGR over the last four years</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/35496f87-3254-4364-9ba8-dd6be872deee.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Piramal Finance Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DECNGOLD] Deccan Gold Mines Ltd Repays All Outstanding Loans After Successful Rights Issue Closure</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DECCAN+GOLD+MINES+LTD.&title=Deccan+Gold+Mines+Ltd+Repays+All+Outstanding+Loans+After+Successful+Rights+Issue+Closure&newsId=4a3ee5ec-d4b5-49c0-85da-a4c8f628b58b&token=NGEzZWU1ZWMtZDRi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a3ee5ec-d4b5-49c0-85da-a4c8f628b58b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 03:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Debt Repayment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Deccan Gold Mines Limited has successfully repaid all outstanding loans along with accrued interest to its lenders following the closure of its ₹ 314.70 crore Rights Issue on December 26, 2025. This significant milestone marks the company&apos;s journey toward financial resilience and growth. The loan repayment includes ₹ 75 crore to Ardent Steels Private Limited, ₹ 120 crore to Godawari Power &amp; Ispat Limited, and ₹ 8 crore to Hira Ferro Alloys Limited. The company is now working with Hira Group to complete procedural formalities, including filing satisfaction of charge and release of pledged shares of Geomysore Services India Private Limited. This achievement strengthens Deccan Gold&apos;s balance sheet, improves capital efficiency, enhances financial flexibility, and increases investor confidence, positioning the company for a high-growth phase.</p><ul><li>Deccan Gold Mines Ltd has repaid all outstanding loans worth ₹ 314.70 crore.</li><li>The repayment includes loans to Ardent Steels Private Limited, Godawari Power &amp; Ispat Limited, and Hira Ferro Alloys Limited.</li><li>This loan repayment strengthens Deccan Gold&apos;s balance sheet and improves capital efficiency.</li><li>The company&apos;s financial flexibility is expected to accelerate project execution.</li><li>Deccan Gold&apos;s achievement increases investor confidence and supports long-term value creation.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a48c11ee-249c-4571-837e-40454598b789.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DECCAN GOLD MINES LTD. | Category: Debt Repayment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[POONAWALLA] Poonawalla Fincorp Ltd Reports 77.5% YoY AUM Growth to Approximately ₹ 55,000 Crore in Q4 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Poonawalla+Fincorp+Ltd&title=Poonawalla+Fincorp+Ltd+Reports+77.5%25+YoY+AUM+Growth+to+Approximately+%E2%82%B9+55%2C000+Crore+in+Q4+2025&newsId=2beb2151-1b80-465e-ae86-b9b5b39b0c83&token=MmJlYjIxNTEtMWI4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2beb2151-1b80-465e-ae86-b9b5b39b0c83</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 02:53:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Poonawalla Fincorp Limited has reported a significant growth in Assets Under Management (AUM) for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The AUM grew by 77.5% YoY and 15.3% QoQ to approximately ₹ 55,000 crore. The company also maintains a strong liquidity position of approximately ₹ 6,450 crore as on 31st December 2025. The growth is attributed to the company&apos;s risk-first approach, robust risk management systems, and a diversified asset base. The company is committed to expanding its business in line with building a long-term sustainable profitable model.</p><ul><li>AUM grew by 77.5% YoY and 15.3% QoQ to approximately ₹ 55,000 crore</li><li>Company maintains a strong liquidity position of approximately ₹ 6,450 crore as on 31st December 2025</li><li>Growth attributed to risk-first approach, robust risk management systems, and a diversified asset base</li><li>Company committed to expanding business in line with building a long-term sustainable profitable model</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cfbae2f6-c4e5-4ab7-b265-27112cb946c4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Poonawalla Fincorp Ltd | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HDFCBANK] HDFC Bank Ltd Reports 9.8% Growth in Period End Advances and 11.5% Growth in Period End Deposits</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HDFC+Bank+Ltd&title=HDFC+Bank+Ltd+Reports+9.8%25+Growth+in+Period+End+Advances+and+11.5%25+Growth+in+Period+End+Deposits&newsId=801f4c92-abe1-4a3f-a881-f4a8be7f8b6f&token=ODAxZjRjOTItYWJl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">801f4c92-abe1-4a3f-a881-f4a8be7f8b6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 02:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>HDFC Bank Ltd has reported a growth of 9.8% in period end advances, 11.5% in period end deposits, 9.0% in average advances under management, and 12.2% in average deposits for the December 2025 quarter. The Bank&apos;s period end gross advances stood at approximately INR 28,445 billion, a growth of 11.9% over the corresponding period last year. The Bank&apos;s period end CASA deposits were approximately INR 9,610 billion, a growth of around 10.1% over the same period last year.</p><ul><li>HDFC Bank reports 9.8% growth in period end advances</li><li>Period end deposits see a growth of 11.5%</li><li>Average advances under management grow by 9.0%</li><li>Average deposits increase by 12.2%</li><li>Period end gross advances stand at INR 28,445 billion, a growth of 11.9%</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/98453f7b-7494-467f-bf2d-e7bde8ca3fc7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HDFC Bank Ltd | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>