<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:15:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[QUADRANT] Quadrant Televentures Ltd. Schedules Fifth Committee of Creditors Meeting for January 27, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Quadrant+Televentures+Limited-%24&title=Quadrant+Televentures+Ltd.+Schedules+Fifth+Committee+of+Creditors+Meeting+for+January+27%2C+2026&newsId=ab27270a-6c15-418d-badd-0f6ed137f1e1&token=YWIyNzI3MGEtNmMx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab27270a-6c15-418d-badd-0f6ed137f1e1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 04:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Quadrant Televentures Limited has announced the scheduling of the Fifth meeting of the Committee of Creditors. The meeting is set to take place on Tuesday, January 27, 2026.</p><ul><li>Quadrant Televentures Ltd. has announced the scheduling of the Fifth meeting of the Committee of Creditors.</li><li>The meeting is scheduled to be held on Tuesday, January 27, 2026.</li><li>This is an update from the company&apos;s financial documentation.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b930f5d0-9a4b-4dff-96f9-18bf421a1a08.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Quadrant Televentures Limited-$ | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TREJHARA] Trejhara Solutions Ltd Changes Terminology in EGM Notice for Convertible Warrants and Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Trejhara+Solutions+Ltd&title=Trejhara+Solutions+Ltd+Changes+Terminology+in+EGM+Notice+for+Convertible+Warrants+and+Equity+Shares&newsId=456ea550-7a04-471f-91d0-6375d1e13f60&token=NDU2ZWE1NTAtN2Ew</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">456ea550-7a04-471f-91d0-6375d1e13f60</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 03:04:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Trejhara Solutions Ltd, in compliance with the directives from stock exchanges, has issued a clarification regarding the terminology used in the Notice for the Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) held on November 10, 2025. The words &apos;Subscription Shares&apos; in points 21(d) and (e) of the explanatory statement will now be read as &apos;Specified Securities&apos;. This change is in accordance with the applicable regulatory provisions. All other contents of the Notice, including the text of the resolutions and the explanatory statement, remain unchanged.</p><ul><li>Trejhara Solutions Ltd changes terminology in EGM Notice</li><li>Words &apos;Subscription Shares&apos; to be read as &apos;Specified Securities&apos;</li><li>Change in compliance with regulatory provisions</li><li>No other changes to the Notice</li><li>Clarification issued pursuant to stock exchange directives</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2537d35e-4560-4e3d-8aea-888e81f80ec4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Trejhara Solutions Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ALLTIME] All Time Plastics Limited Empanelled as Product and Market Development Partner by NECBDC for Engineered Bamboo Initiatives</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=All+Time+Plastics+Ltd&title=All+Time+Plastics+Limited+Empanelled+as+Product+and+Market+Development+Partner+by+NECBDC+for+Engineered+Bamboo+Initiatives&newsId=50f18dcc-458e-4d55-a92b-0720ac5a5b41&token=NTBmMThkY2MtNDU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50f18dcc-458e-4d55-a92b-0720ac5a5b41</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 00:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>MoU</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>All Time Plastics Limited (ATPL) has entered into a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with the North East Cane and Bamboo Development Council (NECBDC), a statutory body under the Ministry of Development of North Eastern Region (MDoNER), Government of India. The MoU, signed on 25th January 2026, empanels ATPL as a Product and Market Development Partner (PMDP) to support initiatives relating to the development and value addition of engineered bamboo boards and panels originating from the North Eastern Region (NER). The proposed engagement is initially envisaged to be anchored in Assam and Nagaland, and is intended to support ecosystem-level interventions across product development and prototyping, manufacturing process inputs, sustainability and certification readiness, and domestic and export market linkage for engineered and value-added bamboo products.</p><ul><li>All Time Plastics Limited has entered into a MoU with the North East Cane and Bamboo Development Council (NECBDC) for engineered bamboo initiatives.</li><li>The MoU was signed at Guwahati in the presence of the Honourable Union Minister of Development of North Eastern Region, Shri Jyotiraditya M. Scindia.</li><li>The engagement is intended to support ecosystem-level interventions across various aspects of engineered bamboo product development and marketing.</li><li>The MoU establishes a non-exclusive and non-binding framework for collaboration between ATPL and NECBDC.</li><li>The engagement provides ATPL with a structured entry point into the engineered bamboo ecosystem, aligned with its long-term focus on responsible sourcing and material diversification.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/343600b0-069a-4426-942b-e20b899df138.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: All Time Plastics Ltd | Category: MoU</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KTKBANK] Karnataka Bank Branches May Be Affected by UFBU Strike on Jan 27, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KARNATAKA+BANK+LTD.&title=Karnataka+Bank+Branches+May+Be+Affected+by+UFBU+Strike+on+Jan+27%2C+2026&newsId=63f53e31-41e8-44ba-b599-6f0ccc69cba0&token=NjNmNTNlMzEtNDFl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63f53e31-41e8-44ba-b599-6f0ccc69cba0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 20:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Strike</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The All India Karnataka Bank Employees Association (AIKBEA) and Karnataka Bank Officers Organisation (KBOO), affiliated to the AIBEA and AIBOA respectively, under the banner of United Forum of Bank Unions (UFBU) have given a call for a one-day strike on 27.01.2026. The strike is due to demands for a 5-day banking week, regulated working hours, and opposition to the disinvestment process in IDBI and 3 RRBs. If the strike materializes, the normal functioning of the Bank&apos;s branches, offices, and departments may be affected. The Bank is taking necessary steps to ensure normal functioning. The expected quantum of loss or damages and the impact on operations are not quantified.</p><ul><li>AIKBEA and KBOO have given a call for a one-day strike on 27.01.2026</li><li>Strike is due to demands for a 5-day banking week and regulated working hours</li><li>Strike also opposes the disinvestment process in IDBI and 3 RRBs</li><li>Bank branches, offices, and departments may be affected if the strike materializes</li><li>Bank is taking necessary steps to ensure normal functioning</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9e2eef30-43f2-4d25-b4c7-80d6da9b8f7a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KARNATAKA BANK LTD. | Category: Strike</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDIAHOME] India Home Loan Ltd. to Approve Un-audited Financial Results for Q3 &amp; 9M 2025 and Increase Authorised Share Capital</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDIA+HOME+LOAN+LTD.&title=India+Home+Loan+Ltd.+to+Approve+Un-audited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+%26+9M+2025+and+Increase+Authorised+Share+Capital&newsId=20b07cbf-6f6f-4b99-a0ae-99569ee6436b&token=MjBiMDdjYmYtNmY2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">20b07cbf-6f6f-4b99-a0ae-99569ee6436b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 20:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>India Home Loan Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 30th January 2026 to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The Board will also consider increasing the authorized share capital of the company and amending the Memorandum of Association, subject to shareholders&apos; approvals. The dealing window for equity shares of the company is closed from 1st January 2026 till 48 hours after the declaration of financial results.</p><ul><li>Board meeting scheduled on 30th January 2026</li><li>Consideration and approval of un-audited financial results for Q3 &amp; 9M 2025</li><li>Proposal to increase authorized share capital and amend Memorandum of Association</li><li>Shareholders&apos; approvals required for proposed changes</li><li>Dealing window for equity shares closed from 1st January 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f29f9ed0-52fb-4cef-a0c8-ba3ad908acb8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDIA HOME LOAN LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[COFORGE] Coforge Ltd Reports Q3 FY2026 Earnings, Releases Transcript of Earnings Conference Call</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Coforge+Ltd&title=Coforge+Ltd+Reports+Q3+FY2026+Earnings%2C+Releases+Transcript+of+Earnings+Conference+Call&newsId=312d39ba-794f-46e7-9e48-a62fc3e3b974&token=MzEyZDM5YmEtNzk0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">312d39ba-794f-46e7-9e48-a62fc3e3b974</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 20:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Coforge Ltd has announced the transcript of its Earnings Conference Call for Q3 FY2026. The announcement was made in accordance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The conference call was held after the Board meeting on January 23, 2026. The transcript is available on the company&apos;s website for investors.</p><ul><li>Coforge Ltd has released the transcript of its Q3 FY2026 Earnings Conference Call.</li><li>The release of the transcript is in accordance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li><li>The conference call was held after the Board meeting on January 23, 2026.</li><li>The transcript is available for investors on the company&apos;s website.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ffcb4f8b-1fad-4b1f-b229-a23a603d78ae.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Coforge Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[POWERGRID] Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd Announces Changes in Senior Management</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=POWER+GRID+CORPORATION+OF+INDIA+LTD.&title=Power+Grid+Corporation+of+India+Ltd+Announces+Changes+in+Senior+Management&newsId=b6eebd42-5486-47cd-93e4-a5cb30aa22a6&token=YjZlZWJkNDItNTQ4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6eebd42-5486-47cd-93e4-a5cb30aa22a6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 16:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd has announced changes in its senior management. The Board of Directors has approved the promotion/appointment of Sanjay Sharma, Abhay Kumar, Abhinav Verma, Vineeta Agarwal, M S Hejib, Akhilesh Kumar Dixit, Kumud Wadhwa, and Harinarayanan Puthan Kalam as Executive Directors. These changes are effective from 25th January 2026. The new appointees bring a combined experience of over 200 years in various fields including telecom marketing, commercial, corporate planning, asset monetization, electrical engineering, project management, and human resource management.</p><ul><li>Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd has announced changes in its senior management.</li><li>Sanjay Sharma, Abhay Kumar, Abhinav Verma, Vineeta Agarwal, M S Hejib, Akhilesh Kumar Dixit, Kumud Wadhwa, and Harinarayanan Puthan Kalam have been appointed as Executive Directors.</li><li>The new appointees bring a combined experience of over 200 years in various fields.</li><li>The appointments are effective from 25th January 2026.</li><li>The new appointees have diverse experience in telecom marketing, commercial, corporate planning, asset monetization, electrical engineering, project management, and human resource management.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b5bb03d8-7bd7-452c-b4e7-1f66ae477904.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: POWER GRID CORPORATION OF INDIA LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MEDPLUS] Medplus Health Services Subsidiary Faces Three-Day Drug License Suspension in Telangana</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Medplus+Health+Services+Ltd&title=Medplus+Health+Services+Subsidiary+Faces+Three-Day+Drug+License+Suspension+in+Telangana&newsId=1ec71efd-7016-4a68-8e60-0fdbcc0d439d&token=MWVjNzFlZmQtNzAx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1ec71efd-7016-4a68-8e60-0fdbcc0d439d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 16:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Medplus Health Services Ltd. has announced that its subsidiary, Optival Health Solutions Private Limited, has received a suspension order for a Drug License of a store situated in the state of Telangana. The suspension is issued under Rule 65 of the Drugs and Cosmetics Act, 1945 and Drugs and Cosmetics Rules, 1945. The order, issued by the Assistant Director, Drugs Control License, Telangana, will result in a potential revenue loss of Rs 2.94 lacs for the three-day suspension period. The company will post the order on its website and on the websites of BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange of India Ltd.</p><ul><li>Medplus Health Services&apos; subsidiary, Optival Health Solutions Private Limited, receives a three-day suspension order for a Drug License in Telangana.</li><li>The suspension is issued under Rule 65 of the Drugs and Cosmetics Act, 1945 and Drugs and Cosmetics Rules, 1945.</li><li>The suspension will potentially cause a revenue loss of Rs 2.94 lacs for the three-day period.</li><li>The order is available on the company&apos;s website and the websites of BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange of India Ltd.</li><li>Medplus Health Services is taking necessary actions to comply with the order and manage the impact on their financials.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e53ca5ad-e9bb-4a91-b088-4e53f18af778.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Medplus Health Services Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[POWERGRID] Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd Announces Changes in Senior Management</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=POWER+GRID+CORPORATION+OF+INDIA+LTD.&title=Power+Grid+Corporation+of+India+Ltd+Announces+Changes+in+Senior+Management&newsId=c01ecd61-792e-40f3-a8f2-d569b3cd6f29&token=YzAxZWNkNjEtNzky</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c01ecd61-792e-40f3-a8f2-d569b3cd6f29</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 16:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd has announced changes in its senior management. The Board of Directors has approved the promotion/appointment of five senior level officials as Executive Directors (ED) effective from 25th January, 2026. The new appointees include Sanjay Sharma, Abhay Kumar, Abhinav Verma, Vineeta Agarwal, and M S Hejib. The company has also announced the promotion of Akhilesh Kumar Dixit and Harinarayanan Puthan Kalam to Executive Directors. Kumud Wadhwa has been appointed as Executive Director (ERP &amp; IT).</p><ul><li>Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd has announced changes in its senior management.</li><li>Five senior level officials have been promoted/appointed as Executive Directors (ED) effective from 25th January, 2026.</li><li>Akhilesh Kumar Dixit and Harinarayanan Puthan Kalam have been promoted to Executive Directors.</li><li>Kumud Wadhwa has been appointed as Executive Director (ERP &amp; IT).</li><li>The new appointees bring a combined experience of over 180 years in various fields including telecom marketing, commercial, corporate planning, asset monetization, substation engineering, asset management, international consultancy, engineering functions, HVDC technology, corporate planning, distribution management system, HR management, and IT.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8fa4d9cc-494f-4f07-866e-f22a095102ec.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: POWER GRID CORPORATION OF INDIA LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JPASSOCIAT] Jaiprakash Associates Executive Director Released on Interim Bail</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JAIPRAKASH+ASSOCIATES+LTD.&title=Jaiprakash+Associates+Executive+Director+Released+on+Interim+Bail&newsId=43d5b509-f93d-4f54-86e5-a39eea760ffa&token=NDNkNWI1MDktZjkz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43d5b509-f93d-4f54-86e5-a39eea760ffa</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 16:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jaiprakash Associates Ltd. has informed that Shri Manoj Gaur, the Executive Director of the company, who was arrested by the Enforcement Directorate in connection with an ongoing investigation under the Prevention of Money Laundering Act (PMLA) initiated against Jaypee Infratech Ltd. and Jaiprakash Associates Ltd., has been released on Interim Bail for 14 days by the Hon’ble Court of Additional Sessions Judge-7, Patiala House, New Delhi on 24th January 2026. This information is in continuation to the disclosure made on 13th November 2025.</p><ul><li>Shri Manoj Gaur, Executive Director of Jaiprakash Associates Ltd., has been released on Interim Bail for 14 days.</li><li>The bail was granted by the Hon’ble Court of Additional Sessions Judge-7, Patiala House, New Delhi on 24th January 2026.</li><li>Gaur was arrested in connection with an ongoing investigation under the Prevention of Money Laundering Act (PMLA) against Jaypee Infratech Ltd. and Jaiprakash Associates Ltd.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4e9fdfed-449e-4ddb-a022-54f838454295.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JAIPRAKASH ASSOCIATES LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>