<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:27:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[EPACK] EPACK Durable Reports 13.5% YoY Revenue Growth in Q3-FY26, Driven by SDA, LDA, and Component Segments</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=EPACK+Durable+Ltd&title=EPACK+Durable+Reports+13.5%25+YoY+Revenue+Growth+in+Q3-FY26%2C+Driven+by+SDA%2C+LDA%2C+and+Component+Segments&newsId=b6cae376-a934-4ce2-a7f5-6b16ad6c92db&token=YjZjYWUzNzYtYTkz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6cae376-a934-4ce2-a7f5-6b16ad6c92db</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:22:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>EPACK Durable Limited, a leading room air conditioner, small domestic appliances, large domestic appliances and component manufacturer, announced its results for the 3rd quarter of financial year 2025-26. The company reported a 13.5% YoY increase in operational revenue, with the Small Domestic Appliances (SDA) and Component segments growing by 30% and 61% YoY respectively. The RAC segment witnessed a marginal 1% year-on-year decline. The company added 2 new customers and reported a healthy pipeline in both the SDA and Components segments. The management remains confident in achieving the full-year target and continuing revenue growth.</p><ul><li>Revenue increased by 13.5% YoY</li><li>SDA segment grew by 30% YoY</li><li>Component Segment reported a 61% YoY growth</li><li>LDA Segment grew by 74% YoY</li><li>Added 2 new customers during the quarter</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/78c6dbe0-29d6-42f1-b537-d5842ea89bd1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: EPACK Durable Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BHARTIARTL] Bharti Airtel Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on February 5, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BHARTI+AIRTEL+LTD.&title=Bharti+Airtel+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+February+5%2C+2026&newsId=d05ab735-5179-4ee8-848d-596af619c1c9&token=ZDA1YWI3MzUtNTE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d05ab735-5179-4ee8-848d-596af619c1c9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bharti Airtel Ltd has informed the BSE that the company&apos;s Board of Directors will meet on February 5, 2026, to consider and approve the Audited Financial Results (Standalone &amp; Consolidated) for the third quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. In accordance with the Company&apos;s Code of Conduct for prohibition of Insider Trading, the Trading Window for dealing in the securities of the Company has been closed from Thursday, January 01, 2026 to Saturday, February 07, 2026 (both days inclusive).</p><ul><li>Bharti Airtel Ltd to consider and approve Audited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended on December 31, 2025.</li><li>Trading Window for dealing in the securities of the Company closed from January 1, 2026 to February 7, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b674a2a5-6765-47f8-b2fb-480c6170cc67.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BHARTI AIRTEL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ECOM] Accedere Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q4 Results, Bonus Shares, and Other Business</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=E.COM+INFOTECH+%28I%29+LTD.&title=Accedere+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q4+Results%2C+Bonus+Shares%2C+and+Other+Business&newsId=5a4fe223-4d37-42b3-99dc-3c8868a51b3c&token=NWE0ZmUyMjMtNGQz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a4fe223-4d37-42b3-99dc-3c8868a51b3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:21:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Accedere Ltd has announced a board meeting scheduled for 28th January, 2026. The meeting will consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The company also plans to consider a bonus share issue, subject to shareholder approval. Additionally, the board will discuss any other business deemed fit. The company&apos;s trading window is closed from 1st January, 2026, and will reopen 48 hours after the financial results are made public on 28th January, 2026.</p><ul><li>Accedere Ltd to consider and approve Q4 results for 2025</li><li>Company plans to issue bonus shares, subject to shareholder approval</li><li>Trading window closed from 1st January, 2026, to 48 hours after results are made public</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b6bca7e9-3122-4d1d-911c-351602c14b2b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: E.COM INFOTECH (I) LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DLCL] Dr Lalchandani Labs Ltd. Announces Rights Issue of 43,32,000 Equity Shares at Rs. 10/- each</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Dr+Lalchandani+Labs+Ltd&title=Dr+Lalchandani+Labs+Ltd.+Announces+Rights+Issue+of+43%2C32%2C000+Equity+Shares+at+Rs.+10%2F-+each&newsId=9e476421-e321-4d79-9448-a5a8623066b1&token=OWU0NzY0MjEtZTMy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e476421-e321-4d79-9448-a5a8623066b1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Rights Issue</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dr Lalchandani Labs Ltd. has announced a Rights Issue of 43,32,000 fully paid-up Equity Shares of face value 210/- each, at a price of Rs. 10/- per share. The entire issue price is payable at the time of making the application. The Rights Issue size is Rs. 4,33,20,000, assuming full subscription. The Record Date for determining the shareholders eligible to apply for the Equity Shares in the Rights Issue is Tuesday, January 27, 2026. The Issue Opening Date is Wednesday, February 04, 2026 and the Issue Closing Date is Friday, February 20, 2026. The Company will have the right to extend the Issue period as it may determine. No withdrawal of Application shall be permitted by any Applicant after the Issue Closing Date. The Outstanding Equity Shares prior to the Issue are 43,33,068 and post Issue, it will be 86,65,068, assuming full subscription and payment of monies.</p><ul><li>Rights Issue of 43,32,000 Equity Shares at Rs. 10/- each</li><li>Entire issue price payable at the time of application</li><li>Record Date for eligible shareholders is Tuesday, January 27, 2026</li><li>Issue Opening Date: Wednesday, February 04, 2026</li><li>Issue Closing Date: Friday, February 20, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9a86df87-0bc7-4cf1-a2b0-104125ba3ba5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Dr Lalchandani Labs Ltd | Category: Rights Issue</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DLCL] Dr Lalchandani Labs Ltd Fixes Record Date for Rights Issue of Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Dr+Lalchandani+Labs+Ltd&title=Dr+Lalchandani+Labs+Ltd+Fixes+Record+Date+for+Rights+Issue+of+Equity+Shares&newsId=517bd391-fcc5-4054-97e1-f1ee7de1f17a&token=NTE3YmQzOTEtZmNj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">517bd391-fcc5-4054-97e1-f1ee7de1f17a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Rights Issue</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dr Lalchandani Labs Ltd has announced the Record Date for the Rights Issue of equity shares. The Record Date is set for Tuesday, January 27, 2026. This move is in accordance with Regulation 42 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The purpose of this Record Date is to determine the shareholders who will be eligible to receive the Rights Entitlements under the Rights Issue.</p><ul><li>Dr Lalchandani Labs Ltd has fixed the Record Date for a Rights Issue of equity shares.</li><li>The Record Date is set for Tuesday, January 27, 2026.</li><li>This move is in accordance with Regulation 42 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li><li>The purpose of this Record Date is to determine the shareholders who will be eligible to receive the Rights Entitlements under the Rights Issue.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d6a4d805-d488-4c89-b83f-b0542f32e04a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Dr Lalchandani Labs Ltd | Category: Rights Issue</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DLCL] Dr Lalchandani Labs Ltd. Announces Rights Issue of 4,33,20,000 Equity Shares at Rs. 10/- each</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Dr+Lalchandani+Labs+Ltd&title=Dr+Lalchandani+Labs+Ltd.+Announces+Rights+Issue+of+4%2C33%2C20%2C000+Equity+Shares+at+Rs.+10%2F-+each&newsId=de8c1b4d-1369-4b3d-a1d0-e0d60b8c604a&token=ZGU4YzFiNGQtMTM2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de8c1b4d-1369-4b3d-a1d0-e0d60b8c604a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dr Lalchandani Labs Ltd. has announced a Rights Issue of 4,33,20,000 fully paid-up Equity Shares of face value 210/- each, at a price of Rs. 10/- per share. The entire issue price is payable at the time of making the application. The Rights Issue size is Rs. 4,33,20,000, assuming full subscription. The Rights Entitlement is 1 (One) Rights Equity Share for every 1 (One) fully paid-up Equity Share held by the eligible shareholders as on the Record Date, which is Tuesday, January 27, 2026. The Issue Opening Date is Wednesday, February 04, 2026 and the Issue Closing Date is Friday, February 20, 2026. The Company has made necessary arrangements with NSDL and CDSL for the credit of Rights Entitlements in dematerialized form in the demat accounts of eligible equity shareholders.</p><ul><li>Dr Lalchandani Labs Ltd. announces Rights Issue of 4,33,20,000 Equity Shares</li><li>Rights Issue price set at Rs. 10/- per Equity Share</li><li>The entire issue price is payable at the time of making the application</li><li>Rights Entitlement: 1 (One) Rights Equity Share for every 1 (One) fully paid-up Equity Share held</li><li>Issue Opening Date: Wednesday, February 04, 2026 and Issue Closing Date: Friday, February 20, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2518e9ea-0a01-4d79-bd9e-f47ce0babe8d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Dr Lalchandani Labs Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EPACK] EPACK Durable Ltd Approves Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 &amp; Nine Months Ended December 31, 2025 and Re-Appoints Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=EPACK+Durable+Ltd&title=EPACK+Durable+Ltd+Approves+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Ended+December+31%2C+2025+and+Re-Appoints+Directors&newsId=ac347e07-70e9-4e49-93f8-d169be7dafd7&token=YWMzNDdlMDctNzBl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac347e07-70e9-4e49-93f8-d169be7dafd7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>EPACK Durable Ltd, at its meeting held on January 20, 2026, approved the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company also took note of the limited review report on the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results. Furthermore, the board recommended the re-appointment of five directors, including Mr. Bajrang Bothra as a Whole Time Director and Ms. Priyanka Gulati, Mr. Krishnamachari Narasimhachari, Mr. Sameer Bhargava, and Mr. Shashank Agarwal as Independent Directors, subject to approval of members of the company.</p><ul><li>EPACK Durable Ltd approved the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The board took note of the limited review report on the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results.</li><li>Five directors, including Mr. Bajrang Bothra and four Independent Directors, were recommended for re-appointment.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/866c0c09-de44-4ed7-9d5e-fab55e3fdcda.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: EPACK Durable Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CHOLAFIN] Cholamandalam Investment and Finance Company Ltd Allots 40,000 Units of Secured Redeemable NCDs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Cholamandalam+Investment+and+Finance+Company+Ltd&title=Cholamandalam+Investment+and+Finance+Company+Ltd+Allots+40%2C000+Units+of+Secured+Redeemable+NCDs&newsId=df9a757a-7f58-4e8a-a24f-6b479d0557ef&token=ZGY5YTc1N2EtN2Y1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df9a757a-7f58-4e8a-a24f-6b479d0557ef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cholamandalam Investment and Finance Company Ltd has confirmed the allotment of 40,000 units of secured redeemable listed NCDs. The allotment was made on 20th January 2026, in line with the listing regulations under 30 and 30(A). The total amount allotted is 400 crs, which is a part of the 1000 crs (including 600 crs green shoe) size of the issue. The tenure of these NCDs is 5 years, with a coupon rate of 7.73% annual, payable on 20th January every year and on maturity date. The securities are secured at 1x, with no special rights, interests, or privileges. There has been no delay in payment of interest or principal amount for a period of more than three months from the due date or default in payment of interest or principal.</p><ul><li>Cholamandalam Investment and Finance Company Ltd allots 40,000 units of secured redeemable NCDs</li><li>The total amount allotted is 400 crs, which is a part of the 1000 crs (including 600 crs green shoe) size of the issue</li><li>The tenure of these NCDs is 5 years, with a coupon rate of 7.73% annual</li><li>The securities are secured at 1x</li><li>No delay or default in payment of interest or principal</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0bfdefe5-139f-4ef9-94ce-84101d5bbe9b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Cholamandalam Investment and Finance Company Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PACEDIGITK] Pace Digitek&apos;s Subsidiary Secures ¥943.5 million Extended Order from BSNL for Advanced Li-lon Battery Solutions</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Pace+Digitek+Ltd&title=Pace+Digitek%27s+Subsidiary+Secures+%C2%A5943.5+million+Extended+Order+from+BSNL+for+Advanced+Li-lon+Battery+Solutions&newsId=d31d3dbf-0772-4b8a-a8e9-2a239669e086&token=ZDMxZDNkYmYtMDc3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d31d3dbf-0772-4b8a-a8e9-2a239669e086</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Pace Digitek Limited, a leading provider of telecom infrastructure and turnkey network solutions, announced that its material subsidiary, Lineage Power Private Limited, has received a ¥943.5 million advance purchase order (APO) from Bharat Sanchar Nigam Limited (BSNL) for Li-lon Battery Solutions. The order includes the supply, installation, and maintenance for 5 years of 25,000 Li-lon modules and 2,500 weather-resistant IP55 racks. The contract is intended to strengthen the 48V DC power infrastructure across BSNL&apos;s national telecom network. The order comprises 25,000 units of 100 AH/48V Li-lon battery modules featuring integrated Battery Management Systems (BMS) and a 5-year warranty followed by an optional 5-year Annual Maintenance Contract (AMC). This order strengthens Pace Digitek’s presence in telecom power solutions, improves near-term order book visibility, adds long-term service revenue through the post-warranty AMC, and deepens engagement with a marquee PSU customer.</p><ul><li>Total Contract Value: ¥943.5 million</li><li>Scope: 25,000 Li-lon modules (100AH/48V) and 2,500 weather-resistant IP55 racks</li><li>Execution Timeline: Within 5 months from receipt of purchase order</li><li>5 year warranty followed by an optional 5-year Annual Maintenance Contract (AMC)</li><li>Strengthens Pace Digitek’s presence in telecom power solutions, improves near-term order book visibility, adds long-term service revenue through the post-warranty AMC, and deepens engagement with a marquee PSU customer</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/00c62a53-f9b5-4454-9f15-54b949ee4874.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Pace Digitek Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KCL] Kabra Commercial Ltd Releases Reconciliation Report for Q4 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kabra+Commercial+Ltd&title=Kabra+Commercial+Ltd+Releases+Reconciliation+Report+for+Q4+2025&newsId=b6c57552-127f-4f39-a800-5d5066fdd6c1&token=YjZjNTc1NTItMTI3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6c57552-127f-4f39-a800-5d5066fdd6c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kabra Commercial Ltd has released the Reconciliation of Share Capital Audit Report for the quarter ended 31st December, 2025. The report has been certified by Agarwal &amp; Associates Chartered Accountants and has been submitted to the Bombay Stock Exchange Limited and Calcutta Stock Exchange Limited. The company&apos;s issued capital is 2,940,000 shares, all of which are listed. The report details the changes in share capital during the quarter under consideration.</p><ul><li>Reconciliation report submitted for Q4 2025</li><li>Certified by Agarwal &amp; Associates Chartered Accountants</li><li>2,940,000 shares issued, all listed</li><li>Details of changes in share capital provided</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/72f0c3df-ce8d-421e-a2e4-20b93bb2acd3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kabra Commercial Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>