<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 18:27:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[BGWTATO] Bhagwati Autocast Ltd Mourns the Loss of Chairman Pravin Natvarlal Bhagwati</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BHAGWATI+AUTOCAST+LTD.&title=Bhagwati+Autocast+Ltd+Mourns+the+Loss+of+Chairman+Pravin+Natvarlal+Bhagwati&newsId=50e9f69b-f0f2-4651-a148-b0452bf9d313&token=NTBlOWY2OWItZjBm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50e9f69b-f0f2-4651-a148-b0452bf9d313</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 15:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bhagwati Autocast Ltd has announced the demise of its Non-Executive - Non Independent Director-Chairperson, Shri Pravin Natvarlal Bhagwati. Shri Bhagwati, aged 90, played a significant role in the company&apos;s growth since its inception in 1984. His passing is an irreparable loss to the family, organization, and all associated with him. The company conveys its deep sorrow and condolences to his family.</p><ul><li>Bhagwati Autocast Ltd announces the demise of its Chairman, Shri Pravin Natvarlal Bhagwati.</li><li>Shri Bhagwati was a Non-Executive - Non Independent Director of the company.</li><li>He played a crucial role in the company&apos;s growth since its inception in 1984.</li><li>His passing is an irreparable loss to the family, organization, and all associated with him.</li><li>The company conveys its deep sorrow and condolences to his family.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c8f121a2-8f06-4977-80d9-8bab6cff6238.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BHAGWATI AUTOCAST LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CONCOR] Harbrinder Singh Bajwa Assumes Additional Charge as Director (Domestic Division) at CONCOR</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CONTAINER+CORPORATION+OF+INDIA+LTD.&title=Harbrinder+Singh+Bajwa+Assumes+Additional+Charge+as+Director+%28Domestic+Division%29+at+CONCOR&newsId=47b4a5e9-ac2d-4bea-90f4-84a980268b96&token=NDdiNGE1ZTktYWMy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47b4a5e9-ac2d-4bea-90f4-84a980268b96</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 15:01:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Container Corporation of India Ltd (CONCOR) announced that Shri Harbrinder Singh Bajwa has assumed the additional charge of Director (Domestic Division) on 01.03.2026. Bajwa is an officer of the 1996 batch of Indian Railway Traffic Service (IRTS) with around 30 years of experience in various capacities in the Divisions, Zones of Indian Railways, and Ministries. He has been involved in policies related to procurement of foodgrains, transportation, coal movement, and Liquid Medical Oxygen across the country. The required procedure for this appointment is being completed as per the Companies Act, 2013 and SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements), Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Shri Harbrinder Singh Bajwa assumes additional charge as Director (Domestic Division) at CONCOR.</li><li>Bajwa is an experienced officer of the 1996 batch of Indian Railway Traffic Service (IRTS).</li><li>He has been involved in various policies related to foodgrains procurement, coal movement, and Liquid Medical Oxygen transportation.</li><li>The appointment is in compliance with BSE and NSE Circular dated 20.06.2018.</li><li>The required procedure for this appointment is being completed as per the Companies Act, 2013 and SEBI Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6672fac3-a1d4-49ce-be05-252a619e2125.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CONTAINER CORPORATION OF INDIA LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDSWFTLAB] Ind-Swift Laboratories: 65,00,000 Fully Convertible Warrants Lapse, ₹19,66,25,000 Forfeited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IND-SWIFT+LABORATORIES+LTD.&title=Ind-Swift+Laboratories%3A+65%2C00%2C000+Fully+Convertible+Warrants+Lapse%2C+%E2%82%B919%2C66%2C25%2C000+Forfeited&newsId=b5194038-4940-4d47-9325-c56ea8ea3ea0&token=YjUxOTQwMzgtNDk0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5194038-4940-4d47-9325-c56ea8ea3ea0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 15:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Warrant Lapse</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Ind-Swift Laboratories Ltd. has announced that 65,00,000 Fully Convertible Warrants, allotted to Saral Incorporated VCC Sub Fund on a preferential basis, have lapsed as the warrant holder did not exercise the option to convert within the stipulated period of 18 months from the date of allotment. The warrants were allotted on August 30, 2024, at an issue price of ₹121 per warrant. The upfront subscription amount of ₹19,66,25,000, which is 25% of the issue price, received at the time of allotment, stands forfeited by the Company.</p><ul><li>65,00,000 Fully Convertible Warrants allotted to Saral Incorporated VCC Sub Fund have lapsed.</li><li>The warrants were allotted on August 30, 2024, at an issue price of ₹121 per warrant.</li><li>The warrant holder did not exercise the option to convert within the stipulated period of 18 months.</li><li>The upfront subscription amount of ₹19,66,25,000 stands forfeited by the Company.</li><li>There is no change in the paid-up equity share capital of the Company pursuant to the above lapse of warrants.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6b551865-d2fb-4854-9c14-986582139895.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IND-SWIFT LABORATORIES LTD. | Category: Warrant Lapse</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MARUTI] Maruti Suzuki India Ltd Reports February 2026 Production Volume</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MARUTI+SUZUKI+INDIA+LTD.&title=Maruti+Suzuki+India+Ltd+Reports+February+2026+Production+Volume&newsId=6e5641ee-e4cf-4367-af93-1c2d44f9daa9&token=NmU1NjQxZWUtZTRj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6e5641ee-e4cf-4367-af93-1c2d44f9daa9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 14:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Maruti Suzuki India Ltd has released the production figures for February 2026. The total production of passenger vehicles stands at 219,612, a significant increase from the previous year&apos;s 183,999. The utility vehicles segment, including models like Brezza, Ertiga, e Vitara, Fronx, Jimny, Victoris, and XL6, saw a production of 102,834 units. The mini and compact segment, including models like Alto, S-Presso, Dzire, Ignis, Swift, and WagonR, saw a production of 88,084 units. The mid-size segment, represented by the Ciaz model, produced 2,900 units. The light commercial vehicle, Super Carry, contributed 3,895 units to the total production. The grand total of passenger vehicles and light commercial vehicles combined is 223,507, a rise from the previous year&apos;s 187,414.</p><ul><li>Maruti Suzuki India Ltd reports February 2026 production volume</li><li>Total passenger vehicles production at 219,612, a significant increase from the previous year&apos;s 183,999</li><li>Utility vehicles segment sees a production of 102,834 units</li><li>Mini and compact segment produces 88,084 units</li><li>Light commercial vehicle, Super Carry, contributes 3,895 units to the total production</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8c7e7db2-5beb-43e8-b253-3b470a29e917.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MARUTI SUZUKI INDIA LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SEAMECLTD] Seamec Ltd&apos;s Vessel SEAMEC II Resumes Contract with ONGC</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SEAMEC+LTD.&title=Seamec+Ltd%27s+Vessel+SEAMEC+II+Resumes+Contract+with+ONGC&newsId=b4b796da-af5e-4bb4-ba6b-5cfd45b0176e&token=YjRiNzk2ZGEtYWY1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4b796da-af5e-4bb4-ba6b-5cfd45b0176e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 14:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Seamec Ltd has informed that its vessel, SEAMEC II, has resumed its contract with ONGC. The vessel sailed back to the field on 1st March 2026 at 11:45 hours, following the completion of its regulatory Flag State Inspection. The intimation was received on 1st March 2026 at 18:17 hours.</p><ul><li>Seamec Ltd&apos;s vessel SEAMEC II has resumed its contract with ONGC.</li><li>The vessel sailed back to the field on 1st March 2026 at 11:45 hours.</li><li>The resumption follows the completion of a regulatory Flag State Inspection.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2fbb019b-956c-4291-bdf3-755fd4c03f80.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SEAMEC LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDUSINDBK] Indusind Bank Ltd withdraws from Jefferies India&apos;s analysts/institutional investors meet in London</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDUSIND+BANK+LTD.&title=Indusind+Bank+Ltd+withdraws+from+Jefferies+India%27s+analysts%2Finstitutional+investors+meet+in+London&newsId=9cb61e69-4637-4afb-ad2d-7d400a710284&token=OWNiNjFlNjktNDYz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9cb61e69-4637-4afb-ad2d-7d400a710284</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 13:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indusind Bank Ltd has informed about its withdrawal from the analysts/institutional investors meet organized by Jefferies India in London on March 2-3, 2026. The decision comes due to unforeseen circumstances. The bank had previously informed about its participation in the meet in a notice dated February 24, 2026.</p><ul><li>Indusind Bank Ltd withdraws from Jefferies India&apos;s analysts/institutional investors meet in London</li><li>The bank was scheduled to participate in the meet on March 2-3, 2026</li><li>The withdrawal is due to unforeseen circumstances</li><li>The bank had previously confirmed its participation in a notice dated February 24, 2026</li><li>The information has been uploaded on the bank&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bfc5d759-21aa-4720-8916-e129e62c3be1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDUSIND BANK LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GMRP&amp;UI] GMR Energy Limited Incorporates New Subsidiary GMR Karnataka Renewable Energy-I Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GMR+Power+and+Urban+Infra+Ltd&title=GMR+Energy+Limited+Incorporates+New+Subsidiary+GMR+Karnataka+Renewable+Energy-I+Limited&newsId=e701b4d4-d932-4348-b22f-d2b79b53029c&token=ZTcwMWI0ZDQtZDkz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e701b4d4-d932-4348-b22f-d2b79b53029c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 13:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>GMR Energy Limited, a wholly owned subsidiary of GMR Power and Urban Infra Ltd, has incorporated a new wholly owned subsidiary company named GMR Karnataka Renewable Energy-I Limited (GKREL). This move is aimed at the development of renewable energy power plants in the state of Karnataka. GKREL has been incorporated with a paid-up capital of Rs. 5 lakh and GMR Energy Limited holds 100% stake in the new subsidiary. The new subsidiary is yet to commence business operations.</p><ul><li>GMR Energy Limited incorporates a new wholly owned subsidiary GKREL</li><li>GKREL aimed at development of renewable energy power plants in Karnataka</li><li>GKREL has a paid-up capital of Rs. 5 lakh</li><li>GMR Energy Limited holds 100% stake in the new subsidiary</li><li>GKREL yet to commence business operations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8be3c489-fe53-4f6b-9cd6-33a8227ef173.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GMR Power and Urban Infra Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDGN] Indegene Ltd Subsidiary Acquires DT Associates and Trilogy Writing and Consulting UK for £2,001,000 and £702,348 Respectively</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Indegene+Ltd&title=Indegene+Ltd+Subsidiary+Acquires+DT+Associates+and+Trilogy+Writing+and+Consulting+UK+for+%C2%A32%2C001%2C000+and+%C2%A3702%2C348+Respectively&newsId=721f3163-4fcd-4bf3-97d8-a1c1545c1a15&token=NzIxZjMxNjMtNGZj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">721f3163-4fcd-4bf3-97d8-a1c1545c1a15</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 12:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Indegene Ltd&apos;s subsidiary, Indegene Healthcare UK Limited, has signed a Share Purchase Agreement (SPA) to acquire 100% equity shares in DT Associates Research and Consulting Services Limited, UK and Trilogy Writing and Consulting Limited, UK. DT Associates is a London-based company providing analytics, technology, and commercial, medical, regulatory and safety services to life science and healthcare organizations, while Trilogy UK provides writing and training services for the pharmaceutical industry. The acquisition is a related party transaction, with the total consideration being £2,703,348. The acquisition is part of Indegene&apos;s internal restructuring and is expected to be completed by 31st March 2026. Both DT Associates and Trilogy UK are based in London, with DT Associates reporting a revenue of £6,400,711 and Trilogy UK reporting a revenue of £2,340,488 in their last financial years.</p><ul><li>Indegene Healthcare UK Limited acquires DT Associates Research and Consulting Services Limited, UK and Trilogy Writing and Consulting Limited, UK.</li><li>The total consideration for the acquisition is £2,703,348.</li><li>The acquisition is a part of Indegene&apos;s internal restructuring.</li><li>DT Associates reported a revenue of £6,400,711 in its last financial year.</li><li>Trilogy UK reported a revenue of £2,340,488 in its last financial year.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d5383f44-c155-488a-9266-d769c0e50daa.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Indegene Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MUFIN] Mufin Green Finance Empanelled with Assam Government for Instant Loans</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Mufin+Green+Finance+Ltd&title=Mufin+Green+Finance+Empanelled+with+Assam+Government+for+Instant+Loans&newsId=f81ea809-462e-4c41-abe1-f54510e36568&token=ZjgxZWE4MDktNDYy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f81ea809-462e-4c41-abe1-f54510e36568</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 11:01:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Mufin Green Finance Limited has been empanelled with the Government of Assam to provide instant loans to more than 5 lakh Assam Government employees directly through the state’s Human Resource Management System (HRMS). This integration enables seamless, real-time access to financing for over five lakh government employees across Assam. Through the HRMS platform, employees can apply for loans and receive approvals instantly — ensuring 24/7 access to funds without delays or paperwork hurdles. Thousands of public sector employees are expected to benefit from the streamlined and transparent loan process. The initiative aligns with broader national objectives of promoting financial inclusion and enhancing access to responsible credit for government staff.</p><ul><li>Mufin Green Finance empanelled with Assam Government for instant loans</li><li>Loans offered directly through the state’s Human Resource Management System (HRMS)</li><li>Seamless, real-time access to financing for over five lakh government employees</li><li>Streamlined and transparent loan process</li><li>Alignment with national objectives of promoting financial inclusion and responsible credit access</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fbf8ad63-90b3-42b2-b958-32b5d302f30b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Mufin Green Finance Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HEROMOTOCO] Hero MotoCorp Delivers Strong 44% Dispatch Growth with 5.58 Lakh Units Sold in February 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HERO+MOTOCORP+LTD.&title=Hero+MotoCorp+Delivers+Strong+44%25+Dispatch+Growth+with+5.58+Lakh+Units+Sold+in+February+2026&newsId=737a4600-9efc-48f0-8759-9ca24dc535e6&token=NzM3YTQ2MDAtOWVm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">737a4600-9efc-48f0-8759-9ca24dc535e6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 11:01:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Hero MotoCorp, the world’s largest manufacturer of motorcycles and scooters, reported its strongest year-on-year (Y-o-Y) dispatch performance for February 2026. The Company dispatched 558,216 units during the month, registering a robust ~44% growth compared to 388,068 units, during the same period last year. The Company also recorded 18% Y-o-Y growth with 458,346 VAHAN registrations in February 2026. The strong performance was driven by continued momentum in the Scooter segment and the 100cc - 125cc segment, which recorded an impressive growth. VIDA, Hero MotoCorp’s emerging mobility business, continued its growth trajectory, recording a three-fold increase in its market share over the same period last year. The Company’s Global Business maintained its growth momentum, recording dispatch growth of ~34% with 41,248 units in February 2026 compared to 30,772 units during the same period last year.</p><ul><li>Hero MotoCorp dispatched 558,216 units in February 2026, a 44% Y-o-Y growth</li><li>The Company recorded 18% Y-o-Y growth with 458,346 VAHAN registrations in February 2026</li><li>Scooter segment and 100cc - 125cc segment recorded impressive growth</li><li>VIDA recorded a three-fold increase in its market share</li><li>Global Business recorded a 34% Y-o-Y dispatch growth in February 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1b5a8bef-8f91-4a2c-8946-be50c33280ce.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HERO MOTOCORP LTD. | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>