<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 18:22:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[FORTISMLR] Fortis Malar Hospitals Ltd Announces Changes in Board Composition: Appointment of Mr. Bidesh Chandra Paul and Resignation of Mr. Chandrasekar Ramaswamy</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Fortis+Malar+Hospitals+Limited&title=Fortis+Malar+Hospitals+Ltd+Announces+Changes+in+Board+Composition%3A+Appointment+of+Mr.+Bidesh+Chandra+Paul+and+Resignation+of+Mr.+Chandrasekar+Ramaswamy&newsId=c5d1e08b-8246-4114-86e3-2a6099a2284f&token=YzVkMWUwOGItODI0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5d1e08b-8246-4114-86e3-2a6099a2284f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Fortis Malar Hospitals Ltd has announced changes in its Board of Directors. Mr. Bidesh Chandra Paul has been appointed as an Additional Director (Non-Independent) effective from January 18, 2026. Mr. Paul is a healthcare and operations leader with over 15 years of experience in manufacturing, R&amp;D, healthcare operations, and supply chain management. On the other hand, Mr. Chandrasekar Ramaswamy has resigned from his position as Whole Time Director and Key Managerial Personnel due to other commitments and responsibilities, effective from the same date.</p><ul><li>Mr. Bidesh Chandra Paul appointed as Additional Director (Non-Independent) of Fortis Malar Hospitals Ltd</li><li>Mr. Paul is a healthcare and operations leader with over 15 years of experience</li><li>Mr. Chandrasekar Ramaswamy has resigned from his position as Whole Time Director and Key Managerial Personnel</li><li>Mr. Ramaswamy&apos;s resignation is due to other commitments and responsibilities</li><li>Both changes are effective from January 18, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ffaa6617-5476-43be-8dc4-b3f623ffaff2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Fortis Malar Hospitals Limited | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DESCO] Desco Infratech Ltd Pays Fine of Rs. 5,900 for Late Submission of Related Party Transactions</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Desco+Infratech+Ltd&title=Desco+Infratech+Ltd+Pays+Fine+of+Rs.+5%2C900+for+Late+Submission+of+Related+Party+Transactions&newsId=355e9252-9b75-46ae-ac69-8a5fd591ca18&token=MzU1ZTkyNTItOWI3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">355e9252-9b75-46ae-ac69-8a5fd591ca18</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 14:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Penal Actions for Non-Compliance</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Desco Infratech Ltd has paid a fine of Rs. 5,900 (inclusive of GST) for late submission of related party transactions in the format as specified and within the prescribed timeline under Regulation 23(9) of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015 for the half year ended September 2025. The delay was inadvertent and has since been rectified. The fine was paid within the stipulated time and the matter was placed before the Board of Directors. The Company has advised to strengthen internal compliance monitoring systems to avoid recurrence of such instances in future.</p><ul><li>Desco Infratech Ltd pays fine of Rs. 5,900 for late submission of related party transactions.</li><li>The delay was inadvertent and has since been rectified.</li><li>The fine was paid within the stipulated time.</li><li>The matter was placed before the Board of Directors.</li><li>Company advised to strengthen internal compliance monitoring systems.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/17aa17c4-b2f7-4589-8931-560828539cff.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Desco Infratech Ltd | Category: Penal Actions for Non-Compliance</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JCTLTD] JCT Ltd Announces 8th Meeting of CoC on January 19, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JCT+LTD.&title=JCT+Ltd+Announces+8th+Meeting+of+CoC+on+January+19%2C+2026&newsId=d7e4875a-e26c-486a-91e9-edb145d9f77f&token=ZDdlNDg3NWEtZTI2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7e4875a-e26c-486a-91e9-edb145d9f77f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 14:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>JCT Ltd has announced the 8th meeting of its Committee of Creditors (CoC) to be held on Monday, the 19th day of January, 2026 at 3.00 P.M. The meeting is scheduled to take place at The Park Hotel, Parliament Street, New Delhi-110001.</p><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/96890b00-cacf-49cf-a41c-97f5ca653b33.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JCT LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CHMBBRW] Chambal Breweries &amp; Distilleries Ltd: Major Board Resignations and Appointment of New Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CHAMBAL+BREWERIES+%26+DISTILLERIES+LTD.&title=Chambal+Breweries+%26+Distilleries+Ltd%3A+Major+Board+Resignations+and+Appointment+of+New+Independent+Director&newsId=20a9bc35-dcb4-4618-8fb8-3473f1b82056&token=MjBhOWJjMzUtZGNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">20a9bc35-dcb4-4618-8fb8-3473f1b82056</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 13:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Chambal Breweries &amp; Distilleries Ltd has announced significant changes in its Board of Directors. Mr. Parasram Jhamnani, Mrs. Amrita Modi, Mr. Rinku Goyal, and Mr. Anmol Jindal have resigned from their positions, effective from 18/01/2026, due to a change in management by takeover. Additionally, Mr. Gaurav Sharma has been appointed as an Additional Independent Director on the same date. Mr. Sharma brings over 22 years of experience in HR leadership across diverse organizations and holds relevant qualifications in ESG and AI leadership.</p><ul><li>Resignation of Mr. Parasram Jhamnani as Managing Director and Chairman</li><li>Resignation of Mrs. Amrita Modi as Director</li><li>Resignation of Mr. Rinku Goyal as an Independent Director</li><li>Resignation of Mr. Anmol Jindal as an Independent Director</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Gaurav Sharma as an Additional Independent Director</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5f4f8665-2098-4c4d-81f9-ef9d0e36f1b8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CHAMBAL BREWERIES & DISTILLERIES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CHMBBRW] Chambal Breweries &amp; Distilleries Ltd: Mass Resignation of Directors and Appointment of New Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CHAMBAL+BREWERIES+%26+DISTILLERIES+LTD.&title=Chambal+Breweries+%26+Distilleries+Ltd%3A+Mass+Resignation+of+Directors+and+Appointment+of+New+Independent+Director&newsId=9e70564f-a621-4e7f-a514-52cbbb46d716&token=OWU3MDU2NGYtYTYy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e70564f-a621-4e7f-a514-52cbbb46d716</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 13:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Chambal Breweries &amp; Distilleries Ltd has announced the resignation of several directors due to a change in management by takeover. The resigning directors include Parasram Jhamnani as Managing Director and Chairman, Amrita Modi as Director, Rinku Goyal and Anmol Jindal as Independent Directors. The resignations are effective from 18/01/2026. Following this, Mr. Gaurav Sharma has been appointed as an Additional Independent Director on the Board of the Company from the same date.</p><ul><li>Parasram Jhamnani, Amrita Modi, Rinku Goyal, and Anmol Jindal have resigned from their positions in Chambal Breweries &amp; Distilleries Ltd.</li><li>The resignations are a result of a change in management by takeover.</li><li>The resignations are effective from 18/01/2026.</li><li>Mr. Gaurav Sharma has been appointed as an Additional Independent Director on the Board of the Company from 18/01/2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f6e6d630-dd82-4d2e-8270-6c23b9179c37.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CHAMBAL BREWERIES & DISTILLERIES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CHMBBRW] Chambal Breweries &amp; Distilleries Ltd: Resignation of Chairman, Managing Director, and Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CHAMBAL+BREWERIES+%26+DISTILLERIES+LTD.&title=Chambal+Breweries+%26+Distilleries+Ltd%3A+Resignation+of+Chairman%2C+Managing+Director%2C+and+Directors&newsId=cbfa3c40-6763-4745-944f-eced7a20bcd6&token=Y2JmYTNjNDAtNjc2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cbfa3c40-6763-4745-944f-eced7a20bcd6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 13:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Chambal Breweries &amp; Distilleries Ltd has announced the resignation of its Chairman and Managing Director, Mr. Parasram Jhamnani, Director, Mrs. Amrita Modi, and Independent Directors, Mr. Rinku Goyal and Mr. Anmol Jindal, effective from 18/01/2026. The resignations are a result of a change in management by takeover. The company has also appointed Mr. Gaurav Sharma as an Additional Independent Director on the Board of the Company.</p><ul><li>Resignation of Chairman and Managing Director, Mr. Parasram Jhamnani.</li><li>Resignation of Director, Mrs. Amrita Modi.</li><li>Resignation of Independent Directors, Mr. Rinku Goyal and Mr. Anmol Jindal.</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Gaurav Sharma as an Additional Independent Director.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/508a73e8-9ebc-44df-929d-aa5e61806d7e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CHAMBAL BREWERIES & DISTILLERIES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STALLION] Stallion India Fluorochemicals Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Discuss Fund Raising Proposal</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Stallion+India+Fluorochemicals+Ltd&title=Stallion+India+Fluorochemicals+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Discuss+Fund+Raising+Proposal&newsId=f8c49b3d-5388-455d-8017-96ee2245cefa&token=ZjhjNDliM2QtNTM4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f8c49b3d-5388-455d-8017-96ee2245cefa</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 13:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Stallion India Fluorochemicals Ltd has informed the BSE that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on 21st January 2026. The agenda of the meeting includes considering a proposal for fund raising through Equity Shares or other securities, subject to regulatory approvals. The company has also announced the closure of the trading window for securities trading from the time of this intimation until 48 hours after the publication of the outcome of the Board Meeting, in compliance with the &apos;Code of Conduct for Prevention of Insider Trading&apos;.</p><ul><li>Stallion India Fluorochemicals Ltd has scheduled a Board Meeting on 21st January 2026</li><li>The agenda includes considering a fund raising proposal through Equity Shares or other securities</li><li>The proposal is subject to regulatory approvals</li><li>The company has announced the closure of the trading window for securities trading</li><li>The trading window will remain closed till 48 hours after the publication of the outcome of the Board Meeting</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/39bc23bd-654b-4b58-b857-c8a95e939074.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Stallion India Fluorochemicals Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SOFTBPO] IDream Film Infrastructure to Allot Shares to Northvale Capital Partners, Triggering Open Offer Process</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SOFTBPO+GLOBAL+SERVICES+LTD.&title=IDream+Film+Infrastructure+to+Allot+Shares+to+Northvale+Capital+Partners%2C+Triggering+Open+Offer+Process&newsId=b6c556cf-6eff-4c4c-bb5c-822eb440aa4f&token=YjZjNTU2Y2YtNmVm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6c556cf-6eff-4c4c-bb5c-822eb440aa4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 12:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>IDream Film Infrastructure Company Limited, formerly known as Softbpo Global Services Limited, is set to allot equity shares to Northvale Capital Partners Private Limited and other proposed allottees. The allotment to Northvale Capital Partners and its associates will trigger the open offer process under Takeover Regulations, making them the new promoters of the company. The total number of equity shares to be allotted is 40,00,000 through cash and 26,64,03,280 through share swap. The allottees include both promoters and non-promoters, with changes in control and management expected consequent to the preferential issue.</p><ul><li>IDream Film Infrastructure to allot shares to Northvale Capital Partners and other proposed allottees</li><li>Allotment to Northvale Capital Partners and associates triggers open offer process under Takeover Regulations</li><li>Northvale Capital Partners and associates to become new promoters of the company</li><li>Total number of equity shares to be allotted: 40,00,000 through cash and 26,64,03,280 through share swap</li><li>Allottees include both promoters and non-promoters, with changes in control and management expected</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/56778bdd-e0f7-45a4-89f9-054241b75526.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SOFTBPO GLOBAL SERVICES LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDIGO] InterGlobe Aviation Faces INR 22.20 Crore Penalty and Systemic Reforms by DGCA</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=InterGlobe+Aviation+Ltd&title=InterGlobe+Aviation+Faces+INR+22.20+Crore+Penalty+and+Systemic+Reforms+by+DGCA&newsId=7002db29-c42b-4ba6-9c67-0e056f7231a9&token=NzAwMmRiMjktYzQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7002db29-c42b-4ba6-9c67-0e056f7231a9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 12:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Regulatory Action</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>InterGlobe Aviation Ltd, the parent company of IndiGo, has been issued 8 orders by the Director General of Civil Aviation (DGCA) based on the findings of an Inquiry Committee. The orders include a one-time systemic penalty of INR 1.80 crore for non-compliances under applicable Civil Aviation Requirements (CARs) and a penalty of INR 20.40 crore for continued non-compliance with revised FDTL CAR for 68 days. The company is also required to furnish a Bank Guarantee of INR 50 crore under the ISRAS. The DGCA has issued cautions, warnings, and operational directives to several key personnel. The financial impact from the orders is INR 22.20 crore. The company has restored normal operations following the December 2025 disruptions and is reviewing the DGCA orders.</p><ul><li>InterGlobe Aviation faces INR 22.20 crore penalty from DGCA</li><li>DGCA issues 8 orders based on Inquiry Committee findings</li><li>Company required to furnish INR 50 crore Bank Guarantee under ISRAS</li><li>Cautions, warnings, and operational directives issued to key personnel</li><li>Company restored normal operations following December 2025 disruptions</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/75766a82-dc42-4009-a71a-7ef17989cc69.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: InterGlobe Aviation Ltd | Category: Regulatory Action</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INSPIRISYS] Inspirisys Solutions Limited Announces Change in Statutory Auditor&apos;s Name</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Inspirisys+Solutions+Ltd&title=Inspirisys+Solutions+Limited+Announces+Change+in+Statutory+Auditor%27s+Name&newsId=33316500-4f44-484c-9cc1-9db3429d71f8&token=MzMzMTY1MDAtNGY0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33316500-4f44-484c-9cc1-9db3429d71f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Inspirisys Solutions Limited has informed the Exchange about a change in the constitution of the Statutory Auditors as per the LODR Regulations, 2015. The Statutory Auditor of the Company, M/s. MSKA &amp; Associates, Chartered Accountants, has converted from a partnership firm into a Limited Liability Partnership (LLP) under the provisions of the Limited Liability Partnership Act, 2008. The firm is now known as MSKA &amp; Associates LLP, Chartered Accountants bearing ICAI Firm Registration Number 105047W (Old) / W101187 (New). This change pertains only to the constitution of the audit firm and does not result in the engagement of new Statutory Auditors. MSKA &amp; Associates LLP shall continue to act and discharge its responsibilities as the Statutory Auditors of the Company for the remaining period of the approved tenure.</p><ul><li>Inspirisys Solutions Limited announces change in Statutory Auditor&apos;s name</li><li>MSKA &amp; Associates, Chartered Accountants, converts into a Limited Liability Partnership (LLP)</li><li>The new name of the Statutory Auditor is MSKA &amp; Associates LLP, Chartered Accountants</li><li>The change is in compliance with the Limited Liability Partnership Act, 2008</li><li>MSKA &amp; Associates LLP will continue as Statutory Auditors for the remaining tenure</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9aa3e943-87b6-4e2a-b5ec-860af9a7276d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Inspirisys Solutions Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>