<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:34:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[FINOPB] Fino Payments Bank&apos;s MD &amp; CEO, Mr. Rishi Gupta, Arrested: CGST and SGST Act Violation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Fino+Payments+Bank+Ltd&title=Fino+Payments+Bank%27s+MD+%26+CEO%2C+Mr.+Rishi+Gupta%2C+Arrested%3A+CGST+and+SGST+Act+Violation&newsId=e121a35e-d7f0-4580-b534-02a2491f1336&token=ZTEyMWEzNWUtZDdm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e121a35e-d7f0-4580-b534-02a2491f1336</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Fino Payments Bank Ltd has informed about the arrest of its Managing Director &amp; CEO, Mr. Rishi Gupta, under the provisions of section 132(1)(a) and 132(1) (i) of the CGST and SGST Act, 2017, respectively on February 27, 2026. The Bank has appointed Mr. Ketan Merchant, Chief Financial Officer, as the Head of the Organization to oversee day-to-day operations until Mr. Gupta&apos;s return or until the Board&apos;s resolution. The investigation is related to business partner(s) of the Bank, and currently, there is no impact on the Bank. However, appropriate disclosures will be made if any impact arises in the future. The Bank is actively addressing the situation, and the disclosure is available on the Bank&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Fino Payments Bank&apos;s MD &amp; CEO, Mr. Rishi Gupta, arrested under CGST and SGST Act, 2017</li><li>Mr. Ketan Merchant appointed as Head of the Organization to oversee day-to-day operations</li><li>Investigation is related to business partner(s) of the Bank, no impact on the Bank currently</li><li>Bank is actively addressing the situation</li><li>Appropriate disclosures will be made if any impact arises in the future</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0427a4bd-d09c-4b05-b063-ca07ae315c7d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Fino Payments Bank Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PNB] Punjab National Bank Keeps Interest Rates Unchanged: MCLR Stays at Existing Level, Repo Linked Lending Rate and Base Rate Remain Steady</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PUNJAB+NATIONAL+BANK&title=Punjab+National+Bank+Keeps+Interest+Rates+Unchanged%3A+MCLR+Stays+at+Existing+Level%2C+Repo+Linked+Lending+Rate+and+Base+Rate+Remain+Steady&newsId=afdcd2ef-cc0d-42c9-a0a0-ddbd41e0abda&token=YWZkY2QyZWYtY2Mw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">afdcd2ef-cc0d-42c9-a0a0-ddbd41e0abda</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Punjab National Bank has announced that its Marginal Cost of Funds Based Lending Rates (MCLR) will remain unchanged with effect from March 1, 2026. The existing Repo linked Lending Rate (RLLR) and Base Rate also remain unchanged at 8.10% and 9.50% respectively. This decision comes as part of the bank&apos;s review of interest rates.</p><ul><li>Punjab National Bank maintains its MCLR rates as of March 1, 2026</li><li>Repo linked Lending Rate (RLLR) remains unchanged at 8.10%</li><li>Base Rate remains steady at 9.50%</li><li>No changes in interest rates reflect bank&apos;s current financial strategy</li><li>The update is part of the bank&apos;s regular review of interest rates</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b63631ea-1299-4911-b5bc-390d708aeb04.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PUNJAB NATIONAL BANK | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[REMSONSIND] Remsons Industries Ltd Receives Order from Commissioner Income Tax Appeal Regulations, 2015</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=REMSONS+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Remsons+Industries+Ltd+Receives+Order+from+Commissioner+Income+Tax+Appeal+Regulations%2C+2015&newsId=4fde95d9-b73a-49bb-916c-cc69ece0d118&token=NGZkZTk1ZDktYjcz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4fde95d9-b73a-49bb-916c-cc69ece0d118</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:27:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Remsons Industries Ltd has received an order under Section 250 of the Income Tax Act, 1961 for the Assessment Year 2021-2022 from the Commissioner of Income Tax Appeals, NFAC, Delhi. The order, which was received on 18th February 2026, upholds the disallowance of certain expenses of Rs. 4.91 crore made by the Assessing Officer. The company is currently evaluating the merits of the matter and will exercise its right to file an appeal before the Hon&apos;ble Income Tax Appellate Tribunal, Mumbai within the prescribed time lines.</p><ul><li>Order received from Commissioner of Income Tax Appeals, NFAC, Delhi under Section 250 of Income Tax Act, 1961 for the Assessment Year 2021-2022</li><li>Order upholds the disallowance of certain expenses of Rs. 4.91 crore made by the Assessing Officer</li><li>Company is evaluating the merits of the matter and will file an appeal before the Hon&apos;ble Income Tax Appellate Tribunal, Mumbai</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/282287b0-676d-4496-b37c-0ce9b40cb7e3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: REMSONS INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GKENERGY] GK Energy Limited: Maharashtra State Goods and Services Tax Department Initiates Search Proceedings</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GK+Energy+Ltd&title=GK+Energy+Limited%3A+Maharashtra+State+Goods+and+Services+Tax+Department+Initiates+Search+Proceedings&newsId=bc9f9450-e2e3-4a42-bb43-c18e6512f209&token=YmM5Zjk0NTAtZTJl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc9f9450-e2e3-4a42-bb43-c18e6512f209</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:21:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>GK Energy Limited has informed the Exchange that Maharashtra State Goods and Services Tax Department has initiated search proceedings at the Registered Office of GK Energy Limited on February 27, 2026 under the applicable provisions of the Maharashtra Goods and Services Tax Act, 2017. The proceedings are ongoing and the Company is extending full cooperation, providing necessary information and assistance to the authorities. As on date, there is no specific communication regarding any violation or contravention and there is no material impact on the financials, operations or other activities of the Company.</p><ul><li>Maharashtra State Goods and Services Tax Department initiates search proceedings at GK Energy Limited&apos;s Registered Office</li><li>Proceedings initiated under the applicable provisions of the Maharashtra Goods and Services Tax Act, 2017</li><li>GK Energy Limited is cooperating with the authorities and providing necessary information</li><li>No specific communication regarding any violation or contravention as of now</li><li>No material impact on the financials, operations or other activities of the Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ac09a303-3ed3-4665-9239-5eed6795aeb8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GK Energy Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHRIRAMFIN] Shriram Finance Ltd Receives Order with Penalties of Over Rs. 8 Crores for FY 2020-23</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shriram+Finance+Ltd&title=Shriram+Finance+Ltd+Receives+Order+with+Penalties+of+Over+Rs.+8+Crores+for+FY+2020-23&newsId=763812b0-4d07-4501-95b6-872a015bebb2&token=NzYzODEyYjAtNGQw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">763812b0-4d07-4501-95b6-872a015bebb2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:12:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Shriram Finance Ltd has received an order from the Additional Commissioner of Central Tax, Secunderabad GST Commissionerate, Tarnaka, Secunderabad, Telangana, imposing penalties for the financial years 2020-2023. The total penalties amount to Rs. 8,34,32,779. The order was received on February 26, 2026, and the company has already forwarded a copy of the order to the concerned officer. The penalties have been levied under Section 74 of the Central Goods and Service Tax Act, 2017, read with the Telangana Goods and Service Tax Act, 2017 and the Integrated Goods and Services Tax Act, 2017. The company is awaiting an opinion from their tax consultant regarding the penalties.</p><ul><li>Shriram Finance Ltd received an order from the Additional Commissioner of Central Tax, Secunderabad GST Commissionerate, Tarnaka, Secunderabad, Telangana</li><li>Penalties for the financial years 2020-2023 amount to Rs. 8,34,32,779</li><li>The order was received on February 26, 2026</li><li>Penalties have been levied under Section 74 of the Central Goods and Service Tax Act, 2017, read with the Telangana Goods and Service Tax Act, 2017 and the Integrated Goods and Services Tax Act, 2017</li><li>The company is awaiting an opinion from their tax consultant regarding the penalties</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d440d436-5019-4b51-a3ad-60dafd9864af.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shriram Finance Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ELPROINTL] Elpro International Acquires Mynd Solutions for INR 11.37 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ELPRO+INTERNATIONAL+LTD.&title=Elpro+International+Acquires+Mynd+Solutions+for+INR+11.37+Crores&newsId=e0ccc433-672f-4fda-86bd-c24a20cad9ba&token=ZTBjY2M0MzMtNjcy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0ccc433-672f-4fda-86bd-c24a20cad9ba</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Elpro International Ltd. has acquired 1,66,442 equity shares of Mynd Solutions Private Limited, a fintech and business services company operating an RBI-licensed Trade Receivables Discounting System (TReDS) platform. The cost of acquisition was INR 11.37 Crores. Mynd Solutions, incorporated in 2002, has a consolidated turnover of INR 104.70 Crores in FY 2024-25. The acquisition is a fresh one, with Elpro previously holding no equity shares in Mynd Solutions.</p><ul><li>Elpro International acquires 1,66,442 equity shares of Mynd Solutions</li><li>Cost of acquisition is INR 11.37 Crores</li><li>Mynd Solutions is a fintech and business services company</li><li>Mynd Solutions operates an RBI-licensed TReDS platform for invoice discounting and supply-chain finance</li><li>Mynd Solutions has a consolidated turnover of INR 104.70 Crores in FY 2024-25</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2aacd2d9-a544-462b-9a0d-31c9f27c9136.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ELPRO INTERNATIONAL LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LOTUSCHO] Lotus Chocolate Company Ltd: Krishnakumar Thirumalai Resigns, Mohammed Rafathullah Appointed as Additional Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LOTUS+CHOCOLATE+CO.LTD.&title=Lotus+Chocolate+Company+Ltd%3A+Krishnakumar+Thirumalai+Resigns%2C+Mohammed+Rafathullah+Appointed+as+Additional+Director&newsId=1195f9a9-bbd3-420a-aa8e-cc87df3cc0a0&token=MTE5NWY5YTktYmJk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1195f9a9-bbd3-420a-aa8e-cc87df3cc0a0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:11:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Lotus Chocolate Company Ltd announced the resignation of Mr. Krishnakumar Thirumalai as a Non-Executive Non-Independent Director, effective from February 27, 2026. The company expressed gratitude for his contributions. The Board has approved the appointment of Mr. Mohammed Rafathullah as an Additional Director (Non-Executive) from the same date, subject to the approval of the members of the company. Mr. Rafathullah is an experienced business leader with a track record in FMCG, Telecom, IT, and ISP businesses in India and South Asia.</p><ul><li>Mr. Krishnakumar Thirumalai resigns from Lotus Chocolate Company Ltd.</li><li>The company expresses gratitude for Thirumalai&apos;s contributions.</li><li>Mr. Mohammed Rafathullah appointed as Additional Director (Non-Executive).</li><li>Rafathullah&apos;s appointment is subject to the approval of the company&apos;s members.</li><li>Rafathullah is an experienced business leader with expertise in sales &amp; distribution, brand management, and manufacturing.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/909473f7-022b-4bdb-a01f-cfa383336387.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LOTUS CHOCOLATE CO.LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MPHASIS] Non-Executive, Non-Independent Director, Ms. Courtney Karlan Della Cava, Resigns from Mphasis Ltd.</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MPHASIS+LTD.&title=Non-Executive%2C+Non-Independent+Director%2C+Ms.+Courtney+Karlan+Della+Cava%2C+Resigns+from+Mphasis+Ltd.&newsId=66d9de24-d200-46ee-8444-017d92e6d61b&token=NjZkOWRlMjQtZDIw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66d9de24-d200-46ee-8444-017d92e6d61b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:11:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mphasis Ltd. has announced the resignation of Ms. Courtney Karlan Della Cava as a Non-Executive, Non-Independent Director. The resignation is effective from February 27, 2026, due to her other commitments and obligations. Ms. Della Cava expressed her gratitude to the Mphasis Board of Directors and management team for their support and guidance during her tenure. She sincerely wishes the company continued success and growth in the future.</p><ul><li>Ms. Courtney Karlan Della Cava resigns from Mphasis Ltd.</li><li>Effective resignation date is February 27, 2026.</li><li>Resignation is due to other commitments and obligations.</li><li>Ms. Della Cava expresses gratitude to the Mphasis Board and management team.</li><li>Wishes continued success and growth for Mphasis Ltd.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/16bdf652-4dbb-4717-9343-09286274f858.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MPHASIS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PRABHA] Prabha Energy Ltd. Postpones Rights Issue Committee Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Prabha+Energy+Ltd&title=Prabha+Energy+Ltd.+Postpones+Rights+Issue+Committee+Meeting&newsId=5b2eb3cf-4cfd-44e3-9adb-df4c33c6cd61&token=NWIyZWIzY2YtNGNm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b2eb3cf-4cfd-44e3-9adb-df4c33c6cd61</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:11:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Right Issue</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Prabha Energy Ltd. has informed BSE that the meeting of the Board of Directors, originally scheduled for February 27, 2026, to consider and approve the terms and conditions of the rights issue, has been postponed. The meeting was postponed due to the Company not yet receiving in-principle approval from BSE Limited &amp; National Stock Exchange of India Limited for the proposed rights issue. The meeting is now rescheduled for March 05, 2026, subject to the receipt of in-principle approval and compliance with applicable regulatory requirements.</p><ul><li>Prabha Energy Ltd. postpones Rights Issue Committee meeting to March 05, 2026</li><li>The postponement is due to not receiving in-principle approval from BSE Limited &amp; National Stock Exchange of India Limited</li><li>The meeting is subject to the receipt of in-principle approval and compliance with applicable regulatory requirements</li><li>The Rights Issue includes consideration and approval of terms and conditions, issue price, rights entitlement ratio, record date, and issue schedule</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bb37286f-fe04-4329-a5e1-87590984a221.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Prabha Energy Ltd | Category: Right Issue</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DPWIRES] D.P. Wires Ltd. Reschedules Extra Ordinary General Meeting Date</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=D.P.+Wires+Ltd&title=D.P.+Wires+Ltd.+Reschedules+Extra+Ordinary+General+Meeting+Date&newsId=907d8125-a2db-42d4-bcca-99c771aff937&token=OTA3ZDgxMjUtYTJk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">907d8125-a2db-42d4-bcca-99c771aff937</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 15:11:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>D.P. Wires Ltd. has informed the BSE that the Board of Directors will meet on 03/03/2026 to consider and approve the rescheduling of the Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) date. The meeting will be held at the registered office of the company in Ratlam, Madhya Pradesh. The Board will also approve the notice for the EGM, fix the cut-off date, appoint a scrutinizer for voting and e-voting, and consider any other matter with the chair&apos;s permission. The company&apos;s trading window remains closed as per the Company’s Code of Conduct for Prevention of Insider Trading.</p><ul><li>The date of the Extra Ordinary General Meeting is being rescheduled.</li><li>The Board will approve the notice for the EGM and fix the cut-off date.</li><li>A scrutinizer for voting and e-voting will be appointed.</li><li>The company&apos;s trading window remains closed.</li><li>The meeting will be held at the registered office of the company in Ratlam, Madhya Pradesh.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/06db8c7b-a5d1-4e3f-95cb-731d8e93ab50.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: D.P. Wires Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>