<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 12:37:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SCHAND] S Chand and Company Ltd Approves Corporate Guarantee of Rs. 10.00 Crores for Subsidiary</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=S+Chand+and+Company+Ltd&title=S+Chand+and+Company+Ltd+Approves+Corporate+Guarantee+of+Rs.+10.00+Crores+for+Subsidiary&newsId=768d39e5-9ee3-4f72-a28c-ce22bbe12dfd&token=NzY4ZDM5ZTUtOWVl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">768d39e5-9ee3-4f72-a28c-ce22bbe12dfd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 12:34:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>S Chand and Company Ltd announced the outcome of its Board Meeting held on January 07, 2026. The Board approved a Corporate Guarantee in favor of HDFC Bank Limited for an amount up to Rs. 10.00 Crores. The guarantee is for a cash credit facility proposed to be taken by Shri Shyamlal Printing Press Private Limited, a wholly owned subsidiary of the Company. The guarantee is provided to secure the grant of the cash credit facility and is also secured by personal guarantees by the Managing Director and Whole-time Director cum promoters of the Company. The financials of the subsidiary are consolidated with the Company, hence there is no impact on a consolidated basis.</p><ul><li>S Chand and Company Ltd approved a Corporate Guarantee in favor of HDFC Bank Limited for an amount up to Rs. 10.00 Crores.</li><li>The guarantee is for a cash credit facility proposed to be taken by Shri Shyamlal Printing Press Private Limited, a wholly owned subsidiary of the Company.</li><li>The guarantee is secured by personal guarantees by the Managing Director and Whole-time Director cum promoters of the Company.</li><li>The financials of the subsidiary are consolidated with the Company, hence there is no impact on a consolidated basis.</li><li>The decision was made during the Board Meeting held on January 07, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/564e03a3-851f-43c0-989d-dcd7e47b2e0f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: S Chand and Company Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PPARIVAH] Paradeep Parivahan Ltd. Approves Issue of Warrants in Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Paradeep+Parivahan+Ltd&title=Paradeep+Parivahan+Ltd.+Approves+Issue+of+Warrants+in+Board+Meeting&newsId=b2036da6-7f01-4120-926e-a7bb99111bae&token=YjIwMzZkYTYtN2Yw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b2036da6-7f01-4120-926e-a7bb99111bae</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 12:33:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Paradeep Parivahan Ltd. has approved the issuance of up to 12,00,000 Fully Convertible Equity Warrants at an issue price of Rs. 156.17 each. The warrants are convertible into 1 (One) fully paid-up equity share of the Company of face value Rs. 10/— each. The decision was made at a Board Meeting held on January 7, 2026. The funds raised will be through preferential issue on private placement basis to the proposed Allottees as per Annexure-I.</p><ul><li>Approval of raising funds through issuance of up to 12,00,000 Fully Convertible Equity Warrants</li><li>Issue price of Rs. 156.17 per warrant</li><li>Warrants are convertible into 1 fully paid-up equity share of the Company</li><li>Funds to be raised through preferential issue on private placement basis</li><li>Appointment of Bigshare Services Pvt. Ltd. as Remote E-Voting Agency and Sunita Jyotirmoy &amp; Associates as scrutinizer to the remote e-voting process</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ffb60654-75f5-4fb1-8b64-c9d09d309e1a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Paradeep Parivahan Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PEIL] Premier Energy and Infrastructure Ltd Approves Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 &amp; Nine Months Ended 31st December, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Premier+Energy+and+Infrastructure+Ltd&title=Premier+Energy+and+Infrastructure+Ltd+Approves+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Ended+31st+December%2C+2025&newsId=97793196-dc94-4853-92ee-9a5a5b1fa3b3&token=OTc3OTMxOTYtZGM5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97793196-dc94-4853-92ee-9a5a5b1fa3b3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 12:32:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Premier Energy and Infrastructure Ltd announced the approval of their unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025 in a meeting of the Board of Directors held on 7th January, 2026. The results were prepared in accordance with Indian Accounting Standard (Ind AS) 34, and the Listing Regulations. The company also enclosed the Limited Review Report by R. Sundararajan &amp; Associates, Chartered Accountants. The details of the unaudited financial results will be available on the company&apos;s website and on the website of the stock exchange.</p><ul><li>Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 &amp; nine months ended 31st December, 2025 approved</li><li>Prepared in accordance with Indian Accounting Standard (Ind AS) 34 and Listing Regulations</li><li>Limited Review Report by R. Sundararajan &amp; Associates, Chartered Accountants</li><li>Details of the unaudited financial results to be available on the company&apos;s website and on the website of the stock exchange</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1f03f4f7-435d-49d2-95d1-4ca93a130511.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Premier Energy and Infrastructure Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TATASTEEL] Tata Steel Achieves &apos;Best-Ever&apos; Quarterly Production and Deliveries in 3QFY2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TATA+STEEL+LTD.&title=Tata+Steel+Achieves+%27Best-Ever%27+Quarterly+Production+and+Deliveries+in+3QFY2026&newsId=6685a94e-923f-43d4-ba05-91fd0be9000b&token=NjY4NWE5NGUtOTIz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6685a94e-923f-43d4-ba05-91fd0be9000b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 12:32:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Tata Steel has reported its production and delivery volumes for the third quarter of the financial year 2026. The company achieved a &apos;best-ever&apos; quarterly crude steel production of 6.34 million tons in India, a 12% increase both quarter-over-quarter and year-over-year. This was primarily due to higher output at Jamshedpur and Kalinganagar facilities. The company&apos;s deliveries also reached a &apos;best-ever&apos; quarterly high of 6 million tons, a 9% increase quarter-over-quarter and 14% year-over-year. Key highlights of domestic deliveries for the quarter include &apos;Automotive &amp; Special Products&apos; vertical achieving &apos;best-ever&apos; volumes of ~0.9 million tons, &apos;Branded Products &amp; Retail&apos; vertical surpassing 2 million tons for the first time, and &apos;Industrial Products &amp; Projects&apos; vertical achieving volumes of ~1.9 million tons.</p><ul><li>Tata Steel India achieved &apos;best-ever&apos; quarterly crude steel production of 6.34 million tons.</li><li>The company&apos;s deliveries also reached a &apos;best-ever&apos; quarterly high of 6 million tons.</li><li>Automotive &amp; Special Products vertical achieved &apos;best-ever&apos; volumes of ~0.9 million tons.</li><li>Branded Products &amp; Retail vertical surpassed 2 million tons for the first time.</li><li>Industrial Products &amp; Projects vertical achieved volumes of ~1.9 million tons.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6cd06c31-0fba-4f2f-b25f-14fe50957a0e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TATA STEEL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MAHESH] Mahesh Developers Ltd. Announces Q1 2025 Financial Results with Moderate Assurance</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Mahesh+Developers+Ltd&title=Mahesh+Developers+Ltd.+Announces+Q1+2025+Financial+Results+with+Moderate+Assurance&newsId=82befac0-a4fe-4107-912d-ea64ae205521&token=ODJiZWZhYzAtYTRm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">82befac0-a4fe-4107-912d-ea64ae205521</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 12:32:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mahesh Developers Ltd. has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter ended 30th June, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at Rs. 1,00,221 Lakhs, with a total income of Rs. 1,00,221 Lakhs. The operating costs were reported at Rs. (2,04) Lakhs. The profit before tax is reported at Rs. 291 Lakhs. The company&apos;s net profit after tax for the period is Rs. (4.38) Lakhs. The total comprehensive income for the period is Rs. 1.64 Lakhs. The company&apos;s earnings per share (EPS) is (0.11) for basic and 0.04 for diluted.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations stands at Rs. 1,00,221 Lakhs</li><li>Total income reported is Rs. 1,00,221 Lakhs</li><li>Operating costs reported at Rs. (2,04) Lakhs</li><li>Profit before tax reported at Rs. 291 Lakhs</li><li>Net profit after tax for the period is Rs. (4.38) Lakhs</li><li>Total comprehensive income for the period is Rs. 1.64 Lakhs</li><li>Earnings per share (EPS) is (0.11) for basic and 0.04 for diluted</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/736a950a-ae7d-474e-9105-9dbd0809ccf2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Mahesh Developers Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SIDDHEGA] Siddheswari Garments Ltd. Announces Unaudited Financial Results for Q2 and Half Year Ended 30 September, 2025 After Delay Due to Auditor&apos;s Demise</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SIDDHESWARI+GARMENTS+LTD.&title=Siddheswari+Garments+Ltd.+Announces+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q2+and+Half+Year+Ended+30+September%2C+2025+After+Delay+Due+to+Auditor%27s+Demise&newsId=4fad5aa3-9646-4ce2-a081-94cbe7ef6447&token=NGZhZDVhYTMtOTY0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4fad5aa3-9646-4ce2-a081-94cbe7ef6447</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 12:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Siddheswari Garments Ltd. announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and half year ended 30 September, 2025. The approval and declaration of the results were delayed due to the sudden demise of the company&apos;s statutory auditor, Mr. Ramesh Kumar Bajaj. The company appointed M/s N Dokania &amp; Associates as the new statutory auditors, who completed the limited review process, and the results were approved at the present board meeting. The review report, prepared in accordance with the Indian Accounting Standards and the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, did not reveal any material misstatement.</p><ul><li>Unaudited financial results for Q2 and half year ended 30 September, 2025 approved after delay due to auditor&apos;s demise.</li><li>New statutory auditors, M/s N Dokania &amp; Associates, appointed to fill the casual vacancy.</li><li>Limited review process completed by the new auditors before results were approved.</li><li>Review report did not reveal any material misstatement.</li><li>Company will assess the impact of the new draft rules for the Companies Act on its financial statements.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e395f063-17e9-4363-85f7-a46c60b2523b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SIDDHESWARI GARMENTS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CHEVIOT] Cheviot Company Acquires Shares of Hindalco Industries Ltd for Long-Term Investment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CHEVIOT+CO.LTD.-%24&title=Cheviot+Company+Acquires+Shares+of+Hindalco+Industries+Ltd+for+Long-Term+Investment&newsId=75622c23-29f4-4054-8c9f-54fb14ab08bb&token=NzU2MjJjMjMtMjlm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75622c23-29f4-4054-8c9f-54fb14ab08bb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 12:32:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cheviot Company Ltd has acquired equity shares of Hindalco Industries Ltd (HIL) through the stock exchange mechanism. The acquisition is a long-term investment and does not aim to acquire control. The value or expected impact of the shares exceeds the threshold specified in Regulation 30(4)(i)(c) of the Listing Regulations, necessitating disclosure. HIL, incorporated in 1958, is engaged in manufacturing metal and metal products. It reported a Total Equity of ¥ 70,206 crores as of 31.3.2025, revenue from operations of ¥ 93,309 crores, and Profit for the year of ¥ 6,387 crores for the year ended 31.3.2025. The acquisition was made without any relation to the promoter/promoter group/group companies, and the shares were purchased at ₹ 937.5754 per share. Cheviot Company Ltd holds 0.01% of HIL&apos;s share capital.</p><ul><li>Cheviot Company Ltd acquires shares of Hindalco Industries Ltd (HIL) through the stock exchange mechanism.</li><li>The acquisition is a long-term investment without the intention to acquire control.</li><li>HIL is a company incorporated in 1958, engaged in manufacturing metal and metal products.</li><li>The value or expected impact of the shares acquired exceeds the threshold specified in Regulation 30(4)(i)(c) of the Listing Regulations.</li><li>The shares were purchased at ₹ 937.5754 per share.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8a666156-20dc-44f3-a066-50b12c1f822d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CHEVIOT CO.LTD.-$ | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HUDCO] HUDCO Signs MoU with Chhattisgarh Government for Rs.1,00,000.00 Crore Financial Assistance</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Housing+%26+Urban+Development+Corporation+Ltd&title=HUDCO+Signs+MoU+with+Chhattisgarh+Government+for+Rs.1%2C00%2C000.00+Crore+Financial+Assistance&newsId=b5278f1a-8d1e-4a48-869c-84ba911dd81c&token=YjUyNzhmMWEtOGQx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5278f1a-8d1e-4a48-869c-84ba911dd81c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 12:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>MoU</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Housing and Urban Development Corporation Limited (HUDCO) has signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with the Government of Chhattisgarh. As per this non-binding MoU, HUDCO may provide financial assistance of up to Rs.1,00,000.00 Crore (Rupees One Lakh Crore) during the next five years for execution of different housing and infrastructure projects in the State of Chhattisgarh. This MoU is only an in-principle arrangement and neither party is bound to commit the loan as borrower or lender.</p><ul><li>HUDCO may provide financial assistance of up to Rs.1,00,000.00 Crore to Chhattisgarh Government</li><li>MoU aims to fund housing and infrastructure projects in Chhattisgarh</li><li>The agreement is non-binding and in-principle</li><li>The financial assistance will be disbursed over the next five years</li><li>The assistance will be in the form of debt</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a09043aa-0819-4698-9d81-e7a0d85ed525.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Housing & Urban Development Corporation Ltd | Category: MoU</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ONGC] Oil and Natural Gas Corporation Makes Significant Progress in Blowout Operations at Well Mori#5</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Oil+and+Natural+Gas+Corporation+Ltd&title=Oil+and+Natural+Gas+Corporation+Makes+Significant+Progress+in+Blowout+Operations+at+Well+Mori%235&newsId=e0aaaa62-0839-44b8-b356-8935242216fa&token=ZTBhYWFhNjItMDgz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0aaaa62-0839-44b8-b356-8935242216fa</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 12:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Oil and Natural Gas Corporation Ltd. (ONGC) is making significant progress in blowout operations at Well Mori#5, operated by PEC contractor M/s Deep Industries. The Crisis Management Team is working according to the approved blowout control plan, and fire intensity, noise levels, and ambient heat have reduced significantly. An approach road has been completed for debris clearance, and a water blanket has been established for continued debris removal and capping the wellhead. The district administration has advised residents to resume normal activities due to the steady progress and low likelihood of escalation. ONGC is prioritizing safety and environmental protection, complying with regulatory requirements and industry best practices.</p><ul><li>Oil and Natural Gas Corporation Ltd. (ONGC) is making significant progress in blowout operations at Well Mori#5.</li><li>The Crisis Management Team is working according to the approved blowout control plan.</li><li>Fire intensity, noise levels, and ambient heat have reduced significantly.</li><li>An approach road has been completed for debris clearance, and a water blanket has been established for continued debris removal and capping the wellhead.</li><li>The district administration has advised residents to resume normal activities due to the steady progress and low likelihood of escalation.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d8fd8958-65fb-465e-83cc-513489124327.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Oil and Natural Gas Corporation Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WEWORK] WeWork India Management Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on Jan 27, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=WeWork+India+Management+Ltd&title=WeWork+India+Management+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+Jan+27%2C+2026&newsId=ed287c51-b307-4edb-8279-d3d8769acb02&token=ZWQyODdjNTEtYjMw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed287c51-b307-4edb-8279-d3d8769acb02</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 12:31:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>WeWork India Management Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 27, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting is scheduled in accordance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, and the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company has been closed from Thursday, January 1, 2026, and will remain closed until 48 hours after the declaration of the aforesaid results.</p><ul><li>WeWork India Management Ltd to consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The meeting is scheduled in accordance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li><li>The trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company has been closed from Thursday, January 1, 2026.</li><li>The trading window will remain closed until 48 hours after the declaration of the aforesaid results.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/36904565-dd23-4c45-8af2-96cc3073ad9a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: WeWork India Management Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>