<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:49:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[LLOYDSME] Thriveni Earthmovers Pvt Ltd Releases Pledge on Lloyds Metals and Energy Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LLOYDS+METALS+AND+ENERGY+LTD.&title=Thriveni+Earthmovers+Pvt+Ltd+Releases+Pledge+on+Lloyds+Metals+and+Energy+Shares&newsId=ff40a0d3-df12-46f9-a0e9-cf4fddd1fab9&token=ZmY0MGEwZDMtZGYx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff40a0d3-df12-46f9-a0e9-cf4fddd1fab9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:42:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Pledge</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Thriveni Earthmovers Pvt Ltd (TEMPL), a promoter of Lloyds Metals and Energy Limited (Target Company), has released a pledge on 64,14,150 (1.18% of the paid-up share capital of the TC) equity shares of the TC held by TEMPL, in favour of ICICI Bank Limited. This unattested pledge agreement was executed on 29th May, 2024.</p><ul><li>Thriveni Earthmovers Pvt Ltd, a promoter of Lloyds Metals and Energy Limited, has released a pledge on 1.18% of the company&apos;s shares.</li><li>The pledge was in favour of ICICI Bank Limited as per an Unattested Pledge Agreement dated 29th May, 2024.</li><li>64,14,150 equity shares of Lloyds Metals and Energy Limited were affected by this pledge release.</li><li>The pledge was released on 19th February, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/278982CD_7798_47A7_8A8D_3B99157335B0_101026.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LLOYDS METALS AND ENERGY LTD. | Category: Pledge</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DHINDIA] Prominent Dilution of Voting Rights in D &amp; H India Ltd by Harsh Vora and Others</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=D%26H+India+Ltd-%24&title=Prominent+Dilution+of+Voting+Rights+in+D+%26+H+India+Ltd+by+Harsh+Vora+and+Others&newsId=5bcee110-31cf-4a1b-8a26-c579750d5292&token=NWJjZWUxMTAtMzFj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5bcee110-31cf-4a1b-8a26-c579750d5292</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dilution</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>According to a disclosure made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011, there has been a significant dilution of voting rights in D &amp; H India Ltd due to non-subscription of Rights Entitlement by the Promoter and Persons Acting in Concert (PAC). The notable changes in shareholding are as follows: Harsh Vora&apos;s holding has decreased from 13.43% to 10.74%, Harsh Kumar Vora (HUF)&apos;s holding has decreased from 8.23% to 6.58%, Saurabh Vora&apos;s holding has decreased from 17.11% to 16.50%, and Kiran Vora, Atithi Vora, and Suhani Doshi&apos;s holdings have decreased from 11.50%, 0.61%, and 0.61% to 2.30%, 1.20%, and 1.20% respectively. The total dilution in shareholding for the Promoter and PAC is 10.30%. This change exceeds 2% of the total voting rights of the Promoter and Promoter Group of the Company.</p><ul><li>Significant dilution of voting rights in D &amp; H India Ltd</li><li>Harsh Vora&apos;s holding decreased from 13.43% to 10.74%</li><li>Harsh Kumar Vora (HUF)&apos;s holding decreased from 8.23% to 6.58%</li><li>Saurabh Vora&apos;s holding decreased from 17.11% to 16.50%</li><li>Kiran Vora, Atithi Vora, and Suhani Doshi&apos;s holdings decreased from 11.50%, 0.61%, and 0.61% to 2.30%, 1.20%, and 1.20% respectively</li><li>Total dilution in shareholding for the Promoter and PAC is 10.30%</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2DDE00B4_AB57_45A9_8E61_EC0250EFA93B_100253.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: D&H India Ltd-$ | Category: Dilution</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LAXMIDENTL] Rajesh Vrajlal Khakhar Acquires 11,000 Shares of Laxmi Dental Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Laxmi+Dental+Ltd&title=Rajesh+Vrajlal+Khakhar+Acquires+11%2C000+Shares+of+Laxmi+Dental+Ltd&newsId=49099376-6caa-4fd5-9a53-a4a402c5a33c&token=NDkwOTkzNzYtNmNh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">49099376-6caa-4fd5-9a53-a4a402c5a33c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:36:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rajesh Vrajlal Khakhar, a promoter, chairman, and whole-time director of Laxmi Dental Ltd (formerly known as Laxmi Dental Export Private Limited), has acquired 11,000 shares of the company. This acquisition represents 0.02% of the total voting rights and share capital of the company. The shares were acquired on the open market on February 23, 2026. After the acquisition, the total voting rights and share capital held by Rajesh Vrajlal Khakhar amount to 16.93% and 0.02% respectively.</p><ul><li>Rajesh Vrajlal Khakhar acquires 11,000 shares of Laxmi Dental Ltd</li><li>The acquisition represents 0.02% of the total voting rights and share capital</li><li>The shares were acquired on the open market on February 23, 2026</li><li>After the acquisition, Rajesh Vrajlal Khakhar holds 16.93% of the total voting rights</li><li>The total share capital held by Rajesh Vrajlal Khakhar is 0.02%</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/72C3D24B_82E9_48E6_9D43_42B732AB165A_100126.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Laxmi Dental Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JUSTO] Promoter Puspamitra Das Acquires 4,000 Equity Shares of Justo Realfintech Ltd Through Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Justo+Realfintech+Ltd&title=Promoter+Puspamitra+Das+Acquires+4%2C000+Equity+Shares+of+Justo+Realfintech+Ltd+Through+Open+Market&newsId=72e5965a-23fe-4752-a5c5-995b1ef69b6b&token=NzJlNTk2NWEtMjNm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72e5965a-23fe-4752-a5c5-995b1ef69b6b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:34:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Puspamitra Das, a promoter of Justo Realfintech Ltd, has acquired 4,000 equity shares of the company through the open market. The acquisition was made on 23rd February 2026. The total share capital of the company stands at INR 18,79,81,420 consisting of 1,87,98,142 Equity Shares of Rs. 10 each, both before and after the acquisition. The total diluted share/voting capital of the TC after the acquisition is also INR 18,79,81,420 consisting of 1,87,98,142 Equity Shares of Rs. 10 each.</p><ul><li>Puspamitra Das, a promoter of Justo Realfintech Ltd, acquires 4,000 equity shares through open market</li><li>The acquisition was made on 23rd February 2026</li><li>The total share capital of the company stands at INR 18,79,81,420 consisting of 1,87,98,142 Equity Shares of Rs. 10 each</li><li>The total diluted share/voting capital of the TC after the acquisition is also INR 18,79,81,420 consisting of 1,87,98,142 Equity Shares of Rs. 10 each</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/444C654D_E66D_421A_AF7C_16E016960286_095935.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Justo Realfintech Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CNL] Creative Newtech Partners with Kaspersky to Strengthen Cybersecurity Solutions Portfolio in India</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Creative+Newtech+Ltd&title=Creative+Newtech+Partners+with+Kaspersky+to+Strengthen+Cybersecurity+Solutions+Portfolio+in+India&newsId=94fbbc60-bb96-4c69-8883-9a876ab4be30&token=OTRmYmJjNjAtYmI5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">94fbbc60-bb96-4c69-8883-9a876ab4be30</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Partnership</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Creative Newtech Limited, a leading market entry specialist and value-added partner across technology and digital solutions, has announced a partnership with Kaspersky, a global cybersecurity and digital privacy company. The partnership aims to expand cybersecurity offerings in India, with the distribution scope covering North, West, and East India. Creative Newtech will distribute Kaspersky’s cybersecurity solutions for consumers and businesses, protecting against various cyber threats through multi-layered, AI-driven security architecture.</p><ul><li>Partnership between Creative Newtech and Kaspersky to expand cybersecurity offerings in India</li><li>Distribution scope covers North, West, and East India</li><li>Kaspersky’s cybersecurity solutions for consumers and businesses to be distributed</li><li>Protection against various cyber threats through multi-layered, AI-driven security architecture</li><li>Alignment with national initiatives such as Digital India and Cyber Surakshit Bharat</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2749b53c-479a-4249-9015-e00bd496c9c5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Creative Newtech Ltd | Category: Partnership</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FLAIR] Flair Writing Industries Limited Commences Manufacturing of Wooden Pencils; Strengthens Creative Portfolio</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Flair+Writing+Industries+Ltd&title=Flair+Writing+Industries+Limited+Commences+Manufacturing+of+Wooden+Pencils%3B+Strengthens+Creative+Portfolio&newsId=0635193e-f6b9-471f-ba02-277fd43dd06f&token=MDYzNTE5M2UtZjZi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0635193e-f6b9-471f-ba02-277fd43dd06f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:28:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Flair Writing Industries Limited has started manufacturing wooden pencils at its step down subsidiary, Flomaxe Stationery Private Limited in Surat. This expansion strengthens the company&apos;s Creative portfolio and enhances its abilities to penetrate further into the largest segment of the stationery industry. The production line will have an estimated annual capacity of 84 Million pieces and will also focus on manufacturing of complimentary products such as range of erasers and sharpeners. This move is a part of the company&apos;s strategy to rapidly scale the creative segment which grew by 72% year on year in 9M FY26.</p><ul><li>Flair Writing Industries Limited has begun manufacturing wooden pencils at Flomaxe Stationery Private Limited in Surat.</li><li>The new manufacturing line has an estimated annual capacity of 84 Million pieces.</li><li>The company will also focus on manufacturing of complimentary products such as range of erasers and sharpeners.</li><li>This expansion strengthens the company&apos;s Creative portfolio and enhances its abilities to penetrate further into the largest segment of the stationery industry.</li><li>This move is a part of the company&apos;s strategy to rapidly scale the creative segment which grew by 72% year on year in 9M FY26.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/829b08f7-0782-48be-b59a-b02ba0404ee3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Flair Writing Industries Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TTL] Promoter Group Acquires 0.0240% Additional Stake in T T Brands Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=T+T+LTD.-%24&title=Promoter+Group+Acquires+0.0240%25+Additional+Stake+in+T+T+Brands+Ltd&newsId=2d6c2103-311e-47f7-9e19-5e2f454b7a68&token=MmQ2YzIxMDMtMzEx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2d6c2103-311e-47f7-9e19-5e2f454b7a68</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:28:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>According to a disclosure made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011, the Promoter Group of T T Brands Ltd has acquired 62,075 shares, thereby increasing their holding to 34.0308%. This acquisition took place through a mode other than open market, off-market, public issue, rights issue, preferential allotment, or inter-se transfer. The total diluted share/voting capital of the company after the acquisition stands at 25,83,10,944.</p><ul><li>Promoter Group acquires 0.0240% additional stake in T T Brands Ltd</li><li>Acquisition of 62,075 shares by the Promoter Group</li><li>Total holding of the Promoter Group increases to 34.0308%</li><li>Acquisition made through a mode other than open market, off-market, public issue, rights issue, preferential allotment, or inter-se transfer</li><li>Total diluted share/voting capital of the company stands at 25,83,10,944 post-acquisition</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0EF6CB30_5E50_4333_8905_3C220DDBC6E3_095618.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: T T LTD.-$ | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DHINDIA] Indo Thai Securities Acquires 8,84,186 Shares in D&amp;H India&apos;s Right Issue, Exceeding 5% Shareholding</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=D%26H+India+Ltd-%24&title=Indo+Thai+Securities+Acquires+8%2C84%2C186+Shares+in+D%26H+India%27s+Right+Issue%2C+Exceeding+5%25+Shareholding&newsId=2708b2a5-5afc-4d42-9ee3-86560a4640d3&token=MjcwOGIyYTUtNWFm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2708b2a5-5afc-4d42-9ee3-86560a4640d3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 04:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Indo Thai Securities Limited, along with its PACs, has acquired 8,84,186 equity shares of D &amp; H India Limited having a face value of Rs. 10/- per share. This acquisition was made pursuant to the right issue of Equity Shares of D &amp; H India Limited on February 19, 2026. As a result, the shareholding of Indo Thai Securities Limited along with its PACs has exceeded 5% of the paid-up capital of D &amp; H India Limited.</p><ul><li>Indo Thai Securities Limited acquires 8,84,186 shares in D &amp; H India Limited&apos;s right issue.</li><li>The acquisition results in Indo Thai Securities Limited and its PACs exceeding 5% shareholding in D &amp; H India Limited.</li><li>The acquisition was made on February 19, 2026.</li><li>The acquired shares have a face value of Rs. 10/- per share.</li><li>Dhanpal Doshi, Sadhana Doshi, Nishit Doshi, Nivya Doshi, Abhisha Doshi, Rajmati Hinged, Rajendra Bandi, Indo Thai Realties Limited, Indo Thai Commodities Private Limited, Prosperity Residency Private Limited, and Indo Thai Wealth Management Private Limited are the PACs involved in the acquisition.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/C997D9F2_C2FD_412E_BE2B_A0F18DC6175E_095329.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: D&H India Ltd-$ | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LUCENT] Mobavenue AI Tech Ltd Chairman Attends Global India - AI Impact Summit 2026, Meets Bhutan PM</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Lucent+Industries+Ltd&title=Mobavenue+AI+Tech+Ltd+Chairman+Attends+Global+India+-+AI+Impact+Summit+2026%2C+Meets+Bhutan+PM&newsId=cfca4db3-0ecf-4242-8f23-70612bdc9782&token=Y2ZjYTRkYjMtMGVj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cfca4db3-0ecf-4242-8f23-70612bdc9782</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 03:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mobavenue AI Tech Ltd announced that its Chairman, Kunal Kothari, participated in the Global India - AI Impact Summit 2026 held in New Delhi on February 18, 2026. The Summit focused on the transformative impact of Artificial Intelligence across sectors, including advancing inclusive growth, strengthening multilateral cooperation, promoting people-centric innovation, and ensuring responsible deployment of emerging technologies. During the visit, Kothari had a special interaction with Tshering Tobgay, Prime Minister of the Kingdom of Bhutan, at the Bhutanese Embassy, discussing topics such as Bhutan’s development philosophy centered around Gross National Happiness, strengthening travel and tourism visibility, enhancing global engagement, and preserving environmental integrity and cultural heritage. Mobavenue AI Tech Ltd believes that such high-level engagements provide valuable global perspective and strengthen its strategic understanding of evolving AI ecosystems across emerging markets.</p><ul><li>Mobavenue AI Tech Ltd Chairman attended the Global India - AI Impact Summit 2026 in New Delhi</li><li>Discussions at the Summit focused on the transformative impact of AI across sectors</li><li>Kunal Kothari had a special interaction with Tshering Tobgay, Prime Minister of Bhutan</li><li>They discussed topics such as Bhutan’s development philosophy, strengthening travel and tourism visibility, and preserving environmental integrity and cultural heritage</li><li>Mobavenue AI Tech Ltd believes high-level engagements provide valuable global perspective</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ccfa8e54-5167-418c-bfa1-ab54b1bc4a37.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Lucent Industries Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ORGANICREC] Organic Recycling Systems Secures Large-Scale EPC Contract for CBG Project in Madhya Pradesh</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Organic+Recycling+Systems+Ltd&title=Organic+Recycling+Systems+Secures+Large-Scale+EPC+Contract+for+CBG+Project+in+Madhya+Pradesh&newsId=c02f9c50-9ff7-4367-9c33-2328a90ea30b&token=YzAyZjljNTAtOWZm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c02f9c50-9ff7-4367-9c33-2328a90ea30b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 03:10:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Organic Recycling Systems (ORSL) has secured a large-scale order from Shreyam Manek Agro Products Pvt. Ltd. for the construction of a state-of-the-art Integrated Compressed Bio-Gas (CBG) and biofertilizer project in Damoh, Madhya Pradesh. The facility is designed to produce an output of 10 TPD (Tons Per Day) of CBG using agro feedstock. ORSL will undertake equity participation, end-to-end EPC execution, encompassing detailed engineering, technology integration, supply of critical equipment, construction, installation, and commissioning of the facility. The project reflects a strategic collaboration and is part of a larger plan of 10 (ten) such integrated projects to be deployed in various locations of Madhya Pradesh with a total outlay of 500-600 Cr INR within a period of 3 years.</p><ul><li>ORSL secures a large-scale EPC contract for a CBG project in Madhya Pradesh</li><li>The project is designed to produce 10 TPD of CBG using agro feedstock</li><li>ORSL will undertake equity participation and end-to-end EPC execution</li><li>The project is part of a larger plan of 10 integrated projects in Madhya Pradesh</li><li>The total outlay of the projects is 500-600 Cr INR within a period of 3 years</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9fe57ae1-6f71-4c30-bd61-b1518b025fbb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Organic Recycling Systems Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>