<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 18:28:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[RIIL] Reliance Industrial Infrastructure Reports Q3 FY 2025-26 Financial Performance with 10.4% Increase in Net Profit</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RELIANCE+INDUSTRIAL+INFRASTRUCTURE+LTD.&title=Reliance+Industrial+Infrastructure+Reports+Q3+FY+2025-26+Financial+Performance+with+10.4%25+Increase+in+Net+Profit&newsId=56810f27-2d67-4f1b-93c7-e2ca1c59907f&token=NTY4MTBmMjctMmQ2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56810f27-2d67-4f1b-93c7-e2ca1c59907f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Reliance Industrial Infrastructure Limited (RIIL) has reported its financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The consolidated total income stands at ₹1,848 lakh, a minor increase of 1.0% compared to the previous quarter and a 54.8% increase compared to the same period last year. The net profit for the quarter is ₹301 lakh, a 9.9% increase from the ₹274 lakh reported in Q3 FY 2024-25. The company continues to provide infrastructure support services, primarily to Reliance Industries Limited, and does not have any expansion plans currently.</p><ul><li>Consolidated total income of ₹1,848 lakh for Q3 FY 2025-26, a 1.0% increase from Q2 and a 54.8% increase from Q3 FY 2024-25.</li><li>Net profit for Q3 FY 2025-26 is ₹301 lakh, a 9.9% increase from ₹274 lakh in Q3 FY 2024-25.</li><li>The company continues to provide infrastructure support services to Reliance Industries Limited.</li><li>No expansion plans are currently on the anvil for the company.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fa57875a-0ade-433a-a34c-fa03a65ed3d7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RELIANCE INDUSTRIAL INFRASTRUCTURE LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RIIL] Reliance Industrial Infrastructure Ltd Approves Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months of FY2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RELIANCE+INDUSTRIAL+INFRASTRUCTURE+LTD.&title=Reliance+Industrial+Infrastructure+Ltd+Approves+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+of+FY2025-26&newsId=3a9644c5-bab2-4f9d-ada8-658c0e48abd6&token=M2E5NjQ0YzUtYmFi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a9644c5-bab2-4f9d-ada8-658c0e48abd6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:21:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Reliance Industrial Infrastructure Ltd has approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The total income for the quarter is Rs. 18,48,89,000 and for the nine months is Rs. 54,89,55,000. The profit before tax for the quarter is Rs. 3,40,351 and for the nine months is Rs. 2,96,114. The profit after tax for the quarter is Rs. 30,10,917 and for the nine months is Rs. 8,77,119. The company has also recognized an incremental liability pertaining to its employees due to the New Labour Codes.</p><ul><li>Reliance Industrial Infrastructure Ltd has approved the unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months of FY2025-26.</li><li>The total income for the quarter is Rs. 18,48,89,000 and for the nine months is Rs. 54,89,55,000.</li><li>The profit before tax for the quarter is Rs. 3,40,351 and for the nine months is Rs. 2,96,114.</li><li>The profit after tax for the quarter is Rs. 30,10,917 and for the nine months is Rs. 8,77,119.</li><li>The company has recognized an incremental liability pertaining to its employees due to the New Labour Codes.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/94a3a324-4863-405b-b372-921b4367508e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RELIANCE INDUSTRIAL INFRASTRUCTURE LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BIOCON] Biocon Ltd Receives Approval for Qualified Institutions Placement</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BIOCON+LTD.&title=Biocon+Ltd+Receives+Approval+for+Qualified+Institutions+Placement&newsId=e6409860-7685-435d-870c-5de49b52b50d&token=ZTY0MDk4NjAtNzY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e6409860-7685-435d-870c-5de49b52b50d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Biocon Limited has received approval for a Qualified Institutions Placement (QIP) by the Fund Raising Committee. The approval was given during a meeting held on January 14, 2026, from 10:12 p.m. to 10:20 p.m. The Placement Document for the QIP, dated January 14, 2026, has been approved and adopted under Chapter VI of the SEBI ICDR Regulations and Sections 23(1)(b), 42 and 62(1)(c) of the Companies Act, 2013. This intimation is being made available on the company&apos;s website and is considered as compliance under the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Biocon Ltd receives approval for a Qualified Institutions Placement</li><li>The approval was given by the Fund Raising Committee during a meeting held on January 14, 2026</li><li>The Placement Document for the QIP, dated January 14, 2026, has been approved and adopted</li><li>The approval is under Chapter VI of the SEBI ICDR Regulations and Sections 23(1)(b), 42 and 62(1)(c) of the Companies Act, 2013</li><li>The intimation is being made available on the company&apos;s website and is considered as compliance under the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/18306021-f05e-4587-a889-3d689538f868.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BIOCON LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BIOCON] Biocon Ltd. Closes Qualified Institutional Placement at Discounted Price of 368.35 per Equity Share</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BIOCON+LTD.&title=Biocon+Ltd.+Closes+Qualified+Institutional+Placement+at+Discounted+Price+of+368.35+per+Equity+Share&newsId=0252deef-6b86-47d3-8f0e-88a0823809a2&token=MDI1MmRlZWYtNmI4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0252deef-6b86-47d3-8f0e-88a0823809a2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:51:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Biocon Limited, a prominent player in the biopharmaceutical industry, has successfully closed its Qualified Institutional Placement (QIP) on January 14, 2026. The issue, which opened on January 12, 2026, saw the allocation of 11,26,64,585 Equity Shares at an issue price of 368.35 per Equity Share, representing a discount of 19.39 per Equity Share or 5% to the floor price of 387.74 per Equity Share. The decision to close the issue was made following the receipt of application forms and funds from eligible qualified institutional buyers in accordance with the terms of the issue. The allocation of equity shares was determined and approved by the Fund Raising Committee in accordance with the SEBI ICDR Regulations.</p><ul><li>Biocon Ltd. closes its Qualified Institutional Placement (QIP) on January 14, 2026.</li><li>11,26,64,585 Equity Shares allotted at an issue price of 368.35 per Equity Share.</li><li>The issue price represents a discount of 19.39 per Equity Share or 5% to the floor price of 387.74 per Equity Share.</li><li>Decision to close the issue made following receipt of application forms and funds from eligible qualified institutional buyers.</li><li>Allocation of equity shares determined and approved by the Fund Raising Committee in accordance with the SEBI ICDR Regulations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8b55092e-9f98-483d-a037-b25cb8ae18bb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BIOCON LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DEEPAKFERT] Mahadhan AgriTech Limited, Wholly Owned Subsidiary of Deepak Fertilisers, Gets Penalty Dropped by Commissioner of Income Tax</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DEEPAK+FERTILISERS+%26+PETROCHEMICALS+CORPORATION+LTD.&title=Mahadhan+AgriTech+Limited%2C+Wholly+Owned+Subsidiary+of+Deepak+Fertilisers%2C+Gets+Penalty+Dropped+by+Commissioner+of+Income+Tax&newsId=80bd092a-3463-495a-94d8-d18b704c33a8&token=ODBiZDA5MmEtMzQ2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80bd092a-3463-495a-94d8-d18b704c33a8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Penalty Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Deepak Fertilisers &amp; Petrochemicals Corporation Ltd. has announced that the penalty orders passed against its wholly owned subsidiary, Mahadhan AgriTech Limited (MAL), have been allowed and the penalty amounting to Rs. 382.81 Crores has been dropped by the Commissioner of Income Tax (Appeals), Mumbai. The penalty was initially imposed for Assessment Years 2016-17 to 2018-19 by the Deputy Commissioner of Income Tax (AO). The appeal for Assessment Year 2015-16, amounting to Rs. 96.03 Crores, is still pending for disposal.</p><ul><li>Penalty of Rs. 382.81 Crores dropped by Commissioner of Income Tax (Appeals), Mumbai for MAL</li><li>Penalty was initially imposed for Assessment Years 2016-17 to 2018-19 by the Deputy Commissioner of Income Tax (AO)</li><li>Appeal for Assessment Year 2015-16, amounting to Rs. 96.03 Crores, is still pending for disposal</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/efcb3690-e9da-44bf-987e-02017ea24b6f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DEEPAK FERTILISERS & PETROCHEMICALS CORPORATION LTD. | Category: Penalty Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PRESTIGE] Prestige Estates Projects Ltd Launches Evergreen at Prestige Raintree Park, a Rs. 5,000 Crore GDV Premium Living Destination in Whitefield, Bengaluru</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PRESTIGE+ESTATES+PROJECTS+LTD.&title=Prestige+Estates+Projects+Ltd+Launches+Evergreen+at+Prestige+Raintree+Park%2C+a+Rs.+5%2C000+Crore+GDV+Premium+Living+Destination+in+Whitefield%2C+Bengaluru&newsId=95bc829d-3402-4b61-9005-d4205edd58f7&token=OTViYzgyOWQtMzQw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95bc829d-3402-4b61-9005-d4205edd58f7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:37:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Prestige Estates Projects Limited, one of India’s leading real estate developers, has announced the launch of Evergreen at Prestige Raintree Park, a premium residential development located in Whitefield, Bengaluru. The project is spread over approximately 24 acres of land and comprises around 2,000 apartments with a total saleable area of 3.2 million square feet. Evergreen at Prestige Raintree Park offers a mix of one, two, three and four-bedroom residences, priced starting from approximately ~92 lakhs. The project is strategically located at the junction of Whitefield and Varthur, offering strong connectivity to key office hubs and established social infrastructure.</p><ul><li>Prestige Estates Projects Limited launches Evergreen at Prestige Raintree Park in Whitefield, Bengaluru.</li><li>The project is spread over approximately 24 acres and comprises around 2,000 apartments.</li><li>Evergreen at Prestige Raintree Park offers a mix of one, two, three and four-bedroom residences.</li><li>The project is strategically located at the junction of Whitefield and Varthur.</li><li>Evergreen at Prestige Raintree Park is estimated to have a Gross Development Value (GDV) of about Rs. 5,000 crores.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2eb06cb7-1eef-4e58-95cf-5977b3b51c10.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PRESTIGE ESTATES PROJECTS LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NETWORK18] Network18 Reports 5% YoY Increase in Q3 Operating Revenue Despite Advertising Challenges</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NETWORK18+MEDIA+%26+INVESTMENTS+LTD.&title=Network18+Reports+5%25+YoY+Increase+in+Q3+Operating+Revenue+Despite+Advertising+Challenges&newsId=d03f5576-0375-4412-ba6f-21a019f2df2e&token=ZDAzZjU1NzYtMDM3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d03f5576-0375-4412-ba6f-21a019f2df2e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:31:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Network18 Media &amp; Investments Limited announced its Q3 FY2025-26 results, showing a 5% YoY increase in operating revenue for the news business. Despite a challenging macro advertising environment, the company maintained its strong position as the #1 news network in the country, with increased TV viewership share and digital reach. The company also renewed its partnership with CNN International for 10 years and launched Creator18, a new vertical to expand advertising reach through the creator ecosystem.</p><ul><li>Operating revenue of News business up 5% YoY to Rs. 500 crores</li><li>Network18 maintains its strong position as the #1 news network in the country</li><li>Renewed partnership with CNN International for 10 years</li><li>Launched Creator18, a new vertical to expand advertising reach through the creator ecosystem</li><li>Network18 continues to be the biggest digital news network on Youtube</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c3663238-a89d-4c08-bc2f-a397c59aa13d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NETWORK18 MEDIA & INVESTMENTS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EXPLEOSOL] Expleo Solutions Ltd. Faces Rs.48,34,061 Demand from Assistant Commissioner of Income Tax</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Expleo+Solutions+Ltd&title=Expleo+Solutions+Ltd.+Faces+Rs.48%2C34%2C061+Demand+from+Assistant+Commissioner+of+Income+Tax&newsId=cc390708-1ee7-4226-a7d2-e277f3a7cc52&token=Y2MzOTA3MDgtMWVl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cc390708-1ee7-4226-a7d2-e277f3a7cc52</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:25:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Expleo Solutions Ltd. has disclosed an order issued by the Assistant Commissioner of Income Tax, Corporate Circle 1(1), Chennai, raising a demand of Rs.48,34,061 for the Assessment Year 2012-13. The demand is on account of disallowance of MAT Credit utilized amounting to Rs.17,42,507. The order was received on 14th January 2026. The company has stated that there is no material impact on its financials or operations due to this demand.</p><ul><li>Expleo Solutions Ltd. disclosed an order from the Assistant Commissioner of Income Tax, Chennai</li><li>The order raises a demand of Rs.48,34,061 for the Assessment Year 2012-13</li><li>The demand is due to disallowance of MAT Credit utilized amounting to Rs.17,42,507</li><li>The order was received on 14th January 2026</li><li>Expleo Solutions Ltd. stated no material impact on its financials or operations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b2acaa20-03f7-4123-8e63-bf68457f5061.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Expleo Solutions Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PRESTIGE] Prestige Estates Announces Record-Breaking Sales and Collections in Q3 and 9M FY26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PRESTIGE+ESTATES+PROJECTS+LTD.&title=Prestige+Estates+Announces+Record-Breaking+Sales+and+Collections+in+Q3+and+9M+FY26&newsId=c368c89a-408c-4101-bbc1-fb1ce20beea5&token=YzM2OGM4OWEtNDA4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c368c89a-408c-4101-bbc1-fb1ce20beea5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:21:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Prestige Estates Projects Limited announced its operational performance for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025 (Q3 FY26 and 9M FY26), delivering record-breaking sales and collections alongside sustained execution momentum. The company recorded pre-sales of 41,836 million in Q3 FY26, representing a 39% year-on-year growth. For the nine months ended FY26, pre-sales surged to 223,273 million, up 122% year-on-year, marking the highest sales ever achieved by the company. Collections for Q3 FY26 stood at 45,475 million, registering a 40% year-on-year growth. Prestige Estates Projects launched 5.02 million sq. ft. during Q3 FY26, taking total launches in 9M FY26 to 23.83 million sq. ft. The company completed 4.72 million sq. ft. during Q3 FY26, taking total completions for 9M FY26 to 12.71 million sq. ft.</p><ul><li>Record-breaking sales of 223,273 million in 9M FY26, surpassing previous full-year peaks</li><li>40% year-on-year growth in collections in Q3 FY26, reaching 45,475 million</li><li>Launched 5.02 million sq. ft. in Q3 FY26, taking total launches in 9M FY26 to 23.83 million sq. ft.</li><li>Completed 4.72 million sq. ft. in Q3 FY26, taking total completions for 9M FY26 to 12.71 million sq. ft.</li><li>Strong occupancy across commercial and retail portfolios, robust development pipeline, and sustained launch and execution momentum</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0e0369ed-1a18-45bb-86b0-66fabc673f9a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PRESTIGE ESTATES PROJECTS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GALAGEX] Galaxy Agrico Exports Ltd. to Consider Rights Issue of Equity Shares Aggregating to Rs. 49 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GALAXY+AGRICO+EXPORTS+LTD.&title=Galaxy+Agrico+Exports+Ltd.+to+Consider+Rights+Issue+of+Equity+Shares+Aggregating+to+Rs.+49+Crores&newsId=a040fe4d-a05a-4794-9d8c-a6bf4e5dc51d&token=YTA0MGZlNGQtYTA1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a040fe4d-a05a-4794-9d8c-a6bf4e5dc51d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:14:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Galaxy Agrico Exports Ltd. has announced a meeting of the Board of Directors on 19th January 2026 to consider and approve the terms and conditions of a Rights Issue of Equity Shares. The issue, which is not expected to exceed Rs. 49 Crores, was previously authorized in November 2024 and received approval from BSE Limited in December 2025. The Board will decide on the rights issue price, payment mechanism, issue size, rights entitlement ratio, record date, and the opening and closing dates of the issue. The Letter of Offer and other related documents will also be approved in this meeting. In compliance with insider trading regulations, the trading window for dealing in the Company&apos;s securities has been closed and will remain so until 48 hours after the outcome of the meeting is declared.</p><ul><li>Galaxy Agrico Exports Ltd. to consider a Rights Issue of Equity Shares not exceeding Rs. 49 Crores</li><li>The Rights Issue was previously authorized in November 2024 and received BSE approval in December 2025</li><li>The Board will decide on the rights issue price, payment mechanism, issue size, rights entitlement ratio, record date, and the opening and closing dates of the issue</li><li>The Letter of Offer and other related documents will be approved in the meeting</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the Company&apos;s securities has been closed in compliance with insider trading regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/544a9643-eab0-4ad0-b6e1-d75e3e2dbdf0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GALAXY AGRICO EXPORTS LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>