<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:38:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[NUTRICIRCLE] Nutricircle Ltd. Announces Q3 Results for FY 2025-2026, Reports Profit Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Nutricircle+Ltd&title=Nutricircle+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+Results+for+FY+2025-2026%2C+Reports+Profit+Growth&newsId=4781fe5d-b264-4a37-9eee-63b103fa9774&token=NDc4MWZlNWQtYjI2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4781fe5d-b264-4a37-9eee-63b103fa9774</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:37:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Nutricircle Ltd. has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December 2025. The Board of Directors held a meeting on 13th February 2026 and approved the financial results. The company&apos;s Chief Operating Decision Maker (CODM) reviews the operations as a single reportable segment. The financial results are reviewed by the statutory auditors of the company. The company has approved the issue of equity shares on a preferential basis for an amount not exceeding Rs.9.73 Crores. Previous year figures have been regrouped and rearranged for comparability.</p><ul><li>Nutricircle Ltd. reported a profit growth in Q3 FY 2025-2026</li><li>The company&apos;s unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December 2025 have been approved by the Board of Directors</li><li>The company&apos;s financial results are reviewed by the statutory auditors</li><li>Nutricircle Ltd. has approved the issue of equity shares on a preferential basis for an amount not exceeding Rs.9.73 Crores</li><li>Previous year figures have been regrouped and rearranged for comparability</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/77436585-99b1-49d8-a054-15c0fe90ab44.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Nutricircle Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BLUECLOUDS] Blue Cloud Softech Solutions Ltd. CEO Resigns Following Elevation as Group CEO</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Blue+Cloud+Softech+Solutions+Ltd&title=Blue+Cloud+Softech+Solutions+Ltd.+CEO+Resigns+Following+Elevation+as+Group+CEO&newsId=27bcc17c-8e39-43c7-82b8-ae24062f3a92&token=MjdiY2MxN2MtOGUz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27bcc17c-8e39-43c7-82b8-ae24062f3a92</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:35:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>CEO</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Blue Cloud Softech Solutions Ltd. has announced the resignation of its CEO, Mr. Vinod Babu Bollikonda, effective from the close of business hours on February 13, 2026. The resignation is a result of his elevation as the Group Chief Executive Officer of the Company. The Company has expressed its appreciation for Mr. Bollikonda&apos;s contributions during his tenure as CEO.</p><ul><li>Blue Cloud Softech Solutions Ltd. announces the resignation of its CEO, Mr. Vinod Babu Bollikonda.</li><li>Mr. Bollikonda&apos;s resignation is due to his elevation as the Group Chief Executive Officer of the Company.</li><li>His resignation is effective from the close of business hours on February 13, 2026.</li><li>The Company has expressed its appreciation for Mr. Bollikonda&apos;s contributions as CEO.</li><li>Mr. Bollikonda will continue as Group CEO from January 1, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8ef293a3-0591-45fd-ace9-7cfbd0e31493.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Blue Cloud Softech Solutions Ltd | Category: CEO</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NUTRICIRCLE] Nutricircle Ltd Approves Allotment of 11,00,000 Equity Shares at Rs. 10/- Each</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Nutricircle+Ltd&title=Nutricircle+Ltd+Approves+Allotment+of+11%2C00%2C000+Equity+Shares+at+Rs.+10%2F-+Each&newsId=6fd3f378-51cb-4103-b464-4d84d3f575ff&token=NmZkM2YzNzgtNTFj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6fd3f378-51cb-4103-b464-4d84d3f575ff</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:34:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In a recent Board Meeting, Nutricircle Ltd approved the allotment of 11,00,000 equity shares of Rs. 10/- each at an issue price of Rs. 10/- each. The allotment is to be made to Mr. Hitesh Mohanlal Patel, Promoter &amp; Managing Director. The company has received the balance subscription amount of Rs. 82,50,000/- for the 11,00,000 convertible warrants into equity shares. The Board has also authorized Mr. Hitesh Patel and Mrs. Aakansha Jain to file necessary applications with BSE for Listing of Shares and do such acts and deeds as deem fit and proper.</p><ul><li>Nutricircle Ltd approved the allotment of 11,00,000 equity shares at Rs. 10/- each.</li><li>The allotment is to be made to Mr. Hitesh Mohanlal Patel, Promoter &amp; Managing Director.</li><li>The company has received the balance subscription amount of Rs. 82,50,000/- for the 11,00,000 convertible warrants into equity shares.</li><li>Mr. Hitesh Patel and Mrs. Aakansha Jain are authorized to file necessary applications with BSE for Listing of Shares.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/35e80d33-e335-42e4-a145-f9b2eb8e53c7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Nutricircle Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BLUECLOUDS] Blue Cloud Softech Solutions Ltd. CEO Resigns Following Elevation as Group CEO</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Blue+Cloud+Softech+Solutions+Ltd&title=Blue+Cloud+Softech+Solutions+Ltd.+CEO+Resigns+Following+Elevation+as+Group+CEO&newsId=f2d00718-90b1-42b1-b828-5920676db5f8&token=ZjJkMDA3MTgtOTBi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f2d00718-90b1-42b1-b828-5920676db5f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>CEO</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Blue Cloud Softech Solutions Ltd. has announced the resignation of its CEO, Mr. Vinod Babu Bollikonda, effective from the close of business hours on February 13, 2026. The resignation is a result of his elevation as the Group Chief Executive Officer of the Company. The Company has expressed its appreciation for Mr. Bollikonda&apos;s contributions during his tenure as CEO.</p><ul><li>Blue Cloud Softech Solutions Ltd. announces resignation of CEO, Mr. Vinod Babu Bollikonda</li><li>Resignation is due to Mr. Bollikonda&apos;s elevation as Group CEO</li><li>Effective from the close of business hours on February 13, 2026</li><li>Company appreciates Mr. Bollikonda&apos;s contributions as CEO</li><li>Mr. Vinod Babu Bollikonda to take over as Group CEO from January 1, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d49b3737-5746-47a0-9427-b8197c848174.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Blue Cloud Softech Solutions Ltd | Category: CEO</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RUBYMILLS] Ruby Mills Ltd Reports Q3 FY 2025-26 Financial Results with Profit Before Tax at ₹ 1,821.18 Lakhs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RUBY+MILLS+LTD.&title=Ruby+Mills+Ltd+Reports+Q3+FY+2025-26+Financial+Results+with+Profit+Before+Tax+at+%E2%82%B9+1%2C821.18+Lakhs&newsId=a75e0404-a772-4e38-be0b-cf0429f96952&token=YTc1ZTA0MDQtYTc3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a75e0404-a772-4e38-be0b-cf0429f96952</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ruby Mills Ltd has reported its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s profit before tax stands at ₹ 1,821.18 Lakhs. The financial results have been prepared in accordance with Indian Accounting Standards (Ind AS) and reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors. The statutory auditors have expressed an unmodified conclusion on these financial results. The financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December, 2025 are available on the Bombay Stock Exchange Limited website, The National Stock Exchange of India Limited website, and on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Profit before tax at ₹ 1,821.18 Lakhs for Q3 FY 2025-26</li><li>Financial results prepared in accordance with Ind AS</li><li>Reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors</li><li>Statutory auditors have expressed an unmodified conclusion on these financial results</li><li>Financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December, 2025 available on various websites</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f0359f62-265a-4391-be16-4a687a818c2e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RUBY MILLS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AXELPOLY] Axel Polymers Ltd. confirms no deviation in utilization of preferential issue proceeds as of December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AXEL+POLYMERS+LTD.&title=Axel+Polymers+Ltd.+confirms+no+deviation+in+utilization+of+preferential+issue+proceeds+as+of+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=7f00da78-1143-48cb-bd5e-5aeaaaad67bb&token=N2YwMGRhNzgtMTE0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7f00da78-1143-48cb-bd5e-5aeaaaad67bb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:32:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Axel Polymers Ltd. has released a statement of deviation and variation for the quarter ended 31st December, 2025, regarding preferential issue proceeds. The company has confirmed that there has not been any deviation or variation in the utilization of net proceeds of the preferential issue of equity shares as of December 31, 2025. The report includes object-wise utilization of issue proceeds along with any variation, as per Regulation 32 of Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Axel Polymers Ltd. confirms no deviation in utilization of preferential issue proceeds as of December 31, 2025.</li><li>The company has released a statement of deviation and variation for the quarter ended 31st December, 2025.</li><li>Object-wise utilization of issue proceeds has been reported with any variation.</li><li>The report is in agreement with the books and records of the Company.</li><li>The report is solely for the purpose of compliance with Regulation 32 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e515d813-de5a-434a-a558-f2c2a0f6e2e0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AXEL POLYMERS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VIKRAN] Vikran Engineering Ltd. Announces Q3 Results, Board Decisions, and Penalty Payment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vikran+Engineering+Ltd&title=Vikran+Engineering+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+Results%2C+Board+Decisions%2C+and+Penalty+Payment&newsId=a8c15a51-5d88-4f06-ae5b-e7094a80182a&token=YThjMTVhNTEtNWQ4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8c15a51-5d88-4f06-ae5b-e7094a80182a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:32:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vikran Engineering Ltd. has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025, along with key decisions from their recent board meeting. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 17,629 INR lakhs. The board approved the availing of a term loan or the issuance of unlisted, secured, rated, redeemable non-convertible debentures for up to approximately Rs. 300 Crores. They also accepted the resignation of the Internal Auditor and noted a penalty levied by the National Stock Exchange for a one-day delay in disclosure of a related party transaction. Measures have been implemented to strengthen internal compliance monitoring mechanisms.</p><ul><li>Q3 revenue from operations at 17,629 INR lakhs</li><li>Approval for term loan or debenture issuance up to approximately Rs. 300 Crores</li><li>Acceptance of resignation from the Internal Auditor</li><li>Payment of penalty for one-day delay in disclosure of related party transaction</li><li>Measures implemented to strengthen internal compliance monitoring mechanisms</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/94206493-d1b2-48c4-8635-ea66e41c8ed9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vikran Engineering Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MULTIBASE] Multibase India Ltd. Announces Q3 &amp; Nine Months Results for 2025, Compliant with SEBI Regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MULTIBASE+INDIA+LTD.&title=Multibase+India+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Compliant+with+SEBI+Regulations&newsId=27aae6ab-9f6b-4d72-a8ed-3c1a75bd81a0&token=MjdhYWU2YWItOWY2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27aae6ab-9f6b-4d72-a8ed-3c1a75bd81a0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Multibase India Limited announced the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, at a Board meeting on February 13, 2026. The results were prepared in accordance with Indian Accounting Standard 34, the Companies Act, 2013, and other recognized accounting principles generally accepted in India. The company&apos;s primary segment is the manufacture and sale of Thermoplastic Elastomers and Silicone-based products. The results were reviewed and recommended by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, announced.</li><li>Results prepared in accordance with Indian Accounting Standards and other recognized accounting principles.</li><li>Company&apos;s primary segment is the manufacture and sale of Thermoplastic Elastomers and Silicone-based products.</li><li>Results reviewed and recommended by the Audit Committee.</li><li>Approved by the Board of Directors at their meeting held on February 13, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a70b9d00-277c-48d5-a1a0-51b80881842f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MULTIBASE INDIA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SANJIVIN] Sanjivani Paranteral Ltd Reports Strong Q3FY26 Performance with 20.25% YoY Revenue Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SANJIVANI+PARANTERAL+LTD.&title=Sanjivani+Paranteral+Ltd+Reports+Strong+Q3FY26+Performance+with+20.25%25+YoY+Revenue+Growth&newsId=c661a8c7-3b4b-4769-aac6-e2816d0ddc70&token=YzY2MWE4YzctM2I0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c661a8c7-3b4b-4769-aac6-e2816d0ddc70</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Sanjivani Paranteral Ltd, a Mumbai-based pharmaceutical company, has reported a robust performance for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations grew by 20.25% YoY to Rs. 208.63 mn. The integration of SPL Infusion Pvt. Ltd., Pune, has strengthened the company&apos;s manufacturing footprint and contributed to the topline growth. The company&apos;s core business continues to show resilience and positive momentum across key markets. The Pune facility is expected to drive steady growth with improving capacity utilization.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations grew by 20.25% YoY to Rs. 208.63 mn</li><li>Profit After Tax (PAT) stood at Rs. 26.16 mn, growing 37.8% YoY</li><li>SPL Infusion Pvt. Ltd., Pune, has contributed to consolidated revenues for the first time</li><li>The Pune facility is expected to drive steady growth with improving capacity utilization</li><li>Core business demonstrates resilience and positive momentum across key markets</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f6853322-e6cb-4f88-9c67-106a057b52ae.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SANJIVANI PARANTERAL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MANGIND] Mangalam Industrial Finance Ltd Confirms No Deviations in Rights Issue Fund Utilization for Q4 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Mangalam+Industrial+Finance+Ltd&title=Mangalam+Industrial+Finance+Ltd+Confirms+No+Deviations+in+Rights+Issue+Fund+Utilization+for+Q4+2025&newsId=c9552066-7dc1-4f29-b5da-96511bd3663c&token=Yzk1NTIwNjYtN2Rj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9552066-7dc1-4f29-b5da-96511bd3663c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 15:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mangalam Industrial Finance Ltd has reported no deviations or variations in the use of proceeds from their Rights Issue of equity shares for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025. The statement, reviewed by the Audit Committee, confirms that the funds raised, amounting to 46,34,86,428, have been allocated towards increasing operational scale of their NBFC activities and general corporate purposes.</p><ul><li>Mangalam Industrial Finance Ltd reports no deviations in Rights Issue fund utilization for Q4 2025</li><li>Funds raised amounting to 46,34,86,428 utilized for increasing operational scale and general corporate purposes</li><li>No deviations or variations in use of proceeds from Rights Issue of equity shares for the quarter</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2b56916a-fea6-4553-97d2-7fc4d1c6f74a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Mangalam Industrial Finance Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>