<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:25:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ABCAPITAL] Aditya Birla Capital Ltd: Chief Technology Officer, Ramesh Narayanaswamy, Resigns</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Aditya+Birla+Capital+Ltd&title=Aditya+Birla+Capital+Ltd%3A+Chief+Technology+Officer%2C+Ramesh+Narayanaswamy%2C+Resigns&newsId=f77d83cf-6f10-4e42-893a-84859e06b718&token=Zjc3ZDgzY2YtNmYx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f77d83cf-6f10-4e42-893a-84859e06b718</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Aditya Birla Capital Limited has announced the resignation of its Chief Technology Officer, Mr. Ramesh Narayanaswamy. According to the company&apos;s disclosure, Mr. Narayanaswamy has tendered his resignation to pursue opportunities outside the company, with his last day being 28 February 2026. The company has provided all the necessary details as per the SEBI Master Circular No. HO/49/14/14(7)2025-CFD-POD2/1/3762/2026 dated January 30, 2026. The resignation letter from Mr. Narayanaswamy is also enclosed in the disclosure.</p><ul><li>Aditya Birla Capital Limited announces the resignation of its Chief Technology Officer, Mr. Ramesh Narayanaswamy.</li><li>Mr. Narayanaswamy has resigned to pursue opportunities outside the company.</li><li>His last working day will be 28 February 2026.</li><li>The company has disclosed all necessary details as per SEBI regulations.</li><li>The resignation letter from Mr. Narayanaswamy is also provided in the disclosure.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/04ad2547-9dd2-45d2-95e4-ce7709216519.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Aditya Birla Capital Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EICHERMOT] Royal Enfield Sold 1,00,905 Motorcycles in February 2026, Registers 11% Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=EICHER+MOTORS+LTD.&title=Royal+Enfield+Sold+1%2C00%2C905+Motorcycles+in+February+2026%2C+Registers+11%25+Growth&newsId=49267b91-3119-4004-a150-96e3bd051b28&token=NDkyNjdiOTEtMzEx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">49267b91-3119-4004-a150-96e3bd051b28</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 08:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Royal Enfield, a subsidiary of Eicher Motors Ltd, reported monthly sales of 1,00,905 motorcycles in February 2026, marking an 11% growth over the same period last year. The company sold 90,670 motorcycles in February 2025. The growth is attributed to sustained demand across markets and the company&apos;s growing global community. Royal Enfield is planning a capacity addition to serve the growing demand, which will take its annual production capacity up to 20 lakh units from the existing 14.6 lakh units.</p><ul><li>Royal Enfield sold 1,00,905 motorcycles in February 2026, registering an 11% growth</li><li>The company sold 90,670 motorcycles in February 2025</li><li>Royal Enfield is planning a capacity addition to serve the growing demand</li><li>The company&apos;s annual production capacity will be increased to 20 lakh units from the existing 14.6 lakh units</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/840e5e4c-c2fd-458e-bb08-8ae7fca30d58.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: EICHER MOTORS LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASIANTILES] Asian Granito India Ltd Announces Effective Date of Composite Scheme of Arrangement</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ASIAN+GRANITO+INDIA+LTD.&title=Asian+Granito+India+Ltd+Announces+Effective+Date+of+Composite+Scheme+of+Arrangement&newsId=915d5732-2e96-4620-a977-8f33cde9f7be&token=OTE1ZDU3MzItMmU5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">915d5732-2e96-4620-a977-8f33cde9f7be</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 08:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Asian Granito India Ltd has informed that the Demerged Company and Resulting Companies have filed the E-Form INC-28 with the Registrar of Companies, Ahmedabad dated 1 March, 2026. The filing has been made in compliance with Section 232(5) of the Companies Act, 2013 read with applicable rules made thereunder. Accordingly, the effective date of the scheme would be 1 March, 2026, being the date on which the certified copy of the order(s) of the Hon’ble NCLT sanctioning the said Scheme was filed with the Registrar of Companies by every Company in relation to which the order was made.</p><ul><li>Asian Granito India Ltd announces the effective date of the Composite Scheme of Arrangement</li><li>The Demerged Company and Resulting Companies have filed the E-Form INC-28 with the Registrar of Companies</li><li>The filing is in compliance with Section 232(5) of the Companies Act, 2013</li><li>The effective date of the scheme is 1 March, 2026</li><li>The certified copy of the order(s) of the Hon’ble NCLT sanctioning the said Scheme was filed with the Registrar of Companies</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e6235fa7-9662-45cf-aa0b-d0eec6b28cb6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ASIAN GRANITO INDIA LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TMCV] Tata Motors Registers 32% YoY Growth in February 2026 Sales</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Tata+Motors+Ltd&title=Tata+Motors+Registers+32%25+YoY+Growth+in+February+2026+Sales&newsId=eb7fa6e3-972e-47cd-8616-1b8262383b99&token=ZWI3ZmE2ZTMtOTcy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eb7fa6e3-972e-47cd-8616-1b8262383b99</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 07:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Tata Motors Limited reported a 32% year-over-year growth in total sales for February 2026, with 42,940 units sold compared to 32,533 units in February 2025. Domestic sales increased by 32.8% to 40,893 units, while international business saw a 17.9% growth to 2,047 units. Specific segments such as HCV trucks, ILMCV trucks, Passenger Carriers, and SCV cargo and pickup also experienced growth ranging from 17.9% to 37.1%. The company&apos;s domestic sales of MH&amp;ICV in February 2026 were 21,423 units, a 34.4% year-over-year increase.</p><ul><li>Tata Motors registered a 32% YoY growth in total sales for February 2026.</li><li>Domestic sales increased by 32.8% to 40,893 units, and international business saw a 17.9% growth.</li><li>HCV trucks, ILMCV trucks, Passenger Carriers, and SCV cargo and pickup segments experienced growth ranging from 17.9% to 37.1%.</li><li>Domestic sales of MH&amp;ICV in February 2026 were 21,423 units, a 34.4% YoY increase.</li><li>Tata Motors Limited is a part of the USD 180 billion Tata Group and is known for its innovation, reliability, and performance in commercial mobility.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/41f1f1a3-aba5-4ce2-a356-2f5998501b27.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Tata Motors Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[COALINDIA] Coal India Ltd Reports Feb’26 Production and Offtake Figures</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=COAL+INDIA+LTD.&title=Coal+India+Ltd+Reports+Feb%E2%80%9926+Production+and+Offtake+Figures&newsId=85b8783e-3f2d-4ebf-8966-ab1c294d880b&token=ODViODc4M2UtM2Yy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85b8783e-3f2d-4ebf-8966-ab1c294d880b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 07:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Coal India Ltd (CIL) has released its provisional production and offtake performance for the month of February 2026 and the period from April 2025 to February 2026. The report includes the performance of CIL and its subsidiary companies.</p><ul><li>Coal production and offtake figures for February 2026 and April 2025 - February 2026 are provided.</li><li>The report includes the performance of CIL and its subsidiary companies.</li><li>The release of this information is in compliance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9df80e6d-a06b-4628-a3b0-1199210a4abc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: COAL INDIA LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TATAMOTORS] Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd. Sales Surge 57% YoY in February 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TATA+MOTORS+LTD.&title=Tata+Motors+Passenger+Vehicles+Ltd.+Sales+Surge+57%25+YoY+in+February+2026&newsId=e0a6d551-c289-4020-88b2-d575d55c0be6&token=ZTBhNmQ1NTEtYzI4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0a6d551-c289-4020-88b2-d575d55c0be6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 07:31:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd. registered total sales of 63,331 units in February 2026, a significant increase of 57% compared to the same month last year. This growth includes sales from Tata Passenger Electric Mobility Limited, a subsidiary of Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd. The company is known for its design, safety, and performance, and is at the forefront of India’s electric vehicle revolution.</p><ul><li>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd. reports a 57% YoY increase in sales for February 2026.</li><li>The total sales for February 2026 stood at 63,331 units, compared to 46,811 units in February 2025.</li><li>The growth includes sales from Tata Passenger Electric Mobility Limited, a subsidiary of Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd.</li><li>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles Ltd. is a leading automobile manufacturer in India, offering a diverse portfolio of cars and SUVs.</li><li>The company is known for its innovation, reliability, and engineering prowess, and is at the forefront of India’s electric vehicle revolution.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1a31eca6-b6d0-4793-a383-da5dc87968ef.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TATA MOTORS LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TVSMOTOR] TVS Motor Company Sales Grows 31% in February 2026, International Business Records Highest Ever Sales</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TVS+MOTOR+COMPANY+LTD.&title=TVS+Motor+Company+Sales+Grows+31%25+in+February+2026%2C+International+Business+Records+Highest+Ever+Sales&newsId=0c72d57b-c5bd-41dd-b11d-7c9129e2a70b&token=MGM3MmQ1N2ItYzVi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c72d57b-c5bd-41dd-b11d-7c9129e2a70b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 07:31:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>TVS Motor Company, a global leader in the two and three-wheeler segments, recorded monthly sales of 529,308 units in February 2026 with a growth of 31% as against 403,976 units in February 2025. The company&apos;s international business recorded the highest ever sales of 1.58 lakh units. Domestic two-wheeler sales grew by 32%, motorcycle sales by 25%, scooter sales by 34%, and electric vehicle sales by 60%. Three-wheeler sales also saw a significant growth of 77%.</p><ul><li>TVS Motor Company records 31% sales growth in February 2026</li><li>International business achieves highest ever sales of 1.58 lakh units</li><li>Domestic two-wheeler sales grow by 32%</li><li>Motorcycle, scooter, and electric vehicle sales see significant growth</li><li>Three-wheeler sales increase by 77%</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c739da9a-d735-4e65-b2f5-d55b44f69f0b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TVS MOTOR COMPANY LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VTL] Vardhman Textiles Ltd Commences Commercial Production of Technical Textiles</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VARDHMAN+TEXTILES+LTD.&title=Vardhman+Textiles+Ltd+Commences+Commercial+Production+of+Technical+Textiles&newsId=9124360f-1222-4f20-b4c0-d28a0c70392e&token=OTEyNDM2MGYtMTIy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9124360f-1222-4f20-b4c0-d28a0c70392e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 07:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Vardhman Textiles Ltd has announced the commencement of commercial production from its Technical Textiles Plant at Baddi, HP. This development comes after the company&apos;s earlier intimations about a capex plan for installing new capacity to produce 15 lakh meters of fabric per month.</p><ul><li>Vardhman Textiles Ltd has started commercial production from its Technical Textiles Plant at Baddi, HP.</li><li>The new capacity is expected to produce 15 lakh meters of fabric per month.</li><li>This development is a part of the company&apos;s earlier announced capex plan.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/71c2edbc-a2bd-45ed-8e2f-aa00bc134d5a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VARDHMAN TEXTILES LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ONGC] Superannuation of Oil and Natural Gas Corporation Ltd&apos;s Director (Strategy &amp; Corporate Affairs)</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Oil+and+Natural+Gas+Corporation+Ltd&title=Superannuation+of+Oil+and+Natural+Gas+Corporation+Ltd%27s+Director+%28Strategy+%26+Corporate+Affairs%29&newsId=9e5aabd8-cf0f-4364-b889-194b4283a993&token=OWU1YWFiZDgtY2Yw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e5aabd8-cf0f-4364-b889-194b4283a993</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 07:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In compliance with Regulation 30 read with Schedule Ill of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations 2015, Oil and Natural Gas Corporation Ltd announces the superannuation of Shri Arunangshu Sarkar (DIN: 10777112), who ceased to be Director (Strategy &amp; Corporate Affairs) of the Company on 01.03.2026 upon attaining the age of superannuation.</p><ul><li>Shri Arunangshu Sarkar superannuated from his position as Director (Strategy &amp; Corporate Affairs) of Oil and Natural Gas Corporation Ltd.</li><li>The superannuation took effect on 01.03.2026.</li><li>Shri Sarkar&apos;s DIN is 10777112.</li><li>The announcement was made in compliance with Regulation 30 read with Schedule Ill of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations 2015.</li><li>This information is for stakeholders&apos; records.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/50318cfa-99be-4f2e-9275-30c6e85f6820.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Oil and Natural Gas Corporation Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ONGC] Oil and Natural Gas Corporation Ltd Announces Senior Management Change: Sanjay Kumar Mazumder to Superannuate on 01.03.2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Oil+and+Natural+Gas+Corporation+Ltd&title=Oil+and+Natural+Gas+Corporation+Ltd+Announces+Senior+Management+Change%3A+Sanjay+Kumar+Mazumder+to+Superannuate+on+01.03.2026&newsId=a0a993fc-91a5-4d74-89f7-a3f1fd21d50f&token=YTBhOTkzZmMtOTFh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0a993fc-91a5-4d74-89f7-a3f1fd21d50f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 07:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Oil and Natural Gas Corporation Ltd (ONGC) has announced a change in its senior management. Sanjay Kumar Mazumder, Executive Director, will be superannuating effective from 01.03.2026. This information is shared in compliance with Regulation 30 read with Schedule Il of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Oil and Natural Gas Corporation Ltd announces a change in senior management</li><li>Sanjay Kumar Mazumder, Executive Director, to superannuate on 01.03.2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/daad2d0a-1da0-4e7f-88a7-a77a34b1eef8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Oil and Natural Gas Corporation Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>