<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:37:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SHIKHARLETR] Shikhar Leasing &amp; Trading Ltd to Approve Standalone Un-audited Financial Results on 10th February 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHIKHAR+LEASING+%26+TRADING+LTD.&title=Shikhar+Leasing+%26+Trading+Ltd+to+Approve+Standalone+Un-audited+Financial+Results+on+10th+February+2026&newsId=d6db6ffe-2175-4fb6-b3a3-6659fec97ed1&token=ZDZkYjZmZmUtMjE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6db6ffe-2175-4fb6-b3a3-6659fec97ed1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shikhar Leasing &amp; Trading Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 10th February 2026 to consider and approve the Standalone Un-audited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The trading window for all Directors and Designated Employees of the Company for trading/dealing in the Equity Shares of the Company will be closed from 1st January 2026 till 12th February 2026, i.e., the end of 48 hours after the declaration of unaudited Financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025.</p><ul><li>Shikhar Leasing &amp; Trading Ltd to consider and approve Standalone Un-audited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025.</li><li>Trading Window for all Directors and Designated Employees of the Company for trading /dealing in the Equity Shares of the Company will be closed from 1st January 2026 till 12th February 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9de43326-1647-477e-b358-3ff91088c775.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHIKHAR LEASING & TRADING LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KASTURI] Rajasthan Global Securities Acquires 7.54% Stake in Kasturi Metal Composite Ltd via IPO Allotment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kasturi+Metal+Composite+Ltd&title=Rajasthan+Global+Securities+Acquires+7.54%25+Stake+in+Kasturi+Metal+Composite+Ltd+via+IPO+Allotment&newsId=c4fdb13a-e898-4d28-a5e6-35635d9a5cbd&token=YzRmZGIxM2EtZTg5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4fdb13a-e898-4d28-a5e6-35635d9a5cbd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rajasthan Global Securities Pvt Ltd, along with PAC LRSD Securities Pvt.Ltd, have acquired a 7.54% stake in Kasturi Metal Composite Limited. The acquisition was made through the allotment of shares in the Initial Public Offering (IPO). The total number of shares acquired is 7,84,000, which is equivalent to 1,03,95,212 shares of Rs.10 each in terms of voting rights. This acquisition has resulted in a change in the equity share capital and total voting capital of Kasturi Metal Composite Limited.</p><ul><li>Rajasthan Global Securities Pvt Ltd and LRSD Securities Pvt.Ltd acquire a 7.54% stake in Kasturi Metal Composite Limited</li><li>The acquisition was made through the allotment of shares in the Initial Public Offering (IPO) of Kasturi Metal Composite Limited</li><li>The total number of shares acquired is 7,84,000, which is equivalent to 1,03,95,212 shares of Rs.10 each in terms of voting rights</li><li>This acquisition has resulted in a change in the equity share capital and total voting capital of Kasturi Metal Composite Limited</li><li>The acquisition was made on 03.02.2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/F59EA08A_B4DC_43F6_8ADD_9E5D1905260E_150300.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kasturi Metal Composite Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SOLARINDS] Solar Industries India Ltd Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SOLAR+INDUSTRIES+INDIA+LTD.&title=Solar+Industries+India+Ltd+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025&newsId=f20b84ef-8e4c-437a-aab7-cd73ad480c13&token=ZjIwYjg0ZWYtOGU0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f20b84ef-8e4c-437a-aab7-cd73ad480c13</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:34:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Solar Industries India Ltd has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 2,504.98 crores for the quarter and 7,540.26 crores for the nine months. The net profit for the quarter is 1,607.20 crores and 5,27.47 crores for the nine months. The company has also reported a debt-equity ratio of 0.22 and a debt service coverage ratio of 1.79.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter is 2,504.98 crores</li><li>Net profit for the quarter is 1,607.20 crores</li><li>Debt-equity ratio stands at 0.22</li><li>Debt service coverage ratio is 1.79</li><li>The company has recognized a financial impact of 3.59 crores due to changes in labor laws</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7c608403-c60c-44b4-b047-65caf9e8fb98.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SOLAR INDUSTRIES INDIA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AXISOL] Axis Solutions Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q3 FY2025-26 Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Axis+Solutions+Ltd&title=Axis+Solutions+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+FY2025-26+Financial+Results&newsId=1066752e-7ca2-48f2-851e-d6f4c3847cbd&token=MTA2Njc1MmUtN2Nh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1066752e-7ca2-48f2-851e-d6f4c3847cbd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:32:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Axis Solutions Ltd has informed the BSE that its Board of Directors will meet on 10 February 2026 to consider and approve the Standalone and Consolidated Un-audited financial results for the quarter ended on 31st December 2025. The Trading Window for trading in the Securities of the Company will remain closed until 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results.</p><ul><li>Axis Solutions Ltd to hold a Board Meeting on 10 February 2026</li><li>Board Meeting to consider and approve Q3 FY2025-26 financial results</li><li>Trading Window to remain closed until 48 hours after the declaration of results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/622fffc8-5c12-4aa8-92e3-a560a2d4d857.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Axis Solutions Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NSLNISP] NMDC Steel Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025, Posts Profit Before Tax of INR 757.78 Cr</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NMDC+Steel+Ltd&title=NMDC+Steel+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Posts+Profit+Before+Tax+of+INR+757.78+Cr&newsId=6898590a-261d-4fd7-ae7a-a388c5b42824&token=Njg5ODU5MGEtMjYx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6898590a-261d-4fd7-ae7a-a388c5b42824</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>NMDC Steel Ltd, a leading steel company, has reported its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company posted a profit before tax of INR 757.78 Cr for the nine months period. The revenue from operations stood at INR 8,503.05 Cr for the same period. The company&apos;s total income was INR 6,296.65 Cr for the nine months ended 31st December 2025. The profit for the period was INR (757.78) Cr. The company&apos;s net worth stood at INR 13,587.87 Cr as of 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s debt equity ratio was 0.47 and the debt service coverage ratio was 0.20 as of the same date.</p><ul><li>NMDC Steel Ltd reports Q3 and nine months results for 2025</li><li>Posted profit before tax of INR 757.78 Cr for the nine months period</li><li>Revenue from operations stood at INR 8,503.05 Cr for the same period</li><li>Total income was INR 6,296.65 Cr for the nine months ended 31st December 2025</li><li>Net worth stood at INR 13,587.87 Cr as of 31st December 2025</li><li>Debt equity ratio was 0.47 and the debt service coverage ratio was 0.20 as of the same date</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e90dbb7b-3c01-4287-b5a7-14edd4ce6e7a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NMDC Steel Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADANIENT] Adani Enterprises Ltd: No Deviation in Utilization of Funds Raised Through Rights Issue in Q4 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADANI+ENTERPRISES+LTD.&title=Adani+Enterprises+Ltd%3A+No+Deviation+in+Utilization+of+Funds+Raised+Through+Rights+Issue+in+Q4+2025&newsId=47b6823a-d8bd-4e9c-bc76-f7bd5ca46612&token=NDdiNjgyM2EtZDhi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47b6823a-d8bd-4e9c-bc76-f7bd5ca46612</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Adani Enterprises Ltd has confirmed that there was no deviation in the utilization of funds raised through a Rights Issue in the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company raised INR 12,465.15 Crores, which were utilized for repayment of borrowings, perpetual debt instruments, general corporate purposes, and issue expenses.</p><ul><li>Adani Enterprises Ltd raised INR 12,465.15 Crores through a Rights Issue in Q4 2025.</li><li>No deviation in the utilization of funds was reported.</li><li>Funds were utilized for repayment of borrowings, perpetual debt instruments, general corporate purposes, and issue expenses.</li><li>The utilization of funds is in line with the objects stated in the Letter of Offer dated November 12, 2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9721535b-6fc1-46ae-af38-2e903dee2197.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADANI ENTERPRISES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ACFL] Apex Capital And Finance Ltd. Announces Changes in Board Meeting Date and Trading Window Closure</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Apex+Capital+And+Finance+Ltd&title=Apex+Capital+And+Finance+Ltd.+Announces+Changes+in+Board+Meeting+Date+and+Trading+Window+Closure&newsId=e280726d-e3ee-4bac-bef7-6a0f724fe437&token=ZTI4MDcyNmQtZTNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e280726d-e3ee-4bac-bef7-6a0f724fe437</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Apex Capital And Finance Ltd. has announced changes in the date of its Board Meeting, which was earlier scheduled for 14.02.2026 and has now been rescheduled to 12.02.2026. Consequently, the Trading Window for dealing in the shares of the company will remain closed for all designated persons and their immediate relatives from Thursday, January 01, 2026 until 48 hours from the date of declaration of the Un-audited financial results of the Company (Standalone) for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025, i.e. 14.02.2026. This information is shared in compliance with the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, and the Company&apos;s Code of Conduct for Prevention of Insider Trading and Code of Practices and procedures for Fair Disclosure of Unpublished Price Sensitive Information.</p><ul><li>Apex Capital And Finance Ltd. has rescheduled its Board Meeting to 12.02.2026</li><li>The Trading Window for dealing in the shares of the company will remain closed from Thursday, January 01, 2026 until 48 hours from the date of declaration of the Un-audited financial results for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/74c15f19-79f8-4d68-b8b7-c0fbecf8d649.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Apex Capital And Finance Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GSPL] Gujarat State Petronet Ltd Appoints Shri Sandeep Kumar, IAS as Additional Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GUJARAT+STATE+PETRONET+LTD.&title=Gujarat+State+Petronet+Ltd+Appoints+Shri+Sandeep+Kumar%2C+IAS+as+Additional+Director&newsId=c39364cb-c7a1-47d2-96fa-8c2fd1ea52a9&token=YzM5MzY0Y2ItYzdh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c39364cb-c7a1-47d2-96fa-8c2fd1ea52a9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gujarat State Petronet Ltd (GSPL) has informed the Exchange about the appointment of Shri Sandeep Kumar, IAS (DIN: 06576903) as an Additional Director on the Board of Directors. The appointment is effective from 28th January, 2026. Shri Sandeep Kumar is a senior officer of the All India Services (AIS) cadre with over 20 years of experience in public administration. He is currently serving as Secretary (Economic Affairs), Finance Department, Government of Gujarat and has held key leadership positions in the power sector. He is not related to any Director or Key Managerial Personnel (KMP) of the Company and is not debarred from holding the office of director by virtue of any SEBI order or any other such authority.</p><ul><li>Gujarat State Petronet Ltd appoints Shri Sandeep Kumar, IAS as Additional Director</li><li>Shri Sandeep Kumar has over 20 years of experience in public administration</li><li>Currently serving as Secretary (Economic Affairs), Finance Department, Government of Gujarat</li><li>Not related to any Director or Key Managerial Personnel (KMP) of the Company</li><li>Not debarred from holding the office of director by virtue of any SEBI order or any other such authority</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6a0392eb-920b-4770-8785-2fb39e4cc9d8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GUJARAT STATE PETRONET LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SJCORP] SJ Corporation Ltd. Announces EGM for Preferential Issue of Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SJ+CORPORATION+LTD.&title=SJ+Corporation+Ltd.+Announces+EGM+for+Preferential+Issue+of+Equity+Shares&newsId=a421a9de-e164-46d1-814d-acba8a853280&token=YTQyMWE5ZGUtZTE2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a421a9de-e164-46d1-814d-acba8a853280</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:28:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SJ Corporation Ltd. has announced an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) to consider the approval of issuing equity shares on a preferential basis to proposed promoters/promoter group and non-promoter/public category investors. The meeting is scheduled for March 02, 2026, and will be held through video conferencing. The company plans to issue 3,50,00,000 (Three Crore Fifty Lakh) equity shares at a price of = 12/- (Rupees Twelve only) including a premium of = 11/- per equity share, aggregating up to ~ 42,00,00,000 (Indian Rupees Forty-Two Crore Only). The proposed allottees include both promoters and non-promoters.</p><ul><li>SJ Corporation Ltd. to issue equity shares on a preferential basis</li><li>3,50,00,000 equity shares to be issued at a price of = 12/- including a premium of = 11/-</li><li>The issuance will aggregate up to ~ 42,00,00,000</li><li>Proposed allottees include both promoters and non-promoters</li><li>The EGM will be held on March 02, 2026, through video conferencing</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/eb1a9964-134e-42cd-aabb-f1f68281da32.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SJ CORPORATION LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GOKAKTEX] Gokak Textiles Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025 on Feb 12, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GOKAK+TEXTILES+LTD.&title=Gokak+Textiles+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025+on+Feb+12%2C+2026&newsId=37ea5d4a-a664-4781-b62b-1d268cdbea6c&token=MzdlYTVkNGEtYTY2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37ea5d4a-a664-4781-b62b-1d268cdbea6c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 09:26:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gokak Textiles Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 12, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting is scheduled in accordance with Regulation 29 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements), Regulations, 2015. The trading window will remain closed 48 hours after the results become generally available information.</p><ul><li>Gokak Textiles Ltd to consider and approve Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The meeting is scheduled in accordance with Regulation 29 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements), Regulations, 2015.</li><li>The trading window will remain closed 48 hours after the results become generally available information.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/449543fd-9b40-4ca8-beac-ad68b5d9f6d1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GOKAK TEXTILES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>