<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 06:28:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[CHOKSI] Choksi Asia Ltd. Approves Shifting of Registered Office and Loan Proposal</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CHOKSI+IMAGING+LTD.&title=Choksi+Asia+Ltd.+Approves+Shifting+of+Registered+Office+and+Loan+Proposal&newsId=5f4d0203-d68e-412b-b98e-84714eef73ea&token=NWY0ZDAyMDMtZDY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f4d0203-d68e-412b-b98e-84714eef73ea</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 06:26:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Choksi Asia Ltd. announced the outcome of its Board Meeting held on Friday, January 9, 2026. The Board approved the shifting of the company&apos;s registered office from Mumbai to the Union Territory of Dadra and Nagar Haveli, subject to shareholder and regulatory approvals. The Board also approved providing any loan, guarantee, or security, and making any investment up to Rs. 60 Crore, in excess of the limits specified under the Companies Act, 2013, subject to shareholder approval. The company has paid a fine of Rs. 5,900 for delay in submission of Related Party Transactions. The Board has instructed the Company Secretary and Finance team to prevent such delays in the future.</p><ul><li>Approval to shift registered office to Union Territory of Dadra and Nagar Haveli</li><li>Proposal to provide loan/guarantee/security up to Rs. 60 Crore approved, subject to shareholder approval</li><li>Payment of fine for delay in submission of Related Party Transactions</li><li>Instructions to prevent future delays in submission of Related Party Transactions</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5ee61cbc-56fc-4d45-9d54-7759056a0aab.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CHOKSI IMAGING LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MANKIND] Mankind Pharma to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on Feb 3, 2026; Trading Window Closed</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Mankind+Pharma+Ltd&title=Mankind+Pharma+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+Feb+3%2C+2026%3B+Trading+Window+Closed&newsId=484d9f96-0881-4101-b673-8c078324791f&token=NDg0ZDlmOTYtMDg4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">484d9f96-0881-4101-b673-8c078324791f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 06:25:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mankind Pharma Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 3, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The company has also informed that the trading window for trading in the securities of the Company will remain closed till February 5, 2026, in accordance with the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015 and the Company&apos;s &apos;Code of Conduct for Prevention of Insider Trading&apos;.</p><ul><li>Mankind Pharma to approve Q3 and nine months financial results on Feb 3, 2026</li><li>Trading window for the company&apos;s securities closed till Feb 5, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/159502be-f73a-41e7-9089-1a416609a7ad.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Mankind Pharma Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AFIL] Akme Fintrade (India) Ltd. to Issue Non-Convertible Debentures Worth INR 30 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Akme+Fintrade+%28India%29+Ltd&title=Akme+Fintrade+%28India%29+Ltd.+to+Issue+Non-Convertible+Debentures+Worth+INR+30+Crores&newsId=ea559502-73e1-45d2-9e19-e8097da6b582&token=ZWE1NTk1MDItNzNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ea559502-73e1-45d2-9e19-e8097da6b582</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 06:25:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Akme Fintrade (India) Limited has approved the issuance of Senior, Secured, Listed, Rated, Transferable, Redeemable, Non-Convertible Debentures up to INR 30 Crores on a private placement basis. The Debentures will be listed on the National Stock Exchange of India Limited. The Company will maintain a minimum security cover of 1.10x over loan receivables. In case of default, the Company will pay an additional interest rate of 2% per annum.</p><ul><li>Akme Fintrade (India) Ltd. to issue Non-Convertible Debentures up to INR 30 Crores</li><li>Debentures to be issued on a private placement basis to eligible investors</li><li>Proposed to be listed on the National Stock Exchange of India Limited</li><li>Minimum security cover of 1.10x to be maintained over loan receivables</li><li>Additional interest rate of 2% per annum in case of default</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cec5a287-95f6-4a73-af46-bea5626c3a92.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Akme Fintrade (India) Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDOTECH] Indo Tech Transformers Ltd Receives Order Worth INR 64.99 Crores from Renew Wind Energy (Jamb) Private Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDO+TECH+TRANSFORMERS+LTD.&title=Indo+Tech+Transformers+Ltd+Receives+Order+Worth+INR+64.99+Crores+from+Renew+Wind+Energy+%28Jamb%29+Private+Limited&newsId=955f79ef-a159-4dea-bf1f-2ddde405e30f&token=OTU1Zjc5ZWYtYTE1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">955f79ef-a159-4dea-bf1f-2ddde405e30f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 06:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Indo Tech Transformers Limited has received a Letter of Intent (LOI) dated January 08, 2026 from Renew Wind Energy (Jamb) Private Limited for the supply of 6 number of transformers. The aggregate value of the order is INR 64.99 Crores plus applicable taxes. The order is for the manufacture and supply of 6 Numbers of transformers, with delivery scheduled between Feb’ 2027 and May’ 2027.</p><ul><li>Indo Tech Transformers Ltd has received an LOI for supply of 6 transformers worth INR 64.99 Crores plus applicable taxes.</li><li>The order is from Renew Wind Energy (Jamb) Private Limited.</li><li>The transformers are 220 kV — 165 MVA.</li><li>Delivery is scheduled between Feb’ 2027 and May’ 2027.</li><li>This order is significant compared to the transactions in the ordinary course of business.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e7400b5d-1ace-48a9-8c82-dd529d7303d0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDO TECH TRANSFORMERS LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASTRAZEN] AstraZeneca Pharma India Ltd Appoints Ms. Aditi Dayarus Mehta as Director — Oncology Business Unit and Mr. Nitin Bindal as Director - Institutional Business &amp; Public Channels</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ASTRAZENECA+PHARMA+INDIA+LTD.&title=AstraZeneca+Pharma+India+Ltd+Appoints+Ms.+Aditi+Dayarus+Mehta+as+Director+%E2%80%94+Oncology+Business+Unit+and+Mr.+Nitin+Bindal+as+Director+-+Institutional+Business+%26+Public+Channels&newsId=8251f0a7-dff7-409d-ae85-19c9fc710efd&token=ODI1MWYwYTctZGZm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8251f0a7-dff7-409d-ae85-19c9fc710efd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 06:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>AstraZeneca Pharma India Ltd has announced the appointment of Ms. Aditi Dayarus Mehta as Director — Oncology Business Unit and Mr. Nitin Bindal as Director - Institutional Business &amp; Public Channels with effect from January 12, 2026. Ms. Mehta is a seasoned pharmaceutical professional with over 15 years of experience in the industry across multiple therapeutic areas and functions. She joins AstraZeneca from Bristol Pfizer India where she spent over a decade across numerous roles, including Business Unit Director — Oncology, Access, Commercial Excellence and most recently was leading the Innovative Vaccine portfolio. Mr. Bindal has over 17 years of diverse experience in the pharmaceutical industry across multiple therapeutic areas and functions. He has a distinguished career at Bristol Pfizer India where he spent over a decade across numerous roles, including National Sales Head and Senior Marketing Manager in Oncology and Neuroscience Business Unit. Prior to Pfizer India, he has contributed to strategy and collaborative teams at Johnson &amp; Johnson, Novartis, Wockhardt, and A Pharmacy.</p><ul><li>Ms. Aditi Dayarus Mehta appointed as Director — Oncology Business Unit at AstraZeneca Pharma India Ltd.</li><li>Mr. Nitin Bindal appointed as Director - Institutional Business &amp; Public Channels at AstraZeneca Pharma India Ltd.</li><li>Ms. Mehta has over 15 years of experience in the pharmaceutical industry across multiple therapeutic areas and functions.</li><li>Mr. Bindal has over 17 years of diverse experience in the pharmaceutical industry across multiple therapeutic areas and functions.</li><li>Both appointments are effective from January 12, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3cb8a3f8-773b-4887-92c3-3fadafb0150b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ASTRAZENECA PHARMA INDIA LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[OLATECH] Olatech Solutions Ltd. Announces Increase in Authorised Share Capital and Preferential Issuance of Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Olatech+Solutions+Ltd&title=Olatech+Solutions+Ltd.+Announces+Increase+in+Authorised+Share+Capital+and+Preferential+Issuance+of+Equity+Shares&newsId=51c77d43-f274-4ef7-9bf6-8cb5f67fe1e1&token=NTFjNzdkNDMtZjI3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">51c77d43-f274-4ef7-9bf6-8cb5f67fe1e1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 06:19:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Olatech Solutions Ltd. held an Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) on Thursday, 08th January, 2026, where members approved the increase in authorised share capital and preferential issuance of equity shares to non-promoter categories. The meeting was held at the company&apos;s registered office in Navi Mumbai. The company provided a remote e-voting facility for members between Monday, 05th January, 2026 and Wednesday, 07th January, 2026. The results of the voting will be announced by intimating to the Stock Exchange and placing on the company&apos;s website. The meeting concluded at 03:45 P.M.</p><ul><li>Olatech Solutions Ltd. held an Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EGM)</li><li>Members approved the increase in authorised share capital</li><li>Preferential issuance of equity shares to non-promoter categories</li><li>Remote e-voting facility provided for members</li><li>Results of the voting to be announced on the company&apos;s website and to the Stock Exchange</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e94f58f6-a423-4ef7-9c85-ebf5d4e7ac41.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Olatech Solutions Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IEX*] CERC Clarifies &apos;Order&apos; as &apos;Directions&apos; in Indian Energy Exchange&apos;s Market Coupling Implementation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Indian+Energy+Exchange+Ltd&title=CERC+Clarifies+%27Order%27+as+%27Directions%27+in+Indian+Energy+Exchange%27s+Market+Coupling+Implementation&newsId=20e0c857-aacc-42aa-a6fe-108b7ef48318&token=MjBlMGM4NTctYWFj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">20e0c857-aacc-42aa-a6fe-108b7ef48318</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 06:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Corporate Action</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Central Electricity Regulatory Commission (CERC) has issued a corrigendum dated January 8, 2026, clarifying that the expression &apos;Order&apos; used in the heading and footer of the publication dated July 23, 2025, in Petition No. 8/SM/2025, shall be read as &apos;Directions&apos;. This change also applies to any reference to the said publication or to Petition No. 8/SM/2025 dated July 23, 2025, as &apos;this order&apos; or &apos;order&apos; within the Petition No. 8/SM/2025 or in any subsequent publication, which should also be read as &apos;directions&apos;. This clarification comes in light of the implementation of market coupling in a phased manner as per the Central Electricity Regulatory Commission (Power Market) Regulations, 2021.</p><ul><li>CERC issues corrigendum clarifying &apos;Order&apos; as &apos;Directions&apos; in Indian Energy Exchange&apos;s market coupling implementation</li><li>The change applies to any reference to the publication or Petition No. 8/SM/2025 dated July 23, 2025, as &apos;this order&apos; or &apos;order&apos;</li><li>The clarification comes in light of the implementation of market coupling in a phased manner as per the Central Electricity Regulatory Commission (Power Market) Regulations, 2021</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0a9106af-d7c6-4c00-a839-62d44370e287.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Indian Energy Exchange Ltd | Category: Corporate Action</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ITCONS] Saurabh Gangal Acquires Shares of ITCONS E-Solutions Ltd Through Warrant Conversion</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ITCONS+E-Solutions+Ltd&title=Saurabh+Gangal+Acquires+Shares+of+ITCONS+E-Solutions+Ltd+Through+Warrant+Conversion&newsId=ffbb4e86-660c-4f09-b30c-934ed4a4041d&token=ZmZiYjRlODYtNjYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ffbb4e86-660c-4f09-b30c-934ed4a4041d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 06:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>According to a disclosure made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011, Saurabh Gangal has acquired shares of ITCONS E-Solutions Ltd due to the conversion of warrants of other shareholders. The acquisition details are as follows: Before the acquisition, Mr. Gangal held 8.10% of the total voting shares. After the acquisition, his holding increased to 6.79% of the total voting shares. The total acquisition was worth Rs. 7,20,31,260, which represents 72,03,126 equity shares of Rs. 10 each. This acquisition increased Mr. Gangal&apos;s total holding to 3.25% of the total diluted share/voting capital of the company.</p><ul><li>Saurabh Gangal has acquired shares of ITCONS E-Solutions Ltd through warrant conversion.</li><li>The acquisition was worth Rs. 7,20,31,260, representing 72,03,126 equity shares of Rs. 10 each.</li><li>Before the acquisition, Mr. Gangal held 8.10% of the total voting shares.</li><li>After the acquisition, his holding increased to 6.79% of the total voting shares.</li><li>This acquisition increased Mr. Gangal&apos;s total holding to 3.25% of the total diluted share/voting capital of the company.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3C9035CA_814E_4C6A_8117_677C73033459_113755.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ITCONS E-Solutions Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ITCONS] Saurabh Gangal Acquires Shares in ITCONS E-Solutions Ltd, Holding Stands at 6.79%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ITCONS+E-Solutions+Ltd&title=Saurabh+Gangal+Acquires+Shares+in+ITCONS+E-Solutions+Ltd%2C+Holding+Stands+at+6.79%25&newsId=65bdfd03-b9ef-4ea8-8cbb-bd3354666e52&token=NjViZGZkMDMtYjll</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65bdfd03-b9ef-4ea8-8cbb-bd3354666e52</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 06:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>According to a disclosure under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011, Saurabh Gangal has acquired shares in ITCONS E-Solutions Ltd. Before the acquisition, Mr. Gangal held 8.10% of the total share/voting capital. Post-acquisition, his holding stands at 6.79%. The total shares carrying voting rights remain unchanged at 489328. The acquisition took place on 08.01.2026, with a total value of Rs. 7,20,31,260/-.</p><ul><li>Saurabh Gangal acquires shares in ITCONS E-Solutions Ltd</li><li>Pre-acquisition holding was 8.10% of total share/voting capital</li><li>Post-acquisition holding stands at 6.79%</li><li>Total shares carrying voting rights remain unchanged at 489328</li><li>The acquisition took place on 08.01.2026 with a total value of Rs. 7,20,31,260/-</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/C853F548_0855_4017_99B1_1462C367E90B_113613.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ITCONS E-Solutions Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BRAHMINFRA] Brahmaputra Infrastructure Ltd Receives LOA for Balance Work of Rs. 113.54 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BRAHMAPUTRA+INFRASTRUCTURE+LTD.&title=Brahmaputra+Infrastructure+Ltd+Receives+LOA+for+Balance+Work+of+Rs.+113.54+Crores&newsId=b34b86cf-bde8-4f7a-a0ff-6196d4407fa5&token=YjM0Yjg2Y2YtYmRl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b34b86cf-bde8-4f7a-a0ff-6196d4407fa5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 06:12:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Brahmaputra Infrastructure Ltd has received a Letter of Acceptance (LOA) for the balance work of constructing a new Legislature Complex at Jammu. The total amount of the LOA is Rs. 113.54 Crores. The LOA was issued by the Office of the Chief Engineer PWD(R&amp;B) JAMMU. The project details include a 18-month execution period and a total order size of Rs. 113.54 Crores. The company assures that no promoters or related parties have any interest in the entity that awarded the order.</p><ul><li>Brahmaputra Infrastructure Ltd receives LOA for balance work of Rs. 113.54 Crores</li><li>LOA issued by Office of the Chief Engineer PWD(R&amp;B) JAMMU</li><li>Project involves construction of new Legislature Complex at Jammu</li><li>18-month execution period</li><li>Order size of Rs. 113.54 Crores</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d4f915be-c30d-4ce4-95dd-13543a8c8d95.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BRAHMAPUTRA INFRASTRUCTURE LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>