<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:03:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ENIL] Entertainment Network (India) Ltd Announces Q3FY26 Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ENTERTAINMENT+NETWORK+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Entertainment+Network+%28India%29+Ltd+Announces+Q3FY26+Financial+Results&newsId=7eba8ed1-9e0e-4f4c-9d2d-eb6ebaed4de6&token=N2ViYThlZDEtOWUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7eba8ed1-9e0e-4f4c-9d2d-eb6ebaed4de6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:03:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Entertainment Network (India) Ltd has announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31 December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 15,981.78 crores, with a net profit of 850.65 crores. The results were reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors on 10 February 2026. The company has recognized an additional expense of 810.03 crores towards gratuity and leave encashment as an exceptional item.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for Q3FY26 stands at 15,981.78 crores</li><li>Net profit for Q3FY26 is 850.65 crores</li><li>Entertainment Network (India) Ltd has recognized an additional expense of 810.03 crores towards gratuity and leave encashment as an exceptional item</li><li>The financial results have been prepared in accordance with Ind AS 34 and Regulation 33 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>The standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025 were reviewed by the Audit Committee and subsequently approved by the Board of Directors of the Company at its meeting held on February 10, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/11585773-0897-4e44-b6f1-2b7c2b3fab90.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ENTERTAINMENT NETWORK (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ROTO] Roto Pumps Ltd Appoints Mr. K. Anand as COO and Mr. John Wilkins as General Manager - Australia; Announces Q3 Results and Amalgamation Scheme</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ROTO+PUMPS+LTD.&title=Roto+Pumps+Ltd+Appoints+Mr.+K.+Anand+as+COO+and+Mr.+John+Wilkins+as+General+Manager+-+Australia%3B+Announces+Q3+Results+and+Amalgamation+Scheme&newsId=0e2d261d-f79b-44ee-9509-6aa87a5a38ee&token=MGUyZDI2MWQtZjc5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e2d261d-f79b-44ee-9509-6aa87a5a38ee</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Roto Pumps Ltd has announced the appointment of Mr. K. Anand as Chief Operating Officer (COO) and Mr. John Wilkins as General Manager - Australia. The company also reported its un-audited financial results for the third quarter and cumulative period ended December 31, 2025. Furthermore, Roto Pumps Ltd approved a Scheme of Amalgamation of Roto Energy Systems Limited (RESL), a wholly owned subsidiary, with the company. The scheme is subject to statutory and regulatory approvals.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. K. Anand as COO</li><li>Appointment of Mr. John Wilkins as General Manager - Australia</li><li>Announcement of Q3 results</li><li>Approval of a Scheme of Amalgamation of Roto Energy Systems Limited (RESL)</li><li>Subject to statutory and regulatory approvals</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b52f223b-b8a6-45cd-a571-39b4006497a0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ROTO PUMPS LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HITECHCORP] Hitech Corporation Ltd. Approves Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025 and Announces Retirement of CFO</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Hitech+Corporation+Ltd-%24&title=Hitech+Corporation+Ltd.+Approves+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025+and+Announces+Retirement+of+CFO&newsId=aeddb335-4e90-466c-a281-aaf258ab4d86&token=YWVkZGIzMzUtNGU5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aeddb335-4e90-466c-a281-aaf258ab4d86</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hitech Corporation Ltd. announced the outcome of its Board Meeting held on 10th February 2026. The Board approved the Audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company also announced the retirement of Mrs. Avan R. Chaina as Chief Financial Officer (CFO) and Key Managerial Personnel (KMP) with effect from February 11, 2026. The Board expressed gratitude for her contributions and initiated the process of identifying a successor.</p><ul><li>Approval of Audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Retirement of Mrs. Avan R. Chaina as CFO and KMP from February 11, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5f022b2e-0f7e-498b-89e8-93aa7cc774b3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Hitech Corporation Ltd-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ROTO] Roto Pumps Ltd Submits Un-audited Financial Results for Q3 &amp; Cumulative Period Ended December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ROTO+PUMPS+LTD.&title=Roto+Pumps+Ltd+Submits+Un-audited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+%26+Cumulative+Period+Ended+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=d4d8aa9b-19fe-48bb-b0db-1497452fdf2f&token=ZDRkOGFhOWItMTlm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4d8aa9b-19fe-48bb-b0db-1497452fdf2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:02:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Roto Pumps Ltd, a leading company in the Pumps &amp; Spares segment, has submitted its un-audited financial results for the third quarter and cumulative period ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 5,779.20 lakhs for the quarter and 15,817.29 lakhs for the cumulative period. The net profit after tax for the quarter is 532.70 lakhs and 1,550.86 lakhs for the cumulative period. The company has recognized an increase of 81.38 lakhs in its gratuity and leave liabilities due to the change in the definition of wages under the Code on Wages, 2019.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for Q3 2025: 5,779.20 lakhs</li><li>Net profit after tax for Q3 2025: 532.70 lakhs</li><li>Net profit after tax for cumulative period ended December 31, 2025: 1,550.86 lakhs</li><li>Increase in gratuity and leave liabilities due to change in wages definition: 81.38 lakhs</li><li>The financial results have been reviewed by R.N. Marwah &amp; Co. LLP, Chartered Accountants</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/df5ca355-8da3-45a5-9e8a-508d82d6cd0e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ROTO PUMPS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PDSL] PDS Ltd Announces Q3 Results, Office Shift, Changes in ESOP Plan, and Management Personnel</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PDS+Ltd&title=PDS+Ltd+Announces+Q3+Results%2C+Office+Shift%2C+Changes+in+ESOP+Plan%2C+and+Management+Personnel&newsId=824c0b0a-1c64-4d1f-9a7e-761e45817c73&token=ODI0YzBiMGEtMWM2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">824c0b0a-1c64-4d1f-9a7e-761e45817c73</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>PDS Ltd has announced the outcome of its Board Meeting, revealing several key decisions. The company has reported its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The Board has also approved the shifting of the company&apos;s registered office from Maharashtra to Haryana, and the increase in the pool size under the PDS Limited Employee Stock Option Plan 2021 - Plan B. Additionally, the company has appointed new senior management personnel and announced changes in key management personnel.</p><ul><li>PDS Ltd reported its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s registered office will be shifted from Maharashtra to Haryana.</li><li>PDS Limited Employee Stock Option Plan 2021 - Plan B&apos;s pool size has been increased for eligible employees.</li><li>Mr. Naresh Sharma, Mr. Sagar Ballari, and Mr. Ankur Agarwal have been appointed as senior management personnel.</li><li>Mr. Rahul Ahuja will step down as Group Chief Financial Officer and Key Managerial Personnel, to be replaced by Mr. Sadik Ismail Sunsara.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3b7f4942-b1ff-415a-afcc-23422a09eed1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PDS Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JAYSHREETEA] Jay Shree Tea &amp; Industries Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Unaudited Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JAY+SHREE+TEA+%26+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Jay+Shree+Tea+%26+Industries+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=103e9470-c2db-435b-b602-54bdf4f3c9ee&token=MTAzZTk0NzAtYzJk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">103e9470-c2db-435b-b602-54bdf4f3c9ee</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:02:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jay Shree Tea &amp; Industries Ltd has released its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The results show a revenue from operations of ₹ 29,168 Lakhs for the quarter and ₹ 74,213 Lakhs for the nine months. The net profit for the quarter is ₹ 73 Lakhs and ₹ 1,035 Lakhs for the nine months. The company has also reported a profit on sale/disposal of Fixed Assets of ₹ 5,572 Lakhs and ₹ 5,497 Lakhs for the quarter and nine months respectively.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter is ₹ 29,168 Lakhs</li><li>Net profit for the quarter is ₹ 73 Lakhs</li><li>Revenue from operations for the nine months is ₹ 74,213 Lakhs</li><li>Net profit for the nine months is ₹ 1,035 Lakhs</li><li>Profit on sale/disposal of Fixed Assets of ₹ 5,572 Lakhs for the quarter and ₹ 5,497 Lakhs for the nine months</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b0ee291d-616b-47de-a392-7d4b0607c202.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JAY SHREE TEA & INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TRIGYN] Trigyn Technologies Ltd Announces Q3 and Nine-Month Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TRIGYN+TECHNOLOGIES+LTD.&title=Trigyn+Technologies+Ltd+Announces+Q3+and+Nine-Month+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=a58cc065-5fdc-4975-9a99-ffa71fe3e521&token=YTU4Y2MwNjUtNWZk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a58cc065-5fdc-4975-9a99-ffa71fe3e521</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Trigyn Technologies Ltd has announced the financial results for the quarter and nine-month period ended December 31, 2025. The Board of Directors approved the standalone and consolidated un-audited financial results, along with the limited review reports issued by the statutory auditors. The review was conducted in accordance with the Standard on Review Engagements (SRE) 2410 and circular issued by the SEBI under Regulation 33 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Approval of standalone and consolidated un-audited financial results for Q3 and nine-month period ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Review of financial results conducted in accordance with the Standard on Review Engagements (SRE) 2410 and circular issued by the SEBI</li><li>The Board meeting commenced at 05:00 P.M. and concluded at 08.00 P.M.</li><li>The unaudited consolidated financial results include results of eight subsidiaries</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c7d7b615-7bf9-4db0-a55a-49285622e9ea.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TRIGYN TECHNOLOGIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADVLIFE] Advance Lifestyles Ltd. Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025, Board Approves Changes to MoA and Name</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADVANCE+LIFESTYLES+LTD.&title=Advance+Lifestyles+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Board+Approves+Changes+to+MoA+and+Name&newsId=aeaa3c29-539b-42e0-8962-f5c476679df7&token=YWVhYTNjMjktNTM5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aeaa3c29-539b-42e0-8962-f5c476679df7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Advance Lifestyles Ltd. announced the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue stood at Rs. 10,325.70 lakhs for the quarter and Rs. 27,894.76 lakhs for the nine-month period. The Board approved alterations to the Main Object clause of the Memorandum of Association, a change of name, adoption of a new set of MoA, and enhancement of limits under Section 186 of the Companies Act, 2013. The Board also appointed M/s. MSDS &amp; Associates as Scrutinizer for Postal Ballot through e-voting and M/s. Bigshare Services Private Limited as an E-Voting Agency for the Postal Ballot. The cut-off date for sending postal ballot notice to shareholders and entitlement of e-voting was set as Friday, 6th February 2026.</p><ul><li>Advance Lifestyles Ltd. announced unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended on 31st December 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue for the quarter was Rs. 10,325.70 lakhs and Rs. 27,894.76 lakhs for the nine-month period.</li><li>The Board approved alterations to the Main Object clause of the Memorandum of Association and a change of name.</li><li>New set of MoA adopted and limits under Section 186 of the Companies Act, 2013 enhanced.</li><li>M/s. MSDS &amp; Associates appointed as Scrutinizer for Postal Ballot through e-voting and M/s. Bigshare Services Private Limited as an E-Voting Agency for the Postal Ballot.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4cad1782-7843-47ca-8421-841929f2a76e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADVANCE LIFESTYLES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[S&amp;SPOWER] S&amp;S Power Switchgear Ltd Announces Q3 2025 Financial Results with 404.29% Profit Before Tax</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=S%26S+POWER+SWITCHGEAR+LTD.&title=S%26S+Power+Switchgear+Ltd+Announces+Q3+2025+Financial+Results+with+404.29%25+Profit+Before+Tax&newsId=3656bfb4-5c70-42cc-aba1-dec7894daa4e&token=MzY1NmJmYjQtNWM3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3656bfb4-5c70-42cc-aba1-dec7894daa4e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>S&amp;S Power Switchgear Ltd announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company reported a profit before tax of 13075 Lakhs, a 404.29% increase compared to the same period last year. The revenue from contracts with customers (net of discounts &amp; rebates) was 385.67 Lakhs for the nine-month period. The total revenue from operations was 423.72 Lakhs. The company operates in a single segment, manufacturing electrical equipment for transmission and distribution of power. The financial results have been reviewed by the Audit committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Profit before tax of 13075 Lakhs, a 404.29% increase compared to the same period last year.</li><li>Revenue from contracts with customers (net of discounts &amp; rebates) of 385.67 Lakhs for the nine-month period.</li><li>Total revenue from operations of 423.72 Lakhs.</li><li>Financial results reviewed by the Audit committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/be08306f-d163-401d-9ddd-8c495dab3fea.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: S&S POWER SWITCHGEAR LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TATACOMM] Tata Communications Appoints Siddhartha Mundra as New Chief Financial Officer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TATA+COMMUNICATIONS+LTD.&title=Tata+Communications+Appoints+Siddhartha+Mundra+as+New+Chief+Financial+Officer&newsId=d85ba805-8053-4ab7-8faf-cf89305784fd&token=ZDg1YmE4MDUtODA1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d85ba805-8053-4ab7-8faf-cf89305784fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 16:02:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tata Communications Ltd. has appointed Mr. Siddhartha Mundra as the new Chief Financial Officer. Mr. Mundra, who has over 22 years of experience in corporate finance, strategy, business operations, private equity, and technology, will join as the Chief Financial Officer - Designate on February 23, 2026, and take over as the Chief Financial Officer on May 1, 2026. He currently serves as the Vice President and is part of the Group CFO &amp; Group Strategy Office at Tata Sons. Mr. Kabir Ahmed Shakir will cease to be the Chief Financial Officer of the Company with effect from the close of business hours on April 30, 2026.</p><ul><li>Tata Communications appoints Siddhartha Mundra as the new Chief Financial Officer.</li><li>Mr. Mundra has over 22 years of experience in corporate finance, strategy, business operations, private equity, and technology.</li><li>Mr. Mundra will join as the Chief Financial Officer - Designate on February 23, 2026, and take over as the Chief Financial Officer on May 1, 2026.</li><li>Mr. Kabir Ahmed Shakir will cease to be the Chief Financial Officer of the Company with effect from the close of business hours on April 30, 2026.</li><li>Mr. Mundra currently serves as the Vice President and is part of the Group CFO &amp; Group Strategy Office at Tata Sons.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/78cbd974-538b-4f70-8051-01a2cee253a8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TATA COMMUNICATIONS LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>