<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 21:24:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[NACLIND] NACL Industries Ltd Shifts Registered and Corporate Offices</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NACL+Industries+Ltd&title=NACL+Industries+Ltd+Shifts+Registered+and+Corporate+Offices&newsId=5de07c19-3ba1-4102-bad6-705c734752f8&token=NWRlMDdjMTktM2Jh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5de07c19-3ba1-4102-bad6-705c734752f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>NACL Industries Limited has announced a shift of its Registered and Corporate Offices. The new Registered Office is located at Coromandel House, 1-2-10, Sardar Patel Road, Secunderabad, Hyderabad, Telangana —- 500003, India, while the new Corporate Office is situated at Pranava One, 17‘ Floor, Commercial Block, Plot No.6-3- 654/1 to 9 and 6-3-654/A, Somajiguda, Hyderabad, Telangana - 500082, India. The shift will be effective from January 28, 2026. All stakeholders have been informed about the change.</p><ul><li>NACL Industries Ltd has shifted its Registered and Corporate Offices.</li><li>The new Registered Office is located at Coromandel House, Secunderabad, Hyderabad.</li><li>The new Corporate Office is situated at Pranava One, Somajiguda, Hyderabad.</li><li>The shift will be effective from January 28, 2026.</li><li>All stakeholders have been informed about the change.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e9c45e3d-1d91-4c4e-8c2b-31197129ff8e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NACL Industries Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NAZARA] Nazara Technologies Acquires 5.23% Stake in Rusk Media for INR 27,14,91,792</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Nazara+Technologies+Ltd&title=Nazara+Technologies+Acquires+5.23%25+Stake+in+Rusk+Media+for+INR+27%2C14%2C91%2C792&newsId=67980c42-0f72-4c9b-b22d-56e287553e28&token=Njc5ODBjNDItMGY3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67980c42-0f72-4c9b-b22d-56e287553e28</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:54:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Nazara Technologies Limited has made a cash payment of INR 27,14,91,792 for the acquisition of 4,276 Series A Compulsorily Convertible Preference Shares of INR 10/- each, representing 5.23% of the share capital, on a fully diluted basis, of Rusk Media Private Limited. This acquisition will increase Nazara Technologies&apos; holding in Rusk Media to 7.18%.</p><ul><li>Nazara Technologies acquires 5.23% stake in Rusk Media for INR 27,14,91,792</li><li>Acquisition made through the purchase of 4,276 Series A Compulsorily Convertible Preference Shares</li><li>This acquisition increases Nazara Technologies&apos; holding in Rusk Media to 7.18%</li><li>The acquisition is in compliance with Regulation 30 read with Schedule III of Listing Regulations</li><li>The payment was made pursuant to the Share Purchase Agreement dated November 12, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e2ecf528-ab95-4ff4-a0a6-115a381b1ffb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Nazara Technologies Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAVFI] Savani Financials Ltd Increases Authorised Share Capital to Rs. 50 Crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SAVANI+FINANCIALS+LTD.&title=Savani+Financials+Ltd+Increases+Authorised+Share+Capital+to+Rs.+50+Crore&newsId=70f4385f-a5a8-41ba-8845-b82796a36bb7&token=NzBmNDM4NWYtYTVh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70f4385f-a5a8-41ba-8845-b82796a36bb7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:54:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Savani Financials Ltd, now known as Mantra Capital Limited, has announced an increase in its authorized share capital. The Board of Directors, in a meeting held on January 30, 2026, approved the increase from Rs. 38,00,00,000/- to Rs. 50,00,00,000/-. This alteration is subject to the approval of the company&apos;s members. The new capital structure will consist of 4,75,00,000 equity shares and 25,00,000 redeemable preference shares, both with a face value of Rs. 10/- each. This change will provide the company with the flexibility to manage its capital in accordance with the Companies Act, 2013.</p><ul><li>Savani Financials Ltd has increased its authorized share capital to Rs. 50,00,00,000/-</li><li>The decision is subject to the approval of the company&apos;s members</li><li>The new capital structure includes 4,75,00,000 equity shares and 25,00,000 redeemable preference shares, both with a face value of Rs. 10/- each</li><li>This change will provide the company with greater flexibility in managing its capital</li><li>The company is previously known as Mantra Capital Limited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6fe20549-cba7-4bdf-9ffd-1bb74802655d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SAVANI FINANCIALS LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAVFI] Savani Financials Ltd to Issue 48,25,000 Equity Shares at Rs. 20/- Each on Preferential Basis</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SAVANI+FINANCIALS+LTD.&title=Savani+Financials+Ltd+to+Issue+48%2C25%2C000+Equity+Shares+at+Rs.+20%2F-+Each+on+Preferential+Basis&newsId=8993eace-d552-4eea-a964-6f17b4d5d983&token=ODk5M2VhY2UtZDU1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8993eace-d552-4eea-a964-6f17b4d5d983</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:51:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Savani Financials Ltd, in a meeting held on January 30, 2026, has approved the issuance of 48,25,000 Equity Shares of face value Rs. 10/- each at an issue price of Rs. 20/- per share, including a premium of Rs. 10/- per share, on a preferential basis. This issuance will aggregate to Rs. 9,65,00,000/- (Nine Crores Sixty Five Lakhs Only) and will increase the company&apos;s paid-up share capital to Rs. 36,77,95,580/- (3,67,79,558 Equity Shares of Face Value of Rs.10/- Each fully Paid-Up). The decision is subject to approval of the members of the Company and other statutory approvals.</p><ul><li>Issuance of 48,25,000 Equity Shares at an issue price of Rs. 20/- per share</li><li>Includes a premium of Rs. 10/- per share</li><li>Aggregates to Rs. 9,65,00,000/- (Nine Crores Sixty Five Lakhs Only)</li><li>Subject to approval of the members of the Company and other statutory approvals</li><li>Will increase the company&apos;s paid-up share capital to Rs. 36,77,95,580/- (3,67,79,558 Equity Shares of Face Value of Rs.10/- Each fully Paid-Up)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fff1572a-0e51-4cc5-9b16-56288be9c281.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SAVANI FINANCIALS LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASHOKA] Ashoka Buildcon Q3 &amp; 9M FY26 Business &amp; Financial Highlights: Profit After Tax Surges 68%, Order Book at Rs. 15,927 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ASHOKA+BUILDCON+LTD.&title=Ashoka+Buildcon+Q3+%26+9M+FY26+Business+%26+Financial+Highlights%3A+Profit+After+Tax+Surges+68%25%2C+Order+Book+at+Rs.+15%2C927+Crores&newsId=fa1d63ab-b186-481f-97a8-dc0f6cd5d8c4&token=ZmExZDYzYWItYjE4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa1d63ab-b186-481f-97a8-dc0f6cd5d8c4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:42:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Ashoka Buildcon Limited, an integrated EPC, BOT and HAM player, reported its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s total income stood at Rs. 1,491.9 crores for Q3 FY26, a decrease of 18% compared to Q3 FY25. The profit before tax was Rs. 49.6 crores, a decrease of 37% compared to the same period last year. However, the profit after tax surged by 68% to Rs. 101.8 crores. The company&apos;s order book stands at Rs. 15,927 crores as on 31st December 2025. Ashoka Buildcon also announced the acquisition of Ashoka Concessions Limited (ACL), a subsidiary of the company, for an aggregate consideration of ~Rs. 667 crores. The company also received letters of acceptance for various projects from BMC, Public Works Department, Daman, and others.</p><ul><li>Profit After Tax surged by 68%</li><li>Order Book at Rs. 15,927 Crores</li><li>Acquisition of Ashoka Concessions Limited (ACL) for ~Rs. 667 crores</li><li>Received Letter of Acceptance for various projects from BMC, Public Works Department, Daman, and others</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/58ab21e2-f05a-44e3-aedf-1611d551cf16.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ASHOKA BUILDCON LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LICHSGFIN] LIC Housing Finance Reports Q3 FY2026 Results: Profit After Tax at Rs. 1383.95 crs, Net Interest Income Up by 5%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LIC+HOUSING+FINANCE+LTD.&title=LIC+Housing+Finance+Reports+Q3+FY2026+Results%3A+Profit+After+Tax+at+Rs.+1383.95+crs%2C+Net+Interest+Income+Up+by+5%25&newsId=436e41e3-b79a-4b15-ab0e-b7e961a8a93d&token=NDM2ZTQxZTMtYjc5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">436e41e3-b79a-4b15-ab0e-b7e961a8a93d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:42:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>LIC Housing Finance Ltd. has announced its unaudited results for the third quarter ended on December 31, 2025. The company reported a profit after tax of Rs. 1383.95 crs, a 4% increase in total disbursements to Rs. 16096 crs, and a 5% growth in net interest income to Rs. 2102 crs. The net interest margin stood at 2.69%. The individual home loan portfolio grew by 4% to Rs. 265890 crs, and the project loan portfolio stood at Rs. 8827 crs. The total outstanding portfolio grew by 5% to Rs. 314268 crs. The provisions for expected credit loss stood at Rs. 5105 crs with a coverage of 54%.</p><ul><li>Profit after tax at Rs. 1383.95 crs</li><li>Net interest income up by 5% to Rs. 2102 crs</li><li>Total disbursements increased by 4% to Rs. 16096 crs</li><li>Individual home loan portfolio grew by 4% to Rs. 265890 crs</li><li>Net interest margin stood at 2.69%</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1508d8e4-e6c1-4162-8aff-9f16dbc80bdd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LIC HOUSING FINANCE LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SYRMA] Syrma SGS Technology Ltd: Monitoring Agency Report for Q3 2025 Reveals No Deviations in Utilization of IPO Proceeds</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Syrma+SGS+Technology+Ltd&title=Syrma+SGS+Technology+Ltd%3A+Monitoring+Agency+Report+for+Q3+2025+Reveals+No+Deviations+in+Utilization+of+IPO+Proceeds&newsId=42e44691-ed99-4cbc-a1f2-ab2a07d7b5d9&token=NDJlNDQ2OTEtZWQ5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42e44691-ed99-4cbc-a1f2-ab2a07d7b5d9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:42:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Crisil Ratings Limited, the Monitoring Agency for Syrma SGS Technology Ltd, has released the report for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The report highlights that the company has utilized the IPO proceeds as per the objects disclosed in the Offer Document. The company has utilized the proceeds towards setting up manufacturing facilities in AP and other expenditures as disclosed in the Offer Document. The Monitoring Agency report does not indicate any deviations or range of deviation, and the agency has not perceived any conflict of interest in its relationship with the issuer.</p><ul><li>Syrma SGS Technology Ltd has utilized IPO proceeds as per the objects disclosed in the Offer Document.</li><li>The company has utilized the proceeds towards setting up manufacturing facilities in AP and other expenditures as disclosed in the Offer Document.</li><li>The Monitoring Agency report does not indicate any deviations or range of deviation.</li><li>The Monitoring Agency has not perceived any conflict of interest in its relationship with the issuer.</li><li>Crisil Ratings Limited has submitted the report in line with the format prescribed by SEBI.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/615f1306-ab2d-44ac-a49a-8e6d48fb0155.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Syrma SGS Technology Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BRITANNIA] Britannia Industries&apos; Chief Business Officer Resigns After 13 Years</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BRITANNIA+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Britannia+Industries%27+Chief+Business+Officer+Resigns+After+13+Years&newsId=f8fc0102-cfd9-4239-82a6-8f6abaf61c21&token=ZjhmYzAxMDItY2Zk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f8fc0102-cfd9-4239-82a6-8f6abaf61c21</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:41:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Britannia Industries Ltd. announced that Mr. Annu Gupta, the Chief Business Officer for International Business, has submitted his resignation. Mr. Gupta has been with the company for 13 years and has decided to pursue an opportunity outside of Britannia. His last working day will be January 31, 2026.</p><ul><li>Mr. Annu Gupta, Chief Business Officer - International Business, has resigned from Britannia Industries Ltd.</li><li>Mr. Gupta has been with the company for 13 years and has decided to pursue an opportunity outside of Britannia.</li><li>His last working day will be January 31, 2026.</li><li>The announcement was made in accordance with Regulation 30 read with Clause 7 of Para A of Part A of Schedule III of the SEBI Listing Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4020198e-1745-4bc2-9237-52f2a587b5b4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BRITANNIA INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MANALIPETC] Assistant Vice President - Projects &amp; Technical Services Retires from Manali Petrochemicals Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MANALI+PETROCHEMICAL+LTD.&title=Assistant+Vice+President+-+Projects+%26+Technical+Services+Retires+from+Manali+Petrochemicals+Ltd&newsId=bdac1499-a085-45cd-a340-723e0f637598&token=YmRhYzE0OTktYTA4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bdac1499-a085-45cd-a340-723e0f637598</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:41:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Manali Petrochemicals Ltd announced the retirement of Mr. T Thangasagaran, Assistant Vice President - Projects &amp; Technical Services and Senior Management Personnel, effective from the close of business hours of 30th January 2026. This retirement also means that Mr. T Thangasagaran ceases to be a Senior Management Personnel of the Company from the same date.</p><ul><li>Mr. T Thangasagaran, Assistant Vice President - Projects &amp; Technical Services and Senior Management Personnel of Manali Petrochemicals Ltd, has retired.</li><li>The retirement is effective from the close of business hours of 30th January 2026.</li><li>Mr. T Thangasagaran ceases to be a Senior Management Personnel of the Company from the same date.</li><li>The disclosure is pursuant to Regulation 30 of Listing Regulations read with SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/CFD/PoD2/CIR/P/0155 dated November 11, 2024.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f42cdf18-8a22-4318-8a6a-583b85cef8ec.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MANALI PETROCHEMICAL LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PRECISIO] Precision Electronics Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results on Feb 7, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PRECISION+ELECTRONICS+LTD.&title=Precision+Electronics+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+on+Feb+7%2C+2026&newsId=de6ebe4f-7eef-4001-910c-48b167932c09&token=ZGU2ZWJlNGYtN2Vl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de6ebe4f-7eef-4001-910c-48b167932c09</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:41:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Precision Electronics Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 7, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting is scheduled in accordance with Regulation 29 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations &amp; Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The trading window for dealing in securities of the company will remain closed for all Designated Persons till 48 hours after the declaration of the unaudited financial results.</p><ul><li>Precision Electronics Ltd to consider and approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Meeting scheduled on February 7, 2026, in accordance with Regulation 29 of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Trading window to remain closed for all Designated Persons till 48 hours after the declaration of results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/77ccc832-5ff8-48ed-9aac-4f1ffaf7d982.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PRECISION ELECTRONICS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>