<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:26:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[JUSTDIAL] Just Dial Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q3 and Q9 Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JUST+DIAL+LTD.&title=Just+Dial+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+and+Q9+Results+for+2025&newsId=f58a1d53-5b88-4023-b2dd-cc3f026208f2&token=ZjU4YTFkNTMtNWI4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f58a1d53-5b88-4023-b2dd-cc3f026208f2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:37:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Just Dial Ltd, a prominent company, has announced a board meeting scheduled for January 13, 2026. The agenda includes the consideration and approval of the unaudited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. This meeting is pursuant to the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Just Dial Ltd has scheduled a board meeting on January 13, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the unaudited financial results for Q3 and Q9 of 2025</li><li>The agenda is in accordance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6abe2d67-77bb-49ac-9aed-f3c6c13b0bd1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JUST DIAL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DEVYANI] Devyani International Ltd Releases First Sustainability Report for FY 2024-25</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Devyani+International+Ltd&title=Devyani+International+Ltd+Releases+First+Sustainability+Report+for+FY+2024-25&newsId=59ed34b5-bf34-4f03-a1d5-63eeb40321f3&token=NTllZDM0YjUtYmYz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59ed34b5-bf34-4f03-a1d5-63eeb40321f3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Sustainability Report</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Devyani International Ltd, a leading Quick Service Restaurant (QSR) company, has released its first Sustainability Report for the financial year 2024-25. The report, titled &apos;Trending Tastes, Fabulous Flavors&apos;, provides an overview of the company&apos;s vision, mission, and commitment to sustainability. It covers the company&apos;s ESG (Environmental, Social, and Governance) performance on a standalone basis for the reporting period 1 April 2024 to 31 March 2025.</p><ul><li>First Sustainability Report released for FY 2024-25</li><li>Company&apos;s vision and commitment to sustainability outlined</li><li>ESG performance for the reporting period 1 April 2024 to 31 March 2025 covered</li><li>Report prepared in reference to Global Reporting Initiative (GRI) framework, Sustainability Accounting Standards Board (SASB), and the 17 Sustainable Development Goals of the United Nations Sustainable Development Group (UNSDG)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c39a0f2a-cf91-4f19-91bc-5be3784335cf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Devyani International Ltd | Category: Sustainability Report</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CLEDUCATE] CL Media Private Limited Faces Rs. 15.46 Crores Tax &amp; Penalty Demand from Central GST</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CL+Educate+Ltd&title=CL+Media+Private+Limited+Faces+Rs.+15.46+Crores+Tax+%26+Penalty+Demand+from+Central+GST&newsId=dcecf99f-8cf9-419e-9f11-dd668ee5473d&token=ZGNlY2Y5OWYtOGNm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dcecf99f-8cf9-419e-9f11-dd668ee5473d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>CL Media Private Limited, a former wholly owned subsidiary of CL Educate Ltd, has received an Order in Original from the Office of the Assistant Commissioner of Central GST, Delhi South. The order, dated December 26, 2025, raises a demand for tax and penalty amounting to Rs. 15.46 crores on CL Media Private Limited and its Directors, pertaining to the period FY18-19 to FY21-22. The demand is for alleged excess availment of Input Tax Credit for the period FY18-19 till FY 21-22. The final quantum is magnified by the number of directors in the company. CL Educate Ltd, based on internal review, has decided to contest the order through the statutory appellate process.</p><ul><li>CL Media Private Limited received an Order in Original from the Office of the Assistant Commissioner of Central GST, Delhi South</li><li>The order raises a demand for tax and penalty amounting to Rs. 15.46 crores on CL Media Private Limited and its Directors</li><li>The demand is for alleged excess availment of Input Tax Credit for the period FY18-19 till FY 21-22</li><li>The final quantum is magnified by the number of directors in the company</li><li>CL Educate Ltd has decided to contest the order through the statutory appellate process</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/73b9bbaa-09e4-4a83-be2c-174a7dbf4911.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CL Educate Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PIIND] PI Industries Ltd Faces Tax Demand of INR 3,90,09,656 for FY 2021-22</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PI+Industries+Ltd&title=PI+Industries+Ltd+Faces+Tax+Demand+of+INR+3%2C90%2C09%2C656+for+FY+2021-22&newsId=e196db13-fe82-4fd6-8289-4111293a097b&token=ZTE5NmRiMTMtZmU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e196db13-fe82-4fd6-8289-4111293a097b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:21:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>PI Industries Ltd has received an order from the Office of the Excise and Taxation Officer-cum-State Tax Officer, Jurisdiction - Bhatinda, resulting in a tax demand under Section 73 of the Central Goods and Service tax (CGST) Act, 2017 read with Punjab Goods and Services Tax (PGST) Act, 2017, and rules thereon. The demand, including interest and penalty, amounts to INR 3,90,09,656 for the financial year 2021-22. The authority has raised this demand due to the disallowance of input tax credits availed by the Company. However, the Company believes it has adequate grounds to contest the order and is in the process of filing an appeal before the appropriate authority. This action is not expected to have a material impact on the Company&apos;s financials, operations, or other activities.</p><ul><li>PI Industries Ltd has received a tax demand under Section 73 of the CGST Act, 2017 and PGST Act, 2017</li><li>The demand, including interest and penalty, amounts to INR 3,90,09,656 for the financial year 2021-22</li><li>The demand is due to the disallowance of input tax credits availed by the Company</li><li>The Company believes it has adequate grounds to contest the order</li><li>The Company is in the process of filing an appeal before the appropriate authority</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ab5658a9-b967-42ad-858b-664c81c656e6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PI Industries Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HRMNYCP] Harmony Capital Service Ltd Promoter Seeks Reclassification to Public Category</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HARMONY+CAPITAL+SERVICES+LTD.&title=Harmony+Capital+Service+Ltd+Promoter+Seeks+Reclassification+to+Public+Category&newsId=b5fa4d87-13ed-407f-b802-053a8de60075&token=YjVmYTRkODctMTNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5fa4d87-13ed-407f-b802-053a8de60075</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:21:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Promoter Reclassification</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Harmony Capital Service Ltd has received a request from Mr. Anish Sharma, Promoter of the Company, for seeking reclassification from the &apos;Promoter&apos; category to the &apos;Public&apos; category due to his nil shareholding in the Company. The Board of Directors will consider this request at its upcoming meeting, subject to compliance with the applicable provisions of the SEBI LODR Regulations and approval of the Stock Exchange(s). The Company will make an application to BSE Limited for approval of the reclassification and take necessary steps upon approval of the Board of Directors. This intimation is for the information of the Exchange and the shareholders of the Company.</p><ul><li>Mr. Anish Sharma, Promoter of Harmony Capital Service Ltd, seeks reclassification from &apos;Promoter&apos; to &apos;Public&apos; category</li><li>Request due to Mr. Sharma&apos;s nil shareholding in the Company</li><li>Board of Directors to consider the request at the upcoming meeting</li><li>Subject to compliance with SEBI LODR Regulations and Stock Exchange(s) approval</li><li>Company to make application to BSE Limited for approval and take necessary steps upon Board&apos;s approval</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8b6ace82-d2da-4083-8594-766062eb858f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HARMONY CAPITAL SERVICES LTD. | Category: Promoter Reclassification</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZOMATO] Eternal Ltd Receives GST Demand Order of INR 1,92,43,792 from Additional Commissioner of State Tax (Appeals), West Bengal</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Zomato+Ltd&title=Eternal+Ltd+Receives+GST+Demand+Order+of+INR+1%2C92%2C43%2C792+from+Additional+Commissioner+of+State+Tax+%28Appeals%29%2C+West+Bengal&newsId=cc15e546-04ea-4bae-9e54-63c4ac3cc7b6&token=Y2MxNWU1NDYtMDRl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cc15e546-04ea-4bae-9e54-63c4ac3cc7b6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:51:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Eternal Limited has filed with the Exchange regarding an order received from the Additional Commissioner of State Tax (Appeals), West Bengal. The order, received on 06 January 2026, confirms a demand of GST of INR 1,92,43,792 with interest of INR 1,58,12,070 and penalty of INR 19,24,380 for the period April 2019 to March 2020. The Company believes it has a strong case on merits and will be filing an appeal against the order before the appropriate authority.</p><ul><li>Eternal Limited received an order from the Additional Commissioner of State Tax (Appeals), West Bengal for the period April 2019 to March 2020.</li><li>The order confirms a demand of GST of INR 1,92,43,792 with interest of INR 1,58,12,070 and penalty of INR 19,24,380.</li><li>The Company believes it has a strong case on merits and will be filing an appeal against the order before the appropriate authority.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/99223b6c-1a56-4db4-a52a-d6fb62aa2083.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Zomato Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDTERRAIN] Indian Terrain Fashions Ltd Reports No Pending Transfer Requests for Physical Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDIAN+TERRAIN+FASHIONS+LTD.&title=Indian+Terrain+Fashions+Ltd+Reports+No+Pending+Transfer+Requests+for+Physical+Shares&newsId=0e10e56a-35f9-4c11-bf56-8302967c4efc&token=MGUxMGU1NmEtMzVm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e10e56a-35f9-4c11-bf56-8302967c4efc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:51:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indian Terrain Fashions Ltd has provided an update on the status of re-lodgement of transfer requests of physical shares from July 2025 till closure of office hours on 6th January 2026. According to the report, there were no pending transfer requests, no requests received, no requests processed, no requests approved, and no requests rejected. This information is for record purposes and kindly requested to acknowledge the receipt.</p><ul><li>Indian Terrain Fashions Ltd reports no pending transfer requests for physical shares</li><li>No requests received, processed, approved, or rejected from July 2025 to 6th January 2026</li><li>Update provided for record purposes</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ad20be40-dd39-4e71-908c-82c3c8301529.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDIAN TERRAIN FASHIONS LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PAEL] PAE Ltd Receives Trading Approval for 10,000,000 Equity Shares from BSE Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PAE+LTD.&title=PAE+Ltd+Receives+Trading+Approval+for+10%2C000%2C000+Equity+Shares+from+BSE+Limited&newsId=814dabc2-3ca4-4004-a113-b71384bb87e9&token=ODE0ZGFiYzItM2Nh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">814dabc2-3ca4-4004-a113-b71384bb87e9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>PAE Ltd has received trading approval from BSE Limited for 10,000,000 Equity Shares of Rs. 10 each. The shares were allotted to promoters on a preferential basis and to existing public shareholders by way of reduction of share capital. The shares will be traded on BSE from 7th January, 2026. This approval is pursuant to the approved Resolution Plan as per the Hon’ble NCLT order dated November 27, 2024, of Mumbai Bench.</p><ul><li>PAE Ltd receives trading approval from BSE Limited for 10,000,000 Equity Shares</li><li>Shares allotted to promoters on a preferential basis and to existing public shareholders by way of reduction of share capital</li><li>Shares to be traded on BSE from 7th January, 2026</li><li>Approval pursuant to the approved Resolution Plan as per the Hon’ble NCLT order dated November 27, 2024, of Mumbai Bench</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/23a95d4c-3e86-4410-bf32-f19bb0e76715.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PAE LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VELHO] Velan Hotels Ltd Faces Penalty for Delay in Filing MGT-15 under Companies Act 2013</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VELAN+HOTELS+LTD.&title=Velan+Hotels+Ltd+Faces+Penalty+for+Delay+in+Filing+MGT-15+under+Companies+Act+2013&newsId=6f1fd4d0-1ac5-4b7d-8678-6777543795a7&token=NmYxZmQ0ZDAtMWFj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f1fd4d0-1ac5-4b7d-8678-6777543795a7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Velan Hotels Ltd has received an Order for Adjudication of penalty under Section 454 of the Companies Act 2013 from the Registrar of Companies (ROC) — Tamilnadu, Coimbatore. The penalty is due to a 30-day delay in filing e-Form MGT-15 for the Annual General Meeting held on 29th September 2022 for the financial year 2021-22. The Company, Managing Director, Executive Director, and CFO have been imposed a penalty of Rs.1,15,000/- and Rs.40,000/- each respectively. There is no material impact other than the penalty on the Company&apos;s financial, operational, or other activities.</p><ul><li>Velan Hotels Ltd has received an Order for Adjudication of penalty under Section 454 of the Companies Act 2013.</li><li>The penalty is due to a 30-day delay in filing e-Form MGT-15 for the Annual General Meeting held on 29th September 2022 for the financial year 2021-22.</li><li>The Company, Managing Director, Executive Director, and CFO have been imposed a penalty of Rs.1,15,000/- and Rs.40,000/- each respectively.</li><li>There is no material impact other than the penalty on the Company&apos;s financial, operational, or other activities.</li><li>The Company and its Officers-in-default will evaluate the order and determine the appropriate course of action in future.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/42c03db0-40ee-4e69-bb00-73d0739d6c07.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VELAN HOTELS LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[QRIL] Statutory Auditor of Quality RO Industries Ltd Resigns</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Quality+RO+Industries+Ltd&title=Statutory+Auditor+of+Quality+RO+Industries+Ltd+Resigns&newsId=b20bc222-2e94-4e65-9eb0-8ebf37ff9531&token=YjIwYmMyMjItMmU5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b20bc222-2e94-4e65-9eb0-8ebf37ff9531</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Auditor</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Quality RO Industries Ltd has disclosed the resignation of its statutory auditor, M/s. Doshi Doshi &amp; Co, Chartered Accountants, due to preoccupation with other assignments. The auditor has confirmed that there are no concerns raised with respect to the management of the Company and no material reason for the resignation. The Company will consider the appointment of new statutory auditors in due course.</p><ul><li>M/s. Doshi Doshi &amp; Co, Chartered Accountants, resigns as statutory auditor of Quality RO Industries Ltd</li><li>The resignation is due to preoccupation with other assignments</li><li>No concerns were raised by the resigning auditor with respect to the management of the Company</li><li>No material reason for the resignation</li><li>The Company will consider the appointment of new statutory auditors in due course</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dbe498a2-40cc-4193-a165-968ccb095b1e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Quality RO Industries Ltd | Category: Auditor</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>