<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:55:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[PINELABS] Pine Labs Collaborates with OpenAI to Engineer Agentic Commerce in India</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Pine+Labs+Ltd&title=Pine+Labs+Collaborates+with+OpenAI+to+Engineer+Agentic+Commerce+in+India&newsId=b7f956dc-13a5-47f4-b3ae-c913aa0d7882&token=YjdmOTU2ZGMtMTNh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7f956dc-13a5-47f4-b3ae-c913aa0d7882</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:39:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Partnership</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Pine Labs, a technology company digitising commerce, has collaborated with OpenAI to build Agentic Commerce. This paradigm shift moves beyond traditional automation, enabling autonomous optimization of financial workflows within secure guardrails. The collaboration, which integrates OpenAI’s APIs directly into Pine Labs’ Al-native infrastructure, is set to transform commerce in India and beyond, with Pine Labs becoming an active, intelligent layer for business.</p><ul><li>Pine Labs and OpenAI collaborate to build Agentic Commerce, a paradigm where financial systems autonomously optimize workflows.</li><li>The collaboration integrates OpenAI’s APIs directly into Pine Labs’ Al-native infrastructure, moving beyond deterministic processing to probabilistic reasoning.</li><li>Pine Labs’ infrastructure is no longer just a participant in a trade, but a driver of efficiency and growth, building the first agentic stack for the next generation of the global economy.</li><li>The collaboration enables Conversational Commerce to reach its full potential, allowing users to delegate entire financial lifecycles to intelligent agents within a single dialogue.</li><li>Pine Labs is opening this agentic stack to its developer ecosystem, providing the tools for third-party innovators to build next-generation, Al-native fintech applications on a trusted foundation.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c536680b-80d4-409a-b532-82469486442c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Pine Labs Ltd | Category: Partnership</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KRYPTONQ] Krypton Industries Ltd Appoints Ms. Vaishnavi Gupta as Additional Non-Executive Independent Director, Accepts Resignation of Mr. Satadal Chattopadhyay</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KRYPTON+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Krypton+Industries+Ltd+Appoints+Ms.+Vaishnavi+Gupta+as+Additional+Non-Executive+Independent+Director%2C+Accepts+Resignation+of+Mr.+Satadal+Chattopadhyay&newsId=0ecb6e85-208d-448e-8a8f-51649c119e06&token=MGVjYjZlODUtMjA4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ecb6e85-208d-448e-8a8f-51649c119e06</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:32:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Krypton Industries Ltd has appointed Ms. Vaishnavi Gupta as an Additional Non-Executive Independent Director, subject to the approval of shareholders. Ms. Gupta is a B. Com graduate with specialization in Accountancy. The company also accepted the resignation of Mr. Satadal Chattopadhyay from the office of Non-Executive Independent Director due to his preoccupation with other professional commitments.</p><ul><li>Krypton Industries Ltd has appointed Ms. Vaishnavi Gupta as an Additional Non-Executive Independent Director.</li><li>Ms. Gupta&apos;s appointment is subject to the approval of shareholders.</li><li>Ms. Gupta is a B. Com graduate with specialization in Accountancy.</li><li>The company accepted the resignation of Mr. Satadal Chattopadhyay from the office of Non-Executive Independent Director.</li><li>Mr. Chattopadhyay resigned due to his preoccupation with other professional commitments.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/605e52d7-f2db-4dce-925c-6de821405967.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KRYPTON INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BHANDHOS] Bhandari Hosiery Exports Ltd Fixes Record Date for Rights Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BHANDARI+HOSIERY+EXPORTS+LTD.&title=Bhandari+Hosiery+Exports+Ltd+Fixes+Record+Date+for+Rights+Issue&newsId=ecec4318-47c0-4829-ba40-38df986bcdcc&token=ZWNlYzQzMTgtNDdj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ecec4318-47c0-4829-ba40-38df986bcdcc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:26:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bhandari Hosiery Exports Ltd has fixed Wednesday, 25th February, 2026 as the record date for the purpose of determining names of the shareholders of the Company eligible to apply for the Equity Shares in the Rights Issue of the Company. The Rights Entitlements of Eligible Equity Shareholders as on record date shall be credited, prior to the issue opening date, in their respective demat accounts. The Company is in the process of obtaining fresh ISIN for the purpose of the Rights Issue.</p><ul><li>Bhandari Hosiery Exports Ltd has fixed a record date for its Rights Issue.</li><li>The record date is Wednesday, 25th February, 2026.</li><li>Eligible shareholders&apos; Rights Entitlements will be credited prior to the issue opening date.</li><li>The Company is obtaining a fresh ISIN for the Rights Issue.</li><li>The information is available on the Company&apos;s website.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d265eba6-c07d-4c28-bd47-9d71bf7eefc3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BHANDARI HOSIERY EXPORTS LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UNIROYAL] Uniroyal Industries Ltd Promoter Transfers 37,53,575 Shares to Son Akhil Mahajan via Inter-se Transfer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=UNIROYAL+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Uniroyal+Industries+Ltd+Promoter+Transfers+37%2C53%2C575+Shares+to+Son+Akhil+Mahajan+via+Inter-se+Transfer&newsId=e3d46f87-aca4-416a-a2c7-8744535a6318&token=ZTNkNDZmODctYWNh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3d46f87-aca4-416a-a2c7-8744535a6318</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Uniroyal Industries Ltd has disclosed an inter-se transfer of shares between promoters. Mr. Akhil Mahajan, a promoter, has acquired 37,53,575 equity shares of the company by way of gift from his father Mr. Arvind Mahajan and mother Mrs. Rashmi Mahajan. This transfer does not involve any consideration and falls within the exception under regulation 10(1)(a)(i) and 10(1)(a)(ii). The aggregate holding of promoter and promoter group remains the same before and after the transfer. The necessary disclosure under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (SAST) Regulation and 7(2) of SEBI (PIT) Regulations has been made for this acquisition.</p><ul><li>Mr. Akhil Mahajan has acquired 37,53,575 equity shares of Uniroyal Industries Ltd from his father Mr. Arvind Mahajan and mother Mrs. Rashmi Mahajan.</li><li>The transfer is in the nature of gift and falls within the exception under regulation 10(1)(a)(i) and 10(1)(a)(ii).</li><li>The aggregate holding of promoter and promoter group remains the same before and after the transfer.</li><li>Necessary disclosure under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (SAST) Regulation and 7(2) of SEBI (PIT) Regulations has been made for this acquisition.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/247edb9e-25a4-41d6-884c-f8bc01de3380.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: UNIROYAL INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HUIL] Hindusthan Urban Infrastructure Revises Record Date for Equity Shares Sub-Division</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Hindusthan+Urban+Infrastructure+Ltd&title=Hindusthan+Urban+Infrastructure+Revises+Record+Date+for+Equity+Shares+Sub-Division&newsId=e8c10aef-1f20-4504-b6a3-e3320755788d&token=ZThjMTBhZWYtMWYy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e8c10aef-1f20-4504-b6a3-e3320755788d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:23:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hindusthan Urban Infrastructure Ltd. has revised the Record Date for the purpose of determining the members eligible for the sub-division/split of the existing equity shares of the Company. The original Record Date was 27th February 2026, but due to the need to align it with the timelines for change of name of the Company and receipt of necessary approvals from the Stock Exchange and the Depositories, the Board of Directors has revised the Record Date to Friday, 13th March 2026. This change is in accordance with Regulation 42 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Hindusthan Urban Infrastructure revises the Record Date for equity shares sub-division</li><li>The original Record Date was 27th February 2026, but has been revised to 13th March 2026</li><li>The revision is to align with the timelines for change of name of the Company and necessary approvals</li><li>The change is in accordance with Regulation 42 of the SEBI Listing Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/04eb7b0c-05ce-40ae-a78e-1fa34af28f72.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Hindusthan Urban Infrastructure Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BHANDHOS] Bhandari Hosiery Exports Ltd Announces Rs. 49.30 Crores Right Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BHANDARI+HOSIERY+EXPORTS+LTD.&title=Bhandari+Hosiery+Exports+Ltd+Announces+Rs.+49.30+Crores+Right+Issue&newsId=ed37533a-f179-4fcb-9d98-da6c41252c9b&token=ZWQzNzUzM2EtZjE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed37533a-f179-4fcb-9d98-da6c41252c9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:23:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bhandari Hosiery Exports Ltd has announced a Right Issue of fully paid Equity Shares aggregating up to Rs. 49.30 Crores. The Right Issue will be made to all existing equity shareholders of the Company on a rights basis in the ratio of 4 Equity shares for every 5 Equity shares held in the Company. The Record Date for the purpose of determining names of shareholders eligible to apply for the Equity Shares in the Rights Issue is 25th February, 2026.</p><ul><li>Right Issue of Equity Shares worth Rs. 49.30 Crores</li><li>Offer made to all existing equity shareholders on a rights basis</li><li>Rights Issue ratio is 4:5</li><li>Record Date set as 25th February, 2026</li><li>Letter of Offer to be filed with BSE Limited, National Stock Exchange of India Limited and Securities and Exchange Board of India</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e368067e-c20a-4e5b-b766-9a54a64eefbe.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BHANDARI HOSIERY EXPORTS LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[METHODHUB] MethodHub Software Ltd: First Monitoring Agency Report for December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Methodhub+Software+Ltd&title=MethodHub+Software+Ltd%3A+First+Monitoring+Agency+Report+for+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=1b5c98d8-0ff3-4331-8570-2665fa0f799d&token=MWI1Yzk4ZDgtMGZm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b5c98d8-0ff3-4331-8570-2665fa0f799d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:19:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The first monitoring agency report for MethodHub Software Ltd for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, shows that the company raised Rs.102.49 Crore through Fresh Issue and Offer for Sale of Equity Shares. The report, prepared by Brickwork Ratings, provides a true and fair view of the utilization of the issue proceeds in relation to the objects of the issue.</p><ul><li>MethodHub Software Ltd raised Rs.102.49 Crore through Fresh Issue and Offer for Sale of Equity Shares.</li><li>The report provides a true and fair view of the utilization of the issue proceeds.</li><li>The monitoring agency report is prepared by Brickwork Ratings.</li><li>The report is in line with the format prescribed by SEBI ICDR Regulations, 2018.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c5f5dad8-de4a-43e2-bae3-4af7267763fe.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Methodhub Software Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FIVESTAR] HDFC Mutual Fund Acquires 2.15% Additional Shares in Five-Star Business Finance Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Five-Star+Business+Finance+Ltd&title=HDFC+Mutual+Fund+Acquires+2.15%25+Additional+Shares+in+Five-Star+Business+Finance+Ltd&newsId=b83dbfa8-9390-419a-a805-caad3dabe2c2&token=YjgzZGJmYTgtOTM5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b83dbfa8-9390-419a-a805-caad3dabe2c2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>HDFC Mutual Fund has acquired an additional 2.15% shares in Five-Star Business Finance Ltd as of February 17, 2026. The total shareholding of HDFC Mutual Fund in the company is now 7.15%. This acquisition was made in accordance with the SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</p><ul><li>HDFC Mutual Fund has increased its shareholding in Five-Star Business Finance Ltd by 2.15%.</li><li>The total shareholding of HDFC Mutual Fund in the company is now 7.15%.</li><li>The acquisition was made in accordance with the SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</li><li>The total paid up equity share capital of the company is Rs. 29,45,44,298/- comprising 29,45,44,298 Equity Shares of Rs. 1/- each.</li><li>The acquisition was made on February 17, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/F3D5CB77_8793_4D7D_9240_70342183B33B_113811.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Five-Star Business Finance Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BANSALWIRE] Bansal Wire Industries&apos; Tax Liability Reduced to Zero in GST Appeal Order</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Bansal+Wire+Industries+Ltd&title=Bansal+Wire+Industries%27+Tax+Liability+Reduced+to+Zero+in+GST+Appeal+Order&newsId=44872e8a-2af0-4607-9cd9-7080fda00987&token=NDQ4NzJlOGEtMmFm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">44872e8a-2af0-4607-9cd9-7080fda00987</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bansal Wire Industries Limited has informed the exchange about receiving an order from the GST Appellate Authority. The order is in favor of the company, reducing the tax liability from 1,01,31,788 to Nil for the financial year 2020-21. This order reaffirms the company&apos;s strong compliance framework and has no financial impact.</p><ul><li>Bansal Wire Industries received an order from the GST Appellate Authority</li><li>The order reduces the tax liability from 1,01,31,788 to Nil</li><li>The order has no financial impact on the company</li><li>The order reaffirms the company&apos;s strong compliance framework</li><li>The order is related to the financial year 2020-21</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/830c6d6a-5cba-4ffb-ac47-e4e907cc677f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Bansal Wire Industries Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BHANDHOS] Bhandari Hosiery Exports Ltd Announces Rs. 49.30 Crores Right Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BHANDARI+HOSIERY+EXPORTS+LTD.&title=Bhandari+Hosiery+Exports+Ltd+Announces+Rs.+49.30+Crores+Right+Issue&newsId=a3323094-e3ff-43f3-9a6d-a4fc297da2cd&token=YTMzMjMwOTQtZTNm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a3323094-e3ff-43f3-9a6d-a4fc297da2cd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bhandari Hosiery Exports Ltd has announced a Right Issue of fully paid Equity Shares aggregating up to Rs. 49.30 Crores. The Right Issue will be made to all existing equity shareholders of the Company on a rights basis in the ratio of 4 Equity shares for every 5 Equity shares held in the Company. The Record Date for the purpose of determining names of shareholders eligible to apply for the Equity Shares in the Rights Issue is 25th February, 2026.</p><ul><li>Right Issue of Equity Shares worth Rs. 49.30 Crores</li><li>Offer for existing equity shareholders in the ratio of 4:5</li><li>Record Date set as 25th February, 2026</li><li>Issue Opening Date is 6th March, 2026</li><li>Last date for off Market Renunciation of the Rights Entitlements is 19th March, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/020030cf-c428-4fb4-bbcd-a6e2a0b9433e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BHANDARI HOSIERY EXPORTS LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>