<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:02:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ACME] Acme Resources Ltd. Approves Q3 and Nine Months Results for FY2025, Announces Resignation of Secretarial Auditor</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Acme+Resources+Ltd&title=Acme+Resources+Ltd.+Approves+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+FY2025%2C+Announces+Resignation+of+Secretarial+Auditor&newsId=ea0d738e-5390-4daa-b204-aace7bf3970e&token=ZWEwZDczOGUtNTM5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ea0d738e-5390-4daa-b204-aace7bf3970e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Acme Resources Ltd. announced the approval of its un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s board noted the resignation of Vikas Gera &amp; Associates as the Secretarial Auditor, citing pre-occupation with other professional assignments. The resignation is effective from February 9, 2026.</p><ul><li>Acme Resources Ltd. approved the un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s board took note of the resignation of Vikas Gera &amp; Associates as the Secretarial Auditor, due to pre-occupation with other professional assignments.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2800cc24-e464-4dc6-9413-8ad58dea363d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Acme Resources Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LLOYDSTEEL] Lloyds Engineering Works Ltd Enters MoU with Windsor Machines Limited for Property Transaction</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Lloyds+Steels+Industries+Ltd&title=Lloyds+Engineering+Works+Ltd+Enters+MoU+with+Windsor+Machines+Limited+for+Property+Transaction&newsId=09019b5f-08bc-47e2-83f6-41b04bcb0c5d&token=MDkwMTliNWYtMDhi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09019b5f-08bc-47e2-83f6-41b04bcb0c5d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Property Transaction</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Lloyds Engineering Works Ltd has entered into a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with Windsor Machines Limited for the purchase of industrial land and factory buildings situated at GIDC Vatva Industrial Area, Ahmedabad. The MoU includes Plot Nos. 5402, 5403, 5404 &amp; 5405, along with existing buildings and fixed assets. The transaction is limited to the execution and completion of the property transaction, and does not create any partnership, agency, joint control or continuing, commercial relationship beyond completion of the transaction. The transaction is not a related party transaction and does not involve any issuance of shares. The MoU was signed on 10th February 2026.</p><ul><li>Lloyds Engineering Works Ltd enters MoU with Windsor Machines Limited</li><li>Purchase of industrial land and factory buildings in GIDC Vatva Industrial Area, Ahmedabad</li><li>Transaction includes Plot Nos. 5402, 5403, 5404 &amp; 5405, along with existing buildings and fixed assets</li><li>Transaction is not a related party transaction</li><li>MoU signed on 10th February 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c8c2c40b-254b-44c8-aea0-a86edf951bbe.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Lloyds Steels Industries Ltd | Category: Property Transaction</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EIHOTEL] EIH Ltd Approves Unaudited Financial Results for Q4 2025, Exceptional Items of Rs. 110.32 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=EIH+LTD.&title=EIH+Ltd+Approves+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q4+2025%2C+Exceptional+Items+of+Rs.+110.32+Crores&newsId=8e4737e6-563c-43c5-8888-518a5ca933f3&token=OGU0NzM3ZTYtNTYz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8e4737e6-563c-43c5-8888-518a5ca933f3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>EIH Ltd, a member of The Oberoi Group, has approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company reported a profit before tax of Rs. 288.35 crores for the quarter. However, the results include exceptional items of Rs. 110.32 crores, which were adjusted pursuant to the order of the Hon&apos;ble High Court dated 2nd June 2025 and 14th October 2025. The company also recognized an incremental obligation of Rs. 29.09 crores on account of increase in employee benefit liabilities arising from past service due to the enactment of the Labour Codes.</p><ul><li>EIH Ltd reported a profit before tax of Rs. 288.35 crores for Q4 2025.</li><li>Exceptional items of Rs. 110.32 crores were adjusted pursuant to the order of the Hon&apos;ble High Court.</li><li>The company recognized an incremental obligation of Rs. 29.09 crores due to the enactment of the Labour Codes.</li><li>EIH Ltd is a member of The Oberoi Group.</li><li>The results are for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d7240d9d-5752-4f41-a8f7-0f8c55c1c173.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: EIH LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[COSMOFE] Cosmo Ferrites Ltd. Approves Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 2025-2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=COSMO+FERRITES+LTD.-%24&title=Cosmo+Ferrites+Ltd.+Approves+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+2025-2026&newsId=9daba34f-2a40-449f-96c2-6dc5bddd21bd&token=OWRhYmEzNGYtMmE0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9daba34f-2a40-449f-96c2-6dc5bddd21bd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cosmo Ferrites Ltd. announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025, and the year-to-date financial results from April 1, 2025, to December 31, 2025. The financial results were reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors. The company&apos;s revenue, expenses, and profit before tax have been reported as per the Indian Accounting Standards (Ind AS 34) and other accounting principles generally accepted in India.</p><ul><li>Cosmo Ferrites Ltd. announced its unaudited financial results for Q3 2025-2026.</li><li>The financial results were reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</li><li>Revenue, expenses, and profit before tax reported as per Indian Accounting Standards (Ind AS 34).</li><li>Interest on promoter&apos;s unsecured loan has been conditionally waived with the right to recompense.</li><li>One-time increase in past period employee benefit liability under the New Labour Codes.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8aa608da-da74-40ea-963b-41864438df5b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: COSMO FERRITES LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADLINE] Adline Chem Lab Ltd Appoints Mr. Vrushank Patel as Chairman and Managing Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Adline+Chem+Lab+Ltd&title=Adline+Chem+Lab+Ltd+Appoints+Mr.+Vrushank+Patel+as+Chairman+and+Managing+Director&newsId=dc91fc8c-905f-42e2-aa09-07ab624e5bd4&token=ZGM5MWZjOGMtOTA1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc91fc8c-905f-42e2-aa09-07ab624e5bd4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Adline Chem Lab Ltd has appointed Mr. Vrushank Balkrushna Patel (DIN: 05310613) as the Chairman and Managing Director of the Company for a term of 5 (Five) Years, effective from 10th February, 2026. Mr. Patel is an undergraduate in Civil Engineering from South Gujarat University and has been actively involved in Green Energy Generation, Real Estate Business, and Import &amp; Trading of Natural Resources since 2013. His appointment comes as a result of the resignation of Mr. Sarang Pathak from the position of Directorship. Mr. Patel is not related to any other directors of the Company and is not debarred from holding the office of Director by virtue of any SEBI Order or any other such authority.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Vrushank Balkrushna Patel as Chairman and Managing Director</li><li>Effective from 10th February, 2026</li><li>Mr. Patel is an undergraduate in Civil Engineering from South Gujarat University</li><li>Actively involved in Green Energy Generation, Real Estate Business, and Import &amp; Trading of Natural Resources since 2013</li><li>Appointment due to the resignation of Mr. Sarang Pathak from the position of Directorship</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/db5105e2-462f-4fc7-b843-00d7720c9eaf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Adline Chem Lab Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EXATO] Exato Technologies Ltd. Postpones Board Meeting to Finalize Un-audited Financial Statements</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Exato+Technologies+Ltd&title=Exato+Technologies+Ltd.+Postpones+Board+Meeting+to+Finalize+Un-audited+Financial+Statements&newsId=cd5e310e-08f1-4b7b-969a-66fcf4d18415&token=Y2Q1ZTMxMGUtMDhm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd5e310e-08f1-4b7b-969a-66fcf4d18415</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Exato Technologies Ltd. has announced the postponement of its board meeting initially scheduled for 11/02/2026 to 13/02/2026. The decision was made due to the requirement of additional time for the finalization of the un-audited Financial Statements. The agenda of the meeting remains the same as previously intimated. Furthermore, in compliance with SEBI regulations, the trading window has been closed and will remain so until 48 hours after the declaration of financial results.</p><ul><li>Exato Technologies Ltd. postpones board meeting to 13/02/2026</li><li>Postponement due to additional time required for finalization of un-audited Financial Statements</li><li>Agenda of the meeting remains the same as previously intimated</li><li>Trading window closed in compliance with SEBI regulations until 48 hours after financial results declaration</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/271c1abb-4739-40b0-9c73-9a284ad03909.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Exato Technologies Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GNFC] Gujarat Narmada Valley Fertilizers &amp; Chemicals Ltd Appoints Shri Rajkumar Beniwal, IAS as Managing Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GUJARAT+NARMADA+VALLEY+FERTILIZERS+%26+CHEMICALS+LTD.&title=Gujarat+Narmada+Valley+Fertilizers+%26+Chemicals+Ltd+Appoints+Shri+Rajkumar+Beniwal%2C+IAS+as+Managing+Director&newsId=58931a4a-1a88-4441-91b2-429f725ec9a9&token=NTg5MzFhNGEtMWE4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58931a4a-1a88-4441-91b2-429f725ec9a9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gujarat Narmada Valley Fertilizers &amp; Chemicals Ltd has appointed Shri Rajkumar Beniwal, IAS as an Additional Director &amp; Managing Director and designated as KMP of the Company. The appointment is effective from December 29, 2025, subject to approval of shareholders of the Company. Shri Rajkumar Beniwal, IAS is not debarred from holding the office of Director by virtue of order of SEBI or any other such authority. The necessary details have been disclosed in the company&apos;s letter dated December 29, 2025.</p><ul><li>Gujarat Narmada Valley Fertilizers &amp; Chemicals Ltd has appointed Shri Rajkumar Beniwal, IAS as an Additional Director &amp; Managing Director and designated as KMP of the Company.</li><li>The appointment is effective from December 29, 2025, subject to approval of shareholders of the Company.</li><li>Shri Rajkumar Beniwal, IAS is not debarred from holding the office of Director by virtue of order of SEBI or any other such authority.</li><li>The necessary details have been disclosed in the company&apos;s letter dated December 29, 2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d719a91b-a0a5-470f-af5d-b6c2d582d8d2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GUJARAT NARMADA VALLEY FERTILIZERS & CHEMICALS LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PREMIERENE] Premier Energies Forms Strategic JV to Strengthen EPC Capabilities in Renewable Energy</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Premier+Energies+Ltd&title=Premier+Energies+Forms+Strategic+JV+to+Strengthen+EPC+Capabilities+in+Renewable+Energy&newsId=4155e4b0-4c64-4c4e-80cb-d508f3263c99&token=NDE1NWU0YjAtNGM2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4155e4b0-4c64-4c4e-80cb-d508f3263c99</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Premier Energies Ltd. has announced a strategic joint venture with BA Prerna Renewables Private Limited to expand its presence in the Engineering, Procurement and Construction (EPC) segment in the renewable energy sector. The joint venture, HeliosAnthos Energies Private Limited, will undertake EPC contracts for solar, wind, and standalone battery solar-wind-battery hybrid projects across India. This joint venture aligns with Premier Energies’ strategy to deepen its downstream capabilities, complement its integrated manufacturing strengths and its business share across the renewable energy value chain.</p><ul><li>Premier Energies and BA Prerna Renewables Private Limited form a strategic joint venture, HeliosAnthos Energies Private Limited.</li><li>The joint venture will undertake EPC contracts for solar, wind, and standalone battery solar-wind-battery hybrid projects across India.</li><li>Premier Energies will hold a 51% equity stake, while BA Prerna Renewables Private Limited will hold the remaining 49% stake.</li><li>The joint venture will offer end-to-end EPC solutions covering land acquisition, transmission connectivity, statutory approvals, detailed engineering, procurement, installation and commissioning.</li><li>This joint venture aligns with Premier Energies’ strategy to deepen its downstream capabilities and complement its integrated manufacturing strengths in the renewable energy sector.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/62f7c2ee-7820-4f7a-9ee1-c515fa6d4f41.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Premier Energies Ltd | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ARSHIYA] Arshiya Ltd. Extends Last Date for Plan Submission till March 15, 2026 in CIRP</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Arshiya+Limited&title=Arshiya+Ltd.+Extends+Last+Date+for+Plan+Submission+till+March+15%2C+2026+in+CIRP&newsId=11e16e7d-96f8-4f06-a0d7-1c40c0981c55&token=MTFlMTZlN2QtOTZm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11e16e7d-96f8-4f06-a0d7-1c40c0981c55</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Arshiya Ltd., under Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP), held its 13th meeting of the Committee of Creditors (COC) on February 10, 2026. The meeting, conducted through video conferencing, discussed various aspects of the CIRP, including an update on the process, extension of the last date for plan submission, approval of CIRP cost, and discussions with lenders to remove charge over Khurja Land in line with the NCLAT order. The Resolution Professional apprised the COC of these matters.</p><ul><li>Arshiya Ltd. holds 13th COC meeting to discuss CIRP updates</li><li>Last date for plan submission extended to March 15, 2026</li><li>CIRP cost approved during the meeting</li><li>Discussions held with lenders to remove charge over Khurja Land</li><li>Meeting conducted in accordance with NCLAT order</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5b9d9ede-4a30-49c6-8855-966ed8977b6b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Arshiya Limited | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KANCOTEA] Kanco Tea &amp; Industries Ltd Approves Q3 and Nine Months Results for FY2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kanco+Tea+%26+Industries+Ltd&title=Kanco+Tea+%26+Industries+Ltd+Approves+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+FY2025-26&newsId=e618a740-2e81-46ae-bc09-c175c97130b1&token=ZTYxOGE3NDAtMmU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e618a740-2e81-46ae-bc09-c175c97130b1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 13:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kanco Tea &amp; Industries Ltd has approved the unaudited standalone and consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue for the nine months is 7,254 lakhs. The Board of Directors reviewed the financial results in a meeting held on 10th February, 2026. The cost of materials consumed represents only green leaf purchased from third parties and change in inventory for own green leaves. The company has prepared Consolidated Financial Results for Consolidation of Financial Statements of Winnow Investments and Securities Private Limited, 100% subsidiary of the Company.</p><ul><li>Kanco Tea &amp; Industries Ltd approved the unaudited standalone and consolidated Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December, 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue for the nine months is 7,254 lakhs.</li><li>The cost of materials consumed represents only green leaf purchased from third parties and change in inventory for own green leaves.</li><li>The company has prepared Consolidated Financial Results for Consolidation of Financial Statements of Winnow Investments and Securities Private Limited, 100% subsidiary of the Company.</li><li>The ultimate tax liability can be ascertained at the end of the year in view of the seasonal nature of tea business and therefore provision for Current Tax has not been made.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/aad7e32f-d130-4cca-b080-27e9ba57c9ba.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kanco Tea & Industries Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>