<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:45:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[AMBIT] Ambitious Plastomac Company Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results on Feb 12, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AMBITIOUS+PLASTOMAC+COMPANY+LTD.&title=Ambitious+Plastomac+Company+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+on+Feb+12%2C+2026&newsId=7f090861-5ac4-46ea-86aa-c9e196ed842f&token=N2YwOTA4NjEtNWFj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7f090861-5ac4-46ea-86aa-c9e196ed842f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:44:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ambitious Plastomac Company Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 12, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The meeting is in compliance with the SEBI LODR Regulations and the Companies Act, 2013. The trading window for promoters, senior management, their immediate relatives, and other connected persons has been closed from January 01, 2026, and will reopen after 48 hours from the general availability of the results.</p><ul><li>Ambitious Plastomac Company Ltd to approve Q3 and nine months results on Feb 12, 2026</li><li>The results are for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025</li><li>The meeting is in compliance with the SEBI LODR Regulations and the Companies Act, 2013</li><li>Trading window closed for promoters, senior management, their immediate relatives, and other connected persons from Jan 1, 2026</li><li>Trading window to reopen after 48 hours from the general availability of the results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/561aec06-8ffe-4c1a-aada-17b835ee3a3f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AMBITIOUS PLASTOMAC COMPANY LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHYAMMETL] Shyam Metalics and Energy Ltd Reports January 2026 Sales: Increase in Realizations Across Segments</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shyam+Metalics+and+Energy+Ltd&title=Shyam+Metalics+and+Energy+Ltd+Reports+January+2026+Sales%3A+Increase+in+Realizations+Across+Segments&newsId=5a36fe09-39bb-48e0-9423-8afda17b0b6b&token=NWEzNmZlMDktMzli</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a36fe09-39bb-48e0-9423-8afda17b0b6b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:44:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Shyam Metalics and Energy Ltd released its sales performance for January 2026, highlighting a decrease in sales volumes and an increase in realizations across various product segments. The company reported a 5.36% decrease in sales volumes and an 11.43% increase in realizations for stainless steel on a YoY basis. Aluminium foil sales decreased by 1.45%, while realizations increased by 13.51% on a YoY basis. Pellet sales saw a 42.14% increase in sales volumes and a 5.76% increase in realizations on a YoY basis. Speciality alloys sales increased by 7.15% in sales volumes and 1.81% in realizations on a YoY basis.</p><ul><li>Decrease in sales volumes for stainless steel and aluminium foil</li><li>Increase in realizations for stainless steel, aluminium foil, pellets, and speciality alloys</li><li>42.14% increase in pellet sales volumes on a YoY basis</li><li>7.15% increase in speciality alloys sales volumes on a YoY basis</li><li>Implementation of a colour coated plant in Jamuria location, producing color coated sheets</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e9b50b7d-d9f2-49e7-bf6a-7b2488d59ee8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shyam Metalics and Energy Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HAL] HAL Refrains from Commenting on AMCA Construction News Due to Pending DRDO Communication</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Hindustan+Aeronautics+Ltd&title=HAL+Refrains+from+Commenting+on+AMCA+Construction+News+Due+to+Pending+DRDO+Communication&newsId=149cd7db-d73b-474a-af27-56a483d77a07&token=MTQ5Y2Q3ZGItZDcz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">149cd7db-d73b-474a-af27-56a483d77a07</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:44:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Other</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hindustan Aeronautics Ltd (HAL) has refrained from commenting on a recent news article that stated HAL would not be constructing the Advanced Medium Combat Aircraft (AMCA), and that there is a competition between Tata, L&amp;T, and Kalyani. The article appeared on the &apos;www.business-standard.com&apos; website on 4th February, 2026. HAL responded to queries from stock exchanges, stating that they cannot comment on the news as they are yet to receive official communication from DRDO. HAL also mentioned that the impact of this article on the company cannot be assessed until they receive the official communication.</p><ul><li>HAL refrains from commenting on the news about AMCA construction due to pending DRDO communication.</li><li>The news stated that HAL would not be constructing the AMCA, with a competition between Tata, L&amp;T, and Kalyani.</li><li>HAL responded to queries from stock exchanges, stating they cannot comment on the news.</li><li>The impact of this article on the company cannot be assessed until official communication is received from DRDO.</li><li>HAL stated that they are not aware of any information that has not been announced to the exchanges which could explain the movement in trading.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1e0fab58-a3b7-41de-a83e-68c45aadb752.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Hindustan Aeronautics Ltd | Category: Other</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MAWANASUG] Mawana Sugars Ltd to Approve Unaudited Financial Results on 14th February 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MAWANA+SUGARS+LTD.&title=Mawana+Sugars+Ltd+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+on+14th+February+2026&newsId=19212ac6-0629-425c-9b01-f3e45815d41a&token=MTkyMTJhYzYtMDYy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19212ac6-0629-425c-9b01-f3e45815d41a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:43:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mawana Sugars Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 14th February 2026 to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for the Quarter and Nine Months period ended on 31st December 2025. The trading window for dealing in securities of the Company will be closed till 16th February 2026 after the declaration of the results, as per the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015 and the Company&apos;s &apos;Code of Internal Procedures and Conduct for Regulating, Monitoring and Reporting of Trading by Insiders&apos;.</p><ul><li>Mawana Sugars Ltd to consider and approve Unaudited Financial Results on 14th February 2026</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities of the Company to be closed till 16th February 2026 after the declaration of results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a84507f1-686f-4d67-8fae-2fb5a8ea347c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MAWANA SUGARS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DELPHIFX] Delphi World Money’s Corporate Travel Segment Re-Energized, Poised to Be the Growth Engine for the Next Phase</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Delphi+World+Money+Ltd&title=Delphi+World+Money%E2%80%99s+Corporate+Travel+Segment+Re-Energized%2C+Poised+to+Be+the+Growth+Engine+for+the+Next+Phase&newsId=199e68f8-aae1-4e38-92d5-69c57b05f899&token=MTk5ZTY4ZjgtYWFl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">199e68f8-aae1-4e38-92d5-69c57b05f899</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:41:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Delphi World Money, India’s emerging integrated travel solutions company, is re-energizing its Corporate Travel business segment. The segment has been reinvented to consolidate operations, scale efficiently, and capture the immense opportunities in India’s corporate travel ecosystem. The Indian corporate travel market is estimated at over 75,000 crore, growing at 8-10% CAGR. Delphi’s Corporate Travel segment has added 10 new corporate clients and now manages travel for over 500,000 employees. It achieved 20%+ year-on-year growth, processing over 3 million travel transactions across multi-location deployments. The segment is expected to benefit from government reforms under the Union Budget 2026-27. Delphi is positioned to lead India’s enterprise travel market with renewed strength, strategic focus, and unrelenting energy.</p><ul><li>Delphi World Money re-energizing its Corporate Travel business segment</li><li>Segment reinvented to consolidate operations and scale efficiently</li><li>Indian corporate travel market estimated at over 75,000 crore, growing at 8-10% CAGR</li><li>Delphi’s Corporate Travel segment added 10 new corporate clients, managing travel for over 500,000 employees</li><li>Segment achieved 20%+ year-on-year growth, processing over 3 million travel transactions</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e7c26909-502f-4e2a-8df9-5891cd60a6da.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Delphi World Money Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LINCOPH] Lincoln Pharmaceuticals to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results on Feb 12, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LINCOLN+PHARMACEUTICALS+LTD.&title=Lincoln+Pharmaceuticals+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+on+Feb+12%2C+2026&newsId=5acfcbd2-07bb-4e71-8653-62a4125fbaf9&token=NWFjZmNiZDItMDdi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5acfcbd2-07bb-4e71-8653-62a4125fbaf9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Lincoln Pharmaceuticals Ltd has announced a board meeting scheduled for February 12, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results (standalone and consolidated) for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The meeting will be held at the company&apos;s registered office. In compliance with the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, the trading window for securities of the company has been closed from January 01, 2026, and will reopen after the expiry of 48 hours from the time the results become generally available.</p><ul><li>Lincoln Pharmaceuticals Ltd has scheduled a board meeting on February 12, 2026, to approve the unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended on December 31, 2025.</li><li>The trading window for securities of the company has been closed from January 01, 2026, in compliance with the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015.</li><li>The trading window will reopen after the expiry of 48 hours from the time the results become generally available.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/11ccdcc8-0a0b-49e9-aa1e-81edee104cc9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LINCOLN PHARMACEUTICALS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CENTEXT] Century Extrusions Ltd Board Meeting on 11/02/2026 to Approve Q3 Results and Consider Rights Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CENTURY+EXTRUSIONS+LTD.&title=Century+Extrusions+Ltd+Board+Meeting+on+11%2F02%2F2026+to+Approve+Q3+Results+and+Consider+Rights+Issue&newsId=b35b56c9-cde7-459c-850c-6718faba0706&token=YjM1YjU2YzktY2Rl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b35b56c9-cde7-459c-850c-6718faba0706</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Century Extrusions Ltd has announced a Board Meeting scheduled on 11th February 2026. The agenda includes considering and approving the Un-Audited Standalone Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December 2025. The Board will also consider raising funds by way of Rights Issue. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company is closed from 1st January 2026 to 13th February 2026. All Insiders are informed not to enter into any transaction involving the securities of the Company during this period.</p><ul><li>Board Meeting scheduled on 11th February 2026</li><li>Consideration and approval of Un-Audited Standalone Financial Results for Q3 2025</li><li>Consideration of raising funds by way of Rights Issue</li><li>Trading window closed from 1st January 2026 to 13th February 2026</li><li>Insiders informed not to enter into any transaction involving the securities of the Company during the closure of the trading window</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8c870799-5069-4eba-a566-7780145085b4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CENTURY EXTRUSIONS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ALMONDZ] Almondz Global Securities Ltd to Approve Q4 2025 Unaudited Financial Results on Feb 11, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ALMONDZ+GLOBAL+SECURITIES+LTD.&title=Almondz+Global+Securities+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+2025+Unaudited+Financial+Results+on+Feb+11%2C+2026&newsId=535988ad-46cf-4934-8c7d-4fb2e2cb5571&token=NTM1OTg4YWQtNDZj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">535988ad-46cf-4934-8c7d-4fb2e2cb5571</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:32:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Almondz Global Securities Ltd has announced a Board of Directors meeting on February 11, 2026. The agenda includes the consideration and approval of the Unaudited Financial Results (Standalone and Consolidated) for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The notice of the meeting is available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Almondz Global Securities Ltd scheduled a Board of Directors meeting on February 11, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for Q4 2025</li><li>The results will be both Standalone and Consolidated</li><li>The notice of the meeting is available on the company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0c85f0bf-98f6-410e-919b-0e68da98a851.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ALMONDZ GLOBAL SECURITIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ISHWATR] Resignation of Chief Financial Officer and Company Secretary &amp; Compliance Officer at Ishwarshakti Holdings &amp; Traders Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ISHWARSHAKTI+HOLDINGS+%26+TRADERS+LTD.&title=Resignation+of+Chief+Financial+Officer+and+Company+Secretary+%26+Compliance+Officer+at+Ishwarshakti+Holdings+%26+Traders+Ltd&newsId=e9fbb350-ab22-4808-b05d-d20947fcb475&token=ZTlmYmIzNTAtYWIy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9fbb350-ab22-4808-b05d-d20947fcb475</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Auditor</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ishwarshakti Holdings &amp; Traders Ltd has announced the resignation of Mr. Shyamsunder Agarwal as Chief Financial Officer and Ms. Chandni Lohar as Company Secretary &amp; Compliance Officer. The resignations are due to personal reasons and to pursue career opportunities outside the organization. Both will cease to be Key Managerial Personnel and their resignations have been accepted by the Management with a relieving date of February 03, 2026. The company has provided the details required under Regulation 30 read with Schedule III of SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/CFD/PoD2/CIR/P/2023/120 dated July 11, 2023 and SEBI/HO/CFD/PoD2/CIR/P/ 0155 dated November 11, 2024 in Annexure I. The copy of Resignation Letters is attached as Annexure - II &amp; Annexure III.</p><ul><li>Mr. Shyamsunder Agarwal has resigned as Chief Financial Officer of Ishwarshakti Holdings &amp; Traders Ltd.</li><li>Ms. Chandni Lohar has resigned as Company Secretary &amp; Compliance Officer of Ishwarshakti Holdings &amp; Traders Ltd.</li><li>Resignations are due to personal reasons and to pursue career opportunities outside the organization.</li><li>Both will cease to be Key Managerial Personnel.</li><li>Resignations have been accepted by the Management with a relieving date of February 03, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1ce8892f-121f-4939-962a-099f1d39e626.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ISHWARSHAKTI HOLDINGS & TRADERS LTD. | Category: Auditor</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SVCIND] SVC Industries Ltd. to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months of FY2025-26 on Feb 11, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SVC+INDUSTRIES+Ltd&title=SVC+Industries+Ltd.+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+of+FY2025-26+on+Feb+11%2C+2026&newsId=f2f7c930-ed88-478c-adf2-74dafda03375&token=ZjJmN2M5MzAtZWQ4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f2f7c930-ed88-478c-adf2-74dafda03375</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:29:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SVC Industries Ltd. has announced a Board of Directors meeting on February 11, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will take place at OIA House, Andheri (East), Mumbai. In accordance with the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, the trading window for the company&apos;s equity shares will remain closed for designated persons, directors, and their immediate relatives from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the financial results are made public.</p><ul><li>SVC Industries to hold a Board of Directors meeting on February 11, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months of FY2025-26</li><li>The meeting will take place at OIA House, Andheri (East), Mumbai</li><li>Trading window for the company&apos;s equity shares to remain closed from January 1, 2026</li><li>Trading window to reopen 48 hours after the financial results are made public</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4bb37221-6c76-49f1-9f5c-0ca4f656efdb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SVC INDUSTRIES Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>