<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:30:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[RGRL] Retro Green Revolution Ltd Appoints Three New Directors and Shifts Registered Office</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Retro+Green+Revolution+Ltd&title=Retro+Green+Revolution+Ltd+Appoints+Three+New+Directors+and+Shifts+Registered+Office&newsId=05ead4b2-d313-4f9f-ac31-0623ab4c7668&token=MDVlYWQ0YjItZDMx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05ead4b2-d313-4f9f-ac31-0623ab4c7668</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Retro Green Revolution Ltd held a Board Meeting on 224 January 2026, where they approved the appointment of Mrs. Nidhi Bharatbhai Gandhi, Dharmik Mukeshbhai Nagariya, and Ripan Das as additional directors. The Board also took note of the resignation of statutory auditor Mayur Shah &amp; Associates and appointed Shweta Jain &amp; Co LLP as the new statutory auditor. Furthermore, the company decided to shift its registered office to a new address in Ahmedabad, effective from 1st February 2026.</p><ul><li>Retro Green Revolution Ltd appoints three new additional directors.</li><li>The company notes the resignation of statutory auditor Mayur Shah &amp; Associates.</li><li>Shweta Jain &amp; Co LLP appointed as the new statutory auditor.</li><li>The registered office of the company will be shifted to a new address in Ahmedabad.</li><li>All changes to be effective from specified dates.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c47155cd-7575-4ccb-a9b4-f02af319bca6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Retro Green Revolution Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EVERESTO] Everest Organics Ltd: No Requests for Re-lodgement of Physical Shares in January 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=EVEREST+ORGANICS+LTD.&title=Everest+Organics+Ltd%3A+No+Requests+for+Re-lodgement+of+Physical+Shares+in+January+2026&newsId=6ab551b6-4565-4943-8ae2-fb833d1ffbba&token=NmFiNTUxYjYtNDU2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ab551b6-4565-4943-8ae2-fb833d1ffbba</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:29:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Everest Organics Ltd has provided an update on the re-lodgement of transfer requests of physical shares, as per the SEBI Circular dated July 2, 2025. The report, as of January 6, 2026, indicates no requests were received, processed, approved, or rejected during the month. The average time taken for processing requests is not applicable (NA) as there were no requests to process.</p><ul><li>No requests for re-lodgement of physical shares received in January 2026.</li><li>No requests for re-lodgement of physical shares processed in January 2026.</li><li>No requests for re-lodgement of physical shares approved in January 2026.</li><li>No requests for re-lodgement of physical shares rejected in January 2026.</li><li>Not applicable (NA) average time taken for processing of requests in January 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4c8bf649-2ef9-467e-85f9-408c1e9f0d3a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: EVEREST ORGANICS LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VOLTAS] Voltas Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results on January 29, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VOLTAS+LTD.&title=Voltas+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+on+January+29%2C+2026&newsId=1b271bb5-9978-4f3b-8518-0f5ba3dabbbe&token=MWIyNzFiYjUtOTk3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b271bb5-9978-4f3b-8518-0f5ba3dabbbe</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:26:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Voltas Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 29, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The meeting is in compliance with Regulation 29 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The trading window for the company&apos;s equity shares will remain closed from Thursday, 25th December, 2025, and will open 48 hours after the financial results are declared to Stock Exchanges.</p><ul><li>Voltas Ltd to consider and approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December, 2025</li><li>Meeting scheduled on 29th January, 2026</li><li>Compliance with Regulation 29 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Trading window for company’s equity shares to open 48 hours after financial results are declared</li><li>Announcement made available on the company’s website www.voltas.com</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1c3a5c4b-6a90-4181-9f71-e99fe373da9d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VOLTAS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ARIHANT] Arihant Foundations &amp; Housing Ltd Reports 39.7% YoY Growth in Pre-Sales Value for Q3 FY26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ARIHANT+FOUNDATIONS+%26+HOUSING+LTD.-%24&title=Arihant+Foundations+%26+Housing+Ltd+Reports+39.7%25+YoY+Growth+in+Pre-Sales+Value+for+Q3+FY26&newsId=d4b4f286-e3fd-4547-a034-1087e042b49c&token=ZDRiNGYyODYtZTNm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4b4f286-e3fd-4547-a034-1087e042b49c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:24:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Arihant Foundations &amp; Housing Limited, a real estate player in Chennai, has reported a 39.7% year-on-year growth in Pre-Sales Value for the third quarter ended December 30, 2025. The Total Area Sold also increased by 53.6% YoY to 3,26,709 sq. ft. The company&apos;s Pre-Sales Value for 9M FY26 stood at ₹337.9 crore. Collections stood at ₹111.02 crore as on December 31, 2025. Arihant Foundations has been a key player in shaping Chennai&apos;s urban landscapes for four decades, with a developed area of over 20 mn sq.ft across various segments including residential, commercial and senior living.</p><ul><li>Pre-Sales Value for 9M FY26 stood at ₹337.9 crore, up by 39.7% YoY</li><li>Total Area Sold for 9M FY26 aggregated to 3,26,709 sq. ft, up by 53.6% YoY</li><li>Collections stood at ₹111.02 crore as on December 31, 2025</li><li>Arihant Foundations has developed an area of over 20 mn sq.ft across various segments</li><li>Arihant Foundations is known for its quality and trustworthiness in Chennai&apos;s real estate market</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/31bc5388-1cd6-4544-8c0e-64d0a6a306a2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ARIHANT FOUNDATIONS & HOUSING LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IXIGO] Le Travenues Technology Grants 98,944 Stock Options Under ESOS 2013, ESOS 2016, and ESOS 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Le+Travenues+Technology+Ltd&title=Le+Travenues+Technology+Grants+98%2C944+Stock+Options+Under+ESOS+2013%2C+ESOS+2016%2C+and+ESOS+2021&newsId=54d6d06e-8389-4be9-9037-88a0c83ed4fc&token=NTRkNmQwNmUtODM4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54d6d06e-8389-4be9-9037-88a0c83ed4fc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Le Travenues Technology Ltd, symbol IXiGO, has granted 98,944 options under its Employees Stock Option Schemes 2013, 2016, and 2021. The options, granted at an exercise price of ₹93/- per option, will vest over a period of one year to four years in equal annual installments of 25% each. The exercise period for the options is five years from the date of vesting, and in case of resignation, vested options can be exercised within 365 days from the last working day with the Company.</p><ul><li>98,944 options granted under ESOS 2013, ESOS 2016, and ESOS 2021</li><li>Options granted at ₹93/- per option</li><li>Vesting period of one year to four years</li><li>Exercise period of five years from the date of vesting</li><li>Options can be exercised within 365 days from the last working day with the Company in case of resignation</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/db02fb38-a110-4336-aa36-62c7b164a7dc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Le Travenues Technology Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUVEN] Suven Life Sciences Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025 on Jan 29, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SUVEN+LIFE+SCIENCES+LTD.&title=Suven+Life+Sciences+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025+on+Jan+29%2C+2026&newsId=38918342-a4a6-45d0-88e2-7e91b1cd9d32&token=Mzg5MTgzNDItYTRh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">38918342-a4a6-45d0-88e2-7e91b1cd9d32</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:21:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Suven Life Sciences Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 29, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will be held at the company&apos;s registered office in Hyderabad. In accordance with the PIT Code, the trading window for dealing in the company&apos;s equity shares by all designated persons and their relatives has been closed from January 1, 2026, and will remain closed until 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results.</p><ul><li>Suven Life Sciences Ltd to consider and approve un-audited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>Board meeting scheduled on January 29, 2026, at the company&apos;s registered office in Hyderabad.</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the company&apos;s equity shares by all designated persons and their relatives closed from January 1, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0f187ac3-5966-4d10-b7f5-73b7c848f598.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SUVEN LIFE SCIENCES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[3PLAND] 3P Land Holdings Ltd. to Approve Q3 &amp; Nine Months Results on 31st January 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=3P+Land+Holdings+Ltd&title=3P+Land+Holdings+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Results+on+31st+January+2026&newsId=a2d5d66c-8722-4bde-864a-e755503d10cd&token=YTJkNWQ2NmMtODcy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2d5d66c-8722-4bde-864a-e755503d10cd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:19:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>3P Land Holdings Ltd. has scheduled a Board Meeting on 31st January 2026 to consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Statements and the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The Trading Window for dealing in the securities of the Company has been closed for all Designated Persons and their immediate relatives from 15th January 2026 to 274th February 2026.</p><ul><li>3P Land Holdings Ltd. to consider and approve Q3 &amp; nine months results on 31st January 2026</li><li>The meeting will discuss Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Statements for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025</li><li>Trading Window for dealing in the securities of the Company is closed for all Designated Persons and their immediate relatives from 15th January 2026 to 274th February 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/04698867-5253-41fb-9a4b-cdac96e2f47c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: 3P Land Holdings Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ORIENTELEC] Orient Electric Ltd Declares Interim Dividend of 0.75 for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Orient+Electric+Ltd&title=Orient+Electric+Ltd+Declares+Interim+Dividend+of+0.75+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=5c1630b5-b348-4e21-93cb-f094bd00d13f&token=NWMxNjMwYjUtYjM0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c1630b5-b348-4e21-93cb-f094bd00d13f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Orient Electric Ltd, a CKA Birla Group company, announced the outcome of their Board Meeting held on January 22, 2026. The company approved the Un-Audited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, and declared an interim dividend of 0.75 per equity share of face value of 1 each for the financial year 2025-26. The record date for determining the shareholders who will be entitled to the dividend is January 29, 2026.</p><ul><li>Orient Electric Ltd announced their Un-Audited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The company declared an interim dividend of 0.75 per equity share of face value of 1 each for the financial year 2025-26.</li><li>The record date for determining the shareholders who will be entitled to the dividend is January 29, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d03d09b7-40c1-4489-a675-2e1ff23eba53.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Orient Electric Ltd | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAATVIKGL] Saatvik Green Energy&apos;s Subsidiary Secures INR 10.15 Crores Order from Renowned IPP/EPC Player</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Saatvik+Green+Energy+Ltd&title=Saatvik+Green+Energy%27s+Subsidiary+Secures+INR+10.15+Crores+Order+from+Renowned+IPP%2FEPC+Player&newsId=0ebd4d1c-54c2-4449-8af7-7754751eff0f&token=MGViZDRkMWMtNTRj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ebd4d1c-54c2-4449-8af7-7754751eff0f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:19:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Saatvik Green Energy Ltd announced that its material subsidiary, Saatvik Solar Industries Private Limited, has received and accepted an order worth INR 10.15 Crores from a renowned Independent Power producer/EPC Player for the supply of solar PV modules. The order is expected to be executed by February 2026.</p><ul><li>Order worth INR 10.15 Crores from a renowned IPP/EPC Player</li><li>Saatvik Solar Industries Private Limited is the recipient of the order</li><li>The order is for supplying solar PV modules</li><li>The order is expected to be executed by February 2026</li><li>The announcement is in compliance with SEBI Listing Regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0b57e6cb-18cd-40a7-a433-5bf2d792b6c2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Saatvik Green Energy Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IIFL] IIFL Finance Ltd declares Interim Dividend of Rs.4/- per equity share for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IIFL+Finance+Ltd&title=IIFL+Finance+Ltd+declares+Interim+Dividend+of+Rs.4%2F-+per+equity+share+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=74fbc3a9-374a-4b9e-8204-a6dcfb1ff299&token=NzRmYmMzYTktMzc0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74fbc3a9-374a-4b9e-8204-a6dcfb1ff299</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 09:19:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>At its meeting held on January 22, 2026, IIFL Finance Ltd&apos;s Board of Directors considered and approved the Unaudited Consolidated and Standalone Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The Board also declared an interim dividend of Rs.4/- per equity share for the Financial Year 2025-26, fixed the record date as January 29, 2026, and appointed Mr. Kailash Gaonkar as the new Chief Information Security Officer.</p><ul><li>Unaudited Consolidated and Standalone Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025, approved</li><li>Interim Dividend of Rs.4/- per equity share declared for FY 2025-26</li><li>Record date for dividend payment set as January 29, 2026</li><li>Mr. Kailash Gaonkar appointed as the new Chief Information Security Officer</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6b02772f-47f2-45c8-aedf-bd41d46b9825.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IIFL Finance Ltd | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>