<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:43:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[PVVINFRA] PVV Infra Ltd Announces Rights Issue of Equity Shares worth 49.33 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PVV+Infra+Ltd&title=PVV+Infra+Ltd+Announces+Rights+Issue+of+Equity+Shares+worth+49.33+Crores&newsId=5a5e30f6-25f1-461b-b0fb-926a0240b96e&token=NWE1ZTMwZjYtMjVm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a5e30f6-25f1-461b-b0fb-926a0240b96e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>PVV Infra Ltd, a company with a history of name and address changes, has announced a Rights Issue of 9,86,64,284 Partly paid-up Equity Shares for an aggregate amount not exceeding 49,33,21,422/-. The offer is on a rights basis to the eligible shareholders of the Company in the ratio of 6 (Six) Rights Equity Shares for every 07 (Seven) fully paid-up Equity Shares held by eligible shareholders as on the Record Date i.e. Thursday, February 05, 2026. The Board of Directors of the Company has approved the Letter of Offer on January 30, 2026.</p><ul><li>PVV Infra Ltd announces a Rights Issue of Equity Shares worth 49.33 Crores.</li><li>The offer is on a rights basis to the eligible shareholders in the ratio of 6 (Six) Rights Equity Shares for every 07 (Seven) fully paid-up Equity Shares.</li><li>The Record Date for the offer is Thursday, February 05, 2026.</li><li>The Board of Directors of the Company has approved the Letter of Offer on January 30, 2026.</li><li>The Rights Equity Shares are proposed to be listed on BSE Limited.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/91b34b54-07e2-4b83-b3b2-8c96fb40caeb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PVV Infra Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TMCV] Tata Motors Reports 29.9% YoY Growth in January 2026 Sales</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Tata+Motors+Ltd&title=Tata+Motors+Reports+29.9%25+YoY+Growth+in+January+2026+Sales&newsId=639d4fdd-9181-4fa0-96a5-c275d3dfd38f&token=NjM5ZDRmZGQtOTE4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">639d4fdd-9181-4fa0-96a5-c275d3dfd38f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Tata Motors Limited has reported a 29.9% Year-over-Year (YoY) growth in total sales for January 2026. The company sold 41,549 units in January 2026 compared to 31,988 units in January 2025. The growth was seen across various categories including HCV Trucks, ILMCV Trucks, Passenger Carriers, SCV cargo, and pickup. Domestic sales increased by 29.1% and international business grew by 42.0%. The company&apos;s domestic sales of MH&amp;ICV stood at 19,676 units in January 2026, a 29.5% YoY growth.</p><ul><li>Tata Motors reports 29.9% YoY growth in total sales for January 2026</li><li>Domestic sales increased by 29.1% and international business grew by 42.0%</li><li>Domestic sales of MH&amp;ICV stood at 19,676 units in January 2026, a 29.5% YoY growth</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2a5d443e-6b3a-4e37-9aa6-fde296a55059.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Tata Motors Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[COALINDIA] Coal India Ltd Reports Jan&apos;26 Production and Offtake Data</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=COAL+INDIA+LTD.&title=Coal+India+Ltd+Reports+Jan%2726+Production+and+Offtake+Data&newsId=ec7d358a-b466-4b30-9d29-ffe6fe22e3bb&token=ZWM3ZDM1OGEtYjQ2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ec7d358a-b466-4b30-9d29-ffe6fe22e3bb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Coal India Ltd (CIL) has released the provisional production and off-take performance of CIL and its subsidiary companies for the month of January 2026 and for the period from April 2025 to January 2026. This is in accordance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations 2015.</p><ul><li>Coal production for January 2026 and April 2025 - January 2026 are provided.</li><li>Offtake figures for January 2026 and April 2025 - January 2026 are also included.</li><li>The report is provisional and for information and record purposes.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/75a7435d-48aa-4830-ab35-5848143d14e7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: COAL INDIA LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ALPHALOGIC] Alphalogic Techsys Ltd to Consider and Approve Un-Audited Financials for Q4 2025 in Board Meeting on 07/02/2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Alphalogic+Techsys+Ltd&title=Alphalogic+Techsys+Ltd+to+Consider+and+Approve+Un-Audited+Financials+for+Q4+2025+in+Board+Meeting+on+07%2F02%2F2026&newsId=486f328f-4c7b-48db-a531-322a109854d6&token=NDg2ZjMyOGYtNGM3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">486f328f-4c7b-48db-a531-322a109854d6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Alphalogic Techsys Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 07/02/2026 to consider and approve the un-audited financials (standalone and consolidated) for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The meeting will also discuss other agenda items. In accordance with the Company&apos;s Code of Conduct and SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulation 2015, the trading window for dealing in the shares of the company for specified persons will be closed from the time of issue of this intimation until 48 hours after the declaration of the outcome of the Board Meeting.</p><ul><li>Alphalogic Techsys Ltd to consider and approve un-audited financials for Q4 2025</li><li>Board Meeting scheduled for 07/02/2026</li><li>Trading window for specified persons to be closed from the time of intimation until 48 hours after the Board Meeting</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3b99404a-ff1c-4d34-a708-77714756eae8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Alphalogic Techsys Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JHS] JHS Svendgaard Laboratories Approves Allotment of 18,01,801 Equity Shares at Rs. 27.75 Each</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JHS+SVENDGAARD+LABORATORIES+LTD.&title=JHS+Svendgaard+Laboratories+Approves+Allotment+of+18%2C01%2C801+Equity+Shares+at+Rs.+27.75+Each&newsId=f22da8c0-d8fe-4cd6-87e1-369c99923a9a&token=ZjIyZGE4YzAtZDhm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f22da8c0-d8fe-4cd6-87e1-369c99923a9a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 05:31:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>JHS Svendgaard Laboratories Ltd. approved the allotment of 18,01,801 equity shares at an issue price of Rs. 27.75 through conversion of warrants. The warrants were issued at an Issue Price of Rs. 27.75/-each to the respective warrant holders belonging to the Non-Promoter Group category. The new equity shares so allotted, shall rank pari-passu with the existing equity shares of the Company. The Paid-up Equity Share Capital of the Company stands increased to Rs. 87,40,57,670/- divided into 8,74,05,767 Equity Shares of face value of Rs. 10/- each.</p><ul><li>Allotment of 18,01,801 equity shares at an issue price of Rs. 27.75 each</li><li>Conversion of 18,01,801 warrants issued at an Issue Price of Rs. 27.75/-each</li><li>Increase in Paid-up Equity Share Capital to Rs. 87,40,57,670/-</li><li>8,74,05,767 Equity Shares of face value of Rs. 10/- each</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/286ca7fb-ffa4-4dd0-8524-c0c7185d0aea.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JHS SVENDGAARD LABORATORIES LTD. | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DIGILOGIC] Digilogic Systems Ltd Repays Indian Bank Term Loan of Rs. 8.42 Crores Using IPO Proceeds</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Digilogic+Systems+Ltd&title=Digilogic+Systems+Ltd+Repays+Indian+Bank+Term+Loan+of+Rs.+8.42+Crores+Using+IPO+Proceeds&newsId=5ce9f9cd-f53f-4dd2-8da1-42a44c7e1aae&token=NWNlOWY5Y2QtZjUz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ce9f9cd-f53f-4dd2-8da1-42a44c7e1aae</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 05:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Digilogic Systems Ltd has fully repaid its outstanding Term Loan facility taken for Project Udaan from Indian Bank on 31.01.2026, utilizing the proceeds from the Company’s recent Initial Public Offering (IPO). The total amount outstanding in this Term Loan was Rs. 8.42 Cr. This was repaid through a combination of Rs. 8 Cr from IPO Proceeds and the balance Rs. 0.42 Cr from Internal Accruals. The prepayment aligns with the stated objectives of the IPO. Project Udaan is on track for completion by end of FY28. The full repayment significantly reduces the company&apos;s debt and financing costs, freeing up capital that will be strategically deployed to accelerate core growth initiatives in the defence and aerospace sectors. The company is confident of achieving 20-25% growth in topline, 30-35% growth in EBITDA, and 40-45% growth in PAT in FY26.</p><ul><li>Digilogic Systems Ltd repays Indian Bank Term Loan of Rs. 8.42 Crores using IPO proceeds</li><li>The repayment aligns with the objectives of the IPO</li><li>The full repayment significantly reduces the company&apos;s debt and financing costs</li><li>The company is on track to achieve 20-25% growth in topline, 30-35% growth in EBITDA, and 40-45% growth in PAT in FY26</li><li>Project Udaan is on track for completion by end of FY28</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/55b24dae-6750-4c7f-90b5-ab6bdafe6bee.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Digilogic Systems Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BPCL] Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd: Changes in Management and Promotions</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BHARAT+PETROLEUM+CORPORATION+LTD.&title=Bharat+Petroleum+Corporation+Ltd%3A+Changes+in+Management+and+Promotions&newsId=f5748b59-cefe-4926-b2a3-4f80a4ff55d1&token=ZjU3NDhiNTktY2Vm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f5748b59-cefe-4926-b2a3-4f80a4ff55d1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 05:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd. has announced changes in its management. Shri Anilkumar P., Executive Director I/C (Biofuels), has superannuated from the services of the Company on 31st January 2026. The Company has promoted three employees as Executive Director (ED) - Shri Dhanapal S, Shri Manoj K, and Shri Mohit Bhatia. Shri Dhanapal S has a B.E Civil Engineering degree and has handled various roles in HRS, LPG, and Quality Control. Shri Manoj K has a B. Tech Electrical Engineering degree and has handled various roles in LPG and E&amp;P. Shri Mohit Bhatia has a P.G Diploma in Executive Management Program and has handled various roles in E&amp;P, Retail &amp; Gas BU.</p><ul><li>Shri Anilkumar P., Executive Director I/C (Biofuels) has superannuated from the services of the Company.</li><li>Shri Dhanapal S, Shri Manoj K, and Shri Mohit Bhatia have been promoted as Executive Director (ED).</li><li>Shri Dhanapal S has a B.E Civil Engineering degree and has handled various roles in HRS, LPG, and Quality Control.</li><li>Shri Manoj K has a B. Tech Electrical Engineering degree and has handled various roles in LPG and E&amp;P.</li><li>Shri Mohit Bhatia has a P.G Diploma in Executive Management Program and has handled various roles in E&amp;P, Retail &amp; Gas BU.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a33da7d4-50b1-4846-9200-0aad7c53d53b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BHARAT PETROLEUM CORPORATION LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[M&amp;M] Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Reports 24% Growth in Total Vehicle Sales in January 2026, Tractor Sales Surge 46%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MAHINDRA+%26+MAHINDRA+LTD.&title=Mahindra+%26+Mahindra+Reports+24%25+Growth+in+Total+Vehicle+Sales+in+January+2026%2C+Tractor+Sales+Surge+46%25&newsId=8079f1c0-7083-42e0-bdce-b0c3aad18b0a&token=ODA3OWYxYzAtNzA4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8079f1c0-7083-42e0-bdce-b0c3aad18b0a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 05:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Ltd. (M&amp;M Ltd.), one of India’s leading automotive companies, announced that its overall auto sales for the month of January 2026 stood at 104,309 vehicles, a growth of 24% including exports. In the Utility Vehicles segment, Mahindra sold 63,510 vehicles in the domestic market, a growth of 25% and overall, 104,309 vehicles, including exports. The domestic sales for Commercial Vehicles stood at 27,656, a growth of 22%. The Farm Equipment Business (FEB) of Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Ltd. reported a robust 46% year-on-year growth in domestic tractor sales in January 2026, with total tractor sales (Domestic + Exports) during the month at 40,643 units.</p><ul><li>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra reports 24% growth in total vehicle sales in January 2026</li><li>Domestic sales of utility vehicles increase by 25%</li><li>Farm Equipment Business (FEB) reports 46% growth in domestic tractor sales in January 2026</li><li>Total tractor sales (Domestic + Exports) at 40,643 units in January 2026</li><li>Exports of tractors grow by 72%</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/913783d3-e880-4db9-ae72-30eac408a4d8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MAHINDRA & MAHINDRA LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VSTTILLERS] VST Tillers Tractors Ltd. Reports January-2026 Sales Quantity</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=V.S.T.TILLERS+TRACTORS+LTD.-%24&title=VST+Tillers+Tractors+Ltd.+Reports+January-2026+Sales+Quantity&newsId=8d2ce626-65c3-49d1-9af6-a403909b273a&token=OGQyY2U2MjYtNjVj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d2ce626-65c3-49d1-9af6-a403909b273a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 05:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>VST Tillers Tractors Ltd. has released its monthly business updates for the period ended January-2026. The sales quantity for this period shows a total of 31432 units for power tillers and tractors combined. Please note that these figures are not audited and may vary once audited.</p><ul><li>VST Tillers Tractors Ltd. reports January-2026 sales quantity</li><li>Total sales for power tillers and tractors is 31432 units</li><li>Figures are not audited and may vary once audited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2aba890d-2d1d-4f45-b5a1-28f0c3e02a00.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: V.S.T.TILLERS TRACTORS LTD.-$ | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GTIL] Gabion Technologies India Ltd Secures Multiple Work Orders Totaling INR 6.35 Crores in January</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Gabion+Technologies+India+Ltd&title=Gabion+Technologies+India+Ltd+Secures+Multiple+Work+Orders+Totaling+INR+6.35+Crores+in+January&newsId=f869f793-7255-42f6-bd2a-5f8edffb87bf&token=Zjg2OWY3OTMtNzI1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f869f793-7255-42f6-bd2a-5f8edffb87bf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 05:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Gabion Technologies India Ltd, a company listed on the BSE SME Exchange, has disclosed multiple work orders received during the week ended January 31, 2026. The total value of these orders, inclusive of GST, amounts to approximately INR 6,35,35,352.60. The orders are for the supply, design, and installation of slope protection systems and allied infrastructure solutions. The execution period for these orders varies as per the respective contract or Letter of Award terms. The company also received a Notice of No Objection from Larsen &amp; Toubro Limited for the supply and use of Wire Mesh for slope protection works under the Mumbai-Ahmedabad High Speed Rail (MAHSR) Project.</p><ul><li>Gabion Technologies India Ltd received multiple work orders during the week ended January 31, 2026.</li><li>The total value of the orders is approximately INR 6,35,35,352.60, inclusive of GST.</li><li>The orders are for the supply, design, and installation of slope protection systems and allied infrastructure solutions.</li><li>The execution period for these orders varies as per the respective contract or Letter of Award terms.</li><li>The company also received a Notice of No Objection from Larsen &amp; Toubro Limited for the supply and use of Wire Mesh for slope protection works under the Mumbai-Ahmedabad High Speed Rail (MAHSR) Project.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/917ad272-4caa-445d-9a9e-399f2c9ae295.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Gabion Technologies India Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>