<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:22:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[RUDRAGAS] Rudra Gas Enterprise Ltd Signs MoU with Gujarat Government for a 330 Crore Biogas Project</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Rudra+Gas+Enterprise+Ltd&title=Rudra+Gas+Enterprise+Ltd+Signs+MoU+with+Gujarat+Government+for+a+330+Crore+Biogas+Project&newsId=16e6503a-3d67-4f84-ba1e-52362e140e59&token=MTZlNjUwM2EtM2Q2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">16e6503a-3d67-4f84-ba1e-52362e140e59</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:21:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Rudra Gas Enterprise Ltd has entered into a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with the Government of Gujarat for the proposed establishment of a Biogas Project in the State of Gujarat. The proposed investment is 330 Crore and the project is expected to commence in the year 2027. The Government of Gujarat will facilitate the company in obtaining necessary permissions/registrations/approvals/clearances from concerned departments as per applicable policies, rules and regulations. The project is expected to generate approximately 125 jobs.</p><ul><li>Rudra Gas Enterprise Ltd has signed an MoU with the Government of Gujarat</li><li>The project is a Biogas Project with a proposed investment of 330 Crore</li><li>The project is expected to commence in the year 2027</li><li>The Government of Gujarat will facilitate necessary permissions/registrations/approvals/clearances</li><li>The project is expected to generate approximately 125 jobs</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8346cf4b-3938-41a3-a00f-e757c62874de.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Rudra Gas Enterprise Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SSLFINANCE] Popees Cares Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Consider Change of Name</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ARCHANA+SOFTWARE+LTD.&title=Popees+Cares+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Consider+Change+of+Name&newsId=21f2501b-ef46-4ef6-a22a-c22c10a5ba80&token=MjFmMjUwMWItZWY0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21f2501b-ef46-4ef6-a22a-c22c10a5ba80</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Popees Cares Ltd has informed the BSE that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on 15/01/2026. The agenda includes the consideration and approval of a change of name for the company. The meeting is set to take place at the company&apos;s registered office at 3.00 p.m.</p><ul><li>Popees Cares Ltd has scheduled a Board meeting for 15/01/2026</li><li>The agenda includes the consideration of a change of name for the company</li><li>The meeting will be held at the company&apos;s registered office</li><li>The meeting is set to start at 3.00 p.m.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ca51242c-3cea-4160-a05a-4404f3b0b379.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ARCHANA SOFTWARE LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FSL] Sad Demise of Mr. Sunil Mitra, Independent Director of Firstsource Solutions Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=FIRSTSOURCE+SOLUTIONS+LTD.&title=Sad+Demise+of+Mr.+Sunil+Mitra%2C+Independent+Director+of+Firstsource+Solutions+Ltd&newsId=5db3ec67-28cd-4f50-84b4-274a96036a8f&token=NWRiM2VjNjctMjhj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5db3ec67-28cd-4f50-84b4-274a96036a8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Firstsource Solutions Ltd regretfully announces the demise of their Independent Director, Mr. Sunil Mitra (DIN: 00113473) on Monday, 12th January, 2026. During his tenure, the company greatly benefited from his vast knowledge and experience. The unexpected loss will be deeply felt by the entire Firstsource Solutions team, who express their condolences to Mr. Mitra&apos;s family.</p><ul><li>Demise of Independent Director Mr. Sunil Mitra</li><li>Beneficial contribution to the company during his tenure</li><li>Deep sympathy, sorrow, and condolences expressed by the board and employees</li><li>Mr. Mitra&apos;s demise details provided as per SEBI LODR and SEBI Master circular requirements</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ac14efb0-47d0-43da-a3a6-2070bac85883.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: FIRSTSOURCE SOLUTIONS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CESC] Sad Demise of Mr. Sunil Mitra, Independent Director of CESC Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CESC+LTD.&title=Sad+Demise+of+Mr.+Sunil+Mitra%2C+Independent+Director+of+CESC+Ltd&newsId=e7cd4945-bf7a-4c42-b8da-e14ad6316649&token=ZTdjZDQ5NDUtYmY3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e7cd4945-bf7a-4c42-b8da-e14ad6316649</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:20:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>CESC Ltd has announced the demise of Mr. Sunil Mitra, an Independent Director of the company. Mr. Mitra was a valuable member of the board, contributing to the company with his vast knowledge and experience. His unexpected demise will be a significant loss to the company. The company expresses its deep sympathy, sorrow, and condolences to his family.</p><ul><li>Mr. Sunil Mitra, an Independent Director of CESC Ltd, has passed away.</li><li>Mitra&apos;s contributions and knowledge were highly beneficial to the company during his tenure.</li><li>The company considers Mitra&apos;s demise an irreparable loss.</li><li>Deep sympathy, sorrow, and condolences are expressed to his family by the company and its employees.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/919b7e0d-fbe7-4285-a45e-2ac5e602f90a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CESC LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FRSHTRP*] Puretrop Fruits Ltd. Approves Q3 &amp; Nine Months Results, Appoints New CEO, and Announces Buyback of Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=FRESHTROP+FRUITS+LTD.&title=Puretrop+Fruits+Ltd.+Approves+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Results%2C+Appoints+New+CEO%2C+and+Announces+Buyback+of+Equity+Shares&newsId=d570ca82-2f02-4f3b-bdac-c8b211df444a&token=ZDU3MGNhODItMmYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d570ca82-2f02-4f3b-bdac-c8b211df444a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Puretrop Fruits Ltd. has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31-12-2025. The board approved the results and appointed Ms. Dipti Ashok Motiani as the Chief Executive Officer (CEO) subject to shareholder&apos;s approval. The board also approved the resignation of Ms. Preeti Jaiswar as Company Secretary and the appointment of Mrs. Vanishika Lunia as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer. Additionally, the board announced a buyback of up to 11,00,000 (Eleven Lakhs) fully paid-up equity shares for an amount not exceeding INR 22,00,00,000. The buyback is subject to approval by shareholders and other regulatory approvals.</p><ul><li>Puretrop Fruits Ltd. announces unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended on 31-12-2025</li><li>Ms. Dipti Ashok Motiani appointed as CEO subject to shareholder&apos;s approval</li><li>Resignation of Ms. Preeti Jaiswar as Company Secretary approved</li><li>Appointment of Mrs. Vanishika Lunia as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer approved</li><li>Buyback of up to 11,00,000 equity shares announced</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/83a01051-097a-46d9-a55f-e86253d228ec.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: FRESHTROP FRUITS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TMB] Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd to Approve Q4 Results on Feb 4, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Tamilnad+Mercantile+Bank+Ltd&title=Tamilnad+Mercantile+Bank+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+Results+on+Feb+4%2C+2026&newsId=8fbc085a-3ef3-4b10-8e01-e8aede4bfa28&token=OGZiYzA4NWEtM2Vm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8fbc085a-3ef3-4b10-8e01-e8aede4bfa28</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:14:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 4, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The meeting is scheduled in accordance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The trading window for dealing in securities of the Bank will be closed from January 1, 2026, to February 6, 2026, for all designated persons and their relatives, as well as for connected persons.</p><ul><li>Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd to consider and approve Q4 results for 2025</li><li>Meeting scheduled on February 4, 2026, in line with SEBI regulations</li><li>Trading window closed from January 1, 2026, to February 6, 2026, for designated persons, their relatives, and connected persons</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d261774e-2930-463e-bcd4-ce533575b722.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Tamilnad Mercantile Bank Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MGEL] Mangalam Global Enterprise Limited Incorporates Wholly-Owned Subsidiary &apos;Mangalam Global General Trading FZE&apos;</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Mangalam+Global+Enterprise+Ltd&title=Mangalam+Global+Enterprise+Limited+Incorporates+Wholly-Owned+Subsidiary+%27Mangalam+Global+General+Trading+FZE%27&newsId=32210a1c-9e11-4318-8b2a-2a1825bec534&token=MzIyMTBhMWMtOWUx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32210a1c-9e11-4318-8b2a-2a1825bec534</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mangalam Global Enterprise Limited has informed the exchange about the incorporation of &apos;Mangalam Global General Trading FZE&apos; as a wholly-owned subsidiary. This is in continuation of their earlier intimation letter regarding the outcome of the Board Meeting. The subsidiary was initially proposed to be named &apos;Mangalam Global Dubai LLP&apos;, but was later changed to its current name. The subsidiary is based in Dubai and is expected to carry on the business of General Trading. The company has provided all the necessary details as required under Regulation 30 of the Listing Regulations and the disclosures are available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Incorporation of a wholly-owned subsidiary &apos;Mangalam Global General Trading FZE&apos;</li><li>Subsidiary is based in Dubai and will carry on the business of General Trading</li><li>Earlier proposed name was &apos;Mangalam Global Dubai LLP&apos;</li><li>Company has provided all necessary details as required under Regulation 30 of the Listing Regulations</li><li>Disclosures are available on the company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/347a9ca0-71a3-41a4-bf2e-bbba44dc28bb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Mangalam Global Enterprise Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAVFI] Savani Financials Ltd. Approves 12.75% Non-Convertible Debenture Issuance of Rs. 2 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SAVANI+FINANCIALS+LTD.&title=Savani+Financials+Ltd.+Approves+12.75%25+Non-Convertible+Debenture+Issuance+of+Rs.+2+Crores&newsId=c6360e5f-ce23-4cac-a88e-d7798f6f9b9a&token=YzYzNjBlNWYtY2Uy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c6360e5f-ce23-4cac-a88e-d7798f6f9b9a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Savani Financials Ltd. held a Capital and Fundraising Committee Meeting on January 12, 2025, during which the Members considered and approved the issuance of 2000 12.75% Secured, Un-listed and Un-rated Non-Convertible Debentures. The total issue size is Rs. 2,00,00,000 (Rupees Two Crores) with a face value of Rs. 10,000/- each (Rupees Ten Thousand only) and a 3-year maturity period. Beacon Trusteeship Limited has been appointed as the Debenture Trustee for this purpose.</p><ul><li>Savani Financials Ltd. approved the issuance of 12.75% Secured, Un-listed and Un-rated Non-Convertible Debentures</li><li>The total issue size is Rs. 2,00,00,000 with a face value of Rs. 10,000/- each</li><li>The debentures have a 3-year maturity period</li><li>Beacon Trusteeship Limited appointed as the Debenture Trustee</li><li>Capital and Fundraising Committee Meeting held on January 12, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d43d047c-5ca8-498f-b6e2-747412975976.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SAVANI FINANCIALS LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADCINDIA] Amphenol Corporation Completes Acquisition of CommScope&apos;s CCS Business, Indirectly Gaining Control Over ADC India Communications Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADC+India+Communications+Limited-%24&title=Amphenol+Corporation+Completes+Acquisition+of+CommScope%27s+CCS+Business%2C+Indirectly+Gaining+Control+Over+ADC+India+Communications+Ltd&newsId=4b0ddc57-3eef-41a0-af6f-54b166ef8f11&token=NGIwZGRjNTctM2Vl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4b0ddc57-3eef-41a0-af6f-54b166ef8f11</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:01:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Amphenol Corporation has completed the acquisition of CommScope&apos;s Connectivity and Cable Solutions (CCS) business. This acquisition includes the purchase of 100% equity interests of CommScope Technologies LLC (CST), which holds 4.54% of the voting share capital of ADC India Communications Limited. CommsScope Connectivity LLC, a wholly owned subsidiary of CST and the &apos;promoter&apos; of ADC India Communications Limited, holds 67.49% of the voting share capital of the company. This acquisition results in an indirect acquisition of the right to direct the exercise of 72.02% of the voting rights in and control over ADC India Communications Ltd by Amphenol Corporation, directly or indirectly through one or more of its subsidiaries.</p><ul><li>Amphenol Corporation completes acquisition of CommScope&apos;s CCS business</li><li>Includes purchase of 100% equity interests of CommScope Technologies LLC (CST)</li><li>CST holds 4.54% of the voting share capital of ADC India Communications Limited</li><li>Indirect acquisition of the right to direct the exercise of 72.02% of the voting rights in and control over ADC India Communications Ltd by Amphenol Corporation</li><li>CommsScope Connectivity LLC, a wholly owned subsidiary of CST and the &apos;promoter&apos; of ADC India Communications Limited, holds 67.49% of the voting share capital of the company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bb0f7680-13d4-4470-adda-781640ebade1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADC India Communications Limited-$ | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PETPLST] Pet Plastics Ltd. Board Meeting on 20/01/2026 to Approve CFO&apos;s Remuneration, Appoint Authorised Person, and Open New Bank Accounts</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PET+PLASTICS+LTD.&title=Pet+Plastics+Ltd.+Board+Meeting+on+20%2F01%2F2026+to+Approve+CFO%27s+Remuneration%2C+Appoint+Authorised+Person%2C+and+Open+New+Bank+Accounts&newsId=121f06cd-43f3-4ee1-98df-70ac0e74d2a5&token=MTIxZjA2Y2QtNDNm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">121f06cd-43f3-4ee1-98df-70ac0e74d2a5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 15:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pet Plastics Ltd. has announced a Board Meeting scheduled for 20th January 2026, at 12:00 PM, at Signature Business Park, Mumbai. The agenda includes considerations such as the remuneration of the Chief Financial Officer, appointment of an authorised person for business agreements during FY 2025-26, and the opening of new current accounts in various banks. The company encourages stakeholders to acknowledge the receipt of this notice.</p><ul><li>Pet Plastics Ltd. to consider and approve CFO&apos;s remuneration</li><li>Authorised person appointment for FY 2025-26 business agreements</li><li>Opening of new current accounts in various banks</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/506b8010-2ca3-452c-9e9a-0292450224bd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PET PLASTICS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>