<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:27:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[GCSL] Gretex Corporate Services Ltd Approves Allotment of 94,459 Equity Shares Upon Warrant Conversion</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Gretex+Corporate+Services+Ltd&title=Gretex+Corporate+Services+Ltd+Approves+Allotment+of+94%2C459+Equity+Shares+Upon+Warrant+Conversion&newsId=3bbbb2a5-a214-4077-b2bc-720251d17fb1&token=M2JiYmIyYTUtYTIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3bbbb2a5-a214-4077-b2bc-720251d17fb1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gretex Corporate Services Ltd announced the allotment of 94,459 equity shares at an issue price of Rs. 379/- (including premium of Rs. 369/-) fully paid-up upon exercising the option available with warrant holder to convert 94,459 Equity Warrants into Equity Shares. The allottee is also entitled to 85,013 bonus equity shares, which shall be released from the demat suspense account and credited to the allottee’s demat account simultaneously with the allotment of equity shares arising from such conversion.</p><ul><li>Gretex Corporate Services Ltd approved the allotment of 94,459 equity shares upon warrant conversion.</li><li>The allotment is at an issue price of Rs. 379/- (including premium of Rs. 369/-).</li><li>The allottee is also entitled to 85,013 bonus equity shares.</li><li>The equity shares allotted on exercise of conversion of Warrants shall rank pari passu in all respects with the existing equity shares of the Company.</li><li>The details of the allotment are provided as per SEBI regulations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/af04745d-87fd-4095-9813-7343ff72d272.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Gretex Corporate Services Ltd | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TREJHARA] Trejhara Solutions Ltd Revises Valuation Report for Preferential Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Trejhara+Solutions+Ltd&title=Trejhara+Solutions+Ltd+Revises+Valuation+Report+for+Preferential+Issue&newsId=294cac5b-cfb3-4577-91da-d6288449ea97&token=Mjk0Y2FjNWItY2Zi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">294cac5b-cfb3-4577-91da-d6288449ea97</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:51:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Trejhara Solutions Ltd has revised its Valuation Report in relation to a proposed preferential issue of Convertible Warrants and Equity Shares. The revision was made after deliberations with the Stock Exchange, with the main change being the removal of the explanation relating to the non-adoption of the Discounted Cash Flow (DCF) method. The Company confirms that all other contents, assumptions, methodologies, and conclusions, including the price arrived at in the Valuation Report, remain unchanged.</p><ul><li>Trejhara Solutions Ltd revises Valuation Report for preferential issue of Convertible Warrants and Equity Shares.</li><li>Revision made after deliberations with the Stock Exchange.</li><li>Explanation relating to non-adoption of DCF method removed.</li><li>All other contents, assumptions, methodologies, and conclusions remain unchanged.</li><li>Price arrived at in the Valuation Report remains the same.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e50e1ea0-3a71-4adf-9cc9-6afa1d7c224a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Trejhara Solutions Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WAKEFIT] Wakefit Innovations Ltd Changes Corporate Identification Number to &apos;L52590KA2016PLC086582&apos;</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Wakefit+Innovations+Ltd&title=Wakefit+Innovations+Ltd+Changes+Corporate+Identification+Number+to+%27L52590KA2016PLC086582%27&newsId=d39b9880-f8f9-4025-a057-85a8bff6ead1&token=ZDM5Yjk4ODAtZjhm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d39b9880-f8f9-4025-a057-85a8bff6ead1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:11:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Wakefit Innovations Limited has announced a change in its Corporate Identification Number (CIN) from &apos;U52590KA2016PLC086582&apos; to &apos;L52590KA2016PLC086582&apos;. This change comes after the listing of the company&apos;s equity shares on BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange of India Limited. The new CIN has been updated by the Ministry of Corporate Affairs. The company has also mentioned that this information is available on their website.</p><ul><li>Wakefit Innovations Ltd changes its Corporate Identification Number to &apos;L52590KA2016PLC086582&apos;</li><li>Change comes after the listing of equity shares on BSE and NSE</li><li>Ministry of Corporate Affairs has updated the new CIN</li><li>Information available on the company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a0114c9e-3314-41cf-a2b3-3d09118f142e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Wakefit Innovations Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HATSUN] Hatsun Agro Product CFO Inadvertently Shares Draft Financial Statements on WhatsApp</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HATSUN+AGRO+PRODUCT+LTD.&title=Hatsun+Agro+Product+CFO+Inadvertently+Shares+Draft+Financial+Statements+on+WhatsApp&newsId=410ecae0-ee31-43bd-8f51-71e1b465d16b&token=NDEwZWNhZTAtZWUz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">410ecae0-ee31-43bd-8f51-71e1b465d16b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hatsun Agro Product Limited, a listed company, reported an incident where its Chief Financial Officer (CFO) inadvertently uploaded draft financial statements of the quarter ended 31 December 2025 to his personal WhatsApp status. This action may have disclosed Unpublished Price Sensitive Information (UPSI) of the company to around 19 people in his contact list, including some insiders. The CFO deleted the status within an hour of posting. The company, upon learning about the incident, informed the stock exchanges, added the exposed individuals to the Structured Digital Database (SDD), closed the trading window, and froze their PANs at the NSDL Issuer Services Portal. An Insider Trading Investigation Committee was constituted to investigate the issue. A caution letter was issued to the CFO, advising greater care and vigilance in handling such information.</p><ul><li>Hatsun Agro Product CFO inadvertently uploads draft financial statements on WhatsApp</li><li>UPSI may have been disclosed to around 19 people, including insiders</li><li>Company informs stock exchanges, adds exposed individuals to SDD, closes trading window, and freezes their PANs</li><li>Insider Trading Investigation Committee constituted to investigate the issue</li><li>Caution letter issued to the CFO for greater care and vigilance</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f2917561-97fd-4f89-a9c2-b5b3b2283b86.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HATSUN AGRO PRODUCT LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ATIL] Apollo Techno Industries Ltd to Approve Half-Yearly Unaudited Standalone Financial Results on Jan 19, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Apollo+Techno+Industries+Ltd&title=Apollo+Techno+Industries+Ltd+to+Approve+Half-Yearly+Unaudited+Standalone+Financial+Results+on+Jan+19%2C+2026&newsId=27746e40-6e19-45e3-8ca3-db311672f37d&token=Mjc3NDZlNDAtNmUx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27746e40-6e19-45e3-8ca3-db311672f37d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Apollo Techno Industries Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 19, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone Financial Results for the Half Year ended 30th September, 2025. The meeting is scheduled in accordance with Regulation 29 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The company also announced that in compliance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015 and the Company&apos;s Code of Conduct, the Trading Window closure period will end 48 hours after the results of the Company are made public.</p><ul><li>Apollo Techno Industries Ltd to consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone Financial Results for the Half Year ended 30th September, 2025 on January 19, 2026.</li><li>The meeting is scheduled in accordance with Regulation 29 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li><li>The company announced compliance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015 and the Company&apos;s Code of Conduct.</li><li>The Trading Window closure period will end 48 hours after the results of the Company are made public.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/241184ee-8a0b-403c-a442-0d36d90bc325.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Apollo Techno Industries Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HATHWAYB] Hathway Bhawani Cabletel &amp; Datacom Ltd Announces Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HATHWAY+BHAWANI+CABLETEL+%26+DATACOM+LTD.&title=Hathway+Bhawani+Cabletel+%26+Datacom+Ltd+Announces+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=1ff48eb2-85b1-4a6b-8069-1e342490e415&token=MWZmNDhlYjItODVi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1ff48eb2-85b1-4a6b-8069-1e342490e415</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:20:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hathway Bhawani Cabletel &amp; Datacom Ltd has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The results were reviewed and approved by the Audit Committee and the Board of Directors in their respective meetings. The company&apos;s total income for the quarter is Rs. 18.37 lakhs and for the nine months is Rs. 179.60 lakhs. The profit before tax for the quarter is Rs. 5.68 lakhs and for the nine months is Rs. 6.88 lakhs. The net profit for the quarter is Rs. 4.33 lakhs and for the nine months is Rs. 4.10 lakhs. The company has not made any provision for the license fees demanded by the Department of Telecommunications, Government of India, as it is confident of defending itself on merit.</p><ul><li>Unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025 announced</li><li>Total income for the quarter is Rs. 18.37 lakhs and for the nine months is Rs. 179.60 lakhs</li><li>Profit before tax for the quarter is Rs. 5.68 lakhs and for the nine months is Rs. 6.88 lakhs</li><li>Net profit for the quarter is Rs. 4.33 lakhs and for the nine months is Rs. 4.10 lakhs</li><li>No provision made for the license fees demanded by the Department of Telecommunications, Government of India, as the company is confident of defending itself on merit</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0389dc0f-639a-4a7a-85f0-754b0d726eda.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HATHWAY BHAWANI CABLETEL & DATACOM LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HATHWAYB] Hathway Bhawani Cabletel &amp; Datacom Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Unaudited Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HATHWAY+BHAWANI+CABLETEL+%26+DATACOM+LTD.&title=Hathway+Bhawani+Cabletel+%26+Datacom+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=41f8acd2-87c8-4102-8db6-389296b86828&token=NDFmOGFjZDItODdj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41f8acd2-87c8-4102-8db6-389296b86828</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hathway Bhawani Cabletel &amp; Datacom Ltd has released its unaudited consolidated and standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The results were reviewed and approved by the Audit Committee and the Board of Directors in their respective meetings. The company&apos;s revenue from operations and other income are reported, along with operational expenses, employee benefit expenses, and exceptional items. The company&apos;s profit before and after tax, as well as other comprehensive income, are also disclosed. The financial results include the standalone financial result of one joint venture, Hathway Bhawani NDS Network Limited.</p><ul><li>Hathway Bhawani Cabletel &amp; Datacom Ltd released unaudited consolidated and standalone financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Results reviewed and approved by Audit Committee and Board of Directors</li><li>Revenue from operations, other income, operational expenses, employee benefit expenses, and exceptional items reported</li><li>Profit before and after tax, as well as other comprehensive income, disclosed</li><li>Standalone financial result of joint venture, Hathway Bhawani NDS Network Limited, included in the financial results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b9964829-a8ef-40f9-bd75-6d129f18c6f1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HATHWAY BHAWANI CABLETEL & DATACOM LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JUSTDIAL] Just Dial Ltd Announces Q3 FY26 Results: Revenue Up 6.4% YoY, Net Profit Down 10.2% YoY</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JUST+DIAL+LTD.&title=Just+Dial+Ltd+Announces+Q3+FY26+Results%3A+Revenue+Up+6.4%25+YoY%2C+Net+Profit+Down+10.2%25+YoY&newsId=8a91b2b2-da13-4110-9d94-401c6e645bdd&token=OGE5MWIyYjItZGEx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a91b2b2-da13-4110-9d94-401c6e645bdd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Just Dial Ltd, India&apos;s leading local search engine company, announced its financial and operating results for the third quarter ended December 31, 2025. The key highlights include a 6.4% YoY increase in revenue, reaching 305.7 Crores, and a 10.0% YoY growth in EBITDA, amounting to 95.2 Crores. However, the net profit saw a decrease of 10.2% YoY, standing at 118.0 Crores. The company&apos;s cash and investments stood at 5,703.0 Crores as of December 31, 2025. Traffic for the quarter stood at 184.5 million users, with 86.2% originating from mobile platforms.</p><ul><li>3Q-FY26 Revenue stood at 305.7 Crores, up 6.4% YoY</li><li>Net Profit stood at 118.0 Crores, down 10.2% YoY</li><li>Traffic in 3Q-FY26 stood at 184.5 million users</li><li>Cash and Investments stood at 5,703.0 Crores as on December 31, 2025</li><li>86.2% traffic originated on Mobile platforms</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/02de7683-388c-4a3f-8fed-87b1a8f59a3c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JUST DIAL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FSL] Firstsource Acquires TeleMedik to Bolster Digital Offerings in U.S. Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=FIRSTSOURCE+SOLUTIONS+LTD.&title=Firstsource+Acquires+TeleMedik+to+Bolster+Digital+Offerings+in+U.S.+Healthcare&newsId=4f89f339-1567-470c-8f44-aac91f2c324e&token=NGY4OWYzMzktMTU2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4f89f339-1567-470c-8f44-aac91f2c324e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Firstsource Solutions Limited, a leading global provider of business management services, has announced the acquisition of TeleMedik, a Puerto Rico based pioneer in technological solutions. This strategic move aims to strengthen Firstsource’s end-to-end clinical and utilization management capabilities, expand its footprint across payer-provider networks, and enrich its Business Process as a Service (BPaaS++) offering for health plan clients. The acquisition will help more payers improve quality, reduce administrative costs, and enhance member and provider experiences.</p><ul><li>Firstsource acquires TeleMedik, a Puerto Rico based pioneer in technological solutions.</li><li>The acquisition significantly strengthens Firstsource’s end-to-end clinical and utilization management capabilities.</li><li>It expands Firstsource’s footprint across payer-provider networks and enriches its Business Process as a Service (BPaaS++) offering for health plan clients.</li><li>The combined organization will support health plans with integrated clinical review, prior authorization, care and disease management, population health, and telemedicine-enabled interventions.</li><li>The acquisition will help more payers improve quality, reduce administrative costs, and enhance member and provider experiences.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/07a9289c-4550-4038-a3e2-b060359524f3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: FIRSTSOURCE SOLUTIONS LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CHIRAHARIT] Chiraharit Ltd Secures Multiple Orders Worth Over Rs. 2.3 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Chiraharit+Ltd&title=Chiraharit+Ltd+Secures+Multiple+Orders+Worth+Over+Rs.+2.3+Crores&newsId=ef6d94ba-7096-4482-9599-ef87becd15f9&token=ZWY2ZDk0YmEtNzA5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef6d94ba-7096-4482-9599-ef87becd15f9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:02:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Chiraharit Ltd has recently announced the receipt of multiple purchase orders from various entities. The orders are for the supply, installation, testing, and commissioning of pipe &amp; fittings for solar module cleaning systems and industrial water supply schemes. The total consideration for these orders is over Rs. 2.3 crores. The orders are expected to be executed within the specified time periods and do not involve any related party transactions.</p><ul><li>Chiraharit Ltd has secured multiple purchase orders from various entities.</li><li>The orders are for the supply, installation, testing, and commissioning of pipe &amp; fittings for solar module cleaning systems and industrial water supply schemes.</li><li>The total consideration for these orders is over Rs. 2.3 crores.</li><li>The orders are expected to be executed within the specified time periods.</li><li>There are no related party transactions involved in these orders.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/088799bd-32b7-4639-b1c9-2d0a895fa7b5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Chiraharit Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>