<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:27:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[OLAELEC] Ola Electric Commences Deliveries of 9.1kWh BESS Solution; Secures Government Certification for 5.2kWh Variant</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ola+Electric+Mobility+Ltd&title=Ola+Electric+Commences+Deliveries+of+9.1kWh+BESS+Solution%3B+Secures+Government+Certification+for+5.2kWh+Variant&newsId=e1074de3-b604-4392-aa50-474b1cca523e&token=ZTEwNzRkZTMtYjYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e1074de3-b604-4392-aa50-474b1cca523e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:12:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Ola Electric Mobility Limited has announced the commencement of deliveries of its Ola Trfad 9.1kWh, the country&apos;s first residential Battery Energy Storage System (BESS) solution powered by 4680 Bharat Cells. The company has also secured the Bureau of Indian Standards (BIS) certification for the 3kW/5.2kWh configuration of Ola QT@[. The 3kW/.5.2kWh variant underwent BIS mandatory certification in compliance with safety and environmental standards. Ola Electric is designed to transform how India stores and consumes energy by providing automotive-grade safety, high-efficiency performance, and zero running and maintenance costs. The system can power various appliances with fast charging times, and backup capacity of up to 1.5 hours on full load.</p><ul><li>Ola Electric commences deliveries of 9.1kWh BESS solution powered by 4680 Bharat Cells</li><li>Secures BIS certification for 3kW/5.2kWh configuration of Ola QT@[</li><li>Ola Electric BESS solution designed, engineered, and manufactured in India</li><li>Provides automotive-grade safety, high-efficiency performance, and zero running and maintenance costs</li><li>Can power various appliances with fast charging times and backup capacity of up to 1.5 hours on full load</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1df6f6a2-d837-4cf8-a8b8-f7f553d31879.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ola Electric Mobility Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TVSMOTOR] TVS Motor Company Sales Grows 29% in January 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TVS+MOTOR+COMPANY+LTD.&title=TVS+Motor+Company+Sales+Grows+29%25+in+January+2026&newsId=0efe908f-67ca-4edb-9ef8-1b85b0c52283&token=MGVmZTkwOGYtNjdj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0efe908f-67ca-4edb-9ef8-1b85b0c52283</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:12:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>TVS Motor Company, a global leader in the two and three-wheeler segments, recorded monthly sales of 511,766 units in January 2026 with a growth of 29% as against 397,623 units in January 2025. The company&apos;s total exports registered a growth of 21% with sales increasing from 101,055 units in January 2025 to 122,343 units in January 2026. The three-wheeler segment also saw a significant growth of 77% with sales increasing from 9,952 units in January 2025 to 17,571 units in January 2026.</p><ul><li>TVS Motor Company records a growth of 29% in January 2026 with sales of 511,766 units.</li><li>Total exports grow by 21% with sales increasing from 101,055 units in January 2025 to 122,343 units in January 2026.</li><li>Three-wheeler segment registers a significant growth of 77% with sales increasing from 9,952 units in January 2025 to 17,571 units in January 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/43debbdb-55b2-4f6a-9b1a-5aceec36800a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TVS MOTOR COMPANY LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VSTTILLERS] No Material Impact on VST Tillers Tractors Ltd After Promoter&apos;s Death</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=V.S.T.TILLERS+TRACTORS+LTD.-%24&title=No+Material+Impact+on+VST+Tillers+Tractors+Ltd+After+Promoter%27s+Death&newsId=151de5cf-cb48-46e9-874c-cecc7437be7d&token=MTUxZGU1Y2YtY2I0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">151de5cf-cb48-46e9-874c-cecc7437be7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>VST Tillers Tractors Ltd announced the sad demise of its promoter, Mr. V. K. Surendra, on 28th January 2026. The company became aware of the event upon receipt of information by the Secretarial Department and immediately disclosed the event to the Stock Exchanges. The delay in disclosure, if any, was not deliberate or intentional. Mr. Surendra was not holding any position as Director, Key Managerial Personnel or part of the Senior Management at the time of his demise. The event does not have any material impact on the operations or management of the Company.</p><ul><li>VST Tillers Tractors Ltd announced the demise of its promoter, Mr. V. K. Surendra.</li><li>The company disclosed the event to the Stock Exchanges immediately upon becoming aware.</li><li>Mr. Surendra was not holding any position in the company at the time of his demise.</li><li>The event does not have any material impact on the operations or management of the Company.</li><li>The delay in disclosure, if any, was not deliberate or intentional.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/aa65aff6-68f5-4211-a796-77694d869f61.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: V.S.T.TILLERS TRACTORS LTD.-$ | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VSTTILLERS] VST Tillers Tractors Ltd. to Approve Un-audited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months of FY2025-2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=V.S.T.TILLERS+TRACTORS+LTD.-%24&title=VST+Tillers+Tractors+Ltd.+to+Approve+Un-audited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+of+FY2025-2026&newsId=1c1fc702-ec61-4c5d-a7ed-0f83eb5e3089&token=MWMxZmM3MDItZWM2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c1fc702-ec61-4c5d-a7ed-0f83eb5e3089</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:11:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>VST Tillers Tractors Ltd. has announced a Board of Directors meeting on February 7, 2026, to consider and approve the Un-audited Financial Results (Standalone &amp; Consolidated) for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will be digitally signed by Chinmaya Chinmaya Khatua, Company Secretary &amp; Compliance Officer.</p><ul><li>VST Tillers Tractors Ltd. to consider and approve Un-audited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months of FY2025-2026</li><li>Board of Directors meeting scheduled on February 7, 2026</li><li>Meeting to be digitally signed by Chinmaya Chinmaya Khatua, Company Secretary &amp; Compliance Officer</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/06d39ed6-1bfc-4ceb-b507-8b4571af2a2c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: V.S.T.TILLERS TRACTORS LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JUBLFOOD] Jubilant FoodWorks Ltd Receives Tax Demand of Rs. 169.59 Crs for FY 2021-22</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jubilant+FoodWorks+Ltd&title=Jubilant+FoodWorks+Ltd+Receives+Tax+Demand+of+Rs.+169.59+Crs+for+FY+2021-22&newsId=73173494-8a93-4e8a-b32b-10305f9b7bad&token=NzMxNzM0OTQtOGE5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73173494-8a93-4e8a-b32b-10305f9b7bad</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 08:11:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jubilant FoodWorks Ltd has received an assessment order from the Income Tax Department, raising a tax demand of Rs. 169.59 Crs for Financial Year 2021-22. The Company believes that the impugned tax demand suffers from mistakes apparent from records and has been made ignoring the contentions of the Company. Hence, the Company is in the process of filing a rectification application and/or appeal in relation thereto. The Company expects to get relief from the relevant Assessing Officer and/or appellate Authority and does not anticipate any material financial implications.</p><ul><li>Jubilant FoodWorks Ltd has received an assessment order from the Income Tax Department for FY 2021-22.</li><li>The tax demand raised is Rs. 169.59 Crs.</li><li>The Company believes that the impugned tax demand suffers from mistakes apparent from records.</li><li>The Company is in the process of filing a rectification application and/or appeal in relation thereto.</li><li>The Company expects to get relief from the relevant Assessing Officer and/or appellate Authority.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/507ef4fc-d8a0-4a0f-8427-7e71b6e9d13d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jubilant FoodWorks Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VISHNU] Vishnu Chemicals Reports Q3FY26 and 9MFY26 Earnings Update with Sequential Revenue, EBITDA and PAT Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VISHNU+CHEMICALS+LTD.&title=Vishnu+Chemicals+Reports+Q3FY26+and+9MFY26+Earnings+Update+with+Sequential+Revenue%2C+EBITDA+and+PAT+Growth&newsId=1f408c3f-78a5-4c5c-8765-399225354367&token=MWY0MDhjM2YtNzhh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f408c3f-78a5-4c5c-8765-399225354367</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 07:34:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Vishnu Chemicals Limited, a leading global player in the manufacturing of speciality chemicals, reported its unaudited financial results for the nine months and quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a 2.5% growth in revenues, 6.0% growth in EBITDA, and 2.6% growth in PAT on a sequential quarterly basis. On a yearly basis, revenues grew by 10.0%, EBITDA by 6.9%, and PAT by 12.7%. The company has completed the transfer of a mining complex and is transitioning towards stable supply and improved margins. Vishnu Strontium Private Limited has commercialised operations and is expected to enhance diversification and profitability in the medium to long term.</p><ul><li>Sequential revenue, EBITDA, and PAT growth in Q3FY26</li><li>Yearly revenue, EBITDA, and PAT growth of 10.0%, 6.9%, and 12.7% respectively in 9MFY26</li><li>Completion of mining complex transfer and transition towards stable supply and improved margins</li><li>Commercialisation of Vishnu Strontium Private Limited&apos;s operations</li><li>Expected enhancement of diversification and profitability in the medium to long term</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/58236797-3ca6-402a-91fc-f06d56859998.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VISHNU CHEMICALS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UNIONBANK] Union Bank of India Announces Elevation of Shri Sarvesh Ranjan as Chief General Manager</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=UNION+BANK+OF+INDIA&title=Union+Bank+of+India+Announces+Elevation+of+Shri+Sarvesh+Ranjan+as+Chief+General+Manager&newsId=a565470b-130a-4b51-bf93-c426623d1f51&token=YTU2NTQ3MGItMTMw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a565470b-130a-4b51-bf93-c426623d1f51</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 07:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Union Bank of India has announced the elevation of Shri Sarvesh Ranjan as the Chief General Manager of the Bank, effective from February 01, 2026. Shri Ranjan, an Engineering Graduate and a seasoned banker with around three decades of banking expertise, has been serving as the General Manager - Central Recon., Transaction Monitoring &amp; AML of the Bank. He has also attended leadership development programs at the University of Applied Sciences at Switzerland and ISB Hyderabad, as well as a certification programme in IT and Cyber Security from IDRBT, Hyderabad. The bank also announced the superannuation of Shri Bhaskara Rao Kare, Chief General Manager, on January 31, 2026.</p><ul><li>Shri Sarvesh Ranjan elevated to the post of Chief General Manager of Union Bank of India.</li><li>Shri Ranjan has around three decades of banking expertise.</li><li>He has attended leadership development programs at the University of Applied Sciences at Switzerland and ISB Hyderabad.</li><li>Shri Ranjan has also completed a certification programme in IT and Cyber Security from IDRBT, Hyderabad.</li><li>Shri Bhaskara Rao Kare, Chief General Manager, superannuated from the services of the Bank on January 31, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ed22047c-4fc7-429a-a5ec-251481a3d001.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: UNION BANK OF INDIA | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GARGI] PNGS Gargi Fashion Jewellery Ltd Opens New Exclusive Brand Store in Noida</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PNGS+Gargi+Fashion+Jewellery+Ltd&title=PNGS+Gargi+Fashion+Jewellery+Ltd+Opens+New+Exclusive+Brand+Store+in+Noida&newsId=a97c59a9-9633-4da6-a42c-6b83c285d807&token=YTk3YzU5YTktOTYz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a97c59a9-9633-4da6-a42c-6b83c285d807</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 07:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>PNGS Gargi Fashion Jewellery Ltd has announced the opening of its new exclusive brand store at Unit No GF-10B Ground Floor, Tower B of the Spectrum Metro Mall, Plot No C and D, Sector- 75, Noida, Uttar Pradesh - 201301. This expansion is a significant step for the company, aiming to strengthen its presence in the region and provide customers with a unique shopping experience.</p><ul><li>PNGS Gargi Fashion Jewellery Ltd has opened a new exclusive brand store in Noida, Uttar Pradesh.</li><li>The new store is located at Unit No GF-10B Ground Floor, Tower B of the Spectrum Metro Mall, Plot No C and D, Sector- 75, Noida, Uttar Pradesh - 201301.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7de62a48-062c-49e8-b568-87ed5b401bdf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PNGS Gargi Fashion Jewellery Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EICHERMOT] Royal Enfield Achieves 1 Million Sales Milestone, Posts 14% YoY Growth in January 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=EICHER+MOTORS+LTD.&title=Royal+Enfield+Achieves+1+Million+Sales+Milestone%2C+Posts+14%25+YoY+Growth+in+January+2026&newsId=43ed9c7c-15cd-4dc7-8534-db37344e8e22&token=NDNlZDljN2MtMTVj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43ed9c7c-15cd-4dc7-8534-db37344e8e22</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 07:02:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Royal Enfield, a subsidiary of Eicher Motors Ltd., has reported monthly sales of 1,04,322 motorcycles in January 2026, marking a milestone of 1 million sales in a record 10 months. The company witnessed a 14% growth over January 2025. The Goan Classic 350, a bobber-inspired motorcycle, was launched with new rider-focused updates. Royal Enfield also partnered with KRAFTON India to bring its iconic motorcycles into the BATTLEGROUNDS MOBILE INDIA (BGMI) universe. The company launched its first-of-its-kind Gymkhana in Bengaluru, offering structured rider skill-up modules.</p><ul><li>Royal Enfield achieves 1 million sales milestone in a record 10 months.</li><li>The company posts 14% YoY growth in January 2026.</li><li>Launch of the 2026 Goan Classic 350 with new features.</li><li>Partnership with KRAFTON India to introduce Royal Enfield motorcycles in BGMI.</li><li>Launch of Royal Enfield Gymkhana in Bengaluru.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0de189a2-ceea-4846-8d38-1ed8877dba9c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: EICHER MOTORS LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NTPC] NTPC Ltd Transfers Coal Mines to NTPC Mining Limited Ahead of Schedule</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NTPC+LTD.&title=NTPC+Ltd+Transfers+Coal+Mines+to+NTPC+Mining+Limited+Ahead+of+Schedule&newsId=83d0298b-64f3-4a47-b2b8-3135ad57c78b&token=ODNkMDI5OGItNjRm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">83d0298b-64f3-4a47-b2b8-3135ad57c78b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 07:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In a recent disclosure, NTPC Ltd announced the transfer of its coal mining business to its wholly-owned subsidiary, NTPC Mining Limited (NML). The transfer includes the Dulanga Coal Mine in Sundergarh, Odisha, and the Talaipalli Coal Mine in Raigarh, Chhattisgarh. Originally scheduled for January 31, 2026, the transfer was completed earlier on February 15, 2026.</p><ul><li>NTPC Ltd transfers coal mines to its subsidiary, NTPC Mining Limited</li><li>Transfer includes Dulanga Coal Mine in Sundergarh, Odisha, and Talaipalli Coal Mine in Raigarh, Chhattisgarh</li><li>Transfer completed ahead of schedule on February 15, 2026</li><li>NTPC Ltd continues to streamline its operations through strategic business updates</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1d8d4da1-c386-4cf6-a9da-031aba1ba399.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NTPC LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>