<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:43:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[TCIIND] TCI Industries Ltd Allots 3750 NCRPS to Promoter and Promoter Group</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TCI+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=TCI+Industries+Ltd+Allots+3750+NCRPS+to+Promoter+and+Promoter+Group&newsId=d9f99ea1-69f6-40b1-82c6-f8d01daffa1e&token=ZDlmOTllYTEtNjlm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d9f99ea1-69f6-40b1-82c6-f8d01daffa1e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:43:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>TCI Industries Ltd has allotted 3750 nos. of 0% Non-Convertible Redeemable Preference Shares (NCRPS) to Transcorp Estates Private Limited and Bunny Investment &amp; Finance Private Limited for cash through Private Placement basis. Each NCRPS carries a preferential right with respect to payment of dividend and repayment in case of a winding up or repayment of capital. The NCRPS are non-participating in the surplus funds and surplus assets and profits. They do not carry any dividend, are non-convertible, and are redeemable at a premium of maximum 18% p.a. on the issue price. The NCRPS are transferable within the select group of identified persons i.e. promoters &amp; promoter group entities and related parties of the Company. The allotment does not affect the paid-up equity share capital of the Company.</p><ul><li>TCI Industries Ltd allotted 3750 NCRPS to Promoter and Promoter Group entities.</li><li>NCRPS are non-convertible and non-participating in the surplus funds and surplus assets and profits.</li><li>NCRPS carry a preferential right with respect to payment of dividend and repayment in case of a winding up or repayment of capital.</li><li>NCRPS are redeemable at a premium of maximum 18% p.a. on the issue price.</li><li>NCRPS are transferable within the select group of identified persons i.e. promoters &amp; promoter group entities and related parties of the Company.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9c3acac3-c07d-430f-8df0-37f4de0c0721.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TCI INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BAJEL] Bajel Projects Announces Joint Venture with Saudi Arabia&apos;s Al Sharif Contracting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Bajel+Projects+Ltd&title=Bajel+Projects+Announces+Joint+Venture+with+Saudi+Arabia%27s+Al+Sharif+Contracting&newsId=d90c8938-4c29-4959-a212-629f750776ce&token=ZDkwYzg5MzgtNGMy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d90c8938-4c29-4959-a212-629f750776ce</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Bajel Projects Limited, a leading player in the power transmission and infrastructure sector, has signed a Joint Venture (JV) agreement with Al Sharif Contracting and Commercial Development Company (ASC), a part of Al Sharif Group Holdings and one of the leading EPC contractors &amp; manufacturers in Saudi Arabia. The partnership is aimed at participating in the significant infrastructure transformation currently underway in the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia, focusing on High Voltage and Extra High Voltage (EHV) Infrastructure, Overhead Transmission Lines, Substation Packages, and Underground Cabling Projects.</p><ul><li>Bajel Projects and Al Sharif Contracting have formed a 50:50 Joint Venture Company (JVCo.) in Saudi Arabia.</li><li>The JVCo. will undertake Engineering, Procurement, and Construction (EPC) business within Saudi Arabia, focusing on High Voltage and Extra High Voltage (EHV) Infrastructure.</li><li>The partnership is strategically positioned to execute projects and be a partner for Saudi utility and infrastructure companies.</li><li>Bajel Projects will contribute its technical strengths in EHV execution, while Al Sharif Group will provide deep regional expertise and market presence.</li><li>The JVCo. will support Bajel Projects&apos; strategic growth objectives and enable it to capture emerging business opportunities in the KSA region.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/74cc4db6-56ca-4a80-8552-0b9091187f1c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Bajel Projects Ltd | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SALSTEEL] S.A.L. Steel Ltd Allots 3,57,50,000 Equity Shares to Sree Metaliks Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=S.A.L.STEEL+LTD.&title=S.A.L.+Steel+Ltd+Allots+3%2C57%2C50%2C000+Equity+Shares+to+Sree+Metaliks+Limited&newsId=fcc1d619-2e7c-4709-b4a8-dfc193f49f1b&token=ZmNjMWQ2MTktMmU3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fcc1d619-2e7c-4709-b4a8-dfc193f49f1b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>S.A.L. Steel Ltd has allotted 3,57,50,000 equity shares to Sree Metaliks Limited on conversion of warrants. The warrants were issued on a preferential basis at an issue price of ₹18 per warrant. The allotment was approved by the board on February 14, 2026. The new equity shares will rank pari-passu with the existing equity shares of the Company. The issued, subscribed and paid-up equity share capital of the Company stands increased to ₹ 3144,76,67,000 consisting of 14,47,66,700 fully paid-up Equity Shares of face value ₹10 each.</p><ul><li>S.A.L. Steel Ltd has allotted 3,57,50,000 equity shares to Sree Metaliks Limited</li><li>The warrants were issued on a preferential basis at an issue price of ₹18 per warrant</li><li>The allotment was approved by the board on February 14, 2026</li><li>The new equity shares will rank pari-passu with the existing equity shares of the Company</li><li>The issued, subscribed and paid-up equity share capital of the Company stands increased to ₹ 3144,76,67,000 consisting of 14,47,66,700 fully paid-up Equity Shares of face value ₹10 each</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b4cc2ac8-e705-4d5d-ab3c-6bdde7f77761.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: S.A.L.STEEL LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GPTINFRA] GPT Infraprojects Wins Contract Worth Rs. 1201.36 Crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GPT+INFRAPROJECTS+LTD.&title=GPT+Infraprojects+Wins+Contract+Worth+Rs.+1201.36+Crore&newsId=a0937268-eba0-4e5d-a067-72883e790644&token=YTA5MzcyNjgtZWJh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0937268-eba0-4e5d-a067-72883e790644</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:39:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>GPT Infraprojects Limited (GPTINFRA) has announced that it has received a contract in a joint venture with Rail Vikas Nigam Limited (RVNL). The contract, worth Rs. 1201.36 Crore, is for the Design and Construction of a new Rail cum Road Bridge No 11 over River Ganga. GPTINFRA&apos;s share in the contract is 40%, which amounts to Rs. 480.54 Crore. The contract is to be executed over a period of 1461 days from the appointed date.</p><ul><li>GPT Infraprojects has won a contract worth Rs. 1201.36 Crore in a joint venture with Rail Vikas Nigam Limited.</li><li>The contract is for the Design and Construction of a new Rail cum Road Bridge No 11 over River Ganga.</li><li>GPTINFRA&apos;s share in the contract is 40%, which amounts to Rs. 480.54 Crore.</li><li>The contract is to be executed over a period of 1461 days from the appointed date.</li><li>GPT Infraprojects is a premier infrastructure company based out of Kolkata, operating through two segments: Infrastructure and Sleeper.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/84a9e1f6-79ab-4d7a-8838-db73a3ecd426.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GPT INFRAPROJECTS LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DCBBANK] DCB Bank Appoints Mrs. Neeta Sudhir Rege as Additional Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DCB+Bank+Limited&title=DCB+Bank+Appoints+Mrs.+Neeta+Sudhir+Rege+as+Additional+Independent+Director&newsId=3e379ce2-648e-4a69-bff1-ef035010c98f&token=M2UzNzljZTItNjQ4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e379ce2-648e-4a69-bff1-ef035010c98f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>DCB Bank Ltd has appointed Mrs. Neeta Sudhir Rege as an Additional and Non-Executive (Independent) Director, effective from February 18, 2026. The appointment is subject to the approval of the Bank&apos;s shareholders. Mrs. Rege is a senior banker with 38 years of experience in Compliance, Financial Crime Compliance, Conduct and Consumer Banking. She is not related to any Director of the Bank and is not debarred from holding office of director by virtue of any SEBI order or any other such authority. The Bank will seek approval of the Shareholders for the said appointment within the prescribed time period, as per the applicable provisions of the Companies Act, 2013 and SEBI Listing Regulations.</p><ul><li>DCB Bank appoints Mrs. Neeta Sudhir Rege as Additional and Non-Executive (Independent) Director.</li><li>Mrs. Rege&apos;s appointment is subject to the approval of the Bank&apos;s shareholders.</li><li>Mrs. Rege has 38 years of experience in Compliance, Financial Crime Compliance, Conduct and Consumer Banking.</li><li>Mrs. Rege is not related to any Director of the Bank and is not debarred from holding office of director.</li><li>The Bank will seek approval of the Shareholders for the said appointment within the prescribed time period.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f9618964-c63e-444b-884e-493a99f5b24c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DCB Bank Limited | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STERPOW] Sterling Powergensys Ltd: Trading Window Remains Closed Until 48 Hours After Q3 Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sterling+Powergensys+Limited&title=Sterling+Powergensys+Ltd%3A+Trading+Window+Remains+Closed+Until+48+Hours+After+Q3+Results&newsId=faf456de-6be1-4063-bd13-f276ddd18d08&token=ZmFmNDU2ZGUtNmJl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">faf456de-6be1-4063-bd13-f276ddd18d08</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sterling Powergensys Ltd has announced that the trading window for dealing in the securities of the company will remain closed for all Directors, KMPs, Designated Persons, Connected Persons and their immediate relatives until 48 hours after the declaration of the Un-audited Standalone Financial Results for the quarter ended 31st December, 2025. The Board Meeting for consideration and approval of these results could not be convened within the expected timeframe.</p><ul><li>Sterling Powergensys Ltd announces extension of trading window closure</li><li>The closure is for all Directors, KMPs, Designated Persons, Connected Persons and their immediate relatives</li><li>The closure is until 48 hours after the declaration of Q3 results</li><li>The Board Meeting for consideration and approval of Q3 results could not be convened within the expected timeframe</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ba366bf8-210e-405e-be84-75e96e36cd3b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sterling Powergensys Limited | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STERPOW] Sterling Powergensys Delays Submission of Unaudited Financial Results for Q4 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sterling+Powergensys+Limited&title=Sterling+Powergensys+Delays+Submission+of+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q4+2025&newsId=48b51a9e-ad4b-4278-93f6-b4aec493554f&token=NDhiNTFhOWUtYWQ0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48b51a9e-ad4b-4278-93f6-b4aec493554f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:28:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sterling Powergensys Ltd. has announced a delay in submitting the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025, as per Regulation 30 and Regulation 33 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The financial statements for the quarter are currently under finalisation, with the delay attributed to temporary and procedural circumstances. The company emphasizes that there is no malafide intention or deliberate non-compliance and is working diligently to complete the financial closing process. The Unaudited Financial Results will be submitted as soon as they are finalised, in accordance with applicable regulatory requirements.</p><ul><li>Sterling Powergensys delays submission of Unaudited Financial Results for Q4 2025</li><li>Financial statements for Q4 2025 are under finalisation</li><li>Delay due to temporary and procedural circumstances</li><li>No malafide intention or deliberate non-compliance</li><li>Company aims to submit Unaudited Financial Results as soon as they are finalised</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1bd34bc4-2324-4875-a2d6-49c34c37a985.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sterling Powergensys Limited | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AVAX] Avax Apparels and Ornaments Ltd: Stock Sub-division, Bonus Issue, and Director Redesignation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Avax+Apparels+and+Ornaments+Ltd&title=Avax+Apparels+and+Ornaments+Ltd%3A+Stock+Sub-division%2C+Bonus+Issue%2C+and+Director+Redesignation&newsId=0deda547-b7c9-42df-a258-28dbe12f6019&token=MGRlZGE1NDctYjdj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0deda547-b7c9-42df-a258-28dbe12f6019</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:24:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Avax Apparels and Ornaments Ltd has announced a sub-division of the face value of each equity share from INR 10 to INR 5. Additionally, the company has approved a bonus issue in the ratio of 3:1. The Board of Directors has also redesignated Mr. Harinderpal Singh Sodhi and Mr. Deepak Kumar as Joint Managing Directors. The record date for determining the entitlement of the members to receive the stock sub-division shares and bonus equity shares will be announced in due course.</p><ul><li>Sub-division of the face value of each Equity Share from INR 10 to INR 5</li><li>Issue of bonus equity shares in the ratio of 3:1</li><li>Redesignation of Mr. Harinderpal Singh Sodhi as a Joint Managing Director</li><li>Redesignation of Mr. Deepak Kumar as a Joint Managing Director</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b527ea23-c6ad-4b13-84a4-79d65d555386.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Avax Apparels and Ornaments Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[3IINFOTECH] 3i Infotech Secures 35th Rank Worldwide for its Annual Report 2024-25</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=3I+INFOTECH+LTD.&title=3i+Infotech+Secures+35th+Rank+Worldwide+for+its+Annual+Report+2024-25&newsId=59338a46-65ac-4f30-96ba-f7a4db4c17e8&token=NTkzMzhhNDYtNjVh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59338a46-65ac-4f30-96ba-f7a4db4c17e8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>3i Infotech Limited, a leading global provider of digital transformation, technology services and technology solutions, has once again made its mark on the international stage at the 2024/25 Vision Awards Annual Report Competition organized by the League of American Communications Professionals (LACP). The Company&apos;s Annual Report titled &apos;Reset. Refocus. Rebound.&apos; achieved an exceptional overall score of 98 out of 100, earning 35th rank globally and securing a prominent place among the Top 100 Annual Reports worldwide. This recognition is a powerful testament of 3i Infotech&apos;s commitment to transparency, governance excellence and meaningful stakeholder communication.</p><ul><li>3i Infotech secures 35th rank worldwide for its Annual Report 2024-25</li><li>Achieved an exceptional overall score of 98 out of 100</li><li>Won the Gold Award at the LACP Vision Awards 2024/25 for the third year in a row</li><li>Received Technical Achievement Award for annual report theme, design and presentation</li><li>Reflects the organisation’s resilience, strategic clarity and the unwavering dedication of the Senior Management Team</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c69cf176-6009-4520-aa15-33c4ab85034c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: 3I INFOTECH LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[YASHPAKKA] Pakka Ltd. Releases Monitoring Agency Report for Q3 FY2025-2026, Revealing Utilization of Preferential Issue Proceeds</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Yash+Pakka+Ltd-%24&title=Pakka+Ltd.+Releases+Monitoring+Agency+Report+for+Q3+FY2025-2026%2C+Revealing+Utilization+of+Preferential+Issue+Proceeds&newsId=130d0f72-45ea-49b8-a6a7-d0921936748e&token=MTMwZDBmNzItNDVl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">130d0f72-45ea-49b8-a6a7-d0921936748e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 09:21:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pakka Ltd. has released a Monitoring Agency Report for the third quarter ended 31st December, 2025, disclosing the utilization of proceeds from the preferential issue of equity shares and fully convertible warrants. The company raised Rs. 244.80 crore through the preferential issue, with Rs. 146.88 crore from equity shares and Rs. 97.92 crore from warrants. The report, issued by CARE Ratings Limited, highlights that all proceeds have been utilized as per the objectives mentioned in the Offer Document.</p><ul><li>Pakka Ltd. raised Rs. 244.80 crore through a preferential issue of equity shares and fully convertible warrants.</li><li>All proceeds have been utilized as per the objectives mentioned in the Offer Document.</li><li>The total capex cost of the Jagriti project has been revised to Rs. 744.15 crore from Rs. 676.26 crore.</li><li>The company has obtained all necessary approvals related to the objects of the issue.</li><li>Pakka Ltd.&apos;s share price is currently trading significantly below the warrant exercise price, potentially impacting the viability of the objectives.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/76d01e9b-af77-4953-9572-2a3808f23984.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Yash Pakka Ltd-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>