<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 09:29:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[MAHASTEEL] Mahamaya Steel&apos;s December 2025 Sales Surge by 13.52%, Q3 FY 2025-26 Sales Up 26.42%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MAHAMAYA+STEEL+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Mahamaya+Steel%27s+December+2025+Sales+Surge+by+13.52%25%2C+Q3+FY+2025-26+Sales+Up+26.42%25&newsId=6ed0edff-0922-4a15-9e38-f685b6d68e8e&token=NmVkMGVkZmYtMDky</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ed0edff-0922-4a15-9e38-f685b6d68e8e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 09:27:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Mahamaya Steel Industries Ltd. has reported a 13.52% increase in total sales volume for December 2025, compared to the previous month. The sales volume for Q3 of FY 2025-26 stands at 53083.41 MT, a significant increase of 26.42% compared to Q2 of FY 2025-26. The company has received a substantial number of orders, indicating a positive demand outlook for the coming months.</p><ul><li>December 2025 sales volume increased by 13.52%</li><li>Q3 FY 2025-26 sales volume up by 26.42% compared to Q2</li><li>Strong operational performance reflected</li><li>Substantial number of orders received</li><li>Healthy demand outlook for the coming months</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bbad7853-257c-4707-bddc-d2bede03baf7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MAHAMAYA STEEL INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHYAM] Ventura Guaranty Ltd Approves Allotment of 6,58,745 Equity Shares Post Amalgamation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VENTURA+GUARANTY+LTD.&title=Ventura+Guaranty+Ltd+Approves+Allotment+of+6%2C58%2C745+Equity+Shares+Post+Amalgamation&newsId=1a3387fa-b372-4515-b1b6-e57ca176f6fa&token=MWEzMzg3ZmEtYjM3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a3387fa-b372-4515-b1b6-e57ca176f6fa</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 09:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ventura Guaranty Ltd has approved the allotment of 6,58,745 equity shares to the shareholders of Kashmira Investment and Leasing Private Limited as part of a scheme of amalgamation. The allotment is in the ratio of 84:100, with 84 shares of Ventura Guaranty Ltd being issued for every 100 shares held in Kashmira Investment and Leasing Private Limited. The equity share capital of the company will increase to Rs. 3,85,35,450/- divided into 38,53,545 equity shares of Rs.10/- each. The allotted shares will rank pari-passu with the existing shares and are proposed to be listed and traded on BSE Limited.</p><ul><li>Ventura Guaranty Ltd approves allotment of 6,58,745 equity shares</li><li>Allotment is in ratio of 84:100 for shareholders of Kashmira Investment and Leasing Private Limited</li><li>Equity share capital of the company to increase to Rs. 3,85,35,450/-</li><li>Allotted shares to rank pari-passu with existing shares</li><li>Allotted shares proposed to be listed and traded on BSE Limited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6c9bf7cc-7475-44ba-8871-6c3f5a30f080.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VENTURA GUARANTY LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BRPL] Independent Director, Mrs. Enu Shah, Resigns from Bansal Roofing Products Ltd.</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Bansal+Roofing+Products+Ltd&title=Independent+Director%2C+Mrs.+Enu+Shah%2C+Resigns+from+Bansal+Roofing+Products+Ltd.&newsId=2a26030b-00d6-4165-ba0c-8f635aec6ec7&token=MmEyNjAzMGItMDBk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a26030b-00d6-4165-ba0c-8f635aec6ec7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 09:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Resignation of Independent Director</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mrs. Enu Shah, an Independent Director of Bansal Roofing Products Ltd., has resigned from her position due to preoccupation and other personal commitments. She will also cease to be the Chairperson of Stakeholders Relationship Committee, Member of Audit Committee and Nomination and Remuneration Committee. The resignation is effective from the close of business hours on December 31, 2025. The Board has accepted her resignation and expressed gratitude for her contributions.</p><ul><li>Mrs. Enu Shah resigns from Bansal Roofing Products Ltd.</li><li>Resignation due to preoccupation and personal commitments.</li><li>Cessation of roles as Chairperson of Stakeholders Relationship Committee, Member of Audit Committee and Nomination and Remuneration Committee.</li><li>Effective from close of business hours on December 31, 2025.</li><li>Board accepts resignation and appreciates contributions.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/24388d68-f41d-4bb9-9695-b4f17cb88427.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Bansal Roofing Products Ltd | Category: Resignation of Independent Director</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GEE] GEE Ltd&apos;s EGM Adjourned Due to Lack of Quorum</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GEE+LTD.&title=GEE+Ltd%27s+EGM+Adjourned+Due+to+Lack+of+Quorum&newsId=64002225-7e61-4ff3-9155-d625ce247c25&token=NjQwMDIyMjUtN2U2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">64002225-7e61-4ff3-9155-d625ce247c25</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 09:21:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gee Limited has informed the Exchange that the Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) held on Monday, January 05, 2026, was adjourned due to the lack of quorum. The EGM was conducted through video conferencing mode as per the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The company will notify the date of the adjourned meeting separately.</p><ul><li>GEE Ltd&apos;s EGM held on January 05, 2026, was adjourned due to the want of quorum</li><li>The EGM was conducted through video conferencing mode</li><li>The company will announce the date of the adjourned meeting separately</li><li>Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, was followed for the EGM</li><li>Umesh Agarwal, Joint Managing Director of GEE Limited, digitally signed the EGM notice</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b7fff047-d7aa-4c1a-8f23-35b7d213eea7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GEE LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[COALINDIA] Coal India Ltd Clarifies Significant Increase in Volume of CIL’s Equity Share Across Exchanges</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=COAL+INDIA+LTD.&title=Coal+India+Ltd+Clarifies+Significant+Increase+in+Volume+of+CIL%E2%80%99s+Equity+Share+Across+Exchanges&newsId=edb0a42d-f3e7-49ac-853d-00cfb09714b0&token=ZWRiMGE0MmQtZjNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">edb0a42d-f3e7-49ac-853d-00cfb09714b0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 09:19:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Coal India Ltd (CIL) has clarified a significant increase in volume of its equity share across exchanges in the recent past. The company has been regularly making disclosures as required under the provisions of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. CIL has filed a disclosure with Stock Exchanges on 03.01.2026 regarding the filing of RHP of Bharat Coking Coal Limited (BCCL), a wholly owned subsidiary of CIL. The RHP filing pertains to the proposed initial public offering (IPO) of BCCL comprising an offer for sale of up to 465,700,000 equity shares by Coal India Limited, which remains subject to receipt of applicable approvals, market conditions, and other relevant considerations.</p><ul><li>Coal India Ltd has clarified a significant increase in volume of its equity share across exchanges</li><li>CIL has been regularly making disclosures as required under the provisions of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>CIL has filed a disclosure with Stock Exchanges on 03.01.2026 regarding the filing of RHP of Bharat Coking Coal Limited (BCCL)</li><li>The RHP filing pertains to the proposed initial public offering (IPO) of BCCL</li><li>The IPO comprises an offer for sale of up to 465,700,000 equity shares by Coal India Limited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b0d5c9cf-237a-4c6a-8445-ab2580b6be0a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: COAL INDIA LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BRPL] Bansal Roofing Products Ltd: Independent Director, Mrs. Enu Shah, Resigns Due to Preoccupation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Bansal+Roofing+Products+Ltd&title=Bansal+Roofing+Products+Ltd%3A+Independent+Director%2C+Mrs.+Enu+Shah%2C+Resigns+Due+to+Preoccupation&newsId=427150a2-b476-46f7-9e42-871a4b285358&token=NDI3MTUwYTItYjQ3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">427150a2-b476-46f7-9e42-871a4b285358</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 09:19:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Auditor</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bansal Roofing Products Ltd has announced the resignation of Mrs. Enu Shah (DIN: 07216454) as an Independent Director, Member of Audit Committee, Member of Nomination and Remuneration Committee, and Chairperson of Stakeholder Relationship Committee, effective from the close of business hours on December 31, 2025. The resignation is due to preoccupation and other personal commitments. Mrs. Enu Shah confirmed that there are no other material reasons for her resignation.</p><ul><li>Mrs. Enu Shah resigns as an Independent Director from Bansal Roofing Products Ltd.</li><li>The resignation is due to preoccupation and personal commitments.</li><li>Mrs. Enu Shah also ceases to be the Chairperson of Stakeholders Relationship Committee and Member of Audit Committee and Nomination and Remuneration Committee.</li><li>Mrs. Enu Shah confirmed no other material reasons for her resignation.</li><li>Bansal Roofing Products Ltd appreciates Mrs. Enu Shah&apos;s contributions during her association with the Company.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a46db590-114f-4e4a-b282-a65b42e32c7c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Bansal Roofing Products Ltd | Category: Auditor</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TRENT] Trent Ltd Clarifies Significant Volume Movement in Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TRENT+LTD.&title=Trent+Ltd+Clarifies+Significant+Volume+Movement+in+Shares&newsId=b0cea109-1254-4dbc-b3f1-2232e299fd06&token=YjBjZWExMDktMTI1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b0cea109-1254-4dbc-b3f1-2232e299fd06</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 09:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Trent Ltd has clarified the significant movement in the volume of its shares in the recent past. The company has informed that all material information, including necessary disclosures in accordance with Regulation 30 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, have been regularly disclosed to the Stock Exchanges. The company is not aware of any other material information that could have bearing on the movement in the share price/volume performance, other than the ordinary course announcements.</p><ul><li>Trent Ltd has clarified the significant volume movement in its shares.</li><li>The company has disclosed all material information in accordance with Regulation 30 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li><li>The company is not aware of any other material information that could have bearing on the movement in the share price/volume performance.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9084daf6-0ea3-41ef-8b7f-6fff0a78a53f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TRENT LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KSR] KSR Footwear Ltd: Price Movement Not Due to Undisclosed Material Events</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KSR+Footwear+Ltd&title=KSR+Footwear+Ltd%3A+Price+Movement+Not+Due+to+Undisclosed+Material+Events&newsId=276708e3-4282-4843-b3e0-adc71c83892b&token=Mjc2NzA4ZTMtNDI4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">276708e3-4282-4843-b3e0-adc71c83892b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 09:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In response to a BSE query, KSR Footwear Ltd stated that the significant movement in the price of its equity shares is purely market-driven. The company, which is newly listed, has consistently disclosed all material events to the Stock Exchanges as per Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations &amp; Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. There are no undisclosed material events that could potentially impact the price or volume of the shares.</p><ul><li>KSR Footwear Ltd has responded to a BSE query regarding the price movement of its equity shares.</li><li>The company stated that the price movement is market-driven and not due to any undisclosed material events.</li><li>KSR Footwear Ltd has a consistent record of disclosing all material events to the Stock Exchanges.</li><li>The disclosures are made in accordance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations &amp; Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li><li>There are no undisclosed material events that could potentially impact the price or volume of the shares.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dc4be904-5c90-4d12-9b7d-81f03a30884e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KSR Footwear Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EIHOTEL] EIH Ltd Faces Rs. 90,69,113 Penalty from Assistant Commissioner, Mumbai</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=EIH+LTD.&title=EIH+Ltd+Faces+Rs.+90%2C69%2C113+Penalty+from+Assistant+Commissioner%2C+Mumbai&newsId=7ccde31e-4aa4-4244-91fd-01da33026c75&token=N2NjZGUzMWUtNGFh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ccde31e-4aa4-4244-91fd-01da33026c75</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 09:10:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>EIH Ltd has disclosed a penalty of Rs. 90,69,113 imposed by the Assistant Commissioner, Mumbai under Section 74 of the Central Goods and Service Tax Act, 2017. The penalty is mainly in relation to ITC claim on input services for the Financial Years 2018-19 to FY 2022-23. The company is expected to take appropriate action within the statutory time limit. The financial impact of the order is equivalent to the penalty imposed.</p><ul><li>EIH Ltd has been imposed a penalty of Rs. 90,69,113 by the Assistant Commissioner, Mumbai under the Central Goods and Service Tax Act, 2017.</li><li>The penalty is mainly in relation to ITC claim on input services for the Financial Years 2018-19 to FY 2022-23.</li><li>The company is expected to take appropriate action within the statutory time limit.</li><li>The financial impact of the order is equivalent to the penalty imposed.</li><li>The disclosure is made pursuant to Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3aa7dacb-42d7-4242-9cac-5e1ef4427818.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: EIH LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUBROS] Subros Ltd Clarifies Significant Increase in Volume is Market Driven</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SUBROS+LTD.&title=Subros+Ltd+Clarifies+Significant+Increase+in+Volume+is+Market+Driven&newsId=b69e23d1-a1a1-456d-9f2f-553b77da81dd&token=YjY5ZTIzZDEtYTFh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b69e23d1-a1a1-456d-9f2f-553b77da81dd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 09:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Subros Ltd has clarified that the significant increase in volume of its equity shares is purely market driven. The company has made all necessary disclosures that have a bearing on its operation/performance, including unpublished price sensitive information, to the Stock Exchange(s) in accordance with the provisions of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The company also stated that there is no information/announcement that may have a bearing on the price/volume behavior in the scrip.</p><ul><li>Subros Ltd clarifies that the significant increase in volume of its equity shares is market driven</li><li>The company has made all necessary disclosures to the Stock Exchange(s) as per SEBI regulations</li><li>There is no information/announcement that may affect the price/volume behavior of the scrip</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/854952f7-4fe8-4f40-bf0c-d82710d625b0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SUBROS LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>