<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 01:22:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[MUTHTFN] Muthoot Capital Services Ltd Issues Commercial Paper Worth INR 50 Crores at 8.7665% Discount Rate</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MUTHOOT+CAPITAL+SERVICES+LTD.&title=Muthoot+Capital+Services+Ltd+Issues+Commercial+Paper+Worth+INR+50+Crores+at+8.7665%25+Discount+Rate&newsId=b98886bd-7352-49ec-9b0b-f80e03c1b9db&token=Yjk4ODg2YmQtNzM1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b98886bd-7352-49ec-9b0b-f80e03c1b9db</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Muthoot Capital Services Limited has announced the issuance of Commercial Paper (CP) amounting to INR 50 Crores on January 21, 2026, with a maturity date of April 30, 2026. The CP carries an 8.7665% discount rate and will be traded at 97.6775. The allotment was made to Vivriti Alpha Debt Fund. CRISIL has assigned an A1+ rating to the CP.</p><ul><li>Muthoot Capital Services Ltd issues Commercial Paper worth INR 50 Crores</li><li>The CP has a discount rate of 8.7665% and will be traded at 97.6775</li><li>Maturity date set for April 30, 2026</li><li>Vivriti Alpha Debt Fund is the allottee</li><li>CRISIL assigns A1+ rating to the Commercial Paper</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d6e11886-e374-4246-b6fe-2cd175fed7dd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MUTHOOT CAPITAL SERVICES LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PNBHOUSING] PNB Housing Finance Identifies Fraud Involving Sarv Realtors, No Material Impact on Financials</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PNB+Housing+Finance+Ltd&title=PNB+Housing+Finance+Identifies+Fraud+Involving+Sarv+Realtors%2C+No+Material+Impact+on+Financials&newsId=c61610a1-884c-4d13-bcd4-3297659fbf5c&token=YzYxNjEwYTEtODg0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c61610a1-884c-4d13-bcd4-3297659fbf5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>PNB Housing Finance Ltd. has identified and declared a fraud involving M/s. Sarv Realtors Private Limited, amounting to Rs. 237.43 Crore. The account was already written-off in FY 2022-23, hence there is no material impact on the overall financials and operations of the Company. The Company is pursuing appropriate legal action. This disclosure is in compliance with Regulation 30 and 51 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations &amp; Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>PNB Housing Finance identified a fraud involving M/s. Sarv Realtors Private Limited</li><li>The fraud amount is Rs. 237.43 Crore</li><li>The account was written-off in FY 2022-23</li><li>No material impact on the Company&apos;s financials and operations</li><li>Legal action is being pursued by the Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4e91eaee-97f0-48e4-a5b9-02f14eccfd04.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PNB Housing Finance Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MUTHTFN] Muthoot Capital Services Ltd Appoints New Chief Internal Auditor and Re-appoints Chief Risk Officer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MUTHOOT+CAPITAL+SERVICES+LTD.&title=Muthoot+Capital+Services+Ltd+Appoints+New+Chief+Internal+Auditor+and+Re-appoints+Chief+Risk+Officer&newsId=bbf4a829-cdbf-4c01-93c9-4909e3d28b66&token=YmJmNGE4MjktY2Ri</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bbf4a829-cdbf-4c01-93c9-4909e3d28b66</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Muthoot Capital Services Ltd has appointed Mr. Krishnaraj S as the new Chief Internal Auditor for a term of 3 years starting from January 21, 2026. Mr. Krishnaraj S is a Chartered Accountant with over 19 years of experience in finance and risk management. He has been instrumental in designing internal controls and ensuring their effective implementation. The company has also re-appointed Mrs. Umadevi Pazhoor Unnikrishnan as the Chief Risk Officer for a term of 3 years starting from March 22, 2026. Mrs. Unnikrishnan has over 18 years of experience in banking, specializing in credit appraisal, credit risk, market risk, and operational risk.</p><ul><li>Mr. Krishnaraj S appointed as Chief Internal Auditor for a term of 3 years starting from January 21, 2026.</li><li>Mr. Krishnaraj S is a Chartered Accountant with over 19 years of experience in finance and risk management.</li><li>Mrs. Umadevi Pazhoor Unnikrishnan re-appointed as Chief Risk Officer for a term of 3 years starting from March 22, 2026.</li><li>Mrs. Unnikrishnan has over 18 years of experience in banking, specializing in credit appraisal, credit risk, market risk, and operational risk.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fbb1549c-8c11-4d40-bb29-67fc505b3bd2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MUTHOOT CAPITAL SERVICES LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WITS] Wherrelz IT Solutions Ltd Postpones Board Meeting to 24th January 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Wherrelz+IT+Solutions+Ltd&title=Wherrelz+IT+Solutions+Ltd+Postpones+Board+Meeting+to+24th+January+2026&newsId=3ab826b5-8d79-4dd1-a8c1-bb716931a4e6&token=M2FiODI2YjUtOGQ3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ab826b5-8d79-4dd1-a8c1-bb716931a4e6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Wherrelz IT Solutions Ltd has postponed its Board Meeting, originally scheduled for 21st January 2026 at 11:30 A.M., due to unavoidable reasons. The meeting will now take place on Saturday, 24th January 2026 at 4.45 P.M., virtually at the registered office of the company. The agenda remains unchanged and will be considered at the rescheduled meeting.</p><ul><li>Wherrelz IT Solutions Ltd postpones its Board Meeting to 24th January 2026</li><li>The original date for the Board Meeting was 21st January 2026 at 11:30 A.M.</li><li>The postponement is due to unavoidable reasons</li><li>The meeting will now take place at 4.45 P.M.</li><li>The agenda for the meeting remains unaltered</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c23128c2-0a22-41ad-9846-ba56b8e9ff96.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Wherrelz IT Solutions Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WAAREEENER] Waaree Energies Delivers Record-Breaking Quarterly Results with 118.81% YoY Revenue Growth and 167.16% YoY EBITDA Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Waaree+Energies+Ltd&title=Waaree+Energies+Delivers+Record-Breaking+Quarterly+Results+with+118.81%25+YoY+Revenue+Growth+and+167.16%25+YoY+EBITDA+Growth&newsId=9d5a64b1-b3b7-467d-806e-b48755c7053f&token=OWQ1YTY0YjEtYjNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d5a64b1-b3b7-467d-806e-b48755c7053f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Waaree Energies Limited, a leading renewable energy company, has reported record-breaking quarterly results for Q3 FY26. The company&apos;s revenue from operation stood at INR 7,565.05 Crores, marking an impressive 118.81% YoY growth. EBITDA for the quarter stood at INR 1,928.15 Crores, reporting a growth of 167.16% YoY with margins of 25.49%. Profit After Tax (PAT) of INR 1,106.79 Crores, reflecting a substantial 118.35% YoY surge. The company has also secured a record order inflow of INR 60,000 Crores, ensuring sustained visibility for the years ahead. Waaree is accelerating its transformation into an integrated clean energy solutions provider, strengthening adjacencies across BESS, inverter, transformer, Renewable Power Infrastructure and green hydrogen electrolyser, creating a resilient and future-ready portfolio.</p><ul><li>Achieved 3.51 GW module production in Q3 FY26, driven by robust operational focus</li><li>Achieved 0.75 GW Cell production in Q3 FY26, driven by robust operational focus</li><li>Reported quarterly revenue from operation of INR 7,565.05 Crores, marking an impressive 118.81% YoY growth</li><li>EBITDA for the quarter stood at INR 1,928.15 Crores reporting a growth of 167.16% YoY with margins of 25.49%</li><li>Profit After Tax (PAT) of INR 1,106.79 Crores, reflecting a substantial 118.35% YoY surge</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1ca2c199-3bd5-4ddf-b15d-2344c965a8ef.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Waaree Energies Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TATVA] Tatva Chintan Pharma Chem Ltd Announces Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Tatva+Chintan+Pharma+Chem+Ltd&title=Tatva+Chintan+Pharma+Chem+Ltd+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=a7992916-78f5-447b-8075-c1c4cf949741&token=YTc5OTI5MTYtNzhm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a7992916-78f5-447b-8075-c1c4cf949741</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:47:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tatva Chintan Pharma Chem Ltd, a specialty chemicals company, announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31 December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations was INR 1,385.88 million for Q3 and INR 3,636.31 million for the nine months period. The net profit before tax for Q3 was INR 187.92 million and INR 381.89 million for the nine months period. The company&apos;s net profit after tax for Q3 was INR 159.84 million and INR 300.58 million for the nine months period. The results were reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for Q3 2025 was INR 1,385.88 million</li><li>Revenue from operations for nine months ended 31 December 2025 was INR 3,636.31 million</li><li>Net profit before tax for Q3 2025 was INR 187.92 million</li><li>Net profit before tax for nine months ended 31 December 2025 was INR 381.89 million</li><li>Net profit after tax for Q3 2025 was INR 159.84 million</li><li>Net profit after tax for nine months ended 31 December 2025 was INR 300.58 million</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3712cb12-772f-43ef-be74-ffefa4c84744.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Tatva Chintan Pharma Chem Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PARMCOS-B] Paramount Cosmetics India Ltd Announces Cut-Off Date and Remote E-Voting Date for 01st Extraordinary General Meeting for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PARAMOUNT+COSMETICS+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Paramount+Cosmetics+India+Ltd+Announces+Cut-Off+Date+and+Remote+E-Voting+Date+for+01st+Extraordinary+General+Meeting+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=78add800-05c8-4558-bcbc-1e68eea9b784&token=NzhhZGQ4MDAtMDVj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78add800-05c8-4558-bcbc-1e68eea9b784</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:47:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Paramount Cosmetics India Ltd has informed the cut-off date and remote e-voting date for the 01st Extraordinary General Meeting for the Financial Year 2025-26. The Register of Members and Share Transfer Books of the Company will remain closed from Saturday, February 07, 2026 to Friday, February 13, 2026 (both days inclusive) for the purpose of the meeting. The company is providing its Members, facility to exercise their vote on the resolutions proposed through ‘Remote e-voting’ or ‘e-voting at the EGM’. The remote e-Voting facility for the Extraordinary General Meeting will commence on Tuesday, February 10, 2026, at 9:00 A.M. (IST) and end on Thursday, February 22, 2026, at 5:00 P.M. (IST).</p><ul><li>Paramount Cosmetics India Ltd announces cut-off date and remote e-voting date for 01st Extraordinary General Meeting for FY 2025-26</li><li>The Register of Members and Share Transfer Books of the Company will remain closed from February 07, 2026 to February 13, 2026</li><li>The company is providing its Members, facility to exercise their vote on the resolutions proposed through ‘Remote e-voting’ or ‘e-voting at the EGM’</li><li>The remote e-Voting facility for the Extraordinary General Meeting will commence on February 10, 2026, and end on February 22, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/42ab86f0-7cfc-45e4-80dc-1ad77ffdca40.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PARAMOUNT COSMETICS (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GRAVITA] Gravita India Ltd. Announces Q3 and Nine-Months Results for 2025, Appoints New Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GRAVITA+INDIA+LTD.&title=Gravita+India+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+Nine-Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Appoints+New+Independent+Director&newsId=82afb582-b748-4302-bbdf-6f54096bc5ea&token=ODJhZmI1ODItYjc0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">82afb582-b748-4302-bbdf-6f54096bc5ea</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:47:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gravita India Ltd. announced the outcome of their Board Meeting held on 21st January 2026. The company approved the un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. Mr. Bhupendra Kumar Dak was recommended for appointment as a Non-Executive Independent Director, subject to shareholder approval. The company&apos;s revenue from operations and total income have increased compared to the previous year&apos;s corresponding period.</p><ul><li>Gravita India Ltd. announced the Q3 and nine-months results for 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s Board approved the un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025.</li><li>Mr. Bhupendra Kumar Dak recommended for appointment as a Non-Executive Independent Director, subject to shareholder approval.</li><li>Revenue from operations and total income have increased compared to the previous year&apos;s corresponding period.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b3bc453d-b721-4ee4-b6df-dc714478277f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GRAVITA INDIA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SASHWAT] Sashwat Technocrats Ltd Announces Q3 Results for FY2025-26 with Limited Review</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sashwat+Technocrats+Limited&title=Sashwat+Technocrats+Ltd+Announces+Q3+Results+for+FY2025-26+with+Limited+Review&newsId=ce1233a4-45a8-416b-bdd6-faa937f1588e&token=Y2UxMjMzYTQtNDVh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce1233a4-45a8-416b-bdd6-faa937f1588e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:46:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sashwat Technocrats Ltd has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at INR X,XXX (previous year INR Y,XXX) and other income is INR Z,XXX (previous year INR A,XXX). The total income for the quarter is INR B,XXX (previous year INR C,XXX). The total expenses for the quarter are INR D,XXX (previous year INR E,XXX). The profit before exceptional items and tax is INR F,XXX (previous year INR G,XXX). The company has reported an exceptional item of INR H,XXX. The profit before tax is INR I,XXX (previous year INR J,XXX). The tax expenses for the quarter are INR K,XXX (previous year INR L,XXX). The net profit after tax is INR M,XXX (previous year INR N,XXX). The total comprehensive income for the period after tax is INR O,XXX (previous year INR P,XXX). The profit attributable to equityholders of the parent company is INR Q,XXX (previous year INR R,XXX). The debt equity ratio is INR S,XXX and the debt service coverage ratio is INR T,XXX. The interest service coverage ratio is INR U,XXX. The earning per share is INR V,XXX.</p><ul><li>Unaudited financial results for Q3 FY2025-26 announced</li><li>Revenue from operations stands at INR X,XXX</li><li>Profit before tax is INR I,XXX</li><li>Net profit after tax is INR M,XXX</li><li>Debt equity ratio is INR S,XXX</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7269bcd7-b870-4495-b81f-a29da548e12c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sashwat Technocrats Limited | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NETTLINX] Nettlinx Ltd to Consider Unaudited Financial Results for Q4 2025 in Board Meeting on 28th January 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NETTLINX+LTD.&title=Nettlinx+Ltd+to+Consider+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q4+2025+in+Board+Meeting+on+28th+January+2026&newsId=68cd6c44-5219-41e2-8974-12b7d51968f2&token=NjhjZDZjNDQtNTIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68cd6c44-5219-41e2-8974-12b7d51968f2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:46:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Nettlinx Ltd, a company listed on the BSE, has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 28th January 2026 to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended 31.12.2025. This includes both standalone and consolidated financial results, along with the Limited Review Report for the same period. The meeting will also consider any other business with the permission of the Chair.</p><ul><li>Nettlinx Ltd to consider unaudited financial results for Q4 2025</li><li>Board meeting scheduled on 28th January 2026</li><li>Includes standalone and consolidated financial results</li><li>Limited Review Report for Q4 2025 will also be considered</li><li>Meeting will consider any other business with the permission of the Chair</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6de80e34-ac36-4817-a797-7d2c72e4934d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NETTLINX LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>