<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:18:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[STYLEBAAZA] Baazar Style Retail Ltd. to Raise Funds Through Issuance of Equity Warrants to Cupid Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Baazar+Style+Retail+Ltd&title=Baazar+Style+Retail+Ltd.+to+Raise+Funds+Through+Issuance+of+Equity+Warrants+to+Cupid+Limited&newsId=0302f5b5-d4b5-4510-a318-51c89c81f0c9&token=MDMwMmY1YjUtZDRi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0302f5b5-d4b5-4510-a318-51c89c81f0c9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Baazar Style Retail Ltd. has approved the issuance of 1,01,00,000 (One Crore One Lakh Only) Equity warrants at an issue price of X 328.25/- per equity warrant to Cupid Limited. This is a preferential issue, convertible into equivalent number of fully paid equity shares of the Company having face value of X5/- (Rupee five only) each, in one or more tranches within a period of 18 months from the date of allotment. The total amount for this issuance is 33,31,53,25,000/- (Rupees Three Hundred and Thirty-one Crores Fifty-Three Lakhs and Twenty-Five Thousand only). Monarch Networth Capital Limited is acting as a sole advisor to this transaction.</p><ul><li>Baazar Style Retail Ltd. to raise funds through issuance of equity warrants</li><li>1,01,00,000 Equity warrants to be issued at an issue price of X 328.25/- per warrant</li><li>Convertible into equivalent number of fully paid equity shares of the Company</li><li>Issue price of X 328.25/- per equity warrant</li><li>Monarch Networth Capital Limited acting as a sole advisor</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ae15dd8d-fb9a-4e6f-bbd0-29fcfdf571e6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Baazar Style Retail Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDUSTOWER] Indus Towers Ltd Incorporates Step-Down Subsidiary in Uganda</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Indus+Towers+Ltd&title=Indus+Towers+Ltd+Incorporates+Step-Down+Subsidiary+in+Uganda&newsId=a40db2bd-1f31-4fe1-b668-ff729b3f5c26&token=YTQwZGIyYmQtMWYz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a40db2bd-1f31-4fe1-b668-ff729b3f5c26</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indus Towers Limited has informed the Exchange regarding the incorporation of a step-down subsidiary in Uganda, Indus Infra Uganda Limited. The new subsidiary, established for telecommunication towers, masts, poles, antennas, and other related infrastructure, will have a share capital of UGX 2,000,000,000. Indus Towers Limited will contribute to the initial share capital in cash at face value, acquiring 100% shareholding and control. The subsidiary was incorporated on January 20, 2026, in Uganda and is yet to commence its business operations.</p><ul><li>Indus Towers Limited incorporates a step-down subsidiary in Uganda.</li><li>Subsidiary named Indus Infra Uganda Limited with a share capital of UGX 2,000,000,000.</li><li>Indus Towers Limited to contribute to the initial share capital in cash.</li><li>100% shareholding and control acquired by Indus Towers Limited.</li><li>Subsidiary incorporated on January 20, 2026, in Uganda and yet to start operations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/61c78ced-14a5-429e-9178-4fc5c5420160.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Indus Towers Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STYLEBAAZA] Baazar Style Retail Ltd. to Raise Funds Through Issuance of Equity Warrants to Cupid Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Baazar+Style+Retail+Ltd&title=Baazar+Style+Retail+Ltd.+to+Raise+Funds+Through+Issuance+of+Equity+Warrants+to+Cupid+Limited&newsId=1ecc00e0-b607-42d7-acae-ff5f80d29a00&token=MWVjYzAwZTAtYjYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1ecc00e0-b607-42d7-acae-ff5f80d29a00</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Baazar Style Retail Ltd. has approved the issuance of 1,01,00,000 (One Crore One Lakh Only) Equity warrants to Cupid Limited at an issue price of = 328.25/- per equity warrant. This decision was made at the Board of Directors meeting held on January 20, 2026. The funds raised will aggregate to = 3,31,53,25,000/- (Rupees Three Hundred and Thirty-one Crores Fifty-Three Lakhs and Twenty-Five Thousand only). The warrants are convertible into equivalent number of fully paid equity shares of the Company having face value of %5/- (Rupee five only) each, in one or more tranches within a period of 18 months from the date of allotment. Monarch Networth Capital Limited is acting as a sole advisor to this transaction.</p><ul><li>Baazar Style Retail Ltd. to raise funds through issuance of equity warrants</li><li>1,01,00,000 Equity warrants to be issued to Cupid Limited</li><li>Issue price set at = 328.25/- per equity warrant</li><li>Funds raised to aggregate to = 3,31,53,25,000/-</li><li>Warrants convertible into equivalent number of fully paid equity shares within 18 months</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9ee0f1f2-f82a-42e1-b95a-e62471f04770.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Baazar Style Retail Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SERIND] SER Industries Ltd: Appointment of New Directors, Changes in Designation, and Proposed Acquisitions</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SER+Industries+Ltd&title=SER+Industries+Ltd%3A+Appointment+of+New+Directors%2C+Changes+in+Designation%2C+and+Proposed+Acquisitions&newsId=638dcfcc-8f5b-4415-b8c3-4d1b58aed71b&token=NjM4ZGNmY2MtOGY1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">638dcfcc-8f5b-4415-b8c3-4d1b58aed71b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SER Industries Ltd has announced several significant changes and proposals in its recent board meeting. The board approved the appointment of Mr. Ayush Munnalal Sharma as an Additional Director (Non-Executive and Independent) for a term of 5 years. Mr. Sunil Kumar Shahi&apos;s designation was changed from Executive Director to Managing Director and Chairman of the Company for a term of 5 years. The board also approved the appointment of Mr. Shrenik Rajiv Karnawat as the Chief Financial Officer (CFO). Furthermore, the board considered increasing the authorized capital from Rs. 6,00,00,000 to Rs. 46,00,00,000 and approved the proposal to be placed before the shareholders. The board also approved the limits of INR 200 Crores for proposals requiring authorisation under Section 180(1)(a) and Section 180(1)(c) of the Companies Act, 2013. The board also approved granting of loans, guarantees, providing securities, or making investments exceeding the prescribed limits under Section 186 up to INR 800 Crores, subject to shareholder approval. The board also approved the proposed acquisition of upto 100% of SNA Milk and Milk Products Limited and DFSU Farmer Connect Private Limited against share swap by way issuance of securities of the Company on a preferential basis.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Ayush Munnalal Sharma as Additional Director</li><li>Change in designation of Mr. Sunil Kumar Shahi to Managing Director and Chairman</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Shrenik Rajiv Karnawat as CFO</li><li>Proposal to increase authorized capital</li><li>Approval of limits for proposals under Section 180(1)(a) and Section 180(1)(c)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/036c27bb-57c8-450d-8b70-a6bfb0b5fcd9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SER Industries Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SERIND] SER Industries Ltd Appoints New CFO and Approves Key Changes in Board and Acquisitions</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SER+Industries+Ltd&title=SER+Industries+Ltd+Appoints+New+CFO+and+Approves+Key+Changes+in+Board+and+Acquisitions&newsId=d7655e66-7bdf-4f9e-80e5-b179ec167bd9&token=ZDc2NTVlNjYtN2Jk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7655e66-7bdf-4f9e-80e5-b179ec167bd9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SER Industries Ltd has made several key announcements in its recent board meeting. The company has appointed Mr. Shrenik Rajiv Karnawat as the Chief Financial Officer (CFO). Furthermore, the board has approved changes in designation and appointment of new directors. The company has also approved the acquisition of upto 100% of SNA Milk and Milk Products Limited and DFSU Farmer Connect Private Limited, with the consideration being share swap. These decisions are subject to approval from shareholders and regulatory authorities.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Shrenik Rajiv Karnawat as CFO</li><li>Change in designation of Mr. Sunil Kumar Shahi from Executive Director to Managing Director and Chairman</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Ayush Munnalal Sharma as Additional Director (Non-Executive and Independent)</li><li>Proposed acquisition of upto 100% of SNA Milk and Milk Products Limited against share swap</li><li>Proposed acquisition of upto 100% of DFSU Farmer Connect Private Limited and issuance of securities against acquisition</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/171dd181-8483-47bf-835a-1bf03a43a77a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SER Industries Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ORIENTTR] Orient Tradelink Ltd Allots 3,32,454 Equity Shares at INR 22 Each, Increasing Paid-Up Equity Share Capital</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ORIENT+TRADELINK+LTD.&title=Orient+Tradelink+Ltd+Allots+3%2C32%2C454+Equity+Shares+at+INR+22+Each%2C+Increasing+Paid-Up+Equity+Share+Capital&newsId=87cae792-f8ea-4259-b2b0-bbc3c7e2a5f2&token=ODdjYWU3OTItZjhl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">87cae792-f8ea-4259-b2b0-bbc3c7e2a5f2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Orient Tradelink Ltd has allotted 3,32,454 equity shares of INR 10 each at a price of INR 22 per share, comprising of a premium of INR 12 per share. The allotment was made to six allottees: Sunita Panwar, Shikha, Bhawna Shadija, Bhim Raj Singh, Vivek Giri Maharaj, and Alisha. The paid-up equity share capital of the company has increased from INR 38,35,31,340 to INR 38,68,55,880 as a result of this allotment. The allotment was approved in a board meeting held on Tuesday, 20th January 2026.</p><ul><li>Orient Tradelink Ltd has allotted 3,32,454 equity shares at INR 22 per share with a premium of INR 12 per share.</li><li>The allotment has increased the company&apos;s paid-up equity share capital from INR 38,35,31,340 to INR 38,68,55,880.</li><li>The allotment was made to six allottees: Sunita Panwar, Shikha, Bhawna Shadija, Bhim Raj Singh, Vivek Giri Maharaj, and Alisha.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/61514081-cb6e-46c3-81ac-5e21992845be.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ORIENT TRADELINK LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SERIND] SER Industries Ltd Announces Preferential Issue of Securities, Changes in Designation, and Acquisitions</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SER+Industries+Ltd&title=SER+Industries+Ltd+Announces+Preferential+Issue+of+Securities%2C+Changes+in+Designation%2C+and+Acquisitions&newsId=cc69c9c5-d654-469e-8335-fd17c53627dc&token=Y2M2OWM5YzUtZDY1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cc69c9c5-d654-469e-8335-fd17c53627dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SER Industries Ltd has announced a series of decisions in its board meeting held on Tuesday, 20th January 2026. The board has approved a change in designation of Mr. Sunil Kumar Shahi from Executive Director to Managing Director and Chairman of the Company for a term of 5 years. The board has also approved the appointment of Mr. Shrenik Rajiv Karnawat as the Chief Financial Officer (CFO) and Mr. Ayush Munnalal Sharma as an Additional Director (Non-Executive and Independent) for a term of 5 years. The board has also decided to place a revised proposal before the shareholders for an increase in the Authorized Share Capital of the Company. The board has evaluated and approved certain proposals under Section 180(1)(a) and Section 180(1)(c) of the Companies Act, 2013. The board has also approved granting of loans, guarantees, providing securities, or making investments exceeding the prescribed limits under Section 186. The company has also approved the proposed acquisition of upto 100% of SNA Milk and Milk Products Limited and DFSU Farmer Connect Private Limited against share swap by way issuance of securities of the Company on a preferential basis.</p><ul><li>Change in designation of Mr. Sunil Kumar Shahi to Managing Director and Chairman</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Shrenik Rajiv Karnawat as CFO</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Ayush Munnalal Sharma as Additional Director</li><li>Proposed increase in Authorized Share Capital</li><li>Approval of proposals under Section 180(1)(a) and Section 180(1)(c) of the Companies Act, 2013</li><li>Approval of granting of loans, guarantees, providing securities, or making investments exceeding the prescribed limits under Section 186</li><li>Proposed acquisition of upto 100% of SNA Milk and Milk Products Limited and DFSU Farmer Connect Private Limited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b884acfb-35e4-4f47-b493-2a677d3b410b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SER Industries Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ORIENTTR] Orient Tradelink Ltd Allots 3,32,454 Equity Shares at INR 22 Each, Increasing Paid-up Equity Share Capital</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ORIENT+TRADELINK+LTD.&title=Orient+Tradelink+Ltd+Allots+3%2C32%2C454+Equity+Shares+at+INR+22+Each%2C+Increasing+Paid-up+Equity+Share+Capital&newsId=95941670-ee75-4411-8ac0-b904d6692933&token=OTU5NDE2NzAtZWU3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95941670-ee75-4411-8ac0-b904d6692933</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:01:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Orient Tradelink Ltd has allotted 3,32,454 equity shares of INR 10 each at a price of INR 22 per share, comprising of a premium of INR 12 per share. The allotment was made to six allottees: Sunita Panwar, Shikha, Bhawna Shadija, Bhim Raj Singh, Vivek Giri Maharaj, and Alisha. The paid-up equity share capital of the company has increased from INR 38,35,31,340 to INR 38,68,55,880 as a result of this allotment. The allotment was approved in a board meeting held on Tuesday, 20th January 2026.</p><ul><li>Orient Tradelink Ltd has allotted 3,32,454 equity shares at INR 22 per share with a premium of INR 12 per share.</li><li>The allotment was made to six allottees: Sunita Panwar, Shikha, Bhawna Shadija, Bhim Raj Singh, Vivek Giri Maharaj, and Alisha.</li><li>The paid-up equity share capital of the company has increased from INR 38,35,31,340 to INR 38,68,55,880.</li><li>The allotment was approved in a board meeting held on Tuesday, 20th January 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1a99e1d5-51b6-49c1-843d-1ae04f40fe3b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ORIENT TRADELINK LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CENTUM] Centum Electronics Secures Prestigious Order from Garden Reach Shipbuilders &amp; Engineers for Advanced Naval Navigation Systems</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CENTUM+ELECTRONICS+LTD.&title=Centum+Electronics+Secures+Prestigious+Order+from+Garden+Reach+Shipbuilders+%26+Engineers+for+Advanced+Naval+Navigation+Systems&newsId=8571d761-8bbf-4550-9b63-25c5c929d782&token=ODU3MWQ3NjEtOGJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8571d761-8bbf-4550-9b63-25c5c929d782</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Centum Electronics Ltd has received an order from Garden Reach Shipbuilders &amp; Engineers Limited (GRSE) for the supply of Advanced Naval Navigation Systems. This order is a significant milestone for the company, adding a new system tailored for deployment on frontline warships to Centum’s suite of offerings. This opportunity positions Centum to expand its presence in the defence maritime domain and underscores its commitment to delivering cutting-edge, mission-critical technologies to India’s armed forces. The order is worth Rs. 29.40 crores (Excluding Taxes) and is to be executed by February, 2028.</p><ul><li>Centum Electronics has secured a prestigious order from Garden Reach Shipbuilders &amp; Engineers Limited (GRSE) for Advanced Naval Navigation Systems.</li><li>The order is a significant milestone for the company, adding a new system tailored for deployment on frontline warships.</li><li>This opportunity positions Centum to expand its presence in the defence maritime domain.</li><li>The order is worth Rs. 29.40 crores (Excluding Taxes).</li><li>The order is to be executed by February, 2028.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/de71d759-a681-4f05-8103-070d17a9ee56.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CENTUM ELECTRONICS LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RBA] Open Offer by Lenexis Foodworks Private Limited and Others for 26.00% Stake in Restaurant Brands Asia Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Restaurant+Brands+Asia+Ltd&title=Open+Offer+by+Lenexis+Foodworks+Private+Limited+and+Others+for+26.00%25+Stake+in+Restaurant+Brands+Asia+Limited&newsId=9f545fae-3cf2-4ae6-a83f-3d7e8aa3eedc&token=OWY1NDVmYWUtM2Nm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9f545fae-3cf2-4ae6-a83f-3d7e8aa3eedc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Open Offer</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Lenexis Foodworks Private Limited, Aayush Agrawal Trust, Inspira Foodworks Private Limited, and Aayush Madhusudan Agrawal, along with Inspira Agro Trading LLC as a person acting in concert, have announced an open offer to acquire up to 20,80,61,717 Equity Shares of Restaurant Brands Asia Limited at a price of INR 70.00 per Equity Share. The total consideration for the offer is up to INR 14,56,43,20,190. The offer is made in accordance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</p><ul><li>Open offer for acquisition of up to 20,80,61,717 Equity Shares of Restaurant Brands Asia Limited</li><li>Offer price is INR 70.00 per Equity Share</li><li>Total consideration is up to INR 14,56,43,20,190</li><li>Offer made by Lenexis Foodworks Private Limited, Aayush Agrawal Trust, Inspira Foodworks Private Limited, and Aayush Madhusudan Agrawal, with Inspira Agro Trading LLC as a person acting in concert</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/285710fd-ecf8-4471-b934-345e937f7170.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Restaurant Brands Asia Ltd | Category: Open Offer</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>