<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:57:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[AAYUSH] Aayush Wellness Ltd Announces Q3 and Nine-Months Results for 2025, Revenue from Operations Increases</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Aayush+Food+and+Herbs+Ltd&title=Aayush+Wellness+Ltd+Announces+Q3+and+Nine-Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Revenue+from+Operations+Increases&newsId=3deff33c-1e7d-4d5f-8f22-60d2c8b75d7d&token=M2RlZmYzM2MtMWU3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3deff33c-1e7d-4d5f-8f22-60d2c8b75d7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 18:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Aayush Wellness Ltd has announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations has increased for the quarter and year to date. The board of directors has approved the financial results in a meeting held on February 12, 2026. The company&apos;s statement of unaudited financial results is prepared in accordance with Indian Accounting Standard 34 and other accounting principles generally accepted in India.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter and year to date has increased</li><li>The unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025 have been approved by the board of directors</li><li>The statement of unaudited financial results is prepared in accordance with Indian Accounting Standard 34 and other accounting principles generally accepted in India</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/87686d57-e3fb-477f-b212-6b1b55a13e43.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Aayush Food and Herbs Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AAYUSH] Aayush Wellness Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Aayush+Food+and+Herbs+Ltd&title=Aayush+Wellness+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=fd6afc69-f88f-486f-9a3f-e927e866bc6c&token=ZmQ2YWZjNjktZjg4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd6afc69-f88f-486f-9a3f-e927e866bc6c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Aayush Wellness Ltd has announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31 December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations for the quarter and period ended December 31, 2025 includes revenue arising from trading in shares and securities. The board has approved the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results. The company&apos;s total income stands at Rs. 4,516.19 lakhs for the quarter and Rs. 10,705.27 lakhs for the nine months ended December 31, 2025.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter and period ended December 31, 2025 includes revenue arising from trading in shares and securities.</li><li>The board has approved the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results.</li><li>Total income stands at Rs. 4,516.19 lakhs for the quarter and Rs. 10,705.27 lakhs for the nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/25c358ec-1856-422b-aa3b-7b41d0291c67.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Aayush Food and Herbs Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FRONTSP] Frontier Springs Ltd: Delay in Q3,9M Financial Results Due to Auditor&apos;s Non-receipt of Limited Review Report</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=FRONTIER+SPRINGS+LTD.&title=Frontier+Springs+Ltd%3A+Delay+in+Q3%2C9M+Financial+Results+Due+to+Auditor%27s+Non-receipt+of+Limited+Review+Report&newsId=8a10dc9e-f023-4e8e-8131-db477789395d&token=OGExMGRjOWUtZjAy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a10dc9e-f023-4e8e-8131-db477789395d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:54:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Frontier Springs Ltd has delayed the release of its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025 due to the non-receipt of a Limited Review Report by the auditor. The delay is attributed to the website of the Institute of Chartered Accountants of India not working, preventing the generation of UDIN. The Board of Directors approved the un-audited financial results in a meeting on February 12, 2026. The company is forwarding the unaudited financial results and the limited review report for the quarter ended December 31, 2025.</p><ul><li>Delay in Q3,9M financial results due to non-receipt of Limited Review Report from the auditor</li><li>The delay is due to the website of the Institute of Chartered Accountants of India not working, preventing UDIN generation</li><li>Un-audited financial results for Q3,9M ended December 31, 2025 approved in a Board meeting on February 12, 2026</li><li>Frontier Springs Ltd forwarding unaudited financial results and limited review report for Q4 2025</li><li>Meeting commenced at 12:45 p.m. and concluded at 3:35 p.m.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c31a73f3-b271-466c-9be7-64f98f95692a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: FRONTIER SPRINGS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WATERBASE] Waterbase Ltd Announces Leadership Realignment: Ramakanth V. Akula to be Managing Director, Chola Varma Alluri to be Chief Executive Officer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=WATERBASE+LTD.&title=Waterbase+Ltd+Announces+Leadership+Realignment%3A+Ramakanth+V.+Akula+to+be+Managing+Director%2C+Chola+Varma+Alluri+to+be+Chief+Executive+Officer&newsId=27128405-61f2-4547-8ad6-bc1ddd25d8b0&token=MjcxMjg0MDUtNjFm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27128405-61f2-4547-8ad6-bc1ddd25d8b0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:46:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Leadership Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Waterbase Ltd, a leading company in its industry, has announced a leadership realignment effective April 1, 2026. The company&apos;s current Whole-Time Director &amp; Chief Executive Officer, Ramakanth V. Akula, will transition to the role of Managing Director. He will focus on strategic direction, capital allocation, stakeholder engagement, and long-term growth initiatives. Chola Varma Alluri, currently the Chief Operating Officer, will be elevated to Chief Executive Officer. He will be responsible for the overall management and day-to-day operations of the Company.</p><ul><li>Ramakanth V. Akula to transition to Managing Director role</li><li>Chola Varma Alluri to be appointed as Chief Executive Officer</li><li>Leadership realignment to enhance executive focus, governance structure, and scalability</li><li>Akula to focus on strategic direction and long-term growth</li><li>Alluri to oversee operational excellence and execution across business verticals</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1c09f26c-3bf5-4cc3-bcbc-01f4f21b74a9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: WATERBASE LTD. | Category: Leadership Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TINNATFL] Fratelli Vineyards Ltd Appoints Sanjay Kumar Jain as Additional Director, Reports Q3&amp;9MFY26 Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Tinna+Trade+Ltd&title=Fratelli+Vineyards+Ltd+Appoints+Sanjay+Kumar+Jain+as+Additional+Director%2C+Reports+Q3%269MFY26+Financial+Results&newsId=1c498609-85ab-44cd-8092-0d2e29102a03&token=MWM0OTg2MDktODVh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c498609-85ab-44cd-8092-0d2e29102a03</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:42:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Fratelli Vineyards Ltd has appointed Mr. Sanjay Kumar Jain as an Additional Director designated as Non-Executive Independent Director, effective from February 12, 2026. The company also released its un-audited standalone and consolidated Financial Results for the third quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025, along with the Statutory Auditor’s Limited Review Report. The Board of Directors also approved the reconstitution of the Committees of the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Sanjay Kumar Jain as Additional Director</li><li>Release of un-audited standalone and consolidated Financial Results for Q3&amp;9MFY26</li><li>Statutory Auditor’s Limited Review Report submitted</li><li>Reconstitution of the Committees of the Board of Directors</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6a395b07-1b56-4f40-96db-28967728df10.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Tinna Trade Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PERSISTENT] Persistent Systems Ltd Appoints Vikram Tulsyan as Senior Vice President and Senior Management Personnel</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PERSISTENT+SYSTEMS+LTD.&title=Persistent+Systems+Ltd+Appoints+Vikram+Tulsyan+as+Senior+Vice+President+and+Senior+Management+Personnel&newsId=9196dc2f-4326-43ce-be85-e518f7249a62&token=OTE5NmRjMmYtNDMy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9196dc2f-4326-43ce-be85-e518f7249a62</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Persistent Systems Ltd has appointed Mr. Vikram Tulsyan as the Senior Vice President (VP) and Senior Management Personnel (SMP) with effect from Thursday, February 12, 2026 (EST). Mr. Tulsyan is a seasoned finance professional with over 20 years of experience, including 6 years in senior leadership roles. His core expertise includes business finance strategy, P&amp;L management, Financial Planning &amp; Analysis, cost management, and financial governance. He brings deep experience in strategic deal structuring, commercial negotiations, global billing and taxation, and oversight of large capex and vendor procurements. This appointment is in line with the company&apos;s commitment to strengthen its leadership and financial strategy.</p><ul><li>Persistent Systems Ltd appoints Vikram Tulsyan as Senior Vice President and Senior Management Personnel</li><li>Mr. Tulsyan is a seasoned finance professional with over 20 years of experience</li><li>His core expertise includes business finance strategy, P&amp;L management, and financial governance</li><li>He brings deep experience in strategic deal structuring and commercial negotiations</li><li>This appointment is in line with the company&apos;s commitment to strengthen its leadership and financial strategy</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/90e6c814-987b-4e12-afeb-cafa1863ec3a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PERSISTENT SYSTEMS LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SYNTHFO] Synthiko Foils Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025, Revenue from Operations at ₹ 2,146.02 Lakhs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SYNTHIKO+FOILS+LTD.&title=Synthiko+Foils+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Revenue+from+Operations+at+%E2%82%B9+2%2C146.02+Lakhs&newsId=6a57b9a1-5689-4c18-880b-550ec67ffedd&token=NmE1N2I5YTEtNTY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a57b9a1-5689-4c18-880b-550ec67ffedd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:41:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Synthiko Foils Ltd has announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations for the quarter is ₹ 702.64 Lakhs and for the nine months is ₹ 2,146.02 Lakhs. The Board of Directors approved the results in their meeting held on February 12, 2026. The company has transferred its business undertaking for manufacturing foils and acquired 100% equity share capital of DC&amp;T Global Private Limited and 99% of BESS Limited. The company&apos;s equity shares have been consolidated from a face value of ₹ 5/- each to ₹ 10/- each.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter is ₹ 702.64 Lakhs and for the nine months is ₹ 2,146.02 Lakhs.</li><li>Company has transferred its business undertaking for manufacturing foils.</li><li>Acquired 100% equity share capital of DC&amp;T Global Private Limited and 99% of BESS Limited.</li><li>Equity shares have been consolidated from a face value of ₹ 5/- each to ₹ 10/- each.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b33070fd-ba5d-4df0-b982-5aacb00f9482.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SYNTHIKO FOILS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZEEMEDIA] Zee Media Corporation Ltd Faces Arbitration Proceedings by Asia Satellite Telecommunications Company</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Zee+Media+Corporation+Limited&title=Zee+Media+Corporation+Ltd+Faces+Arbitration+Proceedings+by+Asia+Satellite+Telecommunications+Company&newsId=74d129ca-e20b-490f-8d72-ecdc8e311ccf&token=NzRkMTI5Y2EtZTIw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74d129ca-e20b-490f-8d72-ecdc8e311ccf</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:41:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Zee Media Corporation Ltd has informed the stock exchange about arbitration proceedings initiated against the company by Asia Satellite Telecommunications Company Limited, a company incorporated in Hong Kong. The proceedings have been initiated before the Singapore International Arbitration Centre (SIAC) with respect to the outstanding amount as alleged to be payable by the Company under the Transponder Capacity Agreement (TCA). The Company became aware of the Notice on February 9, 2026. The TCA has already been terminated. The Opposing party has claimed an amount of USD 1,553,482.05/- (inclusive of interest and liquidated damages). The Company will be taking necessary advice from the legal counsel and will defend the matter accordingly. The financial impact will be limited to the extent of the final order.</p><ul><li>Arbitration proceedings initiated against Zee Media Corporation Ltd by Asia Satellite Telecommunications Company Limited</li><li>Proceedings filed before the Singapore International Arbitration Centre (SIAC)</li><li>Amount in dispute is USD 1,553,482.05/- (inclusive of interest and liquidated damages)</li><li>Company to defend the matter with necessary legal advice</li><li>Financial impact limited to the extent of the final order</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a6342bf8-4534-4f18-9d22-e83300964caf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Zee Media Corporation Limited | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EXCELSOFT] Excelsoft Technologies Ltd: Monitoring Agency Report Submitted for Q3 2025, No Deviations Observed</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Excelsoft+Technologies+Ltd&title=Excelsoft+Technologies+Ltd%3A+Monitoring+Agency+Report+Submitted+for+Q3+2025%2C+No+Deviations+Observed&newsId=a7e3c784-82d6-43ee-b97e-c08cf6d69c77&token=YTdlM2M3ODQtODJk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a7e3c784-82d6-43ee-b97e-c08cf6d69c77</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:34:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Excelsoft Technologies Ltd, a company in the Information Technology - IT Services - IT Enabled Services sector, has submitted a Monitoring Agency Report for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The report, issued by CARE Ratings Limited, indicates no deviation from the objects of the IPO. The utilization of proceeds is as per the objects in the offer document, although a part of the funds utilized towards the first object was routed through the company’s OD account. The report also mentions that all necessary Government/statutory approvals have been obtained and there are no major deviations observed.</p><ul><li>Monitoring Agency Report submitted for Q3 2025</li><li>No deviations from the objects of the IPO observed</li><li>Utilization of proceeds as per the offer document</li><li>Part of the funds utilized towards the first object was routed through the company’s OD account</li><li>All necessary Government/statutory approvals obtained</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/58933b98-5475-49f5-9320-594c0401febd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Excelsoft Technologies Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TINNATFL] Fratelli Vineyards Ltd Announces Q3 &amp; 9M FY26 Financial Results, Appoints New Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Tinna+Trade+Ltd&title=Fratelli+Vineyards+Ltd+Announces+Q3+%26+9M+FY26+Financial+Results%2C+Appoints+New+Independent+Director&newsId=d40269ab-72cb-4d9d-b957-339c9ca9d271&token=ZDQwMjY5YWItNzJj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d40269ab-72cb-4d9d-b957-339c9ca9d271</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 17:32:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Fratelli Vineyards Ltd, formerly known as Tinna Trade Limited, announced its un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended on 31st December 2025. The company reported a revenue from operations of 12,471.59 lakhs for the nine months period. The Board also approved the appointment of Mr. Sanjay Kumar Jain as an Additional Director designated as Non-Executive Independent Director, effective from 12th February 2026.</p><ul><li>Fratelli Vineyards Ltd announced Q3 &amp; 9M FY26 financial results</li><li>Revenue from operations for 9M FY26 was 12,471.59 lakhs</li><li>Mr. Sanjay Kumar Jain appointed as Additional Director and Non-Executive Independent Director</li><li>Appointment effective from 12th February 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/696fe59a-f18b-44a7-b6b8-cd69feed0adc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Tinna Trade Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>