<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:31:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[RCIIND] RCI Industries Approves Un-audited Financial Results for Q3 &amp; Q4 2025, Post Acquisition by JTL Industries</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RCI+Industries+%26+Technologies+Ltd&title=RCI+Industries+Approves+Un-audited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+%26+Q4+2025%2C+Post+Acquisition+by+JTL+Industries&newsId=7c1accc2-96eb-414b-b9be-72f44fc40ec1&token=N2MxYWNjYzItOTZl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c1accc2-96eb-414b-b9be-72f44fc40ec1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>RCI Industries &amp; Technologies Ltd. has approved the un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31.12.2025. The company has been acquired by JTL Industries Limited as per the approved resolution plan. The financial results have been prepared in accordance with Ind AS and other accounting principles generally accepted in India.</p><ul><li>RCI Industries approved un-audited financial results for Q3 &amp; Q4 2025</li><li>Company has been acquired by JTL Industries Limited</li><li>Financial results prepared in accordance with Ind AS and other accounting principles</li><li>Company has fully extinguished the Equity Shares of previous promoters</li><li>Equity share capital of the Company now stands at 10526315 equity shares of Rs. 10 each</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6101c0ca-04bf-4ac3-b375-4e4440148e20.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RCI Industries & Technologies Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZYDUSLIFE] Zydus Lifesciences Ltd Dissolves Wholly Owned Subsidiary Ampliman 1, France</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Zydus+Lifesciences+Ltd&title=Zydus+Lifesciences+Ltd+Dissolves+Wholly+Owned+Subsidiary+Ampliman+1%2C+France&newsId=62853eaf-0ff1-4129-8e74-2479de5c2df9&token=NjI4NTNlYWYtMGZm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62853eaf-0ff1-4129-8e74-2479de5c2df9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Subsidiary Dissolution</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Zydus Lifesciences Ltd has informed about the dissolution of its wholly owned subsidiary, Ampliman 1, France, which is a step down wholly owned subsidiary of the Company. This dissolution is a part of the series of dissolutions of Auroralux S.A.S., Luxembourg and Ampliman 2, France, which were holding companies of Amplitude Surgical, France. Upon dissolution, all the assets and liabilities of Ampliman 1 have been transferred to Zydus MedTech (France) S.A.S. The dissolution of Ampliman 1 will not impact the business operations of the Company.</p><ul><li>Zydus Lifesciences Ltd has dissolved its wholly owned subsidiary, Ampliman 1, France.</li><li>Ampliman 1 was a step down wholly owned subsidiary of the Company and a holding company of Amplitude Surgical, France.</li><li>Upon dissolution, all the assets and liabilities of Ampliman 1 have been transferred to Zydus MedTech (France) S.A.S.</li><li>The dissolution of Ampliman 1 will not impact the business operations of the Company.</li><li>This dissolution is a part of the series of dissolutions of Auroralux S.A.S., Luxembourg and Ampliman 2, France.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b4152269-a6d4-4485-935d-7cbf30c1e903.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Zydus Lifesciences Ltd | Category: Subsidiary Dissolution</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PACEDIGITK] Pace Digitek Ltd Appoints Mr. Ketan Chitnis as COO in Lineage Power Private Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Pace+Digitek+Ltd&title=Pace+Digitek+Ltd+Appoints+Mr.+Ketan+Chitnis+as+COO+in+Lineage+Power+Private+Limited&newsId=6ad0d56e-23b8-46f6-83a0-56e0a701846a&token=NmFkMGQ1NmUtMjNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ad0d56e-23b8-46f6-83a0-56e0a701846a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pace Digitek Ltd has appointed Mr. Ketan Chitnis as the Chief Operating Officer (COO) of its Material Subsidiary, Lineage Power Private Limited. Mr. Chitnis is a seasoned leader with over two decades of professional leadership experience in the Energy Storage Solutions/Battery Energy Storage Systems (BESS) domain. He has been associated with Larsen &amp; Toubro (L&amp;T) Energy (Greentech), Exide Leclanche Energy Private Limited, Waaree Energies Limited, and Base Corporation Limited. In his new role, he will lead the Production, Engineering, Supply Chain Management, Product-Service and Business Development departments. This appointment is in line with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Pace Digitek Ltd appoints Mr. Ketan Chitnis as COO of Lineage Power Private Limited</li><li>Mr. Chitnis has over 20 years of professional leadership experience in the Energy Storage Solutions/Battery Energy Storage Systems (BESS) domain</li><li>He has held leadership roles in Larsen &amp; Toubro (L&amp;T) Energy (Greentech), Exide Leclanche Energy Private Limited, Waaree Energies Limited, and Base Corporation Limited</li><li>In his new role, Mr. Chitnis will lead the Production, Engineering, Supply Chain Management, Product-Service and Business Development departments</li><li>The appointment is in line with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e7f0a48a-1f04-4179-af87-1cc509a38c71.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Pace Digitek Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MUKKA] Mukka Proteins Ltd Incorporates MPL HRC Ecosolutions LLP with 76% Holding</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Mukka+Proteins+Ltd&title=Mukka+Proteins+Ltd+Incorporates+MPL+HRC+Ecosolutions+LLP+with+76%25+Holding&newsId=9ef5b5bb-3ce6-4eed-bebb-c741faeac724&token=OWVmNWI1YmItM2Nl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ef5b5bb-3ce6-4eed-bebb-c741faeac724</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:24:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Mukka Proteins Ltd has incorporated a new LLP named &apos;MPL HRC Ecosolutions LLP&apos; with a capital contribution of Rs. 5,00,000. The LLP is a related party as Mukka Proteins Ltd has a 76% holding in it. The LLP is incorporated for the execution of a project for the treatment and disposal of non-hazardous waste. The LLP is proposed to carry on the business of treatment and disposal of non-hazardous waste. The date of incorporation of MPL HRC Ecosolutions LLP is 16-01-2026.</p><ul><li>Mukka Proteins Ltd has incorporated a new LLP named &apos;MPL HRC Ecosolutions LLP&apos;</li><li>The LLP is incorporated for the execution of a project for the treatment and disposal of non-hazardous waste</li><li>MPL HRC Ecosolutions LLP is a related party with Mukka Proteins Ltd having a 76% holding</li><li>The LLP is proposed to carry on the business of treatment and disposal of non-hazardous waste</li><li>The date of incorporation of MPL HRC Ecosolutions LLP is 16-01-2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/eac0fdfd-afac-4e90-b462-d04980e4cd9c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Mukka Proteins Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BRGIL] SEBI LODR Regulations: Income Tax Department Initiates Search Proceedings at B.R.Goyal Infrastructure Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=B.R.Goyal+Infrastructure+Ltd&title=SEBI+LODR+Regulations%3A+Income+Tax+Department+Initiates+Search+Proceedings+at+B.R.Goyal+Infrastructure+Ltd&newsId=076735b7-b53a-4b03-a70e-f1600905f2de&token=MDc2NzM1YjctYjUz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">076735b7-b53a-4b03-a70e-f1600905f2de</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:24:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pursuant to Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, B.R.Goyal Infrastructure Ltd has informed that the Income Tax Department has initiated a search proceeding at the registered office and multiple premises / locations of the Company since 16 January 2026. The search is currently ongoing and the Company is fully cooperating with the Income Tax Authorities, providing them with necessary information, documentation, and clarification. The Company will update the stakeholders on the impact and further developments as and when the situation permits, as required under Regulation 30 read with Schedule III of SEBI LODR Regulations 2015.</p><ul><li>Income Tax Department initiated search proceedings at B.R.Goyal Infrastructure Ltd since 16 January 2026</li><li>The search is ongoing at the registered office and multiple premises / locations of the Company</li><li>The Company is fully cooperating with the Income Tax Authorities</li><li>The Company will update stakeholders on the impact and further developments as and when the situation permits</li><li>Regulation 30 read with Schedule III of SEBI LODR Regulations 2015 being followed</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bc06f176-60e7-4cb5-a24a-f9236fc24be4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: B.R.Goyal Infrastructure Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CINERAD] GTT Data Solutions Ltd Approves Equity Shares Issuance on Private Placement Basis</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CINERAD+COMMUNICATIONS+LTD.&title=GTT+Data+Solutions+Ltd+Approves+Equity+Shares+Issuance+on+Private+Placement+Basis&newsId=d6779835-ae5f-445c-b450-42acab2ab1a4&token=ZDY3Nzk4MzUtYWU1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6779835-ae5f-445c-b450-42acab2ab1a4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:22:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>GTT Data Solutions Ltd, formerly known as Cinerad Communications Limited, announced that its Board of Directors has approved the issuance of equity shares by way of preferential issue on private placement basis. The decision was made during the Board meeting held on Saturday, January 17, 2026. The equity shares will be issued to the shareholders of Antworks Solutions India Private Limited (ASIPL) and M/s. Insurant AI Limited (UK) for consideration other than cash. The company will issue up to 1,22,51,111 fully paid-up equity shares of ₹ 10/- each at a price of ₹ 82.87/- per equity share, including a premium of ₹ 72.87/- per share, to ASIPL. Additionally, the company will issue up to 19,06,490 fully paid-up equity shares of ₹ 10/- each at a price of ₹ 82.87/- per equity share, to M/s. Insurant AI Limited (UK). The decision is subject to the approval of members and regulatory/governmental authorities. The Board also approved the appointment of Mr. Hamad Jabor Jassim Al-Thani and Mr. Deepak Abasaheb Shinde as Additional Non-Executive Non-Independent Director and Non-Executive Independent Director, respectively. The company also fixed the cut-off date for E-voting &amp; dispatch of notice of Extra Ordinary General Meeting and E-voting period.</p><ul><li>GTT Data Solutions Ltd approves equity shares issuance on private placement basis</li><li>Issuance of up to 1,22,51,111 equity shares to ASIPL and up to 19,06,490 equity shares to M/s. Insurant AI Limited (UK)</li><li>Issue price of ₹ 82.87/- per equity share, including a premium of ₹ 72.87/- per share</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Hamad Jabor Jassim Al-Thani and Mr. Deepak Abasaheb Shinde as Directors</li><li>Fixing of cut-off date for E-voting &amp; dispatch of notice of Extra Ordinary General Meeting and E-voting period</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7a907b23-37df-4e45-9544-aae76a4ea911.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CINERAD COMMUNICATIONS LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FUSION] Fusion Finance Ltd Appoints Krishan Gopal as Chief Financial Officer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Fusion+Micro+Finance+Ltd&title=Fusion+Finance+Ltd+Appoints+Krishan+Gopal+as+Chief+Financial+Officer&newsId=fd4de91e-138b-4a01-b375-f319d6595571&token=ZmQ0ZGU5MWUtMTM4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd4de91e-138b-4a01-b375-f319d6595571</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:21:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Leadership Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Fusion Finance Ltd has appointed Mr. Krishan Gopal as the Chief Financial Officer (CFO) and Key Managerial Personnel (KMP) of the company. Mr. Gopal brings over two decades of rich experience in finance, treasury, fund raising, investor relations, strategic planning, budgeting &amp; accounting functions. His appointment is a significant step in strengthening Fusion’s leadership team and will enhance financial agility, empowering Fusion to accelerate its long-term growth ambitions and deliver sustained value to all stakeholders. Mr. Amandeep Singh, the interim CFO, will cease to hold office upon Mr. Gopal&apos;s appointment.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Krishan Gopal as Chief Financial Officer and Key Managerial Personnel</li><li>Over two decades of experience in finance, treasury, fund raising, investor relations, strategic planning, budgeting &amp; accounting functions</li><li>Strengthening Fusion’s leadership team</li><li>Enhancing financial agility</li><li>Mr. Amandeep Singh ceases to hold office as Interim Chief Financial Officer</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/99bf5b06-9aa6-47b7-a175-12a797dc400c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Fusion Micro Finance Ltd | Category: Leadership Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FUSION] Fusion Finance Ltd Appoints New Chief Financial Officer Mr. Krishan Gopal</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Fusion+Micro+Finance+Ltd&title=Fusion+Finance+Ltd+Appoints+New+Chief+Financial+Officer+Mr.+Krishan+Gopal&newsId=28c01466-56ff-45fb-b8f9-36d285d7b0e0&token=MjhjMDE0NjYtNTZm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">28c01466-56ff-45fb-b8f9-36d285d7b0e0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:21:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Leadership Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Fusion Finance Ltd has appointed Mr. Krishan Gopal as the new Chief Financial Officer (CFO) and Key Managerial Personnel (KMP) of the company. Mr. Gopal brings over two decades of rich experience and expertise in finance, treasury, fund raising, investor relations, strategic planning, budgeting &amp; accounting functions. His appointment is a significant step in strengthening Fusion’s leadership team and will complement the company&apos;s strong capital position and enhance financial agility. Mr. Amandeep Singh, the interim CFO, will cease to hold office upon Mr. Gopal&apos;s appointment.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Krishan Gopal as Chief Financial Officer and Key Managerial Personnel of Fusion Finance Ltd.</li><li>Mr. Gopal brings over two decades of rich experience in finance, treasury, fund raising, investor relations, strategic planning, budgeting &amp; accounting functions.</li><li>Mr. Gopal&apos;s appointment is a significant step in strengthening Fusion’s leadership team.</li><li>Mr. Gopal&apos;s expertise will complement Fusion&apos;s strong capital position and enhance financial agility.</li><li>Mr. Amandeep Singh, the interim CFO, will cease to hold office upon Mr. Gopal&apos;s appointment.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5dbcf493-890b-4848-84ce-d73f6b9abd22.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Fusion Micro Finance Ltd | Category: Leadership Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NETWEB] Netweb Technologies India Ltd Announces Re-Appointment of Managing Director and Whole-Time Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Netweb+Technologies+India+Ltd&title=Netweb+Technologies+India+Ltd+Announces+Re-Appointment+of+Managing+Director+and+Whole-Time+Directors&newsId=232640b4-68eb-4e9c-b7d1-5e987899a463&token=MjMyNjQwYjQtNjhl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">232640b4-68eb-4e9c-b7d1-5e987899a463</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Netweb Technologies India Ltd has announced the re-appointment of Mr. Sanjay Lodha as Managing Director and Mr. Vivek Lodha, Mr. Niraj Lodha, and Mr. Navin Lodha as Whole-Time Directors. The re-appointments are for a period of 5 years, effective from August 14, 2026, to August 13, 2031. The re-appointment of Mr. Sanjay Lodha is not liable to retirement by rotation, while the others are liable to retire by rotation. The re-appointments are subject to the approval of the members of the company.</p><ul><li>Re-appointment of Mr. Sanjay Lodha as Managing Director</li><li>Re-appointment of Mr. Vivek Lodha, Mr. Niraj Lodha, and Mr. Navin Lodha as Whole-Time Directors</li><li>Re-appointments are for a period of 5 years</li><li>Effective from August 14, 2026, to August 13, 2031</li><li>Subject to the approval of the members of the company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4fc54f34-144f-42bc-b08b-1c6fa73cbe18.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Netweb Technologies India Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AVI] AVI Polymers Ltd Postpones Board Meeting for Comprehensive Review of Rights Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AVI+Polymers+Ltd&title=AVI+Polymers+Ltd+Postpones+Board+Meeting+for+Comprehensive+Review+of+Rights+Issue&newsId=4a53cb86-623b-4300-9679-fa27ca516226&token=NGE1M2NiODYtNjIz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a53cb86-623b-4300-9679-fa27ca516226</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:21:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>AVI Polymers Ltd, in a regulatory filing, has announced the postponement of its board meeting initially scheduled for January 17, 2026. The meeting was intended to consider and approve the terms of a rights issue, including the number of equity shares to be offered and the issue price. However, the company has decided to postpone the meeting to allow for additional time to strategically review the proposed transaction. The new date for the board meeting will be intimated to the stock exchange in due course.</p><ul><li>AVI Polymers Ltd postpones board meeting to review rights issue</li><li>Meeting was originally scheduled for January 17, 2026</li><li>Company needs more time for comprehensive planning and strategic review</li><li>New date for the board meeting will be announced later</li><li>Postponement made pursuant to Regulation 29(1)(d) of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f134e4f4-c66c-4fc3-9a5e-a27d980b9b03.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AVI Polymers Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>