<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 12:40:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[CENTUM] Centum Electronics Sharpens Strategic Focus, Exits Loss-Making Canadian Operations, and Plans Restructuring of French Subsidiaries</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CENTUM+ELECTRONICS+LTD.&title=Centum+Electronics+Sharpens+Strategic+Focus%2C+Exits+Loss-Making+Canadian+Operations%2C+and+Plans+Restructuring+of+French+Subsidiaries&newsId=bd02c658-7255-4de7-bd72-6673c089971d&token=YmQwMmM2NTgtNzI1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd02c658-7255-4de7-bd72-6673c089971d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 12:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Centum Electronics Limited, a leading Electronics System Design &amp; Manufacturing (ESDM) company, has announced strategic actions to sharpen its focus on high-growth, high-reliability electronics opportunities and strengthen its financial foundation. This includes the discontinuation of loss-making operations in Canada and the restructuring of French subsidiaries. The company is streamlining its global footprint to reinforce its long-term strategy of building scale and leadership in advanced defence, space and aerospace systems, and Electronics Manufacturing Services (EMS).</p><ul><li>Centum Electronics is exiting its loss-making operations in Canada.</li><li>The company is planning to restructure its French subsidiaries, considering options like divestment, sale, or transfer of businesses, and judicial reorganisation.</li><li>These actions are part of Centum&apos;s ongoing portfolio optimization and disciplined capital allocation strategy.</li><li>Centum Electronics continues to experience robust growth in its core ESDM business in India.</li><li>The company is focusing on high-reliability electronics products and services, and expanding its EMS business across new products, customers, and segments.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/84abb8b1-1de2-49e6-bcef-a7c028d390fe.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CENTUM ELECTRONICS LTD. | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HFCL] HFCL Secures Export Order Worth ~USD 4.67 Million for Optical Fiber Cables</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HFCL+Ltd&title=HFCL+Secures+Export+Order+Worth+~USD+4.67+Million+for+Optical+Fiber+Cables&newsId=2042f6e1-9c00-4475-b8bc-321b28960609&token=MjA0MmY2ZTEtOWMw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2042f6e1-9c00-4475-b8bc-321b28960609</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 12:01:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>HFCL Ltd has announced that it has secured an export order worth ~USD 4.67 million (equivalent to ~INR 42.34 crore) for the supply of optical fiber cables from a renowned international customer. This significant order reaffirms the trust global customers place in the Company’s manufacturing capabilities, technological excellence and product quality. The order is to be executed by May 2026.</p><ul><li>HFCL secures export order worth ~USD 4.67 million for optical fiber cables</li><li>Order from a renowned international customer</li><li>Reaffirms trust in Company’s manufacturing capabilities, technological excellence and product quality</li><li>Order to be executed by May 2026</li><li>Significant order from international customer in the normal course of business</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4eb5afb4-afaa-4a2b-b317-b4590ceb555f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HFCL Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MEHAI] Mehai Technology Ltd Receives Order for Shifting Registered Office from Rajasthan to West Bengal</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Mehai+Technology+Ltd&title=Mehai+Technology+Ltd+Receives+Order+for+Shifting+Registered+Office+from+Rajasthan+to+West+Bengal&newsId=e0c302ac-f6db-47dc-9119-17725f258852&token=ZTBjMzAyYWMtZjZk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0c302ac-f6db-47dc-9119-17725f258852</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 08:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mehai Technology Ltd has announced that it has received an order from the Regional Director, North-West regarding the shifting of its registered office from Rajasthan to West Bengal. This decision comes in accordance with section 13 of the Companies Act, 2013. The company can now proceed to make changes in the Master Data on the MCA Portal regarding the shifting of the registered office.</p><ul><li>Mehai Technology Ltd has received an order for shifting its registered office from Rajasthan to West Bengal.</li><li>The order is in accordance with section 13 of the Companies Act, 2013.</li><li>The company can now proceed to make changes in the Master Data on the MCA Portal.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a9b9089c-8a9a-407d-a330-41513a44a73a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Mehai Technology Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IGIL] International Gemmological Institute India Ltd Completes Acquisition of AGL Holdco Inc by Subsidiary</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=International+Gemmological+Institute+India+Ltd&title=International+Gemmological+Institute+India+Ltd+Completes+Acquisition+of+AGL+Holdco+Inc+by+Subsidiary&newsId=1a735169-faeb-47cf-b9a9-bb156e7e575b&token=MWE3MzUxNjktZmFl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a735169-faeb-47cf-b9a9-bb156e7e575b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 08:09:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>International Gemmological Institute India Ltd (IGI India) has announced the completion of the acquisition of AGL Holdco Inc by its step-down wholly owned subsidiary, International Gemmological Institute Inc (IGI USA). This acquisition was initially approved by the Board of Directors of IGI India in January 2026 and involved an investment in International Gemmological Institute BV (IGI Belgium), a wholly-owned subsidiary of IGI India, and investment by IGI Belgium in IGI USA. The acquisition of AGL Holdco Inc from Christopher P Smith and Helene Smith has resulted in AGL Holdco becoming a wholly-owned subsidiary of IGI USA and a step-down wholly-owned subsidiary of IGI Belgium and IGI India. Additionally, American Gemological Laboratories, LLC, a wholly-owned subsidiary of AGL Holdco, has become a step-down wholly-owned subsidiary of IGI USA, IGI Belgium, and IGI India.</p><ul><li>International Gemmological Institute India Ltd completes the acquisition of AGL Holdco Inc by its step-down wholly owned subsidiary, International Gemmological Institute Inc</li><li>AGL Holdco Inc becomes wholly-owned subsidiary of IGI USA and step-down wholly-owned subsidiary of IGI Belgium and IGI India</li><li>American Gemological Laboratories, LLC becomes a step-down wholly-owned subsidiary of IGI USA, IGI Belgium, and IGI India</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5ace7647-7013-41d5-8539-de8ddd9ce023.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: International Gemmological Institute India Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SOMATEX] Supreme Court Orders National Highways Authority of India to Deposit 50% of Awarded Amount in Arbitration Matter Involving Soma Textiles &amp; Industries&apos; Promoter</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SOMA+TEXTILES+%26+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Supreme+Court+Orders+National+Highways+Authority+of+India+to+Deposit+50%25+of+Awarded+Amount+in+Arbitration+Matter+Involving+Soma+Textiles+%26+Industries%27+Promoter&newsId=b82391c3-03c9-4db3-93cb-ed4d5926197c&token=YjgyMzkxYzMtMDNj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b82391c3-03c9-4db3-93cb-ed4d5926197c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 08:01:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Hon&apos;ble Supreme Court of India, in an arbitration-related matter involving Roadways Solutions India Infra Limited, the Promoter and Holding Company of Soma Textiles &amp; Industries Ltd, has passed directions for the National Highways Authority of India to deposit 50% of the total awarded amount before the Registry of the Hon’ble Delhi High Court within eight weeks. The matter arises out of a Concession Agreement relating to the Vadodara— Mumbai Expressway Project (Packages VIII &amp; IX). Soma Textiles &amp; Industries Ltd is not a party to the proceedings and based on the information currently available, the order does not have any direct material impact on its financial or operational activities.</p><ul><li>Supreme Court orders National Highways Authority of India to deposit 50% of the total awarded amount in an arbitration matter involving Soma Textiles &amp; Industries&apos; Promoter.</li><li>The matter pertains to disputes arising out of a Concession Agreement relating to the Vadodara— Mumbai Expressway Project (Packages VIII &amp; IX).</li><li>Soma Textiles &amp; Industries Ltd is not a party to the proceedings.</li><li>The awarded amount is Rs. 1,019,02,63,440/- plus interest aggregating to Rs. 1,197,72,60,596/- as on 09.02.2026.</li><li>Based on the information currently available, the order does not have any direct material impact on Soma Textiles &amp; Industries Ltd&apos;s financial or operational activities.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/78a273f9-18e4-453d-9fe6-ce422c41add7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SOMA TEXTILES & INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SPICEISL] Spice Islands Industries Ltd. exempted from Regulation 23(9) of SEBI (LODR) Regulation for Q1 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SPICE+ISLANDS+APPARELS+LTD.-%24&title=Spice+Islands+Industries+Ltd.+exempted+from+Regulation+23%289%29+of+SEBI+%28LODR%29+Regulation+for+Q1+2025&newsId=ab5906a4-6c00-4ae8-87a0-01e602ce2b92&token=YWI1OTA2YTQtNmMw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab5906a4-6c00-4ae8-87a0-01e602ce2b92</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 08:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Spice Islands Industries Limited, with a paid-up share capital of Rs. 4,30,00,000/- (Rupees Four Crores Thirty Lakhs Only) and a net worth of Rs. 2,35,70,000/- (Rupees Two Crore Thirty Five Lakhs Seventy Thousand Only) as on March 31, 2025, is exempted from the applicability of Regulation 23(9) of SEBI (LODR) Regulation for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. This exemption is due to the company&apos;s paid-up share capital and net worth being less than Rs. 10 Crores and Rs. 25 Crores, respectively. Consequently, the company is not required to submit &apos;Disclosures of the Related Party Transactions&apos; as per Regulation 23(9) of the Listing Regulations.</p><ul><li>Spice Islands Industries Ltd. is exempted from Regulation 23(9) of SEBI (LODR) Regulation for Q1 2025</li><li>The company&apos;s paid-up share capital and net worth are less than Rs. 10 Crores and Rs. 25 Crores, respectively</li><li>The company is not required to submit &apos;Disclosures of the Related Party Transactions&apos; for Q1 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3dccc480-0d2a-4564-8a1a-d934f2b27db2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SPICE ISLANDS APPARELS LTD.-$ | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHRIGANG] Shri Gang Industries Amends Code of Fair Disclosure of Unpublished Price Sensitive Information</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHRI+GANG+INDUSTRIES+AND+ALLIED+PRODUCTS+LTD.&title=Shri+Gang+Industries+Amends+Code+of+Fair+Disclosure+of+Unpublished+Price+Sensitive+Information&newsId=11d7e53c-e455-4c26-8a35-c4afea224318&token=MTFkN2U1M2MtZTQ1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11d7e53c-e455-4c26-8a35-c4afea224318</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 07:35:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shri Gang Industries &amp; Allied Products Ltd. has amended its Code of practices and procedures for Fair Disclosure of Unpublished Price Sensitive Information under Regulation 8(1) read with Schedule A of SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015. The amendments have been approved by the Board at its meeting held on February 14, 2026. The Code aims to formulate a stated framework and policy for fair disclosure of events and occurrences that could probably have an impact in the price discovery, in the market for securities of the Company. The amended Code and every amendment thereto shall be promptly intimated to the stock exchanges where the securities are listed to promote transparency amongst the investors.</p><ul><li>Shri Gang Industries &amp; Allied Products Ltd. has amended its Code of practices and procedures for Fair Disclosure of Unpublished Price Sensitive Information.</li><li>The amendments have been approved by the Board at its meeting held on February 14, 2026.</li><li>The Code aims to formulate a stated framework and policy for fair disclosure of events and occurrences that could probably have an impact in the price discovery.</li><li>The amended Code and every amendment thereto shall be promptly intimated to the stock exchanges where the securities are listed to promote transparency amongst the investors.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/874fc21e-27b8-40d1-a306-c1755a0b8a04.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHRI GANG INDUSTRIES AND ALLIED PRODUCTS LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ACEMEN] Ace Men Engg Works Ltd Board Meeting Postponed to February 18, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ace+Men+Engg+Works+Ltd&title=Ace+Men+Engg+Works+Ltd+Board+Meeting+Postponed+to+February+18%2C+2026&newsId=5b17e4d7-4e90-4481-84d4-641947e1890d&token=NWIxN2U0ZDctNGU5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b17e4d7-4e90-4481-84d4-641947e1890d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 07:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ace Men Engg Works Ltd has informed the BSE that the meeting of the Board of Directors, originally scheduled on an unspecified date, has been postponed. The new date for the Board Meeting is Wednesday, February 18, 2026. The Board will consider and approve the business submitted vide intimation dated February 11, 2026.</p><ul><li>Ace Men Engg Works Ltd Board Meeting postponed to February 18, 2026</li><li>The Board Meeting will consider and approve the business submitted vide intimation dated February 11, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/04b5b554-b586-4dc1-9bae-b88cc0bc77b5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ace Men Engg Works Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LGT] LGT Business Connextions Ltd: Monitoring Agency Report Confirms Appropriate Utilization of Public Issue Proceeds</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LGT+Business+Connextions+Ltd&title=LGT+Business+Connextions+Ltd%3A+Monitoring+Agency+Report+Confirms+Appropriate+Utilization+of+Public+Issue+Proceeds&newsId=1e9ffb53-e1d2-4502-804f-a492e05ea1a7&token=MWU5ZmZiNTMtZTFk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1e9ffb53-e1d2-4502-804f-a492e05ea1a7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 06:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Monitoring Agency Report for the quarter ended December 31, 2025 for LGT Business Connextions Limited, issued by Infomerics Ratings Limited, confirms the appropriate utilization of proceeds from the public issue. The report was submitted in accordance with Regulation 32(6) of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015 and Regulation 162A of SEBI (Issue of Capital and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2018. The proceeds from the public issue have been utilized for the objects mentioned in the offer document. The report also declares that there is no deviation from the objects and the range of deviation is nil.</p><ul><li>Monitoring Agency Report confirms appropriate utilization of public issue proceeds</li><li>Report submitted in accordance with SEBI regulations</li><li>No deviation from the objects, range of deviation is nil</li><li>Infomerics Ratings Limited is the Monitoring Agency</li><li>Report issued for the quarter ended December 31, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/331b53f4-c809-4e3b-add6-a5a98d5ede08.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LGT Business Connextions Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DIACABS] Diamond Power Infrastructure Limited Reports Q3 and Nine Months FY26 Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Diamond+Power+Infrastructure+Limited-%24&title=Diamond+Power+Infrastructure+Limited+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+FY26+Financial+Results&newsId=55ac1224-69ce-435d-9885-24c6c3dce4a1&token=NTVhYzEyMjQtNjlj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55ac1224-69ce-435d-9885-24c6c3dce4a1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 05:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Diamond Power Infrastructure Limited has shared the investor updates for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The updates will be discussed in upcoming investor calls and provide insights into the company&apos;s performance. The financial results and investor presentation are available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Revenue for the nine months ended December 31, 2025, stood at ₹ 474.08 cr</li><li>The company has order position of ₹ 3300 cr+ as of December 31, 2025</li><li>Diamond Power Infrastructure Limited has a strong approval order position and recognition with 275 customers in leading labs accredited with NABL 1322</li><li>Key approvals and orders contribute to the company&apos;s growth</li><li>The company&apos;s progress and performance are highlighted in the investor presentation for Q3 FY 2025-26</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fc54064a-b8a3-4187-9f3c-c9448db348ad.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Diamond Power Infrastructure Limited-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>