<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:17:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[RAILTEL] RailTel Corporation of India Ltd Announces Promotion of Ms. Madhulika Pathak to Principal Executive Director/Finance</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RailTel+Corporation+of+India+Ltd&title=RailTel+Corporation+of+India+Ltd+Announces+Promotion+of+Ms.+Madhulika+Pathak+to+Principal+Executive+Director%2FFinance&newsId=442cafcb-c8bf-405b-a009-8372b4311ac3&token=NDQyY2FmY2ItYzhi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">442cafcb-c8bf-405b-a009-8372b4311ac3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Promotion</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>RailTel Corporation of India Ltd has announced the promotion of Ms. Madhulika Pathak from Executive Director/Finance to Principal Executive Director/Finance. The promotion is effective from the date she takes over the higher post and she will become part of the Senior Management Personnel of the Company. Ms. Pathak has a rich and varied experience of over 36 years in finance and has worked with different PSUs and private companies. She has been with RailTel since 2013 and has been handling policy framing, marketing finance, capital investment decisions, tendering and related work of finance. She is also assisting in handling domestic and international business opportunities in the field of IT/ICT/Railway Infra/Smart Cities/Data Centre &amp; Cloud/Cybersecurity.</p><ul><li>Ms. Madhulika Pathak promoted to Principal Executive Director/Finance</li><li>Ms. Pathak has over 36 years of experience in finance</li><li>She has worked with different PSUs and private companies</li><li>She has been with RailTel since 2013 and handling policy framing, marketing finance, capital investment decisions, tendering and related work of finance</li><li>She is assisting in handling domestic and international business opportunities in the field of IT/ICT/Railway Infra/Smart Cities/Data Centre &amp; Cloud/Cybersecurity</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/46f81d0c-7816-42e7-947b-775c9b4717ec.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RailTel Corporation of India Ltd | Category: Promotion</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RAILTEL] RailTel Corporation of India Ltd. Loses Rs. 2,62,14,38,750 Order from Bihar Education Project Council</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RailTel+Corporation+of+India+Ltd&title=RailTel+Corporation+of+India+Ltd.+Loses+Rs.+2%2C62%2C14%2C38%2C750+Order+from+Bihar+Education+Project+Council&newsId=fa5a19cc-a928-44cb-93a0-047c9d66b187&token=ZmE1YTE5Y2MtYTky</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa5a19cc-a928-44cb-93a0-047c9d66b187</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Cancellation of Order</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>RailTel Corporation of India Ltd. has announced the cancellation of an order worth Rs. 2,62,14,38,750 from M/s. State Project Director, Bihar Education Project Council. The order was for Procurement, Supply and Installation of Smart Classrooms at Government Middle Schools in Bihar. The cancellation was due to some unavoidable reasons as per the company&apos;s disclosure.</p><ul><li>RailTel Corporation of India Ltd. has lost an order worth Rs. 2,62,14,38,750 from Bihar Education Project Council.</li><li>The order was for Procurement, Supply and Installation of Smart Classrooms at Government Middle Schools in Bihar.</li><li>The cancellation was due to some unavoidable reasons as per the company&apos;s disclosure.</li><li>The order was received through a Letter of Acceptance (&apos;LOA&apos;) from the Customer.</li><li>The cancellation of the order may impact the company&apos;s financial performance.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/29a2905e-5896-4244-a6da-2db850b22607.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RailTel Corporation of India Ltd | Category: Cancellation of Order</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MAHABANK] Bank of Maharashtra Reports on RBI Trade Relief Measures for MSMEs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BANK+OF+MAHARASHTRA&title=Bank+of+Maharashtra+Reports+on+RBI+Trade+Relief+Measures+for+MSMEs&newsId=902c3525-813e-4b94-87d1-b0b5428ddbd0&token=OTAyYzM1MjUtODEz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">902c3525-813e-4b94-87d1-b0b5428ddbd0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In response to a query sought in the earning&apos;s conference call, Bank of Maharashtra has provided details on the RBI Trade Relief Measures Directions, 2025, pertaining to MSMEs. As of 31.12.2025, there were 66 eligible borrowers involved, amounting to Rs. 671 Crores, which is 1.31% of the total MSME portfolio.</p><ul><li>Bank of Maharashtra provides update on RBI Trade Relief Measures for MSMEs</li><li>As of 31.12.2025, there were 66 eligible borrowers under the scheme</li><li>The total amount involved was Rs. 671 Crores</li><li>This amount represents 1.31% of the total MSME portfolio</li><li>The update was provided in response to a query in the earning&apos;s conference call</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/da7bf68a-a96c-4e48-bd65-a979792b48ab.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BANK OF MAHARASHTRA | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RAILTEL] RailTel Corporation of India Loses Rs. 2,57,50,12,000 Smart Classrooms Order in Bihar</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RailTel+Corporation+of+India+Ltd&title=RailTel+Corporation+of+India+Loses+Rs.+2%2C57%2C50%2C12%2C000+Smart+Classrooms+Order+in+Bihar&newsId=8fbb9ea9-f3e0-445f-8e8d-30a0f5fe59a8&token=OGZiYjllYTktZjNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8fbb9ea9-f3e0-445f-8e8d-30a0f5fe59a8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Cancellation of Order</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>RailTel Corporation of India Ltd. has announced the cancellation of a major order for the Procurement, Supply and Installation of Smart Classrooms at Government Secondary and Senior Secondary Schools in Bihar. The order, worth Rs. 2,57,50,12,000, was received from M/s. State Project Director, Bihar Education Project Council. However, due to unavoidable reasons, the customer has cancelled the work order. The company has asked all stakeholders to take note of this information.</p><ul><li>RailTel Corporation of India loses a significant order worth Rs. 2,57,50,12,000</li><li>The order was for the Procurement, Supply and Installation of Smart Classrooms at Government Secondary and Senior Secondary Schools in Bihar</li><li>The customer, M/s. State Project Director, Bihar Education Project Council, has cancelled the order due to unavoidable reasons</li><li>The cancellation of the order could impact the company&apos;s financial performance</li><li>RailTel Corporation of India has asked all stakeholders to take note of this information</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/56dcf9f6-46ae-48e7-9f3c-40fee08883d2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RailTel Corporation of India Ltd | Category: Cancellation of Order</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AMALGAM] Independent Director, Ms. Aradhana Kurup, Resigns from Amalgamated Electricity Company Ltd.</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AMALGAMATED+ELECTRICITY+CO.LTD.&title=Independent+Director%2C+Ms.+Aradhana+Kurup%2C+Resigns+from+Amalgamated+Electricity+Company+Ltd.&newsId=e4ad2bd3-85b8-452a-8b08-f52c3582328e&token=ZTRhZDJiZDMtODVi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e4ad2bd3-85b8-452a-8b08-f52c3582328e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Amalgamated Electricity Company Ltd. announced the resignation of Ms. Aradhana Kurup as an Independent Director from the company&apos;s Board of Directors. The resignation is effective from January 13, 2026, due to personal and professional commitments. Ms. Kurup expressed gratitude towards the board and management for the opportunity to serve and looks forward to working with the company in a more suitable capacity in the future.</p><ul><li>Ms. Aradhana Kurup has resigned from her position as an Independent Director from Amalgamated Electricity Company Ltd.</li><li>The resignation is effective from January 13, 2026.</li><li>Ms. Kurup cited personal and professional commitments as the reason for her resignation.</li><li>She thanked the board and management for the opportunity to serve.</li><li>Ms. Kurup is open to working with the company in a more suitable capacity in the future.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6d29d62f-a268-4350-a105-92333aa096f8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AMALGAMATED ELECTRICITY CO.LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RAJTUBE] Rajasthan Tube Manufacturing Company Ltd: Board Approves Name Change to &apos;NEOOH STREET&apos;, Expansion of Objects Clause, and Appointment of Additional Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RAJASTHAN+TUBE+MANUFACTURING+CO.LTD.&title=Rajasthan+Tube+Manufacturing+Company+Ltd%3A+Board+Approves+Name+Change+to+%27NEOOH+STREET%27%2C+Expansion+of+Objects+Clause%2C+and+Appointment+of+Additional+Directors&newsId=e31925cf-5973-46c0-91a3-f6d06ae1e81b&token=ZTMxOTI1Y2YtNTk3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e31925cf-5973-46c0-91a3-f6d06ae1e81b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Rajasthan Tube Manufacturing Company Ltd, at its meeting held on Tuesday, January 13, 2026, approved several significant changes. These include a proposed change of name to &apos;NEOOH STREET&apos;, subject to shareholder and regulatory approvals. The Board also approved an amendment to the Objects Clause of the Memorandum of Association to enable the Company to carry on various businesses such as marketing, IT, infrastructure, manufacturing, and import/export. Additionally, the Board appointed Mr. Mayur Mukul Ghule and Mr. Darpan Jayraj Kale as Additional Directors. These changes will be subject to shareholder approval at an Extraordinary General Meeting scheduled for 10 February 2026.</p><ul><li>Proposed name change to &apos;NEOOH STREET&apos;</li><li>Amendment of Objects Clause to enable diversification into various businesses</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Mayur Mukul Ghule and Mr. Darpan Jayraj Kale as Additional Directors</li><li>Subject to shareholder approval at the Extraordinary General Meeting on 10 February 2026</li><li>Changes also subject to necessary regulatory approvals</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9b182904-91e8-4460-9998-fb52c7e20ff7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RAJASTHAN TUBE MANUFACTURING CO.LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RAILTEL] RailTel Corporation of India Loses Rs. 89,91,96,639 Order in Bihar</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RailTel+Corporation+of+India+Ltd&title=RailTel+Corporation+of+India+Loses+Rs.+89%2C91%2C96%2C639+Order+in+Bihar&newsId=853906e7-75d1-4267-bdeb-da92353fd4fe&token=ODUzOTA2ZTctNzVk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">853906e7-75d1-4267-bdeb-da92353fd4fe</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>RailTel Corporation of India Ltd. has informed that it received a Letter of Acceptance (LOA) from M/s. State Project Director, Bihar Education Project Council for Supply of Teaching Learning Material of Class I to V for Government Schools in Bihar. The estimated size of the order was Rs. 89,91,96,639. However, due to unavoidable reasons, the Customer has cancelled the Work Order for the above work.</p><ul><li>RailTel Corporation of India lost an order worth Rs. 89,91,96,639 in Bihar.</li><li>The order was for the Supply of Teaching Learning Material of Class I to V for Government Schools in Bihar.</li><li>The order was cancelled due to unavoidable reasons.</li><li>The order was received from M/s. State Project Director, Bihar Education Project Council.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b356ffc4-2454-4595-a29b-dafcf2de35db.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RailTel Corporation of India Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GCSL] Gretex Corporate Services Ltd Approves Allotment of 94,459 Equity Shares Upon Warrant Conversion</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Gretex+Corporate+Services+Ltd&title=Gretex+Corporate+Services+Ltd+Approves+Allotment+of+94%2C459+Equity+Shares+Upon+Warrant+Conversion&newsId=3bbbb2a5-a214-4077-b2bc-720251d17fb1&token=M2JiYmIyYTUtYTIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3bbbb2a5-a214-4077-b2bc-720251d17fb1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gretex Corporate Services Ltd announced the allotment of 94,459 equity shares at an issue price of Rs. 379/- (including premium of Rs. 369/-) fully paid-up upon exercising the option available with warrant holder to convert 94,459 Equity Warrants into Equity Shares. The allottee is also entitled to 85,013 bonus equity shares, which shall be released from the demat suspense account and credited to the allottee’s demat account simultaneously with the allotment of equity shares arising from such conversion.</p><ul><li>Gretex Corporate Services Ltd approved the allotment of 94,459 equity shares upon warrant conversion.</li><li>The allotment is at an issue price of Rs. 379/- (including premium of Rs. 369/-).</li><li>The allottee is also entitled to 85,013 bonus equity shares.</li><li>The equity shares allotted on exercise of conversion of Warrants shall rank pari passu in all respects with the existing equity shares of the Company.</li><li>The details of the allotment are provided as per SEBI regulations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/af04745d-87fd-4095-9813-7343ff72d272.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Gretex Corporate Services Ltd | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TREJHARA] Trejhara Solutions Ltd Revises Valuation Report for Preferential Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Trejhara+Solutions+Ltd&title=Trejhara+Solutions+Ltd+Revises+Valuation+Report+for+Preferential+Issue&newsId=294cac5b-cfb3-4577-91da-d6288449ea97&token=Mjk0Y2FjNWItY2Zi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">294cac5b-cfb3-4577-91da-d6288449ea97</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:51:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Trejhara Solutions Ltd has revised its Valuation Report in relation to a proposed preferential issue of Convertible Warrants and Equity Shares. The revision was made after deliberations with the Stock Exchange, with the main change being the removal of the explanation relating to the non-adoption of the Discounted Cash Flow (DCF) method. The Company confirms that all other contents, assumptions, methodologies, and conclusions, including the price arrived at in the Valuation Report, remain unchanged.</p><ul><li>Trejhara Solutions Ltd revises Valuation Report for preferential issue of Convertible Warrants and Equity Shares.</li><li>Revision made after deliberations with the Stock Exchange.</li><li>Explanation relating to non-adoption of DCF method removed.</li><li>All other contents, assumptions, methodologies, and conclusions remain unchanged.</li><li>Price arrived at in the Valuation Report remains the same.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e50e1ea0-3a71-4adf-9cc9-6afa1d7c224a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Trejhara Solutions Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WAKEFIT] Wakefit Innovations Ltd Changes Corporate Identification Number to &apos;L52590KA2016PLC086582&apos;</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Wakefit+Innovations+Ltd&title=Wakefit+Innovations+Ltd+Changes+Corporate+Identification+Number+to+%27L52590KA2016PLC086582%27&newsId=d39b9880-f8f9-4025-a057-85a8bff6ead1&token=ZDM5Yjk4ODAtZjhm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d39b9880-f8f9-4025-a057-85a8bff6ead1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:11:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Wakefit Innovations Limited has announced a change in its Corporate Identification Number (CIN) from &apos;U52590KA2016PLC086582&apos; to &apos;L52590KA2016PLC086582&apos;. This change comes after the listing of the company&apos;s equity shares on BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange of India Limited. The new CIN has been updated by the Ministry of Corporate Affairs. The company has also mentioned that this information is available on their website.</p><ul><li>Wakefit Innovations Ltd changes its Corporate Identification Number to &apos;L52590KA2016PLC086582&apos;</li><li>Change comes after the listing of equity shares on BSE and NSE</li><li>Ministry of Corporate Affairs has updated the new CIN</li><li>Information available on the company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a0114c9e-3314-41cf-a2b3-3d09118f142e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Wakefit Innovations Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>