<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 04:49:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ABATEAS] Abate AS Industries Launches Indigenous EMR &amp; Clinic Management System for Eye Hospitals</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Abate+As+Industries+Ltd&title=Abate+AS+Industries+Launches+Indigenous+EMR+%26+Clinic+Management+System+for+Eye+Hospitals&newsId=45ad99a6-d11c-48c5-a2fc-c866ca8ef60e&token=NDVhZDk5YTYtZDEx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">45ad99a6-d11c-48c5-a2fc-c866ca8ef60e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 04:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Abate AS Industries Ltd, through its healthcare subsidiary M/s Prudential Management Services Private Limited, has launched its indigenously developed Electronic Medical Record (EMR) System. The system is a comprehensive Eye Hospital Clinic Management System, designed to enhance data accuracy, improve inter-departmental coordination, enable real-time reporting, and strengthen patient experience. It includes an integrated online appointment management module and is expected to reduce manual administrative dependency and improve cost efficiency.</p><ul><li>Launch of indigenously developed Electronic Medical Record (EMR) System for Eye Hospitals</li><li>Improvement in data accuracy and clinical documentation standards</li><li>Enhancement of inter-departmental coordination and workflow efficiency</li><li>Implementation of real-time reporting and centralized management oversight</li><li>Anticipated reduction in patient no-show ratios and improvement in operational planning efficiency</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cfde8681-729e-40cb-a6a1-6bb6e9da55f6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Abate As Industries Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HAZOOR] Hazoor Multi Projects Ltd. Awarded User Fee Collection Contract by NHAI for Balenahalli Fee Plaza in Karnataka</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HAZOOR+MULTI+PROJECTS+LTD.-%24&title=Hazoor+Multi+Projects+Ltd.+Awarded+User+Fee+Collection+Contract+by+NHAI+for+Balenahalli+Fee+Plaza+in+Karnataka&newsId=09f13afa-4f8c-4ad5-a0b2-be7e815f4cf6&token=MDlmMTNhZmEtNGY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09f13afa-4f8c-4ad5-a0b2-be7e815f4cf6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 04:18:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Hazoor Multi Projects Ltd. has been awarded a Letter of Award (LOA) by the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) for engaging as the Contractor for collection of user fee at Balenahalli fee plaza. The contract is for a four lane section of Challakere to Hiriyur from Existing Chainage Km. 359.120 to Km. 411.560 (Design Chainage Km. 358.500 to Km. 414.205) of NH-150A in the State of Karnataka and upkeep/maintenance of adjacent Toilet blocks including recouping the consumable items. The contract is worth Rs. 44,23,80,000/- and is a one-year contract.</p><ul><li>Hazoor Multi Projects Ltd. has been awarded a Letter of Award (LOA) by the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) for user fee collection at Balenahalli fee plaza.</li><li>The contract is for a four lane section of Challakere to Hiriyur from Existing Chainage Km. 359.120 to Km. 411.560 (Design Chainage Km. 358.500 to Km. 414.205) of NH-150A in the State of Karnataka and upkeep/maintenance of adjacent Toilet blocks including recouping the consumable items.</li><li>The contract is worth Rs. 44,23,80,000/-.</li><li>The contract is a one-year contract.</li><li>The contract was awarded through competitive bidding through e-tender.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/862547a1-450d-406f-a298-373344080f52.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HAZOOR MULTI PROJECTS LTD.-$ | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PROFINC] Ramesh Sawalram Saraogi Sells 1.40% Shares of Pro Fin Capital Services Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PRO+FIN+CAPITAL+SERVICES+LTD.&title=Ramesh+Sawalram+Saraogi+Sells+1.40%25+Shares+of+Pro+Fin+Capital+Services+Ltd&newsId=c48aaf79-4a3d-4f12-9d36-552036b86ced&token=YzQ4YWFmNzktNGEz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c48aaf79-4a3d-4f12-9d36-552036b86ced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 04:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Sale</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ramesh Sawalram Saraogi has sold 1.40% shares of Pro Fin Capital Services Ltd, reducing his holding from 13.89% to 12.49%. The sale took place on 16th February 2026, with 83,00,000 shares sold at an undisclosed price. The total equity shares of the company remain unchanged at 59,25,94,326 after the sale.</p><ul><li>Ramesh Sawalram Saraogi sells 1.40% shares of Pro Fin Capital Services Ltd</li><li>Sale took place on 16th February 2026</li><li>83,00,000 shares sold at an undisclosed price</li><li>Pre-sale holding: 13.89%, Post-sale holding: 12.49%</li><li>Total equity shares of the company remain unchanged</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/49DD047C_A792_4953_A8D8_6613454DB914_094312.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PRO FIN CAPITAL SERVICES LTD. | Category: Sale</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[APIL] Sujay P Joshi Acquires 52,000 Shares in Avi Products India Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Avi+Products+India+Ltd&title=Sujay+P+Joshi+Acquires+52%2C000+Shares+in+Avi+Products+India+Ltd&newsId=1229068e-601e-4c3d-a4d1-ba6124ea6560&token=MTIyOTA2OGUtNjAx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1229068e-601e-4c3d-a4d1-ba6124ea6560</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 04:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>According to a disclosure made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011, Sujay P Joshi has acquired 52,000 shares of Avi Products India Ltd. The shares, of a face value of Rs. 10/- each, were acquired on February 13, 2026. This acquisition increases the total voting rights of Sujay P Joshi in the company to 33,06,802 equity shares.</p><ul><li>Sujay P Joshi acquires 52,000 shares in Avi Products India Ltd</li><li>The acquisition was made on February 13, 2026</li><li>The shares acquired have a face value of Rs. 10/- each</li><li>This acquisition increases Sujay P Joshi&apos;s total voting rights to 33,06,802 equity shares</li><li>The acquisition was made in accordance with Regulation 29(2) of the SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3C840F30_5C55_41BE_9B8D_6E3C61E21A05_093927.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Avi Products India Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INFY*] Infosys and Anthropic Collaborate to Unlock AI Value in Complex, Regulated Industries</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INFOSYS+LTD.&title=Infosys+and+Anthropic+Collaborate+to+Unlock+AI+Value+in+Complex%2C+Regulated+Industries&newsId=b7b5d177-1e4f-43a3-94df-1f29247796de&token=YjdiNWQxNzctMWU0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7b5d177-1e4f-43a3-94df-1f29247796de</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 04:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Partnership</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Infosys and Anthropic have formed a strategic collaboration to develop and deliver advanced enterprise AI solutions to companies in telecommunications, financial services, manufacturing, and software development. The collaboration will begin with a dedicated Anthropic Center of Excellence in telecommunications, expanding across other industries. Infosys Topaz and Anthropic’s Claude models, including Claude Code, will automate complex workflows, accelerate software delivery, and build agentic AI solutions. The collaboration aims to help clients reimagine the enterprise operating model and modernize legacy systems.</p><ul><li>Infosys and Anthropic form strategic collaboration to develop and deliver advanced enterprise AI solutions.</li><li>Dedicated Anthropic Center of Excellence to begin in telecommunications, expanding across other industries.</li><li>Infosys Topaz and Anthropic’s Claude models, including Claude Code, to automate complex workflows and accelerate software delivery.</li><li>Collaboration aims to help clients reimagine the enterprise operating model and modernize legacy systems.</li><li>Infosys and Anthropic to build agentic AI solutions tailored to industry-specific operations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a783bebe-10bf-4864-ae43-4c65d757a898.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INFOSYS LTD. | Category: Partnership</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PIRAMALFIN] S&amp;P Global Ratings Upgrades Piramal Finance to &apos;BB&apos; with Stable Outlook</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Piramal+Finance+Ltd&title=S%26P+Global+Ratings+Upgrades+Piramal+Finance+to+%27BB%27+with+Stable+Outlook&newsId=5cb37a42-a235-417b-aae6-1af065065ee6&token=NWNiMzdhNDItYTIz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5cb37a42-a235-417b-aae6-1af065065ee6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 02:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>S&amp;P Global Ratings has upgraded Piramal Finance Limited’s long-term issuer credit rating to ‘BB’ from ‘BB-’, with a Stable outlook, while affirming its ‘B’ short-term issuer credit rating. This upgrade marks a significant milestone in Piramal Finance’s multi-year transformation into a scaled, diversified, retail-focused lending franchise. The rating reflects S&amp;P Global Ratings’ expectation of stronger business stability and earnings resilience at Piramal Finance, driven by the steady run-down of legacy exposures and the transition to a predominantly retail-focused portfolio. Retail loans are projected to account for about 85% of total AUM by FY26. The rating also factors in the company’s strong promoter strength, which provides financial flexibility, strategic stability, and sustained support for long-term growth.</p><ul><li>S&amp;P Global Ratings upgrades Piramal Finance Limited’s long-term issuer credit rating to ‘BB’ from ‘BB-’</li><li>Stable outlook reflects expectations of sustained improvement in profitability and asset quality, supported by strong capitalization and steady market share gains over the next 12-24 months</li><li>Retail loans projected to account for about 85% of total AUM by FY26</li><li>Strong promoter strength providing financial flexibility, strategic stability, and sustained support for long-term growth</li><li>Company has raised nearly 314,000 crore in External Commercial Borrowings (ECBs) across FY 25 and FY 26</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1cfc3645-851c-4f09-a0c5-f67e5a3b9f90.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Piramal Finance Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CSURGSU] Unusual Trading Pattern Observed in Centenial Surgical Suture Ltd Shares on BSE Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CENTENIAL+SURGICAL+SUTURE+LTD.&title=Unusual+Trading+Pattern+Observed+in+Centenial+Surgical+Suture+Ltd+Shares+on+BSE+Limited&newsId=9d8f4f3d-2a0f-4a5c-b8ae-f83a29dfeb97&token=OWQ4ZjRmM2QtMmEw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d8f4f3d-2a0f-4a5c-b8ae-f83a29dfeb97</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 02:01:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investigation</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Centenial Surgical Suture Ltd, Scrip no.: 531308, has reported unusual trades in the company shares on BSE Limited. The company has observed individuals selling and purchasing 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 equity shares during the period from February 06, 2026 to February 13, 2026. The trading details and contact information of these individuals are provided in annexure A. The company suspects manipulative, unethical, and unusual trades in their scrip and requests urgent attention from the authorities. The increase in the scrip price during the past few months does not align with the actual financial performance of the company, suggesting manipulations committed by group entities. The company believes that the anti-money laundering agency&apos;s investigation will reveal that several entities and individuals have derived huge profits while causing loss to genuine investors. The illegal profits were routed through various accounts of different entities and individuals, with some instances of the father selling to the son and the son selling to the father. The company hopes that these illegal activities can be further probed and requests an investigation under various sections of the Securities and Exchange Board of India Act (SEBI Act), 1992.</p><ul><li>Unusual trades observed in Centenial Surgical Suture Ltd shares on BSE Limited</li><li>Individuals involved in selling and purchasing 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 equity shares</li><li>Suspected manipulative, unethical, and unusual trades in the company scrip</li><li>Increase in scrip price not in synchronisation with the actual financial performance</li><li>Request for investigation under various sections of SEBI Act, 1992</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2d202209-f9cc-40d6-96a0-c278bdf5ee3d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CENTENIAL SURGICAL SUTURE LTD. | Category: Investigation</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHREEJISPG] Shreeji Shipping Global Ltd Board Meeting on Feb 24, 2026: Interim Dividend and Other Businesses</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shreeji+Shipping+Global+Ltd&title=Shreeji+Shipping+Global+Ltd+Board+Meeting+on+Feb+24%2C+2026%3A+Interim+Dividend+and+Other+Businesses&newsId=bf564bb4-3e84-4d89-b50f-ffb451613952&token=YmY1NjRiYjQtM2U4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf564bb4-3e84-4d89-b50f-ffb451613952</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 02:01:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shreeji Shipping Global Ltd has scheduled a Board of Directors meeting on February 24, 2026, to consider and approve various matters including the declaration of interim dividends for the financial year 2025-26 and discussing other business items. The meeting will be held in accordance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, and SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015. The &apos;Trading Window&apos; shall be closed for dealing in Equity Shares of the Company for Designated Persons and their immediate relatives from February 17, 2026, till 48 hours after the conclusion of the Board Meeting.</p><ul><li>Shreeji Shipping Global Ltd Board Meeting on February 24, 2026</li><li>Consideration and approval of interim dividends for the financial year 2025-26</li><li>Discussion of other business items</li><li>Meeting held in accordance with SEBI regulations</li><li>Trading Window closed for Designated Persons and their immediate relatives from February 17, 2026, till 48 hours after the Board Meeting</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7a35156a-fea2-4871-b472-cf4b1a96def5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shreeji Shipping Global Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHREEJISPG] Shreeji Shipping Global Ltd. to Declare Interim Dividend for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shreeji+Shipping+Global+Ltd&title=Shreeji+Shipping+Global+Ltd.+to+Declare+Interim+Dividend+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=2ef6556a-7e53-4074-984d-7ce8d21c19fe&token=MmVmNjU1NmEtN2U1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ef6556a-7e53-4074-984d-7ce8d21c19fe</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 02:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shreeji Shipping Global Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 24, 2026, to consider and approve the declaration of the Interim Dividend for the Financial year 2025-26. The meeting will also discuss other business items. In accordance with the SEBI regulations and the Company’s Code of Conduct for Prevention of Insider Trading, the &apos;Trading Window&apos; will be closed for dealing in Equity Shares of the Company for Designated Persons and their immediate relatives from February 17, 2026, till 48 hours after the conclusion of the Board Meeting.</p><ul><li>Board meeting scheduled for February 24, 2026</li><li>Interim Dividend for FY 2025-26 to be considered</li><li>Trading Window to be closed for Designated Persons from February 17, 2026</li><li>Trading Window to remain closed till 48 hours after the Board Meeting</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7a64253f-27a0-47cf-988d-8b6b4d95bcdc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shreeji Shipping Global Ltd | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PTIL] Prabhat Technologies Board Meeting Rescheduled for Financial Results Approval</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Prabhat+Technologies+%28India%29+Ltd&title=Prabhat+Technologies+Board+Meeting+Rescheduled+for+Financial+Results+Approval&newsId=ff52fb38-dd45-4663-b010-959f76308963&token=ZmY1MmZiMzgtZGQ0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff52fb38-dd45-4663-b010-959f76308963</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 16:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Prabhat Technologies (India) Ltd has informed the BSE that the meeting of the Board of Directors, originally scheduled for February 16, 2026, has been rescheduled to February 18, 2026, due to unavoidable reasons. The meeting will consider and approve the Un-audited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in shares of the company will remain closed till 48 hours after the announcement of the Un-audited Financial Results, in accordance with the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015 and the Company&apos;s Code of Conduct for Prevention of Insider Trading.</p><ul><li>Prabhat Technologies Board Meeting rescheduled to February 18, 2026</li><li>Board to consider and approve Un-audited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Trading window to remain closed till 48 hours after the announcement of Un-audited Financial Results</li><li>Compliance with SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Adherence to the Company&apos;s Code of Conduct for Prevention of Insider Trading</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d0e1aaa9-a148-42b5-b327-40a3fc983791.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Prabhat Technologies (India) Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>