<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:20:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[TCIEXP*] TCI Express Ltd Receives Order under GST Act 2017; to File Appeal Against Demand Order</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TCI+Express+Ltd&title=TCI+Express+Ltd+Receives+Order+under+GST+Act+2017%3B+to+File+Appeal+Against+Demand+Order&newsId=dcdcd809-fbf5-49f9-a277-553e025f6a79&token=ZGNkY2Q4MDktZmJm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dcdcd809-fbf5-49f9-a277-553e025f6a79</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:20:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>TCI Express Ltd has received an order under the Goods and Services Tax Act 2017, informing that the demand order issued for the period from FY 2017-18 to FY 2021-22 continues to remain in force. The company believes it has a strong case on merits and will be filing an appeal against the order before the GST Appropriate Authority.</p><ul><li>TCI Express Ltd received an order under the Goods and Services Tax Act 2017</li><li>The order informs that the demand order continues to remain in force for the period from FY 2017-18 to FY 2021-22</li><li>The company will file an appeal against the order before the GST Appropriate Authority</li><li>TCI Express Ltd believes it has a strong case on merits</li><li>No material impact on the financials, operations, or other activities of the company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ee400150-c6bc-4cab-b3d5-16731ad0a4f0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TCI Express Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADANIPORTS] Adani Ports to Announce Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025 on February 3, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADANI+PORTS+AND+SPECIAL+ECONOMIC+ZONE+LTD.&title=Adani+Ports+to+Announce+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025+on+February+3%2C+2026&newsId=3c2889f0-03ef-4a16-9071-6bc8c50b63ef&token=M2MyODg5ZjAtMDNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3c2889f0-03ef-4a16-9071-6bc8c50b63ef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone Ltd has informed the BSE that the meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on February 3, 2026, to consider and approve the Financial Results (Standalone and Consolidated) for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in securities of the Company will remain closed from January 1, 2026, till the expiry of 48 hours from the date when the results are declared and made public on February 3, 2026. The Company will hold investor/analyst calls on February 3, 2026, to discuss the financial results and business outlook.</p><ul><li>Adani Ports to announce Q3 and nine months results for 2025 on February 3, 2026</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities of the Company will be closed from January 1, 2026, till the expiry of 48 hours from the date when the results are declared and made public on February 3, 2026</li><li>Company to hold investor/analyst calls on February 3, 2026, to discuss the financial results and business outlook</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/75dc9a9e-ecdf-4821-9b37-37c76c517425.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADANI PORTS AND SPECIAL ECONOMIC ZONE LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[APIL] Avi Products India Ltd Appoints New Directors and Auditors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Avi+Products+India+Ltd&title=Avi+Products+India+Ltd+Appoints+New+Directors+and+Auditors&newsId=9a9250b3-2b70-48c6-93a4-4378196957fd&token=OWE5MjUwYjMtMmI3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a9250b3-2b70-48c6-93a4-4378196957fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:11:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Avi Products India Ltd has appointed Mr. Manas Ranjan Palo as an Additional Director (Non-Executive-Independent) and Mr. Saroj Kumar Choudhury as an Additional Director (Non-Executive-Non-Independent) for a term of 5 years each. The company has also appointed Mrs Shanu Jain as the Company Secretary and Compliance Officer. Furthermore, M/s N.K. JALAN &amp; CO., Chartered Accountants have been reappointed as Statutory Auditors for a second term of 5 years, and M/s. VKMG &amp; Associates LLP have been appointed as Secretarial Auditors for a term of five consecutive years.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Manas Ranjan Palo as an Additional Director (Non-Executive-Independent)</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Saroj Kumar Choudhury as an Additional Director (Non-Executive-Non-Independent)</li><li>Appointment of Mrs Shanu Jain as the Company Secretary and Compliance Officer</li><li>Reappointment of M/s N.K. JALAN &amp; CO., Chartered Accountants as Statutory Auditors</li><li>Appointment of M/s. VKMG &amp; Associates LLP as Secretarial Auditors</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f8a9617a-60bb-4259-a2aa-3a1a8af10135.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Avi Products India Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WIPRO] Wipro Ltd Releases Auditor&apos;s Report for Q3 2025 with UDIN</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=WIPRO+LTD.&title=Wipro+Ltd+Releases+Auditor%27s+Report+for+Q3+2025+with+UDIN&newsId=f3898a85-9a78-47dc-bce8-3866ada20e9c&token=ZjM4OThhODUtOWE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3898a85-9a78-47dc-bce8-3866ada20e9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:03:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Wipro Ltd, a leading IT company, has released the auditor&apos;s report for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The report, which includes the Unique Document Identification Number (UDIN), was filed with the stock exchanges on January 16, 2026, and is also available on the company&apos;s website. The audit was conducted in accordance with the Standards on Auditing and the report states that the financial statements give a true and fair view of the company&apos;s net profit and other comprehensive income in conformity with the Indian Accounting Standard 34 and other accounting principles generally accepted in India.</p><ul><li>Wipro Ltd has released the auditor&apos;s report for Q3 2025.</li><li>The report includes the Unique Document Identification Number (UDIN).</li><li>The audit was conducted in accordance with the Standards on Auditing.</li><li>The report states that the financial statements give a true and fair view of the company&apos;s net profit and other comprehensive income.</li><li>The report was filed with the stock exchanges on January 16, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a0ef5160-6972-4abd-8633-abcf318df5d6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: WIPRO LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NISMGMT] NIS Management Ltd Receives Notice from ESIC for Alleged Dues Recovery</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NIS+Management+Ltd&title=NIS+Management+Ltd+Receives+Notice+from+ESIC+for+Alleged+Dues+Recovery&newsId=67a47177-e7ea-49a7-9937-3aff4a3d1eed&token=NjdhNDcxNzctZTdl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67a47177-e7ea-49a7-9937-3aff4a3d1eed</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>NIS Management Ltd has received a Notice of Demand from the Employees’ State Insurance Corporation (ESIC) demanding recovery of alleged dues. The dispute pertains to Sections 45-C to 45-I of the Employees’ State Insurance Act, 1948. The Company is currently examining the notice and will be applying for a stay on the operation and enforcement of the demand notice. The potential financial implication is up to INR 64,55,685.</p><ul><li>NIS Management Ltd has received a Notice of Demand from ESIC</li><li>The dispute pertains to Sections 45-C to 45-I of the Employees’ State Insurance Act, 1948</li><li>The Company is examining the notice and will apply for a stay</li><li>The potential financial implication is up to INR 64,55,685</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/11adcba2-578c-45d5-a286-1357e1fb6157.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NIS Management Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADANIPORTS] Adani Ports&apos; Statutory Auditor Converts to LLP</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADANI+PORTS+AND+SPECIAL+ECONOMIC+ZONE+LTD.&title=Adani+Ports%27+Statutory+Auditor+Converts+to+LLP&newsId=1d744ffa-2a68-4c64-a452-29c5218848e4&token=MWQ3NDRmZmEtMmE2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d744ffa-2a68-4c64-a452-29c5218848e4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone Ltd. has been informed by their Statutory Auditors, M S K A &amp; Associates, that the firm has converted into a Limited Liability Partnership (LLP) under the Limited Liability Partnership Act, 2008, effective January 13, 2026. The change in constitution does not affect their tenure or obligations as Statutory Auditors.</p><ul><li>Adani Ports&apos; Statutory Auditor, M S K A &amp; Associates, has converted into a Limited Liability Partnership (LLP) under the Limited Liability Partnership Act, 2008.</li><li>The change in constitution is effective from January 13, 2026.</li><li>The auditor will continue to function and discharge their obligations as Statutory Auditors for the remaining period of the approved tenure.</li><li>The new LLP is now known as MS KA &amp; Associates LLP, Chartered Accountants.</li><li>Companies are requested to take note and record the change.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e4832a71-0bae-4979-ba23-f1cff4859164.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADANI PORTS AND SPECIAL ECONOMIC ZONE LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SPARC] Sun Pharma Advanced Research Company Ltd. to Issue Convertible Warrants to Promoter Group Member</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SUN+PHARMA+ADVANCED+RESEARCH+COMPANY+LTD.&title=Sun+Pharma+Advanced+Research+Company+Ltd.+to+Issue+Convertible+Warrants+to+Promoter+Group+Member&newsId=b63d3ef8-81cc-43e0-9088-8a7adbb5d8de&token=YjYzZDNlZjgtODFj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b63d3ef8-81cc-43e0-9088-8a7adbb5d8de</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:54:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sun Pharma Advanced Research Company Ltd. has announced an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) to consider the issuance of convertible warrants on a preferential basis to a member of the promoter group. The warrants, each convertible into one fully paid-up equity share, will be issued at a price of INR 155.80. The total issue size is INR 5,99,98,58,000. The relevant date for determining the floor price is Friday, January 9, 2026. The warrants can be exercised within 18 months from the date of allotment. The issuance is subject to various approvals, consents, and permissions from relevant authorities.</p><ul><li>Issue of convertible warrants to promoter group member</li><li>Warrants convertible into fully paid-up equity shares</li><li>Issue size of INR 5,99,98,58,000</li><li>Warrants can be exercised within 18 months from the date of allotment</li><li>Subject to various approvals, consents, and permissions</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1ba68771-e179-417b-aae4-bf8de46cf291.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SUN PHARMA ADVANCED RESEARCH COMPANY LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[APIL] Avi Products India Ltd: Board Meeting Approves Key Appointments and Reappointments</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Avi+Products+India+Ltd&title=Avi+Products+India+Ltd%3A+Board+Meeting+Approves+Key+Appointments+and+Reappointments&newsId=8f23fd3f-1c29-4eb7-8145-c33babe2f0bc&token=OGYyM2ZkM2YtMWMy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f23fd3f-1c29-4eb7-8145-c33babe2f0bc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:44:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In a recent board meeting, Avi Products India Ltd approved several key appointments and reappointments. The board appointed Mr. Manas Ranjan Palo as an Additional Director (Non-Executive- Independent) and Mr. Saroj Kumar Choudhury as an Additional Director (Non- Executive- Non-Independent) for a term of 5 years each, subject to approval in the ensuing General Meeting. The board also reappointed M/s N.K. JALAN &amp; CO., Chartered Accountants as Statutory Auditors for a second term of 5 years and appointed M/s. VKMG &amp; Associates LLP as Secretarial Auditors for a term of five consecutive years. Mrs Shanu Jain was appointed as the Company Secretary and Compliance Officer. The board also reconstituted the composition of the Audit Committee, Nomination and Remuneration Committee, and Stakeholder Relationship Committee.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Manas Ranjan Palo as Additional Director (Non-Executive- Independent)</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Saroj Kumar Choudhury as Additional Director (Non- Executive- Non-Independent)</li><li>Reappointment of M/s N.K. JALAN &amp; CO., Chartered Accountants as Statutory Auditors</li><li>Appointment of M/s. VKMG &amp; Associates LLP as Secretarial Auditors</li><li>Appointment of Mrs Shanu Jain as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2abdcf4a-10ec-4bb7-a645-0f697c6402ec.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Avi Products India Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PROTEAN] Protean eGov Technologies Ltd: Suresh Sethi Resigns as MD &amp; CEO, V Easwaran Appointed as Interim CEO</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Protean+eGov+Technologies+Ltd&title=Protean+eGov+Technologies+Ltd%3A+Suresh+Sethi+Resigns+as+MD+%26+CEO%2C+V+Easwaran+Appointed+as+Interim+CEO&newsId=5548359d-14aa-4585-921a-821b54402cf7&token=NTU0ODM1OWQtMTRh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5548359d-14aa-4585-921a-821b54402cf7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:42:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Protean eGov Technologies Ltd announced the resignation of its Managing Director &amp; Chief Executive Officer, Mr. Suresh Sethi, who will be pursuing other interests. His last working day will be March 31, 2026. The company expressed appreciation for his contributions and exemplary leadership during his tenure. Mr. V Easwaran, currently Executive Director and Chief Operating Officer, will assume charge as Interim Chief Executive Officer, effective April 1, 2026.</p><ul><li>Suresh Sethi resigns as MD &amp; CEO of Protean eGov Technologies Ltd</li><li>Sethi to pursue other interests, last working day is March 31, 2026</li><li>Company expresses gratitude for Sethi&apos;s contributions and leadership</li><li>V Easwaran appointed as Interim CEO, effective April 1, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f034c19a-654a-4e5b-adae-ef747e8f03e9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Protean eGov Technologies Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[APIL] Avi Products India Ltd Appoints Mr. Manas Ranjan Palo and Mr. Saroj Kumar Choudhury as Additional Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Avi+Products+India+Ltd&title=Avi+Products+India+Ltd+Appoints+Mr.+Manas+Ranjan+Palo+and+Mr.+Saroj+Kumar+Choudhury+as+Additional+Directors&newsId=002b865a-6afb-4493-be0a-15db1d3027d1&token=MDAyYjg2NWEtNmFm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">002b865a-6afb-4493-be0a-15db1d3027d1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:41:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Avi Products India Ltd has appointed Mr. Manas Ranjan Palo as an Additional Director (Non-Executive-Independent) and Mr. Saroj Kumar Choudhury as an Additional Director (Non-Executive-Non-Independent) in its board meeting held on January 16, 2026. The appointments are subject to the approval of the members in the ensuing General Meeting. The company has also appointed Mrs Shanu Jain as the Company Secretary and Compliance Officer. Furthermore, the company has reappointed M/s N.K. JALAN &amp; CO., Chartered Accountants as Statutory Auditors and appointed M/s. VKMG &amp; Associates LLP as Secretarial Auditors for a term of five consecutive years.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Manas Ranjan Palo as an Additional Director (Non-Executive-Independent)</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Saroj Kumar Choudhury as an Additional Director (Non-Executive-Non-Independent)</li><li>Appointment of Mrs Shanu Jain as the Company Secretary and Compliance Officer</li><li>Reappointment of M/s N.K. JALAN &amp; CO., Chartered Accountants as Statutory Auditors</li><li>Appointment of M/s. VKMG &amp; Associates LLP as Secretarial Auditors</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a635614d-406e-4d83-9aed-1dff1b45464a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Avi Products India Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>