<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:40:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[UDAYJEW] Uday Jewellery Industries Ltd Announces Scheme of Arrangement with Narbada Gems &amp; Jewellery Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Uday+Jewellery+Industries+Ltd&title=Uday+Jewellery+Industries+Ltd+Announces+Scheme+of+Arrangement+with+Narbada+Gems+%26+Jewellery+Limited&newsId=5a229bf1-21a6-4156-8172-3b4fb9a06bc4&token=NWEyMjliZjEtMjFh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a229bf1-21a6-4156-8172-3b4fb9a06bc4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:37:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Merger</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Uday Jewellery Industries Ltd has announced the filing of INC-28 in respect of a Scheme of Arrangement between Narbada Gems &amp; Jewellery Limited and Uday Jewellery Industries Limited. The scheme has been sanctioned by the Hon’ble NCLT Hyderabad Bench and will be effective from 19th February, 2026. Pursuant to the scheme, the Transferor Company shall stand amalgamated into the Company and be dissolved without being wound up. The Authorized share capital of the Company will automatically stand increased. The &apos;Effective Date&apos; of the Scheme is 19 February,2026.</p><ul><li>Uday Jewellery Industries Ltd and Narbada Gems &amp; Jewellery Limited have filed e-form INC-28 with the RoC to make the scheme effective.</li><li>The scheme has been sanctioned by the Hon’ble NCLT Hyderabad Bench and will be effective from 19th February, 2026.</li><li>The Transferor Company shall stand amalgamated into the Company and be dissolved without being wound up.</li><li>The Authorized share capital of the Company will automatically stand increased.</li><li>The &apos;Effective Date&apos; of the Scheme is 19 February,2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/01dbec93-559d-419f-80c3-08f6fe7b00e3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Uday Jewellery Industries Ltd | Category: Merger</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SANOFI] Sanofi India Ltd to Approve Audited Financial Results for Q4 and FY 2025 on 25th February 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sanofi+India+Ltd&title=Sanofi+India+Ltd+to+Approve+Audited+Financial+Results+for+Q4+and+FY+2025+on+25th+February+2026&newsId=36472f87-5a70-40f4-a0ff-b3cc2cef3e76&token=MzY0NzJmODctNWE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">36472f87-5a70-40f4-a0ff-b3cc2cef3e76</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sanofi India Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 25th February 2026 to consider and approve the Audited Financial Results and Statements for the Quarter and Financial Year ended 31st December 2025. The Board will also consider and recommend Final Dividend, if any, for the Financial Year ended 31st December 2025. The trading window for the purpose of publication of Audited Financial Results of the Company for the Quarter and Financial Year ended 31st December 2025 shall remain closed from 1st January 2026 to 27th February 2026 (both days inclusive).</p><ul><li>Sanofi India Ltd to consider and approve the Audited Financial Results for Q4 and FY 2025 on 25th February 2026</li><li>The Board will also consider and recommend Final Dividend, if any, for the Financial Year ended 31st December 2025</li><li>Trading window for the purpose of publication of Audited Financial Results remains closed from 1st January 2026 to 27th February 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b6f1c6b5-4ad7-45f6-a0e7-1fd321faf393.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sanofi India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SANHP] Sangam Health Care Products Ltd to Appoint New Chief Financial Officer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sangam+Health+Care+Products+Ltd&title=Sangam+Health+Care+Products+Ltd+to+Appoint+New+Chief+Financial+Officer&newsId=21e9d63a-c304-4e43-b057-98a58b44c961&token=MjFlOWQ2M2EtYzMw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21e9d63a-c304-4e43-b057-98a58b44c961</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:22:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sangam Health Care Products Ltd has announced that a meeting of the Board of Directors will be held on 24th February 2026. The agenda includes the appointment of a new Chief Financial Officer in compliance with the Companies (Appointment and Qualification of Directors) Rules, 2014 and the Companies (Meetings of Board and its Powers) Regulations, 2015. The meeting will also consider any other business with the permission of the Chair.</p><ul><li>Sangam Health Care Products Ltd to appoint a new Chief Financial Officer</li><li>The appointment is in compliance with the Companies (Appointment and Qualification of Directors) Rules, 2014 and the Companies (Meetings of Board and its Powers) Regulations, 2015</li><li>The meeting is scheduled for 24th February 2026</li><li>The Board will also consider any other business with the permission of the Chair</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/22aab0b6-c586-43cc-a9ed-11adc9b901c7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sangam Health Care Products Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INTELLECT] Arab National Bank Leverages Intellect&apos;s eMACH.ai Wholesale Banking Platform to Accelerate Digital Innovation in Saudi Arabia, Supporting Vision 2030 Transformation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Intellect+Design+Arena+Ltd&title=Arab+National+Bank+Leverages+Intellect%27s+eMACH.ai+Wholesale+Banking+Platform+to+Accelerate+Digital+Innovation+in+Saudi+Arabia%2C+Supporting+Vision+2030+Transformation&newsId=c1b36849-5499-4f24-81b1-3e2a80481aba&token=YzFiMzY4NDktNTQ5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c1b36849-5499-4f24-81b1-3e2a80481aba</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:21:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Intellect Design Arena Ltd. announced that Arab National Bank has implemented Intellect’s eMACH.ai Digital Transaction Banking solution to enhance its digital capabilities. This digital transformation represents a significant milestone in delivering next-generation wholesale banking solutions tailored for the Saudi market. These offerings on cash management, built on Intellect’s eMACH.ai platform, are designed to meet the complex needs of leading industries while aligning with Saudi Arabia’s Vision 2030 digital transformation goals. The eMACH.ai platform differentiates itself by powering 12 industry clusters and 36 sectors, delivering tailored wholesale banking solutions aligned with the Kingdom’s strategic industries.</p><ul><li>ANB implements Intellect’s eMACH.ai Digital Transaction Banking solution to enhance its digital capabilities.</li><li>The new offering aligns with Saudi Arabia’s Vision 2030 digital transformation goals.</li><li>eMACH.ai platform delivers tailored wholesale banking solutions for various industries.</li><li>ANB is committed to driving digital transformation in Saudi Arabia&apos;s wholesale banking sector.</li><li>eMACH.ai platform differentiates itself by powering 12 industry clusters and 36 sectors.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4f2ad607-2ca2-47b6-b2fe-843804b4c453.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Intellect Design Arena Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PURVA] Puravankara launches Premium Residential Development &apos;Purva Silversky&apos; in Bengaluru&apos;s Electronic City</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Puravankara+Ltd&title=Puravankara+launches+Premium+Residential+Development+%27Purva+Silversky%27+in+Bengaluru%27s+Electronic+City&newsId=286fecd2-5509-46a1-a838-2c9d76389d1b&token=Mjg2ZmVjZDItNTUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">286fecd2-5509-46a1-a838-2c9d76389d1b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Puravankara Limited, a trusted real estate developer, has announced the launch of Purva Silversky, a premium residential development in Hebbagodi, Electronic City, Bengaluru. Spread across approximately 6.99 acres, the project comprises 356 exclusive residences across three iconic 32-storey towers. The project boasts nearly 88% open-to-sky spaces and is positioned as a low-density development with just four residences per floor. Strategically located in one of Bengaluru’s most established technology corridors, Purva Silversky enjoys excellent connectivity to major IT hubs, corporate parks, educational institutions, healthcare facilities, and retail destinations. The development features expansive 3, 4 &amp; 5 BHK residences with unit sizes ranging from approximately 1,864 sq ft to over 5,300 sq ft. The project is expected to cater primarily to end-users seeking spacious, well-designed homes with strong connectivity and a holistic lifestyle offering in one of Bengaluru’s key growth corridors. Homes are priced at Rs 12,100+ per sq ft (excluding statutory and other charges). The project is RERA-registered and is scheduled for completion in 2030.</p><ul><li>Puravankara Limited launches a premium residential development &apos;Purva Silversky&apos; in Bengaluru&apos;s Electronic City.</li><li>Spread across approximately 6.99 acres with 356 exclusive residences in three 32-storey towers.</li><li>Nearly 88% open-to-sky spaces and low-density development with just four residences per floor.</li><li>Excellent connectivity to major IT hubs, corporate parks, educational institutions, healthcare facilities, and retail destinations.</li><li>Expansive 3, 4 &amp; 5 BHK residences with unit sizes ranging from approximately 1,864 sq ft to over 5,300 sq ft, priced at Rs 12,100+ per sq ft.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/01536e15-efd6-4cb7-af50-f0d404f8ea3c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Puravankara Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TARMAT] Arton Global Acquires 7.18% Stake in Tarmat Ltd: SEBI Disclosure</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TARMAT+LTD.&title=Arton+Global+Acquires+7.18%25+Stake+in+Tarmat+Ltd%3A+SEBI+Disclosure&newsId=4b5a838f-130c-43b0-abe0-8d9447d3228f&token=NGI1YTgzOGYtMTMw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4b5a838f-130c-43b0-abe0-8d9447d3228f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Arton Global has acquired 7.18% equity shares of Tarmat Ltd, as per the disclosure under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. The acquisition was made through the open market. The total equity shares of Tarmat Ltd before the acquisition were 2.50 cr shares, which increased to 2.50 cr shares after the acquisition. The total diluted share/voting capital of the TC after the said acquisition is also 2.50 cr shares.</p><ul><li>Arton Global acquires 7.18% stake in Tarmat Ltd</li><li>Acquisition made through open market</li><li>Total equity shares of Tarmat Ltd before the acquisition were 2.50 cr shares</li><li>Total equity shares of Tarmat Ltd after the acquisition are also 2.50 cr shares</li><li>Total diluted share/voting capital of the TC after the said acquisition is 2.50 cr shares</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/DC800B7E_0477_4394_BFD6_38A739924110_143454.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TARMAT LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LATIMMETAL] Rahul Timbadia Acquires 25,000 Shares of La Tim Metal &amp; Industries Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=La+Tim+Metal+%26+Industries+Ltd&title=Rahul+Timbadia+Acquires+25%2C000+Shares+of+La+Tim+Metal+%26+Industries+Ltd&newsId=c20bac83-8489-4a57-9fc7-16251d5670f5&token=YzIwYmFjODMtODQ4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c20bac83-8489-4a57-9fc7-16251d5670f5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rahul Timbadia has acquired 25,000 equity shares of La Tim Metal &amp; Industries Limited on February 18, 2026. This disclosure was made under Regulation 29(1) &amp; 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. The acquisition took place on the Bombay Stock Exchange (BSE) Limited. Before the acquisition, Rahul Timbadia held 8.72% of the total share/voting capital and 8.72% of the total diluted share/voting capital. After the acquisition, his holding increased to 8.74% of the total share/voting capital and 8.74% of the total diluted share/voting capital.</p><ul><li>Rahul Timbadia acquired 25,000 equity shares of La Tim Metal &amp; Industries Limited on February 18, 2026.</li><li>The acquisition was made under Regulation 29(1) &amp; 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</li><li>The acquisition took place on the Bombay Stock Exchange (BSE) Limited.</li><li>Before the acquisition, Rahul Timbadia held 8.72% of the total share/voting capital and 8.72% of the total diluted share/voting capital.</li><li>After the acquisition, his holding increased to 8.74% of the total share/voting capital and 8.74% of the total diluted share/voting capital.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/572C2039_1E1F_4958_9F36_F6586281A486_143238.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: La Tim Metal & Industries Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASHAPURMIN] Chetan Shah Acquires 49,000 Equity Shares in Ashapura Minechem Ltd via Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ASHAPURA+MINECHEM+LTD.&title=Chetan+Shah+Acquires+49%2C000+Equity+Shares+in+Ashapura+Minechem+Ltd+via+Open+Market&newsId=ca82e66d-1670-4140-b1f9-d1f012aa192a&token=Y2E4MmU2NmQtMTY3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ca82e66d-1670-4140-b1f9-d1f012aa192a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:08:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>According to a disclosure made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011, Chetan Navnitlal Shah has acquired 49,000 equity shares in Ashapura Minechem Ltd. The acquisition took place in the open market on 18th February, 2026. The total voting rights of Chetan Navnitlal Shah before the acquisition were 14.31% and after the acquisition, they stand at 14.37%.</p><ul><li>Chetan Navnitlal Shah acquires 49,000 equity shares in Ashapura Minechem Ltd</li><li>The acquisition took place in the open market</li><li>Before the acquisition, Chetan Navnitlal Shah&apos;s voting rights were 14.31%</li><li>After the acquisition, Chetan Navnitlal Shah&apos;s voting rights stand at 14.37%</li><li>The acquisition was disclosed under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ADEEFA30_D74F_4717_A871_664BFC6C982E_143647.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ASHAPURA MINECHEM LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BLBLIMITED] BLB Ltd Promoter Brij Rattan Bagri Acquires 0.98% Shares Through Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BLB+LTD.&title=BLB+Ltd+Promoter+Brij+Rattan+Bagri+Acquires+0.98%25+Shares+Through+Open+Market&newsId=9e7fbe4a-7cbc-46c8-9b8c-cd293b9c28bc&token=OWU3ZmJlNGEtN2Ni</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e7fbe4a-7cbc-46c8-9b8c-cd293b9c28bc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>BLB Ltd Promoter Brij Rattan Bagri has acquired 5,14,716 equity shares of the company, which is 0.98% of the total equity share capital, through the open market. The acquisition took place on 18th February 2026. After the acquisition, Bagri&apos;s holding of shares carrying voting rights stands at 43.47%.</p><ul><li>Brij Rattan Bagri, Promoter &amp; Managing Director of BLB Limited, acquired 5,14,716 equity shares of the company on 18th February 2026 through the open market.</li><li>The acquisition represents 0.98% of the total equity share capital and 0.98% of the total voting rights of the company.</li><li>Before the acquisition, Bagri&apos;s holding was 42.49% of the total equity share capital and voting rights.</li><li>After the acquisition, Bagri&apos;s holding stands at 43.47% of the total equity share capital and voting rights.</li><li>The total equity share capital of the company remains unchanged at Rs. 5,28,65,258.00</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/90EAC4BF_7A98_47D4_84D4_03B81EC6B7CC_143547.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BLB LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[POONADAL] Poona Dal &amp; Oil Industries Ltd: Sunil Deepchand Parakh Acquires Shares Through Inter-se Transfer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=POONA+DAL+%26+OIL+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Poona+Dal+%26+Oil+Industries+Ltd%3A+Sunil+Deepchand+Parakh+Acquires+Shares+Through+Inter-se+Transfer&newsId=06b91aed-ae5f-4ae0-9e1f-a1ee1e0b5ab2&token=MDZiOTFhZWQtYWU1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06b91aed-ae5f-4ae0-9e1f-a1ee1e0b5ab2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 09:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Exchange has received a disclosure under Regulation 10(6) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011 for Sunil Parakh. Sunil Deepchand Parakh, a part of the Promoter Category of Poona Dal and Oil Industries Limited, has acquired equity shares of the company from Sunil Deepchand Parakh HUF, also a part of the Promoter Category, through an inter-se transfer of shares by way of an off-market transaction. The transaction details are as follows: Sunil Deepchand Parakh acquired 321,110 shares, which is 5.63% of the total shares of the company, on 18th February 2026. This inter-se transfer among promoters is in compliance with Regulation 10(1)(a)(i) and Regulation 10(1)(a)(ii) of SEBI(SAST) Regulation,2011.</p><ul><li>Sunil Deepchand Parakh acquires 321,110 shares of Poona Dal and Oil Industries Limited from Sunil Deepchand Parakh HUF.</li><li>The acquisition is through an inter-se transfer of shares by way of an off-market transaction.</li><li>The transaction is in compliance with Regulation 10(1)(a)(i) and Regulation 10(1)(a)(ii) of SEBI(SAST) Regulation,2011.</li><li>The total shares acquired are 5.63% of the total shares of the company.</li><li>The transaction took place on 18th February 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/DF25CD63_1D5B_41E6_A590_414C70061DFE_142715.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: POONA DAL & OIL INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>