<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:25:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[INTELLECT] Intellect Design Arena Launches Purple Fabric-powered Tech Services TeamSpace, Boosting Productivity and Governance</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Intellect+Design+Arena+Ltd&title=Intellect+Design+Arena+Launches+Purple+Fabric-powered+Tech+Services+TeamSpace%2C+Boosting+Productivity+and+Governance&newsId=e7e7de15-e1e6-4495-a748-7b57a6cc6b0b&token=ZTdlN2RlMTUtZTFl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e7e7de15-e1e6-4495-a748-7b57a6cc6b0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:05:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Intellect Design Arena Ltd., a global leader in Al-First, enterprise-grade platforms, has launched Tech Services TeamSpace, built on Purple Fabric, the world’s first Open Business Impact Al platform. The platform, designed for Tech Services companies employing between 50 and 5000 professionals, offers a governed Agentic Al environment that strengthens productivity, compresses delivery timelines, enhances quality, and enables mid-sized firms to compete confidently with larger global players. The platform is available under Intellect’s Enterprise Al on Tap model, starting at just ¥99,500 per month.</p><ul><li>Launch of Purple Fabric-powered Tech Services TeamSpace</li><li>Designed for Tech Services companies with 50-5000 employees</li><li>Offers a governed Agentic Al environment</li><li>Strengthens productivity, compresses delivery timelines, and enhances quality</li><li>Available under Intellect’s Enterprise Al on Tap model for ¥99,500 per month</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e0a1e791-2413-4f8b-ab49-9089959b982c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Intellect Design Arena Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LLFICL] Leading Leasing Finance and Investment Company Ltd: Appointment of Ms. Shweta as Additional Director and Resignation of Mr. Saumik Arvind Ghervada</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Leading+Leasing+Finance+And+Investment+Company+Ltd&title=Leading+Leasing+Finance+and+Investment+Company+Ltd%3A+Appointment+of+Ms.+Shweta+as+Additional+Director+and+Resignation+of+Mr.+Saumik+Arvind+Ghervada&newsId=71864814-712c-4ba1-8b96-4ef43106b8ca&token=NzE4NjQ4MTQtNzEy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71864814-712c-4ba1-8b96-4ef43106b8ca</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Leading Leasing Finance and Investment Company Ltd approved the appointment of Ms. Shweta as an Additional Director for a period of five consecutive years and the resignation of Mr. Saumik Arvind Ghervada due to pre-occupancy. The meeting was held on 21st February 2026 and concluded at 02:00 PM.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Ms. Shweta as Additional Director for a period of five consecutive years.</li><li>Resignation of Mr. Saumik Arvind Ghervada due to pre-occupancy.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/65c2fbbd-fa1b-463e-812c-cafb0c63f38c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Leading Leasing Finance And Investment Company Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[THIRDFIN] UVS Hospitality to Acquire 51% Stake in Calcio Restaurants for Rs. 35 Crores via Share Swap</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=THIRDWAVE+FINANCIAL+INTERMEDIARIES+LTD.&title=UVS+Hospitality+to+Acquire+51%25+Stake+in+Calcio+Restaurants+for+Rs.+35+Crores+via+Share+Swap&newsId=23c56c62-81b3-4f01-b699-0387fd314e2d&token=MjNjNTZjNjItODFi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23c56c62-81b3-4f01-b699-0387fd314e2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>UVS Hospitality and Services Ltd. has approved the acquisition of up to 51% of the paid-up equity share capital of Calcio Restaurants Private Limited through a share swap. The deal is valued at approximately Rs. 35,02,67,100. The acquisition is expected to be completed within 15 days from the date of approval from the shareholders or other relevant authorities including the Stock Exchange.</p><ul><li>UVS Hospitality to acquire 51% stake in Calcio Restaurants for Rs. 35 Crores via share swap</li><li>Calcio Restaurants is a Mumbai-based company incorporated in 2020, operating in the hotels and restaurants sector</li><li>The acquisition is expected to be completed within 15 days from the date of approval from the shareholders or other relevant authorities</li><li>The deal is a share swap, with the non-cash consideration to be discharged by way of issuance of equity shares of the Company on a preferential basis</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4c1ee9e8-f488-4a4a-8e6b-8ccfa2976b19.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: THIRDWAVE FINANCIAL INTERMEDIARIES LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AFIL] Akme Fintrade (India) Ltd Approves Preferential Issue of Convertible Warrants Worth Rs. 85,75 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Akme+Fintrade+%28India%29+Ltd&title=Akme+Fintrade+%28India%29+Ltd+Approves+Preferential+Issue+of+Convertible+Warrants+Worth+Rs.+85%2C75+Crores&newsId=b6b29ce9-18cb-4cbf-b04d-a072521947c5&token=YjZiMjljZTktMThj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6b29ce9-18cb-4cbf-b04d-a072521947c5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:02:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Akme Fintrade (India) Ltd announced the outcome of its Board Meeting held on February 21, 2026. The Board approved the issuance of upto 12,25,00,000 (Twelve Crore Twenty Five Lakhs) warrants, each convertible into one equity share, at a price of Rs. 7/- each. The total worth of the warrants is Rs. 85,75,00,000. The decision is subject to necessary approvals from the members of the Company and other regulatory authorities.</p><ul><li>Akme Fintrade (India) Ltd to issue upto 12,25,00,000 warrants worth Rs. 85,75,00,000</li><li>Warrants to be convertible into one equity share at a price of Rs. 7/- each</li><li>Issuance to be made in accordance with Section 42 and Section 62(1)(c) of the Companies Act, 2013</li><li>Subject to necessary approvals from members and regulatory authorities</li><li>Extra-ordinary general meeting of the members to be held on Friday, 20th March, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d2d24de0-b70f-4224-9fc6-69eaac911ef2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Akme Fintrade (India) Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAMOR] Samor Reality Ltd Amends Partnership Deed for &apos;The Leela by Samor&apos; Project</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Samor+Reality+Ltd&title=Samor+Reality+Ltd+Amends+Partnership+Deed+for+%27The+Leela+by+Samor%27+Project&newsId=e39c3efe-406c-4fa0-a3fe-ec05f3737720&token=ZTM5YzNlZmUtNDA2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e39c3efe-406c-4fa0-a3fe-ec05f3737720</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Samor Reality Limited has executed an Amendment to the Deed of Partnership dated 18th February, 2026 for its real estate project &apos;The Leela by Samor&apos;. The amendment involves the sale/transfer of part of its share/interest in the partnership to Swastik Landmark Projects LLP. The capital contribution and profit/loss sharing ratios have been revised accordingly. The Board of Directors has authorized Mr. Birjukumar Ajitbhai Shah, Managing Director, to negotiate, finalize, and execute the transaction.</p><ul><li>Samor Reality Ltd has amended the Deed of Partnership for &apos;The Leela by Samor&apos; project.</li><li>The amendment involves the sale/transfer of part of its share/interest to Swastik Landmark Projects LLP.</li><li>The capital contribution ratios have been revised as per the amendment.</li><li>The profit/loss sharing ratios have also been revised.</li><li>Mr. Birjukumar Ajitbhai Shah, Managing Director, has been authorized to negotiate and finalize the transaction.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dfffb5d9-bc22-4fff-aefc-efbb30e7c8ec.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Samor Reality Ltd | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SYRMA] Syrma SGS Technology Extends Long-Stop Date for Ksolare Energy Acquisition</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Syrma+SGS+Technology+Ltd&title=Syrma+SGS+Technology+Extends+Long-Stop+Date+for+Ksolare+Energy+Acquisition&newsId=0feb7e92-cdeb-4500-945e-54dbc2066bf8&token=MGZlYjdlOTItY2Rl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0feb7e92-cdeb-4500-945e-54dbc2066bf8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Syrma SGS Technology Ltd. has agreed to extend the Long Stop Date for the acquisition of a 49% equity stake in Ksolare Energy Private Limited until April 15, 2026. This extension is in connection with the proposed acquisition, which was initially slated for fulfillment of conditions precedent. The extension agreement was reached by the parties involved in the acquisition, which also includes Premier Energies Limited. The documents related to this extension have been uploaded to the company&apos;s website for reference.</p><ul><li>Syrma SGS Technology extends Long-Stop Date for Ksolare Energy acquisition</li><li>Proposed acquisition of 49% equity stake in Ksolare Energy Private Limited</li><li>Extension agreed upon by all parties involved</li><li>Extension until April 15, 2026</li><li>Documents available on the company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3cd1c67f-f4b6-4f44-badc-00359fea0c90.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Syrma SGS Technology Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[USK] Udayshivakumar Infra Ltd: Promoter Acquires Equity Shares Worth INR 77005</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Udayshivakumar+Infra+Ltd&title=Udayshivakumar+Infra+Ltd%3A+Promoter+Acquires+Equity+Shares+Worth+INR+77005&newsId=657ec9a3-4783-4de8-ad6d-ab65b6fd06eb&token=NjU3ZWM5YTMtNDc4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">657ec9a3-4783-4de8-ad6d-ab65b6fd06eb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Udayshivakumar Infra Ltd. has received a disclosure from its Promoter and Managing Director, Mr. Udayshivakumar, under Regulation 7(2)(a) of SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015. The disclosure is in Form C and pertains to the acquisition of equity shares of the company. The Promoter acquired equity shares worth INR 77005. The transaction took place on the market exchange.</p><ul><li>Promoter, Mr. Udayshivakumar, acquires equity shares worth INR 77005</li><li>Transaction took place on the market exchange</li><li>The Promoter&apos;s share holding increased to 65.44%</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a569a4f7-e088-433b-bb03-a8fa0e4523ca.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Udayshivakumar Infra Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HYPERSOFT] Hypersoft Technologies Fined by BSE Limited for Delayed Submission of Shareholder Complaints Statement</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Hypersoft+Technologies+Ltd&title=Hypersoft+Technologies+Fined+by+BSE+Limited+for+Delayed+Submission+of+Shareholder+Complaints+Statement&newsId=e2b69815-0f16-4b93-8008-b297931d45cf&token=ZTJiNjk4MTUtMGYx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e2b69815-0f16-4b93-8008-b297931d45cf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:31:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hypersoft Technologies Ltd. has been fined by BSE Limited for a delay in submitting the statement on shareholder complaints under Regulation 13(3) of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015 for the quarter ended 31% December 2025. The delay was inadvertent and due to oversight. The Company is strengthening its internal compliance monitoring mechanisms to avoid such instances in the future. The fine imposed is Rs. 2,360 (Inclusive of GST). The Company does not foresee any impact on its financial operations or other activities due to this fine.</p><ul><li>Hypersoft Technologies fined by BSE Limited for delayed submission of shareholder complaints statement</li><li>Fine of Rs. 2,360 (Inclusive of GST) imposed</li><li>The delay was inadvertent and due to oversight</li><li>Company strengthening internal compliance monitoring mechanisms</li><li>No foreseen impact on financial or other activities</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bb199439-0650-4e13-b2b9-6ba446c0e4ba.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Hypersoft Technologies Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHARIKA] Sharika Enterprises Secures Rs. 64 Lakh Order from LS Cable India</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sharika+Enterprises+Ltd&title=Sharika+Enterprises+Secures+Rs.+64+Lakh+Order+from+LS+Cable+India&newsId=219c7181-6729-41c1-a2fd-52b951c0e8ac&token=MjE5YzcxODEtNjcy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">219c7181-6729-41c1-a2fd-52b951c0e8ac</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sharika Enterprises Ltd has announced the receipt of a purchase order from LS Cable India Private Limited for the supply of 48F OPGW Cable. The contract is worth Rs. 64,47,840/- (Rupees Sixty-Four Lakh Forty-Seven Thousand Eight Hundred Forty only) and is to be executed by 15th March, 2026. This disclosure is pursuant to Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015 and SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/CFD/CFD-PoD-1/P/CIR/2023/123 dated 13th July, 2023.</p><ul><li>Sharika Enterprises has received a purchase order from LS Cable India Private Limited.</li><li>The contract is for the supply of 48F OPGW Cable.</li><li>The contract is worth Rs. 64,47,840/-.</li><li>The contract is to be executed by 15th March, 2026.</li><li>This disclosure is pursuant to Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015 and SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/CFD/CFD-PoD-1/P/CIR/2023/123 dated 13th July, 2023.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ad1c85b4-ad6b-4a5b-8e14-b4694ce4183e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sharika Enterprises Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHARIKA] Sharika Enterprises Ltd Receives Order Worth Rs. 2 Crore from LS Cable India Private Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sharika+Enterprises+Ltd&title=Sharika+Enterprises+Ltd+Receives+Order+Worth+Rs.+2+Crore+from+LS+Cable+India+Private+Limited&newsId=52bff672-12b4-4be5-bfaf-636cdb89b288&token=NTJiZmY2NzItMTJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">52bff672-12b4-4be5-bfaf-636cdb89b288</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Sharika Enterprises Ltd has announced the receipt of a purchase order from LS Cable India Private Limited for the supply of 24F/48F OPGW Cable. The order is worth Rs. 2,12,92,820/- and is a domestic purchase order. The contract is to be executed within four weeks from the date of the order.</p><ul><li>Sharika Enterprises Ltd has received a purchase order from LS Cable India Private Limited for the supply of 24F/48F OPGW Cable.</li><li>The order is worth Rs. 2,12,92,820/-.</li><li>The contract is a domestic purchase order.</li><li>The contract is to be executed within four weeks from the date of the order.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/06cf54d6-e93b-40af-81a4-3df1723ef7ef.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sharika Enterprises Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>