<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:55:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[NOVIS] Nova Iron &amp; Steel Ltd. Announces Q3 and Nine Months Unaudited Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NOVA+IRON+%26+STEEL+LTD.&title=Nova+Iron+%26+Steel+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=fb1a7b03-1288-4407-a27e-c743b434da90&token=ZmIxYTdiMDMtMTI4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fb1a7b03-1288-4407-a27e-c743b434da90</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:55:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Nova Iron &amp; Steel Ltd. has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31/12/2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 10,803.54 Lakhs for the quarter and 41,691.38 Lakhs for the nine months period. The company&apos;s total income, cost of materials consumed, other income, finance costs, depreciation, and profit before tax have also been reported. The company has not recognized interest on borrowings with respect to certain lenders, leading to a qualified opinion from the independent auditor.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter is 10,803.54 Lakhs</li><li>Nine months revenue from operations is 41,691.38 Lakhs</li><li>Cost of materials consumed for the quarter is 8,132.35 Lakhs</li><li>Profit before tax for the quarter is 1,177.34 Lakhs</li><li>Qualified opinion from the independent auditor due to unrecognized interest on borrowings</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d3bdc032-15de-4956-a6d5-fcb369b54017.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NOVA IRON & STEEL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHIVAGR] Shivagrico Implements Ltd Appoints Mr. Arvind Joshi and Mrs. Kavita Jain as Additional Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHIVAGRICO+IMPLEMENTS+LTD.&title=Shivagrico+Implements+Ltd+Appoints+Mr.+Arvind+Joshi+and+Mrs.+Kavita+Jain+as+Additional+Directors&newsId=06485ac7-f9d5-4c30-b768-7c62bd86f239&token=MDY0ODVhYzctZjlk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06485ac7-f9d5-4c30-b768-7c62bd86f239</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:55:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shivagrico Implements Ltd has appointed Mr. Arvind Joshi and Mrs. Kavita Jain as additional directors designated as Non-Executive Independent Directors. The appointments are for a tenure of five years commencing from 26th February, 2026, subject to the approval of shareholders at their ensuing general meeting. The company has also appointed M/S Sharma Umesh &amp; Co. Chartered Accountant as an Internal Auditor for the financial year 2025-2026. Ms. Priyanka Shah has resigned from the post of Non-Executive Independent Director with effect from 26th February, 2026.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Arvind Joshi as Additional Director</li><li>Appointment of Mrs. Kavita Jain as Additional Director</li><li>Appointment of M/S Sharma Umesh &amp; Co. Chartered Accountant as Internal Auditor</li><li>Resignation of Ms. Priyanka Shah as Non-Executive Independent Director</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ee1f6dbe-8ce2-48bf-bba7-ee2bd2c793e9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHIVAGRICO IMPLEMENTS LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ATFL] Dr. Om Prakash Manchanda Resigns as Independent Director of Sundrop Brands Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AGRO+TECH+FOODS+LTD.&title=Dr.+Om+Prakash+Manchanda+Resigns+as+Independent+Director+of+Sundrop+Brands+Ltd&newsId=5ab768e9-c9e8-4a89-acfd-8ffd30ef7cdf&token=NWFiNzY4ZTktYzll</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ab768e9-c9e8-4a89-acfd-8ffd30ef7cdf</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:52:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dr. Om Prakash Manchanda has resigned as the Independent Director of Sundrop Brands Ltd (formerly known as Agro Tech Foods Limited) due to his enhanced professional commitments. His resignation will be effective from February 27, 2026. Dr. Manchanda has also stepped down from all the relevant Committees of the Board of Directors. The Board has expressed its gratitude for his contributions and guidance during his tenure.</p><ul><li>Dr. Om Prakash Manchanda has resigned as the Independent Director of Sundrop Brands Ltd.</li><li>His resignation is due to enhanced professional commitments.</li><li>His resignation will be effective from February 27, 2026.</li><li>Dr. Manchanda has also stepped down from all the relevant Committees of the Board of Directors.</li><li>The Board has expressed its gratitude for his contributions and guidance during his tenure.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/817b65d1-9cad-4eae-a1fe-d45ee53e39ac.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AGRO TECH FOODS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AADHARHFC] Blackstone Acquires Control of Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd with 28.28 Crore Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Aadhar+Housing+Finance+Ltd&title=Blackstone+Acquires+Control+of+Aadhar+Housing+Finance+Ltd+with+28.28+Crore+Shares&newsId=6bcd9c05-908b-47e8-973c-d123174eeb42&token=NmJjZDljMDUtOTA4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6bcd9c05-908b-47e8-973c-d123174eeb42</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:51:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd informs about a change in control of the company. BCP Topco VII Pte. Ltd., the promoter of the company, entered into a share purchase agreement with BCP Asia Il Holdco VII Pte. Ltd. on July 25, 2025. The agreement stated that BCP Asia Il Holdco VII Pte. Ltd. would acquire up to 28,20,52,121 equity shares of the company at a price not exceeding Rs. 425.00 per equity share. The acquisition has been completed on February 25, 2026. Post the acquisition, BCP Asia Il Holdco VII Pte. Ltd. now holds 28,27,88,827 equity shares of the company and has been classified as a &apos;Promoter&apos; of the company. The Seller and the current promoter group have ceased to be the &apos;promoter&apos; and members of the &apos;promoter group&apos; of the company.</p><ul><li>Blackstone&apos;s BCP Asia Il Holdco VII Pte. Ltd. has acquired 28,20,52,121 equity shares of Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd.</li><li>The acquisition has been completed on February 25, 2026.</li><li>BCP Asia Il Holdco VII Pte. Ltd. now holds 28,27,88,827 equity shares of the company and has been classified as a &apos;Promoter&apos;.</li><li>The Seller and the current promoter group have ceased to be the &apos;promoter&apos; and members of the &apos;promoter group&apos; of the company.</li><li>AXDI LDII SPV 1 LTD has acquired 44,139,236 equity shares of the company on February 26, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cd94f6f6-a07e-435f-8a73-37e660186068.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PASHUPATI] Pashupati Cotspin Ltd Announces 1:10 Equity Share Split</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Pashupati+Cotspin+Ltd&title=Pashupati+Cotspin+Ltd+Announces+1%3A10+Equity+Share+Split&newsId=b9cc9b9d-54a9-4981-9e55-5769059fd034&token=YjljYzliOWQtNTRh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b9cc9b9d-54a9-4981-9e55-5769059fd034</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Split</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Pashupati Cotspin Ltd, in its 8th Board Meeting under Regulation 30 of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015, has approved the sub-division of 1 existing Equity Share of the Company having a face value of Rs. 10/- into 1 Equity Share of Re. 1/- each. The Record Date for the purpose of the sub-division of equity shares will be intimated after taking necessary approvals. The Company has also approved the alteration of the Capital Clause of the Memorandum of Association of the Company to give effect to the aforesaid sub-division of equity shares.</p><ul><li>Pashupati Cotspin Ltd approves sub-division of 1 existing Equity Share into 1 Equity Share of Re. 1/- each</li><li>The Record Date for the purpose of the sub-division of equity shares will be intimated after taking necessary approvals</li><li>The Company has also approved the alteration of the Capital Clause of the Memorandum of Association of the Company to give effect to the aforesaid sub-division of equity shares</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a5728b04-44c3-469f-9479-546b5ab0f9d5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Pashupati Cotspin Ltd | Category: Split</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NOVIS] Nova Iron &amp; Steel Ltd. Announces Q2 and Half-Yearly Results for 2025, Reports Qualified Opinion from Auditor</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NOVA+IRON+%26+STEEL+LTD.&title=Nova+Iron+%26+Steel+Ltd.+Announces+Q2+and+Half-Yearly+Results+for+2025%2C+Reports+Qualified+Opinion+from+Auditor&newsId=3fcd7047-5059-4741-b181-240573dfbaca&token=M2ZjZDcwNDctNTA1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3fcd7047-5059-4741-b181-240573dfbaca</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:43:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Nova Iron &amp; Steel Ltd. has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and half-year ending 30/09/2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at ₹ 10,838.85 Lakhs, with a net profit of ₹ 13,974.45 Lakhs. However, the company&apos;s independent auditor, MNRS &amp; Associates, has issued a qualified opinion due to certain issues related to asset disposal and interest recognition. The company has disposed off charged assets in favor of Shree Balaji Steel and Metal Private Limited, which has not been approved in accordance with SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015. Additionally, the company has not recognized interest on borrowings with certain lenders, making it impossible to determine the impact. The company&apos;s total assets stand at ₹ 52,664.00 Lakhs, with total liabilities of ₹ 32,064.00 Lakhs as of 30/09/2025.</p><ul><li>Nova Iron &amp; Steel Ltd. reports revenue from operations of ₹ 10,838.85 Lakhs for Q2 and half-year 2025.</li><li>The company reports a net profit of ₹ 13,974.45 Lakhs for Q2 and half-year 2025.</li><li>MNRS &amp; Associates issues a qualified opinion due to issues with asset disposal and interest recognition.</li><li>The company has disposed off charged assets without proper approval from SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</li><li>Interest on borrowings with certain lenders has not been recognized, making the impact unascertainable.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5bd2af14-c43f-4c6d-8447-d7cdc59146e9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NOVA IRON & STEEL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[OMAXE] Omaxe Ltd Approves Allotment of Rs. 18,50,00,000 Unrated Senior Secured Non-Convertible Debentures</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=OMAXE+LTD.&title=Omaxe+Ltd+Approves+Allotment+of+Rs.+18%2C50%2C00%2C000+Unrated+Senior+Secured+Non-Convertible+Debentures&newsId=4fc3e6b6-19f2-4fd4-8880-556a84f8966c&token=NGZjM2U2YjYtMTlm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4fc3e6b6-19f2-4fd4-8880-556a84f8966c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:42:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Omaxe Ltd has approved the allotment of 185 Unrated Senior Secured Non-Convertible Debentures of face value of Rs.10,00,000 each, amounting to Rs. 18,50,00,000 on Private Placement basis. This is the third tranche of the total 1,994 NCDs having a face value of Rs. 10,00,000 each, amounting to Rs. 199.40 Crore. The NCDs will be redeemed in full at the end of the Tenor for an amount equal to the Issue Price plus the amount of Committed Return and additional return (if any). The charge/security created over the assets include an exclusive first charge by way of mortgage over the project land, leasehold rights, and development share, and an exclusive first charge by way of hypothecation over all bank accounts, receivables and over all current and non-current assets, both tangible and intangible, of the Project.</p><ul><li>Omaxe Ltd approves allotment of Rs. 18,50,00,000 Unrated Senior Secured Non-Convertible Debentures</li><li>This is the third tranche of the total 1,994 NCDs having a face value of Rs. 10,00,000 each</li><li>The NCDs will be redeemed in full at the end of the Tenor for an amount equal to the Issue Price plus the amount of Committed Return and additional return (if any)</li><li>The charge/security created over the assets include an exclusive first charge by way of mortgage over the project land, leasehold rights, and development share</li><li>An exclusive first charge by way of hypothecation over all bank accounts, receivables and over all current and non-current assets, both tangible and intangible, of the Project</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1d973497-5cf2-4983-ad03-3ad31a3f5f46.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: OMAXE LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TATACOMM] Tata Communications Ltd Announces Dissolution of Wholly Owned Indirect Subsidiary BUC Mobile, Inc.</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TATA+COMMUNICATIONS+LTD.&title=Tata+Communications+Ltd+Announces+Dissolution+of+Wholly+Owned+Indirect+Subsidiary+BUC+Mobile%2C+Inc.&newsId=2636c5a1-1e68-420b-bfe3-dca500940cb4&token=MjYzNmM1YTEtMWU2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2636c5a1-1e68-420b-bfe3-dca500940cb4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Subsidiaries</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tata Communications Ltd has informed about the dissolution of its wholly owned indirect subsidiary, BUC Mobile, Inc., which was domiciled in Delaware, United States of America. The dissolution was effective from February 16, 2026, following the completion of requisite filings with the Secretary of State of the State of Delaware. The subsidiary did not contribute any amount to the turnover or revenue or income and net worth of the company in the last financial year.</p><ul><li>Tata Communications Ltd announces the dissolution of its wholly owned indirect subsidiary, BUC Mobile, Inc.</li><li>The dissolution was effective from February 16, 2026.</li><li>BUC Mobile, Inc. was domiciled in Delaware, United States of America.</li><li>The dissolution followed the completion of requisite filings with the Secretary of State of the State of Delaware.</li><li>BUC Mobile, Inc. did not contribute to the turnover or revenue or income and net worth of the company in the last financial year.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dd9f393c-4451-4853-903c-5223a35d95ef.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TATA COMMUNICATIONS LTD. | Category: Subsidiaries</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CUPID] Cupid Limited Receives Disclosure from Promoter Aditya Kumar Halwasiya under SEBI Regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CUPID+LTD.-%24&title=Cupid+Limited+Receives+Disclosure+from+Promoter+Aditya+Kumar+Halwasiya+under+SEBI+Regulations&newsId=0f42155a-5dc4-40b0-9308-4fb183f17ada&token=MGY0MjE1NWEtNWRj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f42155a-5dc4-40b0-9308-4fb183f17ada</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:42:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cupid Limited has received a disclosure from its Promoter and Chairman, Mr. Aditya Kumar Halwasiya, in compliance with Regulation 29(2) of the SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. The disclosure pertains to the acquisition of 2,27,000 equity shares of Cupid Limited in the open market. The total voting rights of Mr. Halwasiya before and after the acquisition are 32.70% and 32.71% respectively.</p><ul><li>Cupid Limited receives disclosure from Promoter Aditya Kumar Halwasiya under SEBI regulations.</li><li>Disclosure is in compliance with Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</li><li>Aditya Kumar Halwasiya acquires 2,27,000 equity shares of Cupid Limited in the open market.</li><li>Before the acquisition, Mr. Halwasiya&apos;s voting rights were 32.70%. After the acquisition, his voting rights increased to 32.71%.</li><li>Cupid Limited is listed on BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange Limited.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/01b97017-a4dc-4c80-bdd9-94cfd4ca9309.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CUPID LTD.-$ | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CAPACITE] Capacite Infraprojects Receives ~?537 Crore LOI from Raymond Realty</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Capacite+Infraprojects+Ltd&title=Capacite+Infraprojects+Receives+~%3F537+Crore+LOI+from+Raymond+Realty&newsId=e23ee800-cd5f-4671-afcc-715ee0097be4&token=ZTIzZWU4MDAtY2Q1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e23ee800-cd5f-4671-afcc-715ee0097be4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 12:41:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Capacite Infraprojects Ltd has received a Letter of Intent (LOI) from Raymond Realty Limited for a total contract value of ~ X 537 Crore. The LOI is for the construction of &apos;Towers F, G and NTA&apos; and &apos;Retail Building&apos; in the projects of &apos;Address by GS-3&apos; and &apos;Invictus-2&apos; at Thane. This order does not fall under related party transactions and has been received in the normal course of business. Capacite Infraprojects is dedicated to expanding its portfolio with quality orders and showcasing its growing expertise in project execution.</p><ul><li>Capacite Infraprojects received LOI from Raymond Realty Limited for ~X 537 Crore</li><li>The LOI is for the construction of &apos;Towers F, G and NTA&apos; and &apos;Retail Building&apos; in the projects of &apos;Address by GS-3&apos; and &apos;Invictus-2&apos; at Thane</li><li>The order does not fall under related party transactions</li><li>Capacite Infraprojects is committed to delivering exceptional service and meeting timelines</li><li>Capacit&apos;e Infraprojects is rapidly emerging as a marquee contractor in the building space</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0792ec5c-0663-4d3c-a2ca-cb8d424467a6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Capacite Infraprojects Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>