<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:38:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[KHAICHEM] Khaitan Chemicals &amp; Fertilizers Terminates Share Subscription and Shareholder Agreement</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KHAITAN+CHEMICALS+%26+FERTILIZERS+LTD.&title=Khaitan+Chemicals+%26+Fertilizers+Terminates+Share+Subscription+and+Shareholder+Agreement&newsId=c35fa54b-6124-4ec7-9cae-c2b74f4a16b4&token=YzM1ZmE1NGItNjEy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c35fa54b-6124-4ec7-9cae-c2b74f4a16b4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:37:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Khaitan Chemicals &amp; Fertilizers Ltd has terminated a Share Subscription and Shareholders’ Agreement (SSSHA) with KRSKA Solar Private Limited and KRSKA Capital Private Limited. The agreement was initially intended for the acquisition of 26% equity stake in KRSKA Solar Private Limited and for consumption of 85% of the power generated by the said entity. However, the conditions precedent stipulated under the Agreement were not fulfilled within the agreed timelines, leading to the termination of the SSSHA. The termination does not have any material financial impact on the Company.</p><ul><li>Khaitan Chemicals &amp; Fertilizers Ltd has terminated a Share Subscription and Shareholders’ Agreement (SSSHA) with KRSKA Solar Private Limited and KRSKA Capital Private Limited.</li><li>The SSSHA was intended for the acquisition of 26% equity stake in KRSKA Solar Private Limited and for consumption of 85% of the power generated by the said entity.</li><li>The conditions precedent stipulated under the Agreement were not fulfilled within the agreed timelines, leading to the termination of the SSSHA.</li><li>No funds were infused pursuant to the SSSHA, no equity shares or OCRPS were allotted to the Company, and the Company does not hold any equity or convertible securities in KRSKA Solar Private Limited.</li><li>The termination of the SSSHA does not have any material financial impact on the Company.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/eed046fb-d367-414c-a417-5acc58ad99f6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KHAITAN CHEMICALS & FERTILIZERS LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TTL] Promoter Group T.T. Brands Limited Acquires 1,44,547 Shares of T T Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=T+T+LTD.-%24&title=Promoter+Group+T.T.+Brands+Limited+Acquires+1%2C44%2C547+Shares+of+T+T+Ltd&newsId=815d0e79-9e35-4867-bad3-dcf46b3ba69f&token=ODE1ZDBlNzktOWUz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">815d0e79-9e35-4867-bad3-dcf46b3ba69f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:36:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>T.T. Brands Limited, a Promoter Group, has acquired 1,44,547 Equity Shares of T T Ltd from 11th to 13th February 2026. The shares were purchased from the open market. Before the acquisition, the Promoter Group held 33.8376% of the total voting rights. After the acquisition, the Promoter Group&apos;s holding increased to 33.8935% of the total voting rights.</p><ul><li>T.T. Brands Limited, a Promoter Group, has acquired 1,44,547 Equity Shares of T T Ltd.</li><li>The shares were purchased from the open market between 11th to 13th February 2026.</li><li>Before the acquisition, the Promoter Group held 33.8376% of the total voting rights.</li><li>After the acquisition, the Promoter Group&apos;s holding increased to 33.8935% of the total voting rights.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/eaf085d8-c5c6-46a8-b76e-69309dff15be.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: T T LTD.-$ | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ALKEM] Alkem Subsidiary Enzene Achieves Zero Data Integrity Observations in USFDA Inspection</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Alkem+Laboratories+Ltd&title=Alkem+Subsidiary+Enzene+Achieves+Zero+Data+Integrity+Observations+in+USFDA+Inspection&newsId=ec4c642b-0253-4451-800c-c82a57b0aa38&token=ZWM0YzY0MmItMDI1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ec4c642b-0253-4451-800c-c82a57b0aa38</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>USFDA</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Alkem Laboratories Ltd. has disclosed the completion of a Pre-Approval Inspection (PAI) by the United States Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) at the manufacturing facility of its subsidiary, Enzene Biosciences Limited, in India. The USFDA issued a Form 483 with 6 procedural observations, but Enzene received zero observations related to data integrity, validating its quality systems and the reliability of regulatory filings. Enzene is preparing its response to the USFDA and has initiated appropriate corrective and preventive actions.</p><ul><li>USFDA completes Pre-Approval Inspection at Alkem subsidiary Enzene Biosciences Limited&apos;s manufacturing facility in India</li><li>Enzene receives zero data integrity observations, validating quality systems and regulatory filings reliability</li><li>USFDA issues Form 483 with 6 procedural observations</li><li>Enzene preparing response to USFDA within stipulated timeline</li><li>Enzene initiates appropriate corrective and preventive actions</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/016454bb-ef53-49a2-a8fb-d0020c8107e6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Alkem Laboratories Ltd | Category: USFDA</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EPACK] EPACK Durable Ltd&apos;s Q3 FY2026 Monitoring Agency Report Submitted</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=EPACK+Durable+Ltd&title=EPACK+Durable+Ltd%27s+Q3+FY2026+Monitoring+Agency+Report+Submitted&newsId=dfa17f6f-7f12-49bd-a35e-621801b9b722&token=ZGZhMTdmNmYtN2Yx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dfa17f6f-7f12-49bd-a35e-621801b9b722</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>EPACK Durable Ltd has submitted the Monitoring Agency Report for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The report, prepared by ICRA Limited, does not constitute a commentary on the quality of the objects of the issue or the appropriateness or reasonableness of costs or spending by EPACK Durable Ltd. The report highlights that there is no material deviation in the utilization of issue proceeds, which is different from the objects stated in the offer document but in line with the change of objects approved by shareholders&apos; resolution.</p><ul><li>EPACK Durable Ltd has submitted the Monitoring Agency Report for Q3 FY2026.</li><li>The report was prepared by ICRA Limited, a Monitoring Agency appointed by the company.</li><li>There is no material deviation in the utilization of issue proceeds.</li><li>The utilization is different from the objects stated in the offer document but in line with the change of objects approved by shareholders&apos; resolution.</li><li>The report does not constitute a commentary on the quality of the objects of the issue or the appropriateness or reasonableness of costs or spending by EPACK Durable Ltd.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/067acaa3-4e7f-4363-8e66-c167fc5c42da.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: EPACK Durable Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DOLFIN] Dolfin Rubbers Ltd. Approves Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended 31st December, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Dolfin+Rubbers+Ltd&title=Dolfin+Rubbers+Ltd.+Approves+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+31st+December%2C+2025&newsId=0034a870-e3e6-4e70-aa62-5d5c3b9ae124&token=MDAzNGE4NzAtZTNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0034a870-e3e6-4e70-aa62-5d5c3b9ae124</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dolfin Rubbers Ltd. held a board meeting on 14th February, 2026, where they considered and approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The meeting was conducted in accordance with the Indian Accounting Standard (IND AS) as notified by the Ministry of Corporate Affairs and in compliance with the SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The company operates in one business segment and the figures of the corresponding previous periods/year have been regrouped/reclassified where necessary to conform to the current period&apos;s presentation. The Board has recommended Nil dividend.</p><ul><li>Approval of unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December, 2025</li><li>Meeting conducted in accordance with Indian Accounting Standards and SEBI regulations</li><li>Company operates in one business segment</li><li>Figures of corresponding previous periods regrouped/reclassified</li><li>Board recommended Nil dividend</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e347dd8c-4f7b-4f23-90c0-522bfa437d19.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Dolfin Rubbers Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MURUDCERA] Murudeshwar Ceramics Ltd Announces Q3 Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MURUDESHWAR+CERAMICS+LTD.&title=Murudeshwar+Ceramics+Ltd+Announces+Q3+Results+for+2025&newsId=fd361779-05b8-4c1a-8711-eb93c0872d92&token=ZmQzNjE3NzktMDVi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd361779-05b8-4c1a-8711-eb93c0872d92</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Murudeshwar Ceramics Ltd has announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s Board of Directors reviewed and approved these results in a meeting held on February 13, 2026. The results have been prepared in accordance with Indian Accounting Standard 34 and other applicable accounting principles.</p><ul><li>Unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025 approved.</li><li>Results prepared in accordance with Indian Accounting Standard 34 and other applicable accounting principles.</li><li>Board Meeting held on February 13, 2026 to review and approve the results.</li><li>Review report submitted by K.G. Rao &amp; Co. Chartered Accountants INDIA.</li><li>Company&apos;s associate RNS Power Limited included in the consolidated financial results.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/16734f0b-5528-4def-952e-d48c74543c7d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MURUDESHWAR CERAMICS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SCHNEIDER] Schneider Electric Infrastructure Ltd Receives Stay Order on INR 17,12,36,410 Tax Demand</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SCHNEIDER+ELECTRIC+INFRASTRUCTURE+LTD.&title=Schneider+Electric+Infrastructure+Ltd+Receives+Stay+Order+on+INR+17%2C12%2C36%2C410+Tax+Demand&newsId=25d53ba7-046a-4d61-aefe-5e619f94b0d2&token=MjVkNTNiYTctMDQ2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">25d53ba7-046a-4d61-aefe-5e619f94b0d2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Schneider Electric Infrastructure Ltd has received a stay order from the Income Tax Appellate Tribunal, Ahmedabad ‘D’ Bench, in relation to a tax matter. The Company was demanded an additional income tax of INR 17,12,36,410 by the Deputy Commissioner of Income Tax. Following a stay application filed by the Company seeking stay on collection/recovery of the outstanding demand, the Company has been directed to pay 20% of the disputed tax demand, i.e. INR 3,42,47,282, in two instalments. The first instalment of 10% is to be paid on or before 26.02.2026 and the second instalment of 10% on or before 26.03.2026. The stay order was received by the Company on February 13, 2026 at 04:19 p.m. (IST).</p><ul><li>Schneider Electric Infrastructure Ltd receives stay order from the Income Tax Appellate Tribunal, Ahmedabad ‘D’ Bench</li><li>Company was demanded additional income tax of INR 17,12,36,410 by the Deputy Commissioner of Income Tax</li><li>Company directed to pay 20% of the disputed tax demand, i.e. INR 3,42,47,282, in two instalments</li><li>First instalment of 10% to be paid on or before 26.02.2026, second instalment of 10% on or before 26.03.2026</li><li>Stay order received by the Company on February 13, 2026 at 04:19 p.m. (IST)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6b32fcb5-4a67-48f0-863b-4580fc534c7b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SCHNEIDER ELECTRIC INFRASTRUCTURE LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MIDWESTLTD] Midwest Ltd Receives Monitoring Agency Report for Q4 2025 from CRISIL Ratings Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Midwest+Ltd&title=Midwest+Ltd+Receives+Monitoring+Agency+Report+for+Q4+2025+from+CRISIL+Ratings+Limited&newsId=96dc0c12-aa62-46f6-b5d0-c1069533a95d&token=OTZkYzBjMTItYWE2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">96dc0c12-aa62-46f6-b5d0-c1069533a95d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>CRISIL Ratings Limited, the Monitoring Agency, has issued a report on the utilization of proceeds raised through the Initial Public Offer (IPO) of Midwest Ltd for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The report, pursuant to Regulation 32(6) of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, and Regulation 41(4) of SEBI (Issue of Capital and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2018, confirms that the proceeds have been utilized as per the disclosures in the Offer Document. The report is available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>CRISIL Ratings Limited, a reputed monitoring agency, has issued a report on Midwest Ltd&apos;s IPO proceeds utilization for Q4 2025.</li><li>The report confirms that the proceeds have been utilized as per the disclosures in the Offer Document.</li><li>The report is available on the company&apos;s website for public access.</li><li>The monitoring agency did not find any deviation from the objects or range of deviation.</li><li>The report is in line with the format prescribed by SEBI.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3500980a-31ec-41af-b7e7-71153bf82467.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Midwest Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CYBELEIND] Cybele Industries Ltd Reports Q3 Results for FY2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CYBELE+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Cybele+Industries+Ltd+Reports+Q3+Results+for+FY2025-26&newsId=3a28e25a-94db-492d-9919-72043eebab90&token=M2EyOGUyNWEtOTRk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a28e25a-94db-492d-9919-72043eebab90</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cybele Industries Ltd has reported its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter ended 31/12/2025. The company&apos;s revenue and net profit for the quarter and nine-month period ended on December 30, 2025, have been reviewed by Karpagam Krishnan &amp; Natarajan. The review report does not contain any material misstatements and the company has complied with the applicable accounting standards and regulations.</p><ul><li>Cybele Industries Ltd has reported its Q3 results for FY2025-26.</li><li>The company&apos;s standalone and consolidated financial results have been reviewed by Karpagam Krishnan &amp; Natarajan.</li><li>No material misstatements were found in the review report.</li><li>The company has complied with the applicable accounting standards and regulations.</li><li>The review report indicates that the company&apos;s revenue and net profit for the quarter and nine-month period ended on December 30, 2025, have been reviewed.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8ec20462-2ecb-4faa-a59d-229fc7e66d28.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CYBELE INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PATANJALI] GQG Partners Emerging Markets Equity Fund A Disposes Off Shares of Patanjali Foods Ltd, Resulting in 2% Change in Shareholding</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Patanjali+Foods+Ltd&title=GQG+Partners+Emerging+Markets+Equity+Fund+A+Disposes+Off+Shares+of+Patanjali+Foods+Ltd%2C+Resulting+in+2%25+Change+in+Shareholding&newsId=6d629021-4e3e-4596-aa28-bd6e6c22016b&token=NmQ2MjkwMjEtNGUz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d629021-4e3e-4596-aa28-bd6e6c22016b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:27:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>GQG Partners Emerging Markets Equity Fund A has disposed off equity shares of Patanjali Foods Limited by way of multiple on-market transactions, resulting in an aggregate change of shareholding in excess of 2%. This disclosure was made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. The transactions took place from September 16, 2024 until February 11, 2026, leading to a 2.04% change in shareholding. GQG Partners LLC, the investment manager, made the investment decision on behalf of the Acquirer and PACs.</p><ul><li>GQG Partners Emerging Markets Equity Fund A disposed off equity shares of Patanjali Foods Limited</li><li>Multiple on-market transactions took place from September 16, 2024 until February 11, 2026</li><li>The transactions resulted in an aggregate change of shareholding in excess of 2%</li><li>GQG Partners LLC, the investment manager, made the investment decision on behalf of the Acquirer and PACs</li><li>The disclosure was made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/393D7E97_B524_44B3_8BEB_22B3DD964A19_114549.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Patanjali Foods Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>