<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:42:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[CARRARO] Carraro India Ltd Cancels Scheduled Analysts/Investors Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Carraro+India+Ltd&title=Carraro+India+Ltd+Cancels+Scheduled+Analysts%2FInvestors+Meeting&newsId=18421bfb-9c24-4320-85b6-92a3358c967e&token=MTg0MjFiZmItOWMy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18421bfb-9c24-4320-85b6-92a3358c967e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Carraro India Ltd has announced the cancellation of an analysts/investors meeting that was scheduled to take place on Wednesday, February 18, 2026. The meeting was to be held in a one-on-one format at 2:00 PM onwards at Sine Wieck. The reason for the cancellation has not been disclosed in the announcement.</p><ul><li>Carraro India Ltd cancels scheduled analysts/investors meeting</li><li>Meeting was set for Wednesday, February 18, 2026</li><li>One-on-one meeting format</li><li>Scheduled to start at 2:00 PM</li><li>Meeting to be held at Sine Wieck</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/692cb6cd-6aea-40d7-a657-7cbf2e2c3df5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Carraro India Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TAKE] Take Solutions Ltd Announces Extra Ordinary General Meeting on 7th March 2026 with e-Voting Facility</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TAKE+SOLUTIONS+LTD.&title=Take+Solutions+Ltd+Announces+Extra+Ordinary+General+Meeting+on+7th+March+2026+with+e-Voting+Facility&newsId=b69f6a6f-6849-4a00-902e-e5851fd1828d&token=YjY5ZjZhNmYtNjg0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b69f6a6f-6849-4a00-902e-e5851fd1828d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:39:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Take Solutions Ltd has announced that the Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EOGM) will be held on Saturday, 07 March 2026 at 12:00 p.m. (IST) through Video Conferencing (VC) or Other Audio-Visual Means (OAVM). The EOGM is in compliance with the applicable provisions of the Companies Act, 2013 and the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The Company is providing remote e-voting facility to its shareholders to cast their votes on the resolutions proposed to be transacted at the EOGM. The cut-off date for determining Members eligible for e-voting is 28th February 2026. The remote e-voting will commence on Wednesday, 04 March 2026 at 9:00 a.m. (IST) and end on Friday, 06 March 2026 till 5:00 p.m. (IST).</p><ul><li>Take Solutions Ltd announced an Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EOGM) on 7th March 2026</li><li>The EOGM will be held through Video Conferencing (VC) or Other Audio-Visual Means (OAVM)</li><li>The Company is providing remote e-voting facility for shareholders from 4th March to 6th March 2026</li><li>The cut-off date for determining Members eligible for e-voting is 28th February 2026</li><li>The EOGM is in compliance with the applicable provisions of the Companies Act, 2013 and the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/44d488f5-31ec-4262-a82f-d97beea6a409.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TAKE SOLUTIONS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CHOICEIN] Choice Consultancy Services Private Limited Emerges as Successful Resolution Applicant for Feedback Infra Private Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CHOICE+INTERNATIONAL+LTD.&title=Choice+Consultancy+Services+Private+Limited+Emerges+as+Successful+Resolution+Applicant+for+Feedback+Infra+Private+Limited&newsId=e5b9fc69-c075-479e-9abc-48f5508963b4&token=ZTViOWZjNjktYzA3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5b9fc69-c075-479e-9abc-48f5508963b4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:39:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Choice Consultancy Services Private Limited (CCSPL), a material subsidiary of Choice International Ltd, has been declared as the Successful Resolution Applicant by the Committee of Creditors of Feedback Infra Private Limited under the Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code, 2016. The Committee of Creditors has approved the Resolution Plan with requisite majority. The implementation of the Resolution Plan is subject to the terms and conditions specified in the LOI and approval of the Hon’ble National Company Law Tribunal and/or other regulatory authorities, courts or tribunals, as may be applicable under law. The Company will make further disclosures as and when there are material developments in this matter.</p><ul><li>Choice Consultancy Services Private Limited (CCSPL) is declared as the Successful Resolution Applicant by the Committee of Creditors of Feedback Infra Private Limited</li><li>The Resolution Plan has been approved by the Committee of Creditors with requisite majority</li><li>The implementation of the Resolution Plan is subject to approval from the Hon’ble National Company Law Tribunal and/or other regulatory authorities, courts or tribunals</li><li>Choice International Ltd will make further disclosures as and when there are material developments in this matter</li><li>CCSPL is a material subsidiary of Choice International Ltd</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/45941287-d206-437a-b2f6-e89fc1ab3ef8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CHOICE INTERNATIONAL LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DHABRIYA] Dhabriya Polywood Ltd. and Subsidiary Receive Work Orders from Godrej Group Worth ₹ 25.30 Crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Dhabriya+Polywood+Ltd&title=Dhabriya+Polywood+Ltd.+and+Subsidiary+Receive+Work+Orders+from+Godrej+Group+Worth+%E2%82%B9+25.30+Crore&newsId=bd17ae61-9470-4077-b280-91dffb3d9191&token=YmQxN2FlNjEtOTQ3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd17ae61-9470-4077-b280-91dffb3d9191</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:38:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Dhabriya Polywood Limited and its wholly owned subsidiary, Dynasty Modular Furnitures Private Limited, have received work orders/Letters of Intent (LOI) from the Godrej Group for a total value of ₹ 25.30 Crore (inclusive of GST). The work orders are for Façade Glazing Aluminium, Modular Kitchen Works, and Door &amp; Window works.</p><ul><li>Dhabriya Polywood Ltd. and Dynasty Modular Furnitures Pvt. Ltd. have received work orders from Godrej Group.</li><li>The total value of the work orders is ₹ 25.30 Crore (inclusive of GST).</li><li>The work orders are for Façade Glazing Aluminium, Modular Kitchen Works, and Door &amp; Window works.</li><li>The project is scheduled to be completed in 24 months for Façade Glazing Aluminium and Modular Kitchen Works, and in 12 months for Door &amp; Window works.</li><li>The broad consideration for the orders is ₹ 16.10 Crore for Façade Glazing Aluminium and ₹ 9.20 Crore for Modular Kitchen Works and Door &amp; Window works.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ee62cdb0-281d-41a3-b919-188ca5b4652b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Dhabriya Polywood Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IEX*] Indian Energy Exchange Ltd Subsidiary&apos;s Name Change to ICX Private Limited Approved</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Indian+Energy+Exchange+Ltd&title=Indian+Energy+Exchange+Ltd+Subsidiary%27s+Name+Change+to+ICX+Private+Limited+Approved&newsId=0194d968-34e0-4361-84a3-b87b470469a9&token=MDE5NGQ5NjgtMzRl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0194d968-34e0-4361-84a3-b87b470469a9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:37:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indian Energy Exchange Ltd (IEX) has announced that the name of its wholly owned subsidiary, International Carbon Exchange Private Limited, has been changed to ICX Private Limited. This change will be effective from February 18, 2026, following the approval received from the Registrar of Companies, Ministry of Corporate Affairs. The company will also update its website with this information.</p><ul><li>Indian Energy Exchange Ltd&apos;s wholly owned subsidiary&apos;s name changed to ICX Private Limited</li><li>The change will be effective from February 18, 2026</li><li>The name change has been approved by the Registrar of Companies, Ministry of Corporate Affairs</li><li>The updated information will be available on the company&apos;s website: www.iexindia.com</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a65dd8bc-3108-4862-871f-9db82d54746b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Indian Energy Exchange Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BANDHANBNK] Bandhan Bank Ltd Receives ESG Rating of &apos;67&apos; for FY 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Bandhan+Bank+Ltd&title=Bandhan+Bank+Ltd+Receives+ESG+Rating+of+%2767%27+for+FY+2025&newsId=a81dcd0c-bdb5-43d1-baa2-50713a122cef&token=YTgxZGNkMGMtYmRi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a81dcd0c-bdb5-43d1-baa2-50713a122cef</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bandhan Bank Ltd has been assigned an ESG (Environmental, Social and Governance) Rating of &apos;67&apos; by SEBI registered ESG Rating Provider, NSE Sustainability Ratings and Analytics Limited. The rating is based on public disclosures made by the Bank and other publicly available information, placing the Bank in the &apos;Aspiring&apos; rating category for the Financial Year 2025. This disclosure is being simultaneously uploaded on the Bank’s website.</p><ul><li>Bandhan Bank Ltd receives ESG Rating of &apos;67&apos; from NSE Sustainability Ratings and Analytics Limited</li><li>The rating is based on public disclosures and other publicly available information</li><li>Bandhan Bank Ltd is placed in the &apos;Aspiring&apos; rating category for FY 2025</li><li>This disclosure is being uploaded on the Bank’s website for transparency</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9d66d8b1-a00e-4abc-bdee-953c261bae3b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Bandhan Bank Ltd | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RVNL] Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd Receives LOA from Northern Railway for Design and Construction of New Rail Cum Road Bridge</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Rail+Vikas+Nigam+Ltd&title=Rail+Vikas+Nigam+Ltd+Receives+LOA+from+Northern+Railway+for+Design+and+Construction+of+New+Rail+Cum+Road+Bridge&newsId=62ba05b2-c51f-4804-a5bd-e51a4514b8c5&token=NjJiYTA1YjItYzUx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62ba05b2-c51f-4804-a5bd-e51a4514b8c5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd (RVNL) has announced that it has received a Letter of Acceptance (LOA) from Northern Railway for the design and construction of a new rail cum road bridge over the river Ganga. The project, which includes sub and super structure of the bridge, four line tracks on the lower deck, and six lane road on the upper deck, is estimated to cost Rs. 12,01,35,69,000. The project is expected to be completed in 48 months.</p><ul><li>RVNL received LOA from Northern Railway for design and construction of a new rail cum road bridge over river Ganga.</li><li>The project includes sub and super structure of the bridge, four line tracks on the lower deck, and six lane road on the upper deck.</li><li>The project is estimated to cost Rs. 12,01,35,69,000.</li><li>The project is expected to be completed in 48 months.</li><li>The announcement was made in accordance with Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dd781bcd-1536-4571-a7e7-2a06d2d0d8a6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SWOEF] Swojas Foods Ltd Allots 20,00,000 Equity Shares Following Conversion of Convertible Warrants</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SWOJAS+ENERGY+FOODS+LTD.&title=Swojas+Foods+Ltd+Allots+20%2C00%2C000+Equity+Shares+Following+Conversion+of+Convertible+Warrants&newsId=23a286a3-617f-4a56-8356-3ac7b4fcb30f&token=MjNhMjg2YTMtNjE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23a286a3-617f-4a56-8356-3ac7b4fcb30f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:29:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Swojas Foods Ltd has allotted 20,00,000 equity shares following the conversion of convertible warrants by some non-promoter warrant holders. The allotment was made at an issue price of Rs. 16.50 (including a premium of Rs. 6.50) per share, upon receipt of the remaining exercise price of Rs. 12.375 per share warrant. This move has increased the company&apos;s paid-up equity share capital from Rs. 33,06,26,500 to Rs. 35,06,26,500. The newly issued and allotted equity shares will be listed and traded on the stock exchange after the necessary approvals are obtained.</p><ul><li>Allotment of 20,00,000 equity shares following conversion of convertible warrants.</li><li>Issue price of Rs. 16.50 per share (including a premium of Rs. 6.50).</li><li>Remaining exercise price of Rs. 12.375 per share warrant received.</li><li>Increase in the company&apos;s paid-up equity share capital from Rs. 33,06,26,500 to Rs. 35,06,26,500.</li><li>Application for listing and trading approval of the Stock Exchange for the newly issued and allotted Equity Shares will be made in due course of time.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f14fb56a-df76-4df0-8c51-a94b498089d1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SWOJAS ENERGY FOODS LTD. | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SWOEF] Swojas Foods Ltd Allots 20,00,000 Equity Shares Following Conversion of Convertible Warrants</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SWOJAS+ENERGY+FOODS+LTD.&title=Swojas+Foods+Ltd+Allots+20%2C00%2C000+Equity+Shares+Following+Conversion+of+Convertible+Warrants&newsId=13fac2c6-7b2d-460b-a5cc-bb5a00c1c090&token=MTNmYWMyYzYtN2Iy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13fac2c6-7b2d-460b-a5cc-bb5a00c1c090</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:29:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Swojas Foods Ltd has allotted 20,00,000 equity shares following the conversion of convertible warrants by some non-promoter warrant holders. The allotment was made at an issue price of Rs. 16.50 (Rupees Sixteen and Fifty Paise Only) each, with the equity shares ranking pari-passu with the existing equity shares of the Company in all respects. The conversion has increased the Company&apos;s paid-up equity share capital from Rs. 33,06,26,500/- to Rs. 35,06,26,500/-. The application for listing and trading approval of the newly issued and allotted Equity Shares will be made in due course of time.</p><ul><li>Swojas Foods Ltd has allotted 20,00,000 equity shares following the conversion of convertible warrants.</li><li>The allotment was made at an issue price of Rs. 16.50 (Rupees Sixteen and Fifty Paise Only) each.</li><li>The conversion has increased the Company&apos;s paid-up equity share capital from Rs. 33,06,26,500/- to Rs. 35,06,26,500/-.</li><li>The application for listing and trading approval of the newly issued and allotted Equity Shares will be made in due course of time.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/78225ed1-95ba-4023-939f-e5fc65508563.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SWOJAS ENERGY FOODS LTD. | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CROMPTON] Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals Ltd Launches EA400 AC Stabilizer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Crompton+Greaves+Consumer+Electricals+Ltd&title=Crompton+Greaves+Consumer+Electricals+Ltd+Launches+EA400+AC+Stabilizer&newsId=65315ea5-b491-4fa3-b21d-6adf0444ad13&token=NjUzMTVlYTUtYjQ5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65315ea5-b491-4fa3-b21d-6adf0444ad13</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals Ltd has launched a new product, the EA400 AC Stabilizer. This launch is in line with the company&apos;s commitment to regular product updates and improvements. The product is categorized under B2C Lighting Domestic. It&apos;s important to note that this launch does not meet the materiality threshold but is disclosed as a part of good corporate governance practices.</p><ul><li>Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals Ltd has launched the EA400 AC Stabilizer</li><li>The product is categorized under B2C Lighting Domestic</li><li>This launch is a part of the company&apos;s commitment to regular product updates and improvements</li><li>The launch does not meet the materiality threshold</li><li>The disclosure is made as a part of good corporate governance practices</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c73e9834-6d11-4b78-ad29-ea5cc11fd8fc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Crompton Greaves Consumer Electricals Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>