<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:59:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[RPPINFRA] R P P Infra Projects Ltd: Promoters&apos; Inter-se Transfer of 39,60,000 Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RPP+INFRA+PROJECTS+LTD.&title=R+P+P+Infra+Projects+Ltd%3A+Promoters%27+Inter-se+Transfer+of+39%2C60%2C000+Equity+Shares&newsId=aa73ef34-aebe-4eb0-bf6f-57450605b28d&token=YWE3M2VmMzQtYWVi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa73ef34-aebe-4eb0-bf6f-57450605b28d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>R P P Infra Projects Ltd has received a disclosure under Regulation 10(5) in respect of acquisition under Regulation 10(1)(a) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. The proposed acquisition involves 39,60,000 Equity shares by way of promoters&apos; inter-se transfer amongst immediate relatives. The proposed date of transfer is on or after 06/02/2026. This transfer is between Ms. Nithya Arulsundaram and Ms. N A Tharunya, who are relatives under the SEBI regulations.</p><ul><li>R P P Infra Projects Ltd receives disclosure under Regulation 10(5) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011</li><li>Proposed acquisition of 39,60,000 Equity shares by promoters&apos; inter-se transfer</li><li>Transfer to take place amongst immediate relatives</li><li>Proposed date of transfer on or after 06/02/2026</li><li>Transfer between Ms. Nithya Arulsundaram and Ms. N A Tharunya</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/838E6526_2144_49AE_A73A_BC40162E0749_095220.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RPP INFRA PROJECTS LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IOC] Indian Oil Corporation Ltd Announces Changes in Senior Management Personnel</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDIAN+OIL+CORPORATION+LTD.&title=Indian+Oil+Corporation+Ltd+Announces+Changes+in+Senior+Management+Personnel&newsId=ab883c32-e4b4-412a-b31c-5839b34ae4e5&token=YWI4ODNjMzItZTRi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab883c32-e4b4-412a-b31c-5839b34ae4e5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:31:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indian Oil Corporation Ltd has announced changes in its senior management personnel. The following executives have superannuated from the services of the company on 31st January 2026: Dr. Mukesh Ranjan Das, Executive Director (Human Resources), Marketing Head Office; Executive Director (Quality Control), Marketing Head Office; Executive Director (Operations), Marketing Head Office; Mr. M. Sudhakar, Executive Director (Regional Services), Southern Regional Office; Mr. Subodh Kumar Bajpai, Executive Director (H,S&amp;E), Marketing Head Office; and Mr. Atanu Sanyal, Executive Director &amp; Refinery Head, Haldia Refinery. This information is for record purposes.</p><ul><li>Indian Oil Corporation Ltd announces changes in senior management personnel</li><li>Dr. Mukesh Ranjan Das, Executive Director (Human Resources), Marketing Head Office, has superannuated</li><li>Executive Director (Quality Control), Marketing Head Office, has superannuated</li><li>Executive Director (Operations), Marketing Head Office, has superannuated</li><li>Mr. M. Sudhakar, Executive Director (Regional Services), Southern Regional Office, has superannuated</li><li>Mr. Subodh Kumar Bajpai, Executive Director (H,S&amp;E), Marketing Head Office, has superannuated</li><li>Mr. Atanu Sanyal, Executive Director &amp; Refinery Head, Haldia Refinery, has superannuated</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f940dd96-927c-4e6e-9d74-f18342eef2b6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDIAN OIL CORPORATION LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SSWL] Steel Strips Wheels Ltd. Achieves Highest Ever Monthly Net Turnover in January, Recording a 17.32% YOY Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=STEEL+STRIPS+WHEELS+LTD.-%24&title=Steel+Strips+Wheels+Ltd.+Achieves+Highest+Ever+Monthly+Net+Turnover+in+January%2C+Recording+a+17.32%25+YOY+Growth&newsId=bd99907d-0a3c-44e6-b4f7-66d084e40e46&token=YmQ5OTkwN2QtMGEz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd99907d-0a3c-44e6-b4f7-66d084e40e46</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Steel Strips Wheels Limited (SSWL) has achieved its highest ever monthly net turnover in January 2026, recording a growth of 17.32% YOY. The company also achieved the highest ever monthly units sold during the month. The key highlights for January 2026 include a 17% YOY growth in overall sales, a 25% YOY growth in the aluminum segment by value, a 25% YOY growth in the tractor segment by value, and a 20% YOY growth in domestic monthly sales in the CV segment by value.</p><ul><li>Highest Ever Monthly Sales overall (up by 17% YOY)</li><li>Highest Ever Monthly Sales in the Aluminum Segment (up by 25% YOY by Value)</li><li>Highest Ever Monthly Sales in the Tractor Segment (up by 25% YOY by Value)</li><li>Highest Ever Domestic Monthly Sales in the CV Segment (up by 20% YOY by Value)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/43becfdf-b0f9-4b78-868b-9f3eb8583471.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: STEEL STRIPS WHEELS LTD.-$ | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HYUNDAI] Hyundai Motor India Ltd Achieves Highest-ever Monthly Domestic Sales of 59,107 Units in January 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Hyundai+Motor+India+Ltd&title=Hyundai+Motor+India+Ltd+Achieves+Highest-ever+Monthly+Domestic+Sales+of+59%2C107+Units+in+January+2026&newsId=ae24317c-f3e5-4b60-89e9-f01ef2626da0&token=YWUyNDMxN2MtZjNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae24317c-f3e5-4b60-89e9-f01ef2626da0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Hyundai Motor India Ltd (HMIL) recorded its highest-ever monthly domestic sales of 59,107 units in January 2026, registering a 9.5% year-on-year growth. HMIL also achieved its highest-ever total monthly sales of 73,137 units in January 2026, with a robust year-on-year growth of 11.5%, including monthly export sales of 14,030 units with year-on-year growth of 20.9%. The remarkable 20.9% growth in exports to 14,030 units underscores the trust brand Hyundai continues to inspire across global markets.</p><ul><li>Hyundai Motor India Ltd achieved its highest-ever monthly domestic sales of 59,107 units in January 2026</li><li>HMIL also achieved its highest-ever total monthly sales of 73,137 units in January 2026</li><li>Exports contributed 14,030 units in January 2026 with a year-on-year growth of 20.9%</li><li>The e VENUE and AURA achieved their highest-ever monthly sales</li><li>Hyundai continues to inspire trust across global markets as reflected by the 20.9% growth in exports</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6b5fdfdb-0426-4928-9850-910e35b6864a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Hyundai Motor India Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CYIENTDLM] Nippon India Mutual Fund Sells Shares of Cyient DLM Ltd on Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Cyient+DLM+Ltd&title=Nippon+India+Mutual+Fund+Sells+Shares+of+Cyient+DLM+Ltd+on+Open+Market&newsId=90dcc6bf-e521-4e5c-bf73-beeae3b5782f&token=OTBkY2M2YmYtZTUy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90dcc6bf-e521-4e5c-bf73-beeae3b5782f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Sale of Property</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Nippon India Mutual Fund has sold shares of Cyient DLM Ltd on behalf of Nippon Life India Trustee Limited A/c. The sale transactions were conducted on the open market during the period from January 21, 2025 to January 29, 2026. The total equity share capital and total voting capital of the company remains unchanged after the sale.</p><ul><li>Nippon India Mutual Fund sold shares of Cyient DLM Ltd on behalf of Nippon Life India Trustee Limited A/c</li><li>The sale transactions were conducted on the open market</li><li>The sale period ranged from January 21, 2025 to January 29, 2026</li><li>The total equity share capital and total voting capital of the company remains unchanged after the sale</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5C17ECFA_1224_44F0_B179_79B9F5011561_095605.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Cyient DLM Ltd | Category: Sale of Property</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LTTS] L&amp;T Technology Services&apos; CBO - EMEA &amp; RoW, Rajkumar Ravindranathan, Resigns Effective January 31, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=L%26T+Technology+Services+Ltd&title=L%26T+Technology+Services%27+CBO+-+EMEA+%26+RoW%2C+Rajkumar+Ravindranathan%2C+Resigns+Effective+January+31%2C+2026&newsId=f6a51808-25c7-4fd7-960f-cbdedff61ce5&token=ZjZhNTE4MDgtMjVj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6a51808-25c7-4fd7-960f-cbdedff61ce5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>L&amp;T Technology Services Ltd has announced the resignation of Mr. Rajkumar Ravindranathan as Chief Business Officer - EMEA &amp; RoW (Senior Management Personnel) effective close of business hours January 31, 2026. Mr. Ravindranathan has tendered his resignation to pursue career opportunities outside the group.</p><ul><li>Mr. Rajkumar Ravindranathan has resigned as Chief Business Officer - EMEA &amp; RoW from L&amp;T Technology Services Ltd.</li><li>He has resigned to pursue career opportunities outside the group.</li><li>The resignation will be effective from the close of business hours of January 31, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8eae8a95-9b7d-4d5f-a290-4d8e5a55e959.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: L&T Technology Services Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ESCORTS] Escorts Kubota Ltd Reports 46.9% Growth in Tractor Sales for January 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Escorts+Kubota+Ltd&title=Escorts+Kubota+Ltd+Reports+46.9%25+Growth+in+Tractor+Sales+for+January+2026&newsId=32ffe460-a663-4de7-9e63-ab74f8a872a0&token=MzJmZmU0NjAtYTY2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32ffe460-a663-4de7-9e63-ab74f8a872a0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Escorts Kubota Limited Agri Machinery Business sold 9,799 tractors in January 2026, a 46.9% increase compared to 6,669 tractors sold in January 2025. Domestic tractor sales grew by 50.8%, while export tractor sales increased by 8.3%. The growth is attributed to positive rural sentiment, increased farm activity, improved water availability, reduction in GST rate, favorable government policies, and ongoing state subsidies. The Construction Equipment Business Division sold 524 machines in January 2026, a slight decrease from the 544 machines sold in January 2025.</p><ul><li>Tractor sales grew by 46.9% in January 2026</li><li>Domestic tractor sales increased by 50.8%</li><li>Export tractor sales rose by 8.3%</li><li>Construction Equipment Business Division sold 524 machines in January 2026</li><li>Industry volume shows early signs of stabilization in Construction Equipment sector</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/46f1f5b9-bc7c-4461-ab81-41d7bc4d3e33.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Escorts Kubota Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NATIONALUM] National Aluminium Company Ltd: Executive Director (M&amp;R) Superannuates</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NATIONAL+ALUMINIUM+CO.LTD.&title=National+Aluminium+Company+Ltd%3A+Executive+Director+%28M%26R%29+Superannuates&newsId=b8c7b9bf-577f-46bd-ba63-7fa2ce306b3e&token=YjhjN2I5YmYtNTc3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8c7b9bf-577f-46bd-ba63-7fa2ce306b3e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 03:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In compliance with Regulation 30 of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015, National Aluminium Company Ltd. announces the superannuation of its Executive Director (M&amp;R), Shri Niranjan Samal, effective from 31.01.2026.</p><ul><li>National Aluminium Company Ltd. announces the superannuation of its Executive Director (M&amp;R), Shri Niranjan Samal.</li><li>The superannuation will be effective from 31.01.2026.</li><li>This update falls under the compliance of Regulation 30 of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6be3ac00-fe44-4166-b51b-e28c959a5ae2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NATIONAL ALUMINIUM CO.LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SMLISUZU] SML Mahindra Ltd Reports 30% YoY Growth in Passenger Vehicle Sales for January 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SML+ISUZU+LIMITED&title=SML+Mahindra+Ltd+Reports+30%25+YoY+Growth+in+Passenger+Vehicle+Sales+for+January+2026&newsId=087a1598-5ddc-42a2-8120-4b581ade458c&token=MDg3YTE1OTgtNWRk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">087a1598-5ddc-42a2-8120-4b581ade458c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 02:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>SML Mahindra Ltd, in compliance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations 2015, has released its sales figures for January 2026. The company has reported a significant 30% year-over-year growth in passenger vehicle sales, with 12672 units sold compared to 10618 units in January 2025. The cargo vehicles segment also saw an increase, with 3188 units sold in January 2026 compared to 2025&apos;s 2024 units.</p><ul><li>SML Mahindra Ltd reports a 30% YoY growth in passenger vehicle sales for January 2026</li><li>12672 passenger vehicles sold in January 2026 compared to 10618 in January 2025</li><li>Cargo vehicles segment also sees an increase, with 3188 units sold in January 2026 compared to 2024 units in January 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/09fb9310-8d5f-42a0-98c2-3bc1d1d6fca6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SML ISUZU LIMITED | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[COALINDIA] Coal India Ltd: Executive Director (Co-ordination) Alok Lalit Kumar Retires</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=COAL+INDIA+LTD.&title=Coal+India+Ltd%3A+Executive+Director+%28Co-ordination%29+Alok+Lalit+Kumar+Retires&newsId=8c6f0aab-9221-42d1-ae11-606ab4e6911d&token=OGM2ZjBhYWItOTIy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c6f0aab-9221-42d1-ae11-606ab4e6911d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 01:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Coal India Ltd announced that Executive Director (Co-ordination) Alok Lalit Kumar has relinquished his charge with effect from 01.02.2026. This disclosure is pursuant to Regulation 30 of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations 2015 and SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations 2015.</p><ul><li>Alok Lalit Kumar retires as Executive Director (Co-ordination) of Coal India Ltd</li><li>Retirement is effective from 01.02.2026</li><li>Disclosure is pursuant to Regulation 30 of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations 2015 and SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/93f2fd93-03dc-4e6f-acfb-5a13f5378405.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: COAL INDIA LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>