<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:37:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SHYAMMETL] Shyam Metalics and Energy Ltd Receives ESG Rating of &apos;55&apos; for FY 2024-25</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shyam+Metalics+and+Energy+Ltd&title=Shyam+Metalics+and+Energy+Ltd+Receives+ESG+Rating+of+%2755%27+for+FY+2024-25&newsId=7b688693-e0b7-463f-8f36-31bac4b3c2cf&token=N2I2ODg2OTMtZTBi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b688693-e0b7-463f-8f36-31bac4b3c2cf</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:37:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Rating</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shyam Metalics and Energy Ltd has been assigned an ESG rating of &apos;55&apos; by NSE Sustainability Ratings and Analytics Limited. The rating is based on the information/data of the Company pertaining to financial year 2024-25 available in the public domain. The Company did not engage NSE Sustainability Ratings &amp; Analytics Limited for ESG rating, and the rating was done independently. This disclosure is also available on the Company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Shyam Metalics and Energy Ltd receives an ESG rating of &apos;55&apos; from NSE Sustainability Ratings and Analytics Limited</li><li>The rating is based on the financial year 2024-25 data available in the public domain</li><li>The Company did not engage NSE Sustainability Ratings &amp; Analytics Limited for ESG rating</li><li>The rating was done independently</li><li>The disclosure is available on the Company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6b1ab227-cce8-47e9-a29e-b4cf81e5fb5a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shyam Metalics and Energy Ltd | Category: Rating</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AXISCADES] High Court Quashes Income Tax Department&apos;s Notice Against Axiscades Aerospace &amp; Technologies</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Axiscades+Technologies+Ltd&title=High+Court+Quashes+Income+Tax+Department%27s+Notice+Against+Axiscades+Aerospace+%26+Technologies&newsId=e1eabf32-b702-44f1-9e6e-29a64fb4123f&token=ZTFlYWJmMzItYjcw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e1eabf32-b702-44f1-9e6e-29a64fb4123f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:34:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In an update to the ongoing litigation, Axiscades Technologies Ltd. announced that the High Court of Karnataka has quashed the impugned notice, demand notice, penalty notice, and consequential orders issued by the Income Tax Department for the fiscal year 2014-15. The notice was in relation to the admissibility of capital loss in the income tax returns of AXISCADES Aerospace &amp; Technologies Private Limited, a Wholly Owned Subsidiary.</p><ul><li>High Court of Karnataka quashes Income Tax Department&apos;s notice against Axiscades Aerospace &amp; Technologies</li><li>Notice was in relation to the admissibility of capital loss in the income tax returns for the fiscal year 2014-15</li><li>The quashing includes impugned notice, demand notice, penalty notice, and consequential orders</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b6748acd-2a2f-49d8-80c3-a1b2b22308e8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Axiscades Technologies Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VTL] Vardhman Textiles Ltd Dematerializes 3,090 Shares in December 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VARDHMAN+TEXTILES+LTD.&title=Vardhman+Textiles+Ltd+Dematerializes+3%2C090+Shares+in+December+2025&newsId=29331200-a60d-4b1f-ac3f-bd538654ea19&token=MjkzMzEyMDAtYTYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29331200-a60d-4b1f-ac3f-bd538654ea19</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:34:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vardhman Textiles Ltd, a company based in Ludhiana, Punjab, has dematerialized 3,090 equity shares in December 2025. This was done after due verification of Share Certificates, and the share certificates have been cancelled and substituted with the name of the Depository as the Registered Owner in the company&apos;s record. The dematerialization was carried out for shares held in both CDSL and NSDL. In CDSL, shares with Distinctive Numbers -1 and -2 were dematerialized, while in NSDL, shares with Distinctive Numbers -1 and -2 were dematerialized. The total number of shares dematerialized in NSDL was 2,550.</p><ul><li>Vardhman Textiles Ltd dematerialized 3,090 equity shares in December 2025.</li><li>Share certificates were cancelled and substituted with the name of the Depository as the Registered Owner.</li><li>CDSL reported dematerialization of shares with Distinctive Numbers -1 and -2.</li><li>NSDL reported dematerialization of shares with Distinctive Numbers -1 and -2.</li><li>A total of 2,550 shares were dematerialized in NSDL.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0e0007db-8f78-4c51-a978-c126d778f577.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VARDHMAN TEXTILES LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUNCLAYLTD] TVS Holdings Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025 on Jan 28, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SUNDARAM-CLAYTON+LTD.&title=TVS+Holdings+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025+on+Jan+28%2C+2026&newsId=21dd5378-6a9d-4a4a-9544-e5d7564caab9&token=MjFkZDUzNzgtNmE5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21dd5378-6a9d-4a4a-9544-e5d7564caab9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:31:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>TVS Holdings Ltd has announced a board meeting on 28th January 2026 to consider and approve the unaudited (limited reviewed) Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. This announcement comes in compliance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The trading window for dealing in the Company’s scrips by the Designated Persons of the Company including their immediate relatives will remain closed from 1st January 2026 to 30th January 2026.</p><ul><li>TVS Holdings Ltd to consider and approve unaudited (limited reviewed) Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December 2025.</li><li>Board meeting scheduled on 28th January 2026.</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the Company’s scrips by the Designated Persons of the Company including their immediate relatives to remain closed from 1st January 2026 to 30th January 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/764af6d7-308a-4787-bf5b-eee0484e48f4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SUNDARAM-CLAYTON LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ABINFRA] A B Infrabuild Ltd Secures Rs. 54 Crore Contract for Construction of Road Over Bridge</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=A+B+Infrabuild+Ltd&title=A+B+Infrabuild+Ltd+Secures+Rs.+54+Crore+Contract+for+Construction+of+Road+Over+Bridge&newsId=2692be98-a508-4e89-a937-4156e1490ef7&token=MjY5MmJlOTgtYTUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2692be98-a508-4e89-a937-4156e1490ef7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>A B Infrabuild Ltd has been awarded a new project for the construction of a Road Over Bridge (ROB) on the Baruva (Bav) - Mandasa Road (Mms) Railway Station on HWH-VSKP Main Line under Khurdha Road Division. The contract, worth Rs. 54,26,17,718.17, has a time period of 24 months. The order was awarded to the domestic entity, East Coast Railways, which is a part of Indian Railways.</p><ul><li>A B Infrabuild Ltd has been awarded a new project for the construction of a Road Over Bridge (ROB)</li><li>The contract is worth Rs. 54,26,17,718.17</li><li>The project has a time period of 24 months</li><li>The order was awarded to the domestic entity, East Coast Railways, which is a part of Indian Railways</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/11b3a8f6-9813-412c-9820-ca83b3b515ab.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: A B Infrabuild Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUNRINV] Sunrise Industrial Traders Ltd to Approve Q3 Financial Results on Jan 16, 2026; Trading Window Closed</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SUNRISE+INDUSTRIAL+TRADERS+LTD.&title=Sunrise+Industrial+Traders+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+Financial+Results+on+Jan+16%2C+2026%3B+Trading+Window+Closed&newsId=9f92202c-1136-4f79-8e49-54e169995083&token=OWY5MjIwMmMtMTEz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9f92202c-1136-4f79-8e49-54e169995083</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sunrise Industrial Traders Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 16, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results (standalone) for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company will also take note of the limited review report issued by the statutory auditor for the same quarter. In accordance with the company&apos;s Code of conduct of Prevention of insider trading pursuant to SEBI [Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations 2015, the trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company by its designated employees, Director and promoters has been closed from January 1, 2026, and will remain closed until 48 hours after the announcement of the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, to the public.</p><ul><li>Sunrise Industrial Traders Ltd to approve Q3 financial results on January 16, 2026</li><li>Trading window closed for designated employees, Director, and promoters from January 1, 2026</li><li>Closure of trading window to remain in effect until 48 hours after public announcement of results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9cdfb16c-81b8-4a02-a9da-cf84e5827396.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SUNRISE INDUSTRIAL TRADERS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TRIL] Transformers and Rectifiers (India) Ltd: No Deviation from Objects in QIP Utilization as of 31.12.2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TRANSFORMERS+AND+RECTIFIERS+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Transformers+and+Rectifiers+%28India%29+Ltd%3A+No+Deviation+from+Objects+in+QIP+Utilization+as+of+31.12.2025&newsId=3f73179a-8321-453d-acea-4985f8ffb584&token=M2Y3MzE3OWEtODMy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3f73179a-8321-453d-acea-4985f8ffb584</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:22:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>According to the Monitoring Agency Report issued by India Ratings &amp; Research Private Limited, Transformers and Rectifiers (India) Ltd has not deviated from the objects of the issue in the utilization of funds raised through the Qualified Institutions Placement (QIP) as of 31st December 2025. The report, reviewed by the Audit Committee of the Company, states no deviation based on the Management undertaking and Statutory Auditor certificate. The issue-related expenses were slightly higher than mentioned in the placement document, but have been ratified and approved by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>No deviation from the objects of the QIP issue</li><li>Issue-related expenses were higher than mentioned in the placement document but have been approved by the Board of Directors</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f55cd6e3-338e-4440-8061-7acc636e2323.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TRANSFORMERS AND RECTIFIERS (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BAJAJHLDNG] Bajaj Holdings Acquires 17.56% Stake in Insurance Subsidiaries from Allianz SE</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BAJAJ+HOLDINGS+%26+INVESTMENT+LTD.&title=Bajaj+Holdings+Acquires+17.56%25+Stake+in+Insurance+Subsidiaries+from+Allianz+SE&newsId=73935968-ce7e-4bd7-8517-1ed4bdae8f93&token=NzM5MzU5NjgtY2U3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73935968-ce7e-4bd7-8517-1ed4bdae8f93</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:21:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bajaj Holdings &amp; Investment Ltd., along with Bajaj Finserv Ltd. and Jamnalal Sons Pvt. Ltd., have acquired a 17.56% equity stake in Bajaj General Insurance Limited and Bajaj Life Insurance Limited from Allianz SE. The acquisition was made at a price of INR 4,808.24 per share for Bajaj General and INR 2,654.12 per share for Bajaj Life. Post-acquisition, the Company, Bajaj Finserv Ltd., and Jamnalal Sons Pvt. Ltd. collectively hold 97% equity stake in each of the insurance companies. The remaining 3% stake is proposed to be acquired through a buyback offer, subject to necessary approvals.</p><ul><li>Bajaj Holdings &amp; Investment Ltd., Bajaj Finserv Ltd., and Jamnalal Sons Pvt. Ltd. have acquired a 17.56% equity stake in Bajaj General Insurance Limited and Bajaj Life Insurance Limited from Allianz SE.</li><li>The acquisition was made at a price of INR 4,808.24 per share for Bajaj General and INR 2,654.12 per share for Bajaj Life.</li><li>Post-acquisition, the Company, Bajaj Finserv Ltd., and Jamnalal Sons Pvt. Ltd. collectively hold 97% equity stake in each of the insurance companies.</li><li>The remaining 3% stake is proposed to be acquired through a buyback offer, subject to necessary approvals.</li><li>The acquisition is expected to be completed by 31 July 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fe3bac8d-8631-4514-90dc-d409b093d93e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BAJAJ HOLDINGS & INVESTMENT LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DAICHI] Dai-Ichi Karkaria Ltd. Receives Refund of Rs. 8,47,704/- in Income Tax Case</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DAI-ICHI+KARKARIA+LTD.-%24&title=Dai-Ichi+Karkaria+Ltd.+Receives+Refund+of+Rs.+8%2C47%2C704%2F-+in+Income+Tax+Case&newsId=a33eb1ee-e6c9-49f5-aaae-ac4ba9d1baf0&token=YTMzZWIxZWUtZTZj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a33eb1ee-e6c9-49f5-aaae-ac4ba9d1baf0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:21:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dai-Ichi Karkaria Ltd. has received an Order from the Income-Tax Assessing Officer via email on January 7, 2026, giving effect to the Income Tax Appellate Tribunal’s order dated June 30, 2025 which ruled in favour of the Company. The effect to the ITAT’s Order is given by the Income Tax Department by granting a refund of Rs. 8,47,704/- (comprising Tax amount of Rs. 6,53,890/- and interest amount of Rs. 1,93,814/-).</p><ul><li>Dai-Ichi Karkaria Ltd. has received a refund of Rs. 8,47,704/- in an income tax case.</li><li>The Income Tax Appellate Tribunal’s order dated June 30, 2025 ruled in favour of the Company.</li><li>The refund comprises a tax amount of Rs. 6,53,890/- and an interest amount of Rs. 1,93,814/-.</li><li>The Order was received via email on January 7, 2026.</li><li>The refund is in relation to the Assessment Year 2017-18.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3ebf1d49-dd9d-4004-8fb5-ff386bffb4a8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DAI-ICHI KARKARIA LTD.-$ | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MANOJJEWEL] Manoj Jewellers Ltd: Board Approves Re-Appointments, Increase in Authorised Share Capital, and More</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Manoj+Jewellers+Ltd&title=Manoj+Jewellers+Ltd%3A+Board+Approves+Re-Appointments%2C+Increase+in+Authorised+Share+Capital%2C+and+More&newsId=d4aae54f-9a51-4542-91a2-494443a912b8&token=ZDRhYWU1NGYtOWE1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4aae54f-9a51-4542-91a2-494443a912b8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:21:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Manoj Jewellers Ltd announced the approval of various decisions during their Board of Directors meeting on Thursday, 08th January 2026. The board approved the re-appointment of Mr. Suganchand Ramesh Kumar and Mr. Prasanchand Daga Prathik as Additional Directors (Non-Executive Independent), pending shareholder approval. The company also decided to increase their Authorised Share Capital. Additionally, the board approved the draft of the Postal Ballot Notice and appointed M/s. Dilip Swarnkar &amp; Associates, Practicing Company Secretaries as Scrutinizer for the postal Ballot of the company.</p><ul><li>Re-appointment of Mr. Suganchand Ramesh Kumar as Additional Director (Non-Executive Independent)</li><li>Re-appointment of Mr. Prasanchand Daga Prathik as Additional Director (Non-Executive Independent)</li><li>Increasing in Authorised Share Capital of Company</li><li>Approval of Draft of Postal Ballot Notice</li><li>Appointment of M/s. Dilip Swarnkar &amp; Associates as Scrutinizer for the postal Ballot of Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/714610fc-4b09-427b-8032-2b66a83b1296.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Manoj Jewellers Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>