<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:57:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[HARAFIN] Haryana Financial Corporation Reports Q3 Results with Net Profit of ₹ 8.56 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HARYANA+FINANCIAL+CORPORATION+LTD.&title=Haryana+Financial+Corporation+Reports+Q3+Results+with+Net+Profit+of+%E2%82%B9+8.56+Crores&newsId=3b7ff4fa-dc41-45cb-b0ab-dafb4ee7c4bb&token=M2I3ZmY0ZmEtZGM0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b7ff4fa-dc41-45cb-b0ab-dafb4ee7c4bb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:54:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Haryana Financial Corporation Ltd. has reported its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The corporation has reported a net profit of ₹ 8.56 crores for the quarter. The board of directors has also approved the recommendation to the state government for winding up/liquidation under section 45 of SFCs Act, 1951. The state government has decided to delist the shares of the corporation from the Bombay Stock Exchange, which is currently under process.</p><ul><li>Net profit of ₹ 8.56 crores for the quarter</li><li>Recommendation to the state government for winding up/liquidation under section 45 of SFCs Act, 1951</li><li>State government&apos;s decision to delist shares from Bombay Stock Exchange</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bfbda71f-0ec2-4478-925b-b3dc5887b70f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HARYANA FINANCIAL CORPORATION LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[7TEC] Saven Technologies Urges Shareholders to Update Email IDs, PAN, and Bank Mandates</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SAVEN+TECHNOLOGIES+LTD.&title=Saven+Technologies+Urges+Shareholders+to+Update+Email+IDs%2C+PAN%2C+and+Bank+Mandates&newsId=f970b32b-da9e-4cbd-89a4-daba2fbef85b&token=Zjk3MGIzMmItZGE5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f970b32b-da9e-4cbd-89a4-daba2fbef85b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Saven Technologies Ltd has issued a communication to its shareholders, urging them to update or register their email IDs, PAN, and bank mandates with the company or its Registrar &amp; Transfer Agent, XL Softech Systems Limited. This is in accordance with the Companies Act, 2013, the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, and other applicable laws and regulations. The company has been granted permission to communicate to shareholders through their registered email ids. The shareholders are also encouraged to register and/or update their PAN and bank mandate to ensure timely and secure receipt of dividends and other considerations, and to prevent fraudulent encashment of warrants. The company has provided procedures for updation for both physical and demat holdings.</p><ul><li>Saven Technologies urges shareholders to update email IDs, PAN, and bank mandates</li><li>Communication issued in accordance with the Companies Act, 2013, SEBI Listing Regulations, and other applicable laws and regulations</li><li>Updation necessary for timely and secure receipt of dividends and other considerations</li><li>Procedures provided for updation for both physical and demat holdings</li><li>Physical dispatch of communications not possible due to circulars</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9cef0caa-ce1d-42b7-b1ff-d9465466383f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SAVEN TECHNOLOGIES LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHAHCON] Shah Construction Company Ltd Reports Q3 Results with 26.8% YoY Revenue Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHAH+CONSTRUCTION+CO.LTD.&title=Shah+Construction+Company+Ltd+Reports+Q3+Results+with+26.8%25+YoY+Revenue+Growth&newsId=7e8250c0-516c-4315-b9b5-8429e6e3178d&token=N2U4MjUwYzAtNTE2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7e8250c0-516c-4315-b9b5-8429e6e3178d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:54:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Shah Construction Company Ltd has announced its financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at INR 371.30 crores, marking a 26.8% year-over-year growth. The profit before tax is INR 50.27 crores. The company operates without different segments, and the financial results were reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for Q3 FY2025-2026 stands at INR 371.30 crores, a 26.8% YoY growth.</li><li>Profit before tax is INR 50.27 crores.</li><li>The company does not operate with different segments.</li><li>Financial results were reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/da75156f-9d0a-4798-aef8-0a44c11d0897.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHAH CONSTRUCTION CO.LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DAULAT] Daulat Securities Ltd. Announces Q3 Results with 10.56% Profit on Investment Sale</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DAULAT+SECURITIES+LTD.&title=Daulat+Securities+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+Results+with+10.56%25+Profit+on+Investment+Sale&newsId=e0e0e2e3-6868-4a23-93dc-a25e512c6e7a&token=ZTBlMGUyZTMtNjg2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0e0e2e3-6868-4a23-93dc-a25e512c6e7a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:51:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Daulat Securities Ltd. has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter ended on 31st December, 2025. The company reported a revenue from operations of INR XX,XXX and a profit before tax of INR XXX. The profit before exceptional items and tax stands at INR XXX. The company&apos;s profit before tax showed an increase compared to the previous quarter and year. The company&apos;s financial results were reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors at their respective meetings. The company is in the business of Share Broking &amp; Depository services and operates in a capital market where quarterly results are not indicative of likely annual results.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations: INR XX,XXX</li><li>Profit before tax: INR XXX</li><li>Profit before tax increase compared to previous quarter and year</li><li>Reviewed by Audit Committee</li><li>Approved by Board of Directors</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d6dd5d79-35da-48b0-8364-fcea401f3316.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DAULAT SECURITIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[REMSONSIND] Remsons Industries Ltd Announces Q3 Results and Re-Appoints Internal Auditor</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=REMSONS+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Remsons+Industries+Ltd+Announces+Q3+Results+and+Re-Appoints+Internal+Auditor&newsId=fb894a02-fc1c-46fe-a37d-f2ff24152fa3&token=ZmI4OTRhMDItZmMx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fb894a02-fc1c-46fe-a37d-f2ff24152fa3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Remsons Industries Ltd announced the outcome of their Board Meeting held on 12th February, 2026. The company approved the un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The company also re-appointed M/s. H A M &amp; Co., Chartered Accountants, Mumbai as Internal Auditors for the financial year 2026-27. The company has sold residential property in Gurgaon and realized gains, which have been classified as an exceptional item in the previous year. The company has also assessed and disclosed the incremental impact of the New Labour Codes, which has been presented as an exceptional item in the consolidated interim financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</p><ul><li>Approval of un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 2025</li><li>Re-appointment of M/s. H A M &amp; Co., Chartered Accountants, Mumbai as Internal Auditors for FY 2026-27</li><li>Realization of gains from sale of residential property in Gurgaon classified as exceptional item in previous year</li><li>Assessment and disclosure of incremental impact of New Labour Codes presented as exceptional item in Q3 2025 results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c3305124-7be4-490a-ad84-ba43ebe8e261.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: REMSONS INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KRYPTONQ] Krypton Industries Ltd. Confirms Non-Applicability of Escrow Payment Mechanism</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KRYPTON+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Krypton+Industries+Ltd.+Confirms+Non-Applicability+of+Escrow+Payment+Mechanism&newsId=7a726377-173f-4fc8-a6dd-3d72108d41c2&token=N2E3MjYzNzctMTcz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7a726377-173f-4fc8-a6dd-3d72108d41c2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In a recent communication, Krypton Industries Ltd. has clarified that the requirement for submission of the Escrow Payment Mechanism is not applicable to the company. This clarification comes in response to a mail dated 12 February, 2026, regarding the submission of details relating to the Escrow Payment Mechanism. The company stated that it has not issued or does not have any instruments or arrangements for which the said mechanism is applicable under the relevant SEBI Regulations. This information is for record purposes.</p><ul><li>Krypton Industries Ltd. has confirmed the non-applicability of the Escrow Payment Mechanism</li><li>The company has clarified its position in response to a mail dated 12 February, 2026</li><li>Krypton Industries Ltd. has no instruments or arrangements that require the Escrow Payment Mechanism</li><li>The notification is for informational and record-keeping purposes</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/73f627b1-f58f-40fa-b112-ee7d398e94c3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KRYPTON INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VAPIPPR] Vapi Enterprise Ltd. Announces Q3 Results with 86.43 Lacs Income from Operations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VAPI+PAPER+MILLS+LTD.&title=Vapi+Enterprise+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+Results+with+86.43+Lacs+Income+from+Operations&newsId=b363e876-ba0c-41b1-8764-ba10ac4f84c8&token=YjM2M2U4NzYtYmEw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b363e876-ba0c-41b1-8764-ba10ac4f84c8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vapi Enterprise Ltd., formerly known as Vapi Paper Mills Limited, has announced its un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2026. The company&apos;s income from operations stands at 86.43 Lacs, with a net profit of 7.00 Lacs after tax. The earnings per share of Rs.10/- each for the period not annualised are 1.44 for basic and 1.44 for diluted. The company operates in one segment and the previous period&apos;s/ year&apos;s figures have been regrouped/reclassified, wherever necessary.</p><ul><li>Income from Operations: 86.43 Lacs</li><li>Net Profit: 7.00 Lacs</li><li>Earnings per Share: 1.44 (Basic and Diluted)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/16bc6f32-a1df-4024-a970-5289e277bafe.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VAPI PAPER MILLS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SCAPDVR] GACM Technologies Ltd. Shifts Registered Office within Hyderabad</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Stampede+Capital+Ltd+-+DVR&title=GACM+Technologies+Ltd.+Shifts+Registered+Office+within+Hyderabad&newsId=c4383035-0045-4810-9b45-62b3442ca5f8&token=YzQzODMwMzUtMDA0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4383035-0045-4810-9b45-62b3442ca5f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:42:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>GACM Technologies Ltd. has announced a shift in its registered office within the same city, Hyderabad, Telangana. The Board of Directors approved the change at a meeting held on Wednesday, February 11, 2026. The new address is 2nd Floor, GHMC No- 3-260/KA/201/NR PLOT NO. 260, Guttala Begumpet, Kavuri Hills, Hyderabad- 500033, Telangana, while the old address was KURA Towers, 10th Floor, D. No. 1-11-254 &amp; 1-11-255 S.P. Road, Begumpet, Hyderabad- 500016, Telangana, India. This change is purely administrative and does not impact the company&apos;s operations.</p><ul><li>GACM Technologies Ltd. has shifted its registered office within Hyderabad, Telangana.</li><li>The shift is purely administrative and does not affect the company&apos;s operations.</li><li>The old registered office was at KURA Towers, 10th Floor, D. No. 1-11-254 &amp; 1-11-255 S.P. Road, Begumpet, Hyderabad- 500016, Telangana, India.</li><li>The new registered office is located at 2nd Floor, GHMC No- 3-260/KA/201/NR PLOT NO. 260, Guttala Begumpet, Kavuri Hills, Hyderabad- 500033, Telangana.</li><li>The change was approved at a Board of Directors meeting held on Wednesday, February 11, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/87c643d9-3178-4d30-9fbb-965693be6e27.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Stampede Capital Ltd - DVR | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HARAFIN] Haryana Financial Corporation Approves Q3 Results with a Net Profit of ₹ 8.56 Crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HARYANA+FINANCIAL+CORPORATION+LTD.&title=Haryana+Financial+Corporation+Approves+Q3+Results+with+a+Net+Profit+of+%E2%82%B9+8.56+Crore&newsId=a83815a1-1330-41e5-8650-e8234c152256&token=YTgzODE1YTEtMTMz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a83815a1-1330-41e5-8650-e8234c152256</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:42:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Haryana Financial Corporation (HFC) have approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The corporation reported a net profit of ₹ 8.56 crore for the quarter. The total income for the quarter was ₹ 11.65 crore, while the total expenditure stood at ₹ 2.94 crore. The corporation has recommended to the State Government for its winding up/liquidation under section 45 of SFCs Act 1951. The State Government has also decided to delist the shares of the corporation from the Bombay Stock Exchange, which is currently under process.</p><ul><li>Haryana Financial Corporation reported a net profit of ₹ 8.56 crore for the quarter ended 31st December, 2025.</li><li>The total income for the quarter was ₹ 11.65 crore.</li><li>The total expenditure for the quarter was ₹ 2.94 crore.</li><li>The corporation has recommended to the State Government for its winding up/liquidation under section 45 of SFCs Act 1951.</li><li>The State Government has decided to delist the shares of the corporation from the Bombay Stock Exchange.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e675cf0b-76c1-40a4-946c-878f0270c758.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HARYANA FINANCIAL CORPORATION LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EVERESTO] Everest Organics Ltd Postpones Board Meeting to Consider Q3 Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=EVEREST+ORGANICS+LTD.&title=Everest+Organics+Ltd+Postpones+Board+Meeting+to+Consider+Q3+Financial+Results&newsId=074c889f-cd27-4b6b-8fef-10d1842fa398&token=MDc0Yzg4OWYtY2Qy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">074c889f-cd27-4b6b-8fef-10d1842fa398</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:41:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Everest Organics Ltd has postponed its board meeting, originally scheduled for February 11, 2026, to February 14, 2026. The meeting will consider the un-audited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2026, along with other business transactions. The trading window for dealing in securities of the company, which was closed on January 1, 2026, will reopen 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results.</p><ul><li>Everest Organics Ltd postpones board meeting to February 14, 2026</li><li>Un-audited financial results for Q3 2026 to be considered</li><li>Trading window for securities to reopen 48 hours after result declaration</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0c94c11c-7729-4f33-a761-ab345c1b0896.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: EVEREST ORGANICS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>