<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:37:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[EXHICON] EXHICON Subsidiary, United Helicharters, Granted Air Operator Permit by DGCA</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Exhicon+Events+Media+Solutions+Ltd&title=EXHICON+Subsidiary%2C+United+Helicharters%2C+Granted+Air+Operator+Permit+by+DGCA&newsId=ee9445ff-9a56-44e0-9c47-75f27ebedece&token=ZWU5NDQ1ZmYtOWE1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee9445ff-9a56-44e0-9c47-75f27ebedece</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>In a significant development, the Directorate General of Civil Aviation (DGCA) under the Government of India has granted an Air Operator Permit (AOP) to United Helicharters Private Limited, a subsidiary of Exhicon Events Media Solutions Limited. The permit, issued on February 20, 2026, allows UHPL to conduct commercial non-scheduled air operations until February 19, 2031. UHPL, established in 1998 and acquired by EXHICON in 2024, has a strong operational foundation within India’s rotary aviation ecosystem, providing various aviation support services. The AOP empowers UHPL to undertake commercial non-scheduled helicopter operations, deploy aircraft listed under its approved operational specifications, operate under DGCA’s regulatory and safety oversight framework, and expand into various aviation segments.</p><ul><li>DGCA grants AOP to United Helicharters, a subsidiary of Exhicon Events Media Solutions Limited</li><li>AOP allows UHPL to conduct commercial non-scheduled air operations until 2031</li><li>UHPL has a strong operational foundation within India’s rotary aviation ecosystem</li><li>AOP empowers UHPL to undertake commercial non-scheduled helicopter operations</li><li>UHPL can expand into various aviation segments with the AOP</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4502c57b-523d-458a-a9f8-ea6e53f4a3c1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Exhicon Events Media Solutions Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUNSKY] Sunsky Logistics Ltd Appoints M/s. Parth P. Shah and Associates as Secretarial Auditor for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sunsky+Logistics+Ltd&title=Sunsky+Logistics+Ltd+Appoints+M%2Fs.+Parth+P.+Shah+and+Associates+as+Secretarial+Auditor+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=f9fc5afd-49eb-4db7-90d7-3f62b4d636ea&token=ZjlmYzVhZmQtNDll</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9fc5afd-49eb-4db7-90d7-3f62b4d636ea</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sunsky Logistics Ltd, formerly known as Sunsky Logistics Private Limited, has appointed M/s. Parth P. Shah and Associates as the Secretarial Auditor for the financial year starting from April 1, 2025, and ending on March 31, 2026. The appointment was approved during the Board Meeting held on February 21, 2026. M/s. Parth P. Shah and Associates is a firm of Practicing Company Secretaries providing professional services in the areas of Corporate Laws, Secretarial Compliance, and Regulatory Advisory. The firm has experience in handling secretarial audits, corporate governance matters, board and shareholder compliances, and other statutory and regulatory requirements under the Companies Act, 2013 and allied laws.</p><ul><li>Sunsky Logistics Ltd appoints M/s. Parth P. Shah and Associates as Secretarial Auditor for FY 2025-26</li><li>The appointment was approved during the Board Meeting held on February 21, 2026</li><li>M/s. Parth P. Shah and Associates is a firm of Practicing Company Secretaries providing professional services in Corporate Laws, Secretarial Compliance, and Regulatory Advisory</li><li>The firm has experience in handling secretarial audits, corporate governance matters, board and shareholder compliances</li><li>The appointment is for the financial year starting from April 1, 2025, and ending on March 31, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b28ae98f-bd4c-4630-b9be-036c163327c9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sunsky Logistics Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[YASTF] Yash Trading &amp; Finance Ltd Announces EGM on 18th March 2026 Through Video Conferencing</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=YASH+TRADING+%26+FINANCE+LTD.&title=Yash+Trading+%26+Finance+Ltd+Announces+EGM+on+18th+March+2026+Through+Video+Conferencing&newsId=c9652fba-400b-44fe-ad38-481da914ee6f&token=Yzk2NTJmYmEtNDAw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9652fba-400b-44fe-ad38-481da914ee6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:31:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Yash Trading &amp; Finance Ltd has announced an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) to be held on Wednesday, 18th March, 2026 at 03:00 PM (IST) through Video Conferencing (VC)/ Other Audio Visual Means (OAVM). The company offers e-voting facility through Purva Sharegistry (India) Pvt. Ltd for the members to cast their votes on all the resolutions set out in the Notice convening the EGM. The remote e-voting period commences on Sunday, 15th March, 2026 at 9.00 a.m. (IST) and ends on Tuesday, 17th March, 2026 at 5.00 p.m. (IST). Any person who becomes a member of the Company after dispatch of Notice and holds shares as on cut-off date may obtain the sequence number from the Company&apos;s Registrar and Share Transfer Agent.</p><ul><li>Yash Trading &amp; Finance Ltd announces EGM on 18th March 2026 through Video Conferencing</li><li>E-voting facility offered through Purva Sharegistry (India) Pvt. Ltd</li><li>Remote e-voting period commences on 15th March 2026 and ends on 17th March 2026</li><li>Members holding shares as on cut-off date are eligible to avail the e-voting facility</li><li>Any member after dispatch of Notice can obtain the sequence number from the Company&apos;s Registrar and Share Transfer Agent</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8abb5d1b-f91a-43ae-a168-56c06fbf3c43.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: YASH TRADING & FINANCE LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CIPLA] Cipla&apos;s Lanreotide Injection Supply Partner Pharmathen Receives OAI Classification from USFDA</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CIPLA+LTD.&title=Cipla%27s+Lanreotide+Injection+Supply+Partner+Pharmathen+Receives+OAI+Classification+from+USFDA&newsId=9454f391-9d5e-4e05-b6af-71646fccd615&token=OTQ1NGYzOTEtOWQ1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9454f391-9d5e-4e05-b6af-71646fccd615</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>USFDA</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cipla Ltd. has informed about the USFDA classification of the cGMP inspection at the Rodopi, Greece manufacturing facility of Pharmathen International S.A., the supply partner for Lanreotide Injection to Cipla USA Inc. The USFDA has classified the inspection as Official Action Indicated (OAI). This information is provided for record purposes.</p><ul><li>Cipla&apos;s supply partner for Lanreotide Injection, Pharmathen International S.A.&apos;s Rodopi, Greece manufacturing facility inspected by USFDA</li><li>USFDA classifies the inspection as Official Action Indicated (OAI)</li><li>Cipla USA Inc. is a wholly owned subsidiary of Cipla Ltd.</li><li>Lanreotide Injection supply may be affected due to the USFDA classification</li><li>Cipla Ltd. shares the information for record purposes</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e1107f95-0491-426e-ad83-9e31782b72eb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CIPLA LTD. | Category: USFDA</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VBCFERROQ] Chrome Silicon Ltd. Submits Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 2025 with Late Attached Limited Audit Review Report</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VBC+FERRO+ALLOYS+LTD.-%24&title=Chrome+Silicon+Ltd.+Submits+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+2025+with+Late+Attached+Limited+Audit+Review+Report&newsId=6357e9ce-b0df-46f2-a720-a48677389ecd&token=NjM1N2U5Y2UtYjBk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6357e9ce-b0df-46f2-a720-a48677389ecd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Chrome Silicon Ltd. (formerly VBC Ferro Alloys Ltd) has submitted their unaudited financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025, including the late attached Limited Audit Review Report. The company&apos;s operations were suspended since 30.05.2025 due to significant market fluctuations, and they will continue to monitor market conditions to resume operations at an appropriate time. The financial results are prepared in accordance with Indian Accounting Standards, the Companies Act, 2013, and guidelines issued by the Securities and Exchange Board of India. The company has complied with all applicable Ind AS except for IND AS 109 and 19.</p><ul><li>Chrome Silicon Ltd. submitted unaudited financial results for Q3 2025</li><li>Limited Audit Review Report inadvertently not attached initially</li><li>Operations suspended since 30.05.2025 due to market fluctuations</li><li>Company will monitor market conditions to resume operations</li><li>Financial results prepared in accordance with Ind AS, Companies Act, 2013, and SEBI guidelines</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4b2f8fab-5700-441c-9abf-3035cd205a49.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VBC FERRO ALLOYS LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VIRTUALS] Kati Patang Lifestyle Converts Warrants to Equity Shares, Increasing Paid-up Capital</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VIRTUALSOFT+SYSTEMS+LTD.&title=Kati+Patang+Lifestyle+Converts+Warrants+to+Equity+Shares%2C+Increasing+Paid-up+Capital&newsId=985c654c-f451-4ecc-9b33-86e091e08480&token=OTg1YzY1NGMtZjQ1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">985c654c-f451-4ecc-9b33-86e091e08480</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Kati Patang Lifestyle Ltd. has allotted 54,35,000 equity shares to various promoter and non-promoter warrant holders following the conversion of warrants into equity shares. The allotment, made for a cash consideration of Rs. 4,07,62,500, increased the company&apos;s paid-up equity shares from 3,58,98,280 to 4,13,33,280. The allotted equity shares rank pari-passu with the existing fully paid equity shares, including dividend rights.</p><ul><li>Kati Patang Lifestyle converts warrants to equity shares, increasing paid-up capital.</li><li>54,35,000 equity shares allotted to promoter and non-promoter warrant holders.</li><li>Allotment made for a cash consideration of Rs. 4,07,62,500.</li><li>Paid-up equity shares increased from 3,58,98,280 to 4,13,33,280.</li><li>Allotted equity shares rank pari-passu with existing fully paid equity shares.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7fe824d9-d758-4d79-939c-0b3e89244696.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VIRTUALSOFT SYSTEMS LTD. | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RISHYRN] Rishab Special Yarns Ltd. Announces Changes in Authorized Share Capital, Name, and Fundraising Plans</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RISHAB+SPECIAL+YARNS+LTD.&title=Rishab+Special+Yarns+Ltd.+Announces+Changes+in+Authorized+Share+Capital%2C+Name%2C+and+Fundraising+Plans&newsId=6de4e9a2-7c68-47f9-99eb-687c693358f6&token=NmRlNGU5YTItN2M2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6de4e9a2-7c68-47f9-99eb-687c693358f6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:11:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rishab Special Yarns Ltd. announced these changes and plans at a Board Meeting held on February 21, 2026. The Board approved an increase in the company&apos;s Authorised Share Capital, subject to shareholder approval through a Postal Ballot. The company also proposed a change of name to Impera Worldwide Limited, again subject to shareholder approval. The Board appointed Shravan A. Gupta &amp; Associates as the Scrutinizer for the Postal Ballot process. Additionally, the Board approved a proposal to raise funds through the issuance of equity shares by way of a Rights Issue, with the total amount and other terms to be determined at a future meeting.</p><ul><li>Approval to increase Authorised Share Capital and amend the memorandum of association</li><li>Proposal to change the company&apos;s name to Impera Worldwide Limited</li><li>Appointment of Shravan A. Gupta &amp; Associates as the Scrutinizer for the Postal Ballot process</li><li>Plan to raise funds through a Rights Issue of equity shares</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7cbf1cb2-13a0-4907-bf45-ed91ce6e5f36.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RISHAB SPECIAL YARNS LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MEDPLUS] Medplus Health Services Subsidiary Faces Two Suspension Orders for Karnataka Drug Licenses</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Medplus+Health+Services+Ltd&title=Medplus+Health+Services+Subsidiary+Faces+Two+Suspension+Orders+for+Karnataka+Drug+Licenses&newsId=6a1ac096-41f4-4f0a-9f64-dfdcf266a8fd&token=NmExYWMwOTYtNDFm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a1ac096-41f4-4f0a-9f64-dfdcf266a8fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Medplus Health Services Ltd. has announced that its subsidiary, Optival Health Solutions Private Limited, has received two suspension orders for a Drug License of a store situated in the state of Karnataka. The first suspension order was received on 20.02.2026 for a Davanagere Circle store situated at Vinobha Cosmetics Act, Nagar, Karnataka, under Rule 65 of Drugs and Cosmetics Suspension of Drug Rules, 1945. This suspension could potentially result in a revenue loss of Rs 1.40 lacs. The second suspension order was also received on 20.02.2026 for a store situated at KSRTC, Davanagere, Karnataka, which could potentially result in a revenue loss of Rs 2.79 lacs. These orders will be available on the company&apos;s website, as well as on the websites of BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange of India Ltd.</p><ul><li>Medplus Health Services subsidiary, Optival Health Solutions Private Limited, received two suspension orders for Drug Licenses in Karnataka.</li><li>The first suspension order was received for a Davanagere Circle store situated at Vinobha Cosmetics Act, Nagar, Karnataka, potentially causing a revenue loss of Rs 1.40 lacs.</li><li>The second suspension order was received for a store situated at KSRTC, Davanagere, Karnataka, potentially causing a revenue loss of Rs 2.79 lacs.</li><li>These suspension orders were received on 20.02.2026 and will be available on the company&apos;s website and other relevant platforms.</li><li>Medplus Health Services Ltd. is a company registered in Telangana, India, with CIN No: L85110TG2006PLC051845.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bfada837-9460-40bb-aaba-ebd1038edb48.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Medplus Health Services Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VIRTUALS] Kati Patang Lifestyle Ltd Converts Warrants into Equity Shares Worth INR 4,07,62,500</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VIRTUALSOFT+SYSTEMS+LTD.&title=Kati+Patang+Lifestyle+Ltd+Converts+Warrants+into+Equity+Shares+Worth+INR+4%2C07%2C62%2C500&newsId=0a8ffb1c-7bae-4c13-bd81-cd6091d2383e&token=MGE4ZmZiMWMtN2Jh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a8ffb1c-7bae-4c13-bd81-cd6091d2383e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Kati Patang Lifestyle Ltd has issued and allotted 54,35,000 equity shares of face value of Rs.10/- each fully paid up to various warrant holders of the promoter group and non-promoter group. The allotment has been made for cash, upon the receipt of the remaining exercise price of Rs. 7.50/- per Share Warrant, aggregating to Rs. 4,07,62,500/-. The equity shares allotted on conversion of the warrants shall rank pari-passu, in all respects with the existing fully paid equity shares of the Company, including dividend, if any.</p><ul><li>Kati Patang Lifestyle Ltd has converted warrants into equity shares worth INR 4,07,62,500.</li><li>54,35,000 equity shares have been allotted to various warrant holders of the promoter group and non-promoter group.</li><li>The allotment has been made for cash upon the receipt of the remaining exercise price of Rs. 7.50/- per Share Warrant.</li><li>The equity shares allotted on conversion of the warrants shall rank pari-passu with the existing fully paid equity shares of the Company.</li><li>The total number of equity shares of the Company has increased from 3,58,98,280 to 4,13,33,280 after the allotment.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3d2842c0-7cfe-4272-a51b-5833c9e02d48.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VIRTUALSOFT SYSTEMS LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NELCO] Nelco Ltd Appoints Protiviti India Member Private Limited as Internal Auditor for 3 Years</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NELCO+LTD.&title=Nelco+Ltd+Appoints+Protiviti+India+Member+Private+Limited+as+Internal+Auditor+for+3+Years&newsId=5f84f913-4065-4867-ba44-28a1e774113b&token=NWY4NGY5MTMtNDA2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f84f913-4065-4867-ba44-28a1e774113b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Nelco Ltd has announced the appointment of Protiviti India Member Private Limited as its Internal Auditor for a period of 3 consecutive years commencing from FY 2026-27. The decision was made in a Board meeting held on January 30, 2026, based on the recommendation of the Audit Committee. Protiviti is a global consulting firm with expertise in various fields including finance, technology, operations, data, digital, legal, HR, risk and internal audit.</p><ul><li>Nelco Ltd appoints Protiviti India Member Private Limited as Internal Auditor</li><li>Appointment is for a period of 3 consecutive years starting from FY 2026-27</li><li>Appointment is based on the recommendation of the Audit Committee</li><li>Protiviti is a global consulting firm with expertise in various fields</li><li>Decision was made in a Board meeting held on January 30, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d2210172-e3cc-47ab-b9f2-dc36dae2be3f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NELCO LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>