<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 21:18:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ADANIGREEN] Adani Green Energy Provides Clarification on SEC Fraud Case Allegations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Adani+Green+Energy+Ltd&title=Adani+Green+Energy+Provides+Clarification+on+SEC+Fraud+Case+Allegations&newsId=be99fb0f-f8e4-4e85-90f0-da16e76f7930&token=YmU5OWZiMGYtZjhl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be99fb0f-f8e4-4e85-90f0-da16e76f7930</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:46:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Adani Green Energy Ltd has provided a clarification on a news item regarding a civil complaint brought by the United States Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) against Mr. Gautam Adani and Mr. Sagar Adani. The company is not a party to these proceedings, and no charges have been brought against it. The SEC proceedings are civil in nature, and there are no charges of bribery or corruption against the defendants. The content of the Press Report does not trigger any disclosure requirements under Regulation 30 read with Schedule Ill of SEBI Listing Regulations and has no adverse impact on the business or operations of the company.</p><ul><li>Adani Green Energy Ltd provides clarification on a civil complaint by the SEC against its directors.</li><li>The company is not a party to the SEC proceedings and no charges have been brought against it.</li><li>The SEC proceedings are civil in nature, with no charges of bribery or corruption against the defendants.</li><li>The Press Report does not trigger any disclosure requirements under SEBI Listing Regulations.</li><li>There is no adverse impact on the business or operations of Adani Green Energy Ltd.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e5bfb845-1efc-4f56-a0e9-77dc1fa6a66b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Adani Green Energy Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADANIGREEN] Adani Green Energy Clarifies on SEC Proceedings Against Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Adani+Green+Energy+Ltd&title=Adani+Green+Energy+Clarifies+on+SEC+Proceedings+Against+Directors&newsId=5d4ed8c1-d97b-4be3-8c92-e203b6350020&token=NWQ0ZWQ4YzEtZDk3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d4ed8c1-d97b-4be3-8c92-e203b6350020</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:45:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Adani Green Energy Ltd has issued a clarification regarding a media report on the SEC seeking alternate means of service of summons and complaint upon its directors, Mr. Gautam Adani and Mr. Sagar Adani. The company is not a party to these proceedings and no charges have been brought against it. The proceedings are civil in nature and there are no charges of bribery or corruption against the defendants. The press report does not have any adverse impact on the business or operations of the company.</p><ul><li>Adani Green Energy Ltd has issued a clarification on a media report related to SEC proceedings against its directors.</li><li>The company is not a party to these proceedings and no charges have been brought against it.</li><li>The SEC proceedings are civil in nature and there are no charges of bribery or corruption against the defendants.</li><li>The press report does not have any adverse impact on the business or operations of the company.</li><li>The SEC made an application for alternate means of service of summons and complaint upon the defendants on January 21, 2026 (New York time) / January 22, 2026 (India time).</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/70053139-f451-4272-92fb-abc2bca8c561.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Adani Green Energy Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NIITMTS] NIIT USA Inc. Approves Additional Equity Investment of USD 300,000 in NIIT Brazil LTDA</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NIIT+Learning+Systems+Ltd&title=NIIT+USA+Inc.+Approves+Additional+Equity+Investment+of+USD+300%2C000+in+NIIT+Brazil+LTDA&newsId=2f702727-74da-43cf-80b5-79fd89abbf77&token=MmY3MDI3MjctNzRk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2f702727-74da-43cf-80b5-79fd89abbf77</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>NIIT USA Inc., a wholly owned subsidiary of NIIT Learning Systems Limited, has approved an additional equity investment of up to USD 300,000 in its wholly owned subsidiary, NIIT Brazil LTDA. The decision was made during a board meeting on January 23, 2026, to meet NIIT Brazil&apos;s funds requirement for growth and working capital. The existing capital of NIIT Brazil is USD 200,000 (Brazilian Real 1,093,000). The proposed equity investments are subject to applicable regulatory and customary approvals. The decision is not expected to have a material impact on the consolidated financials of the Company. NIIT Brazil will continue to remain a wholly owned subsidiary of NIIT USA and a step-down subsidiary of the Company.</p><ul><li>NIIT USA Inc. approved an additional equity investment of up to USD 300,000 in NIIT Brazil LTDA</li><li>The decision was made to meet NIIT Brazil&apos;s funds requirement for growth and working capital</li><li>NIIT Brazil&apos;s existing capital is USD 200,000 (Brazilian Real 1,093,000)</li><li>The proposed equity investments are subject to applicable regulatory and customary approvals</li><li>The decision is not expected to have a material impact on the consolidated financials of the Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6416e7cc-161c-4101-83bf-18895c85c13d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NIIT Learning Systems Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GOCOLORS] Go Fashion (India) Ltd to Approve Q3 &amp; Year-to-Date Unaudited Financial Results on Jan 29, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Go+Fashion+%28India%29+Ltd&title=Go+Fashion+%28India%29+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+%26+Year-to-Date+Unaudited+Financial+Results+on+Jan+29%2C+2026&newsId=19c21765-b438-4220-843c-aa9e7a157eab&token=MTljMjE3NjUtYjQz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19c21765-b438-4220-843c-aa9e7a157eab</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:45:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Go Fashion (India) Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 29, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and year to date ended December 31, 2025. This is in accordance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations &amp; Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Go Fashion (India) Ltd to hold a Board Meeting on January 29, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and year-to-date ended December 31, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0e265ad7-9be0-48f2-ae32-1ebabf74e3f3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Go Fashion (India) Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SIRCA] Sirca Paints India Ltd to Approve Q4 2025 Financial Results on Jan 31, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sirca+Paints+India+Ltd&title=Sirca+Paints+India+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+2025+Financial+Results+on+Jan+31%2C+2026&newsId=351d1278-cce2-4105-aa8f-c97e49a9f115&token=MzUxZDEyNzgtY2Nl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">351d1278-cce2-4105-aa8f-c97e49a9f115</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:45:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sirca Paints India Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 31, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The trading window will be closed from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the conclusion of the Board Meeting.</p><ul><li>Sirca Paints India Ltd to approve Q4 2025 financial results on January 31, 2026</li><li>The meeting is in accordance with SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Trading window to remain closed from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the Board Meeting</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f8c76e31-f4da-4c35-9411-ea25d21d532c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sirca Paints India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CEREBRAINT] Cerebra Integrated Technologies Ltd Receives E-Auction Sale Notice from Canara Bank</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CEREBRA+INTEGRATED+TECHNOLOGIES+LTD.&title=Cerebra+Integrated+Technologies+Ltd+Receives+E-Auction+Sale+Notice+from+Canara+Bank&newsId=d47c6c12-5168-46f8-aa2c-fb8a28d2cfff&token=ZDQ3YzZjMTItNTE2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d47c6c12-5168-46f8-aa2c-fb8a28d2cfff</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:45:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cerebra Integrated Technologies Ltd, in compliance with the disclosure obligations under Regulation 30 of the SEBI LODR Regulations, 2015, has announced the receipt of an e-auction sale notice under Section 13(4) of the SARFAESI Act, 2002 from Canara Bank, a secured lender. This notice was received on 23rd January, 2026, following an earlier intimation dated 15th July, 2025.</p><ul><li>Cerebra Integrated Technologies Ltd has received an e-auction sale notice from Canara Bank, a secured lender.</li><li>The notice was received on 23rd January, 2026, in accordance with Section 13(4) of the SARFAESI Act, 2002.</li><li>This disclosure is made in compliance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI LODR Regulations, 2015.</li><li>The company had previously received a demand notice under Section 13(4) of the SARFAESI Act, 2002 from Secured Lender.</li><li>This announcement is made to keep stakeholders informed about the company&apos;s legal obligations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/747a8007-cb00-46f8-8220-995d893ab8c9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CEREBRA INTEGRATED TECHNOLOGIES LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ATGL] Adani Total Gas Ltd Clarifies on Media Reports Regarding Legal Proceedings</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Adani+Total+Gas+Ltd&title=Adani+Total+Gas+Ltd+Clarifies+on+Media+Reports+Regarding+Legal+Proceedings&newsId=82fc7544-eaf8-42e7-9c64-600d4eac41f5&token=ODJmYzc1NDQtZWFm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">82fc7544-eaf8-42e7-9c64-600d4eac41f5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:45:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Adani Total Gas Ltd has issued a clarification regarding certain media reports, specifically a report titled &apos;US regulator seeking measures to serve Gautam, Sagar Adani legal summons, Bloomberg reports&apos; published on January 23, 2026. The company stated that there are no allegations made against it in these proceedings and it is not a party to them. The company also mentioned that the content of the report does not trigger any disclosure requirements under Regulation 30 read with Schedule III of SEBI Listing Regulations.</p><ul><li>Adani Total Gas Ltd has issued a clarification regarding media reports</li><li>The reports titled &apos;US regulator seeking measures to serve Gautam, Sagar Adani legal summons, Bloomberg reports&apos; published on January 23, 2026 is being referred</li><li>Adani Total Gas Ltd is not a party to these proceedings and there are no allegations made against the company</li><li>The content of the report does not trigger any disclosure requirements under SEBI Listing Regulations</li><li>The clarification is in response to a clarification sought by the Stock Exchanges</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/75eb9056-f7e0-4514-9d5b-ae1c82a50d10.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Adani Total Gas Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KHYATI] Khyati Multimedia Entertainment Ltd Announces Application for Re-classification of Promoters under SEBI Regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KHYATI+MULTIMEDIA-ENTERTAINMENT+LTD.&title=Khyati+Multimedia+Entertainment+Ltd+Announces+Application+for+Re-classification+of+Promoters+under+SEBI+Regulations&newsId=2fcee99a-daf2-405f-b321-60df7fdbc066&token=MmZjZWU5OWEtZGFm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2fcee99a-daf2-405f-b321-60df7fdbc066</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Khyati Multimedia Entertainment Ltd has informed about the filing of an application for re-classification of certain promoters from the category of ‘promoter group’ to ‘public’ in terms of Regulation 31A of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The application was filed with BSE Limited on 23rd January, 2026. The company will keep BSE informed of the developments in relation to the reclassification application in accordance with SEBI LODR.</p><ul><li>Khyati Multimedia Entertainment Ltd files application for re-classification of promoters</li><li>Promoters to be re-classified from ‘promoter group’ to ‘public’ category</li><li>Application filed with BSE Limited on 23rd January, 2026</li><li>Company to keep BSE informed of the developments as per SEBI LODR regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e7bf834e-8a2f-4c04-b333-1559cb3110ea.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KHYATI MULTIMEDIA-ENTERTAINMENT LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CEWATER] Concord Enviro Systems Acquires Convertible Preference Shares of Nala Membranes Inc. for US$ 1,999,310.04</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Concord+Enviro+Systems+Ltd&title=Concord+Enviro+Systems+Acquires+Convertible+Preference+Shares+of+Nala+Membranes+Inc.+for+US%24+1%2C999%2C310.04&newsId=a0e801d9-c2b6-452a-a63b-c684f07da22a&token=YTBlODAxZDktYzJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0e801d9-c2b6-452a-a63b-c684f07da22a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:51:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Concord Enviro Systems Ltd has acquired Preferred Stock of NALA Membranes Inc., a corporation incorporated in the state of North Carolina, USA. The company operates in the advanced membrane and filtration technology space and is engaged in the development and manufacture of flat sheet membranes and membrane elements. The acquisition is in line with the Company’s strategic objectives and is expected to strengthen its business and technological capabilities. Nala Membranes Inc. has developed a one of its kind chlorine resistant membrane, which is expected to transform the wastewater recycle and ZLD process. The investment is proposed to support capital expenditure and commercialization of the technology of NALA Membranes Inc. that will help to scale up the business of the company. Further, the investment aligns with the listed entity’s focus on environmental and waste water treatment technologies. The proposed investment by the Company is US$ 1,999,310.04 for 8% and control of 528,918 shares.</p><ul><li>Concord Enviro Systems Ltd acquires Preferred Stock of NALA Membranes Inc.</li><li>NALA Membranes Inc. operates in the advanced membrane and filtration technology space.</li><li>The acquisition is in line with Concord Enviro Systems&apos; strategic objectives.</li><li>NALA Membranes Inc. has developed a one of its kind chlorine resistant membrane.</li><li>The investment aligns with Concord Enviro Systems&apos; focus on environmental and waste water treatment technologies.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1f33a715-c744-494d-9bcb-f329c8a6a03c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Concord Enviro Systems Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDOBORAX] Promoter Sajal Sushilkumar Jain Sells 26.35% Stake in Indo Borax &amp; Chemicals Ltd for INR 2,16,71,16,450</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDO+BORAX+%26+CHEMICALS+LTD.-%24&title=Promoter+Sajal+Sushilkumar+Jain+Sells+26.35%25+Stake+in+Indo+Borax+%26+Chemicals+Ltd+for+INR+2%2C16%2C71%2C16%2C450&newsId=d69b9804-67ed-4a20-bd74-8a68e62dc862&token=ZDY5Yjk4MDQtNjdl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d69b9804-67ed-4a20-bd74-8a68e62dc862</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Sale of Property</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sajal Sushilkumar Jain, a promoter of Indo Borax &amp; Chemicals Ltd, has sold 84,55,390 equity shares of the company, representing approximately 26.35% of the total paid-up equity share capital. The sale took place on January 23, 2026, off the market, for a total consideration of INR 2,16,71,16,450. This sale was disclosed to the company and the stock exchanges as required under applicable laws.</p><ul><li>Sajal Sushilkumar Jain sells 26.35% stake in Indo Borax &amp; Chemicals Ltd</li><li>Transaction value INR 2,16,71,16,450</li><li>Sale took place on January 23, 2026</li><li>Off-market transaction</li><li>Disclosure made to the company and stock exchanges</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/22bebbce-e8ae-4e74-b0cc-e7c4e6f87fcc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDO BORAX & CHEMICALS LTD.-$ | Category: Sale of Property</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>