<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:25:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[TEXRAIL] Texmaco Rail &amp; Engineering Ltd Secures Rs. 2.96 Crores Order from East Coast Railways</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TEXMACO+RAIL+%26+ENGINEERING+LTD.&title=Texmaco+Rail+%26+Engineering+Ltd+Secures+Rs.+2.96+Crores+Order+from+East+Coast+Railways&newsId=0ef062a1-3472-480d-9b12-b3d0bb4dcfd4&token=MGVmMDYyYTEtMzQ3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ef062a1-3472-480d-9b12-b3d0bb4dcfd4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:23:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Texmaco Rail &amp; Engineering Ltd has been awarded an order of Rs. 2.96 crores by East Coast Railways for the setup of a bird prevention system as per RDSO guidelines in KUR Division. The entire work is to be completed within 365 days from the date of issue of the Letter of Acceptance.</p><ul><li>Order value: Rs. 2.96 crores</li><li>Awarded by: East Coast Railways</li><li>Project details: Setup of bird prevention system as per RDSO guidelines in KUR Division</li><li>Execution period: 365 days from the date of issue of Letter of Acceptance</li><li>Company: An adventz group company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/717a411c-4ba0-48cf-bab8-0734023246ee.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TEXMACO RAIL & ENGINEERING LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHENTRA] Acquirers Amit Lalit Jain and Hanissh Kanakraj Jaain Make Open Offer for 26.00% Stake in Shentracon Chemicals Limited at € 0.50 Per Share</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shentracon+Chemicals+Ltd&title=Acquirers+Amit+Lalit+Jain+and+Hanissh+Kanakraj+Jaain+Make+Open+Offer+for+26.00%25+Stake+in+Shentracon+Chemicals+Limited+at+%E2%82%AC+0.50+Per+Share&newsId=73781cf5-9bb7-47ee-8270-c13bf2df9346&token=NzM3ODFjZjUtOWJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73781cf5-9bb7-47ee-8270-c13bf2df9346</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:23:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Open Offer</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bonanza Portfolio Limited, as the Manager to the Offer, has submitted a Pre-offer advertisement and corrigendum to the BSE for an open offer made by Acquirers Amit Lalit Jain and Hanissh Kanakraj Jaain to acquire 11,53,917 equity shares of Shentracon Chemicals Limited, representing 26.00% of the fully paid up Equity and voting share capital, at a negotiated price of € 0.50 per share. The offer is in accordance with Regulation 18(7) of the SEBI (SAST) Regulations.</p><ul><li>Acquirers Amit Lalit Jain and Hanissh Kanakraj Jaain make an open offer to acquire 26.00% of Shentracon Chemicals Limited&apos;s equity shares.</li><li>The offer price is € 0.50 (Rupees Zero Point Fifty Paisa Only) per equity share, payable in cash.</li><li>The offer is in accordance with Regulation 18(7) of the SEBI (SAST) Regulations.</li><li>The offer is not a competing offer and there has been no competitive bid to this Offer.</li><li>The offer is being made to Shareholders of the Target Company and is a mandatory offer.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/C56525A9-0473-4AEC-A349-E45F36337332-145109.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shentracon Chemicals Ltd | Category: Open Offer</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SOFCOM] Sofcom Systems Ltd Assures Regular Disclosures and Compliance with SEBI Regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sofcom+Systems+Ltd&title=Sofcom+Systems+Ltd+Assures+Regular+Disclosures+and+Compliance+with+SEBI+Regulations&newsId=1dfe0961-92a4-499a-ac5b-23765e00418b&token=MWRmZTA5NjEtOTJh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1dfe0961-92a4-499a-ac5b-23765e00418b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:21:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sofcom Systems Ltd has complied with the SEBI (LODR) Regulation, 2015 and regularly submitted all Disclosures and material events under Regulation 30. The company has informed the stock exchange of all price sensitive information and will continue to provide necessary information as and when asked. The company&apos;s management cannot comment on the price movement of the company&apos;s equity shares, which are freely traded on the stock exchange.</p><ul><li>Sofcom Systems Ltd complies with SEBI (LODR) Regulation, 2015</li><li>Regular submission of Disclosures and material events under Regulation 30</li><li>Informed stock exchange of all price sensitive information</li><li>Committed to providing necessary information to the stock exchange</li><li>Company&apos;s equity shares are freely traded on the stock exchange</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/63925dc7-f931-483a-b45d-bbf36393c8ba.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sofcom Systems Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BERGEPAINT] Berger Paints India Ltd Receives ESG Score of 64 for FY2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BERGER+PAINTS+INDIA+LTD.&title=Berger+Paints+India+Ltd+Receives+ESG+Score+of+64+for+FY2025&newsId=3eebe6be-b30a-44d3-882f-5e1ccbf372a6&token=M2VlYmU2YmUtYjMw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3eebe6be-b30a-44d3-882f-5e1ccbf372a6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:18:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Rating</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Berger Paints India Ltd has been assigned an ESG score of 64 for the financial year 2025 by NSE Sustainability Ratings &amp; Analytics Limited. The intimation was received from BSE Limited on 8th January, 2026 over e-mail.</p><ul><li>Berger Paints India Ltd has received an ESG score of 64 for the financial year 2025</li><li>The score was assigned by NSE Sustainability Ratings &amp; Analytics Limited</li><li>The intimation was received from BSE Limited on 8th January, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/62df696f-6cdd-4aa0-8ed4-d2a29149d750.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BERGER PAINTS INDIA LTD. | Category: Rating</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ARVIND] Arvind Ltd Announces New Leadership Chapter: Susheel Kaul to Step Down as MD &amp; President - Textiles</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ARVIND+LTD.&title=Arvind+Ltd+Announces+New+Leadership+Chapter%3A+Susheel+Kaul+to+Step+Down+as+MD+%26+President+-+Textiles&newsId=de3b6bc8-7e5b-4461-956b-7c13fe838819&token=ZGUzYjZiYzgtN2U1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de3b6bc8-7e5b-4461-956b-7c13fe838819</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:13:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Arvind Ltd, a leading textile and apparel manufacturing company, has announced a significant leadership change. Susheel Kaul, the current MD and President of the textiles and apparel business, will step down from his role. He will be relieved from his duties with effect from close of business hours on March 31, 2026. Kaul will be replaced by Punit Lalbhai, the Vice Chairman of the company, who will take over the textiles and apparel business as part of the company&apos;s long-term succession plan. Kaul will continue in his role as MD and will take up key strategic projects, working closely with the management to shape the future growth initiatives of the group.</p><ul><li>Susheel Kaul to step down as MD &amp; President - Textiles at Arvind Ltd</li><li>Punit Lalbhai, Vice Chairman, to take over as head of textiles and apparel business</li><li>Kaul to continue in his role as MD and take up key strategic projects</li><li>Change is part of the company&apos;s long-term succession plan</li><li>Effective from April 1, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cd68e663-f632-48b9-a396-2d82495efd6e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ARVIND LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AHCL] Anlon Healthcare Completes 67.48% Acquisition of Apiqo Organics</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Anlon+Healthcare+Ltd&title=Anlon+Healthcare+Completes+67.48%25+Acquisition+of+Apiqo+Organics&newsId=a67a124e-80cf-46f3-a828-0b74f9216ddf&token=YTY3YTEyNGUtODBj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a67a124e-80cf-46f3-a828-0b74f9216ddf</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Anlon Healthcare Ltd has successfully completed the acquisition of 67.48% equity shareholding of Apiqo Organics Private Limited (formerly known as M/s Apple Life Science, a partnership firm) as per the Share Purchase Agreement dated December 2, 2025. This acquisition makes Apiqo Organics a subsidiary of Anlon Healthcare Limited and is in compliance with Section 179 (3) (e) &amp; (j) and all other applicable provisions of Companies Act, 2013. The investment details were previously disclosed on December 2, 2025, in accordance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, and SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/CFD/PoD2/CIR/P/0155 dated November 11, 2024.</p><ul><li>Anlon Healthcare Ltd acquires 67.48% equity shareholding of Apiqo Organics Private Limited.</li><li>Apiqo Organics becomes a subsidiary of Anlon Healthcare Limited post-acquisition.</li><li>The acquisition is in compliance with Section 179 (3) (e) &amp; (j) and all other applicable provisions of Companies Act, 2013.</li><li>Investment details were disclosed on December 2, 2025, as per SEBI regulations.</li><li>The acquisition is expected to bolster Anlon Healthcare&apos;s market presence and operations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e9d66c59-19d5-47a8-994f-de7807d2e5c2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Anlon Healthcare Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CANFINHOME] Can Fin Homes Ltd to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and 9 Months of FY2025-26 on Jan 17, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CAN+FIN+HOMES+LTD.&title=Can+Fin+Homes+Ltd+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+9+Months+of+FY2025-26+on+Jan+17%2C+2026&newsId=1c1b9ce5-c056-43ed-b80c-94f33791adce&token=MWMxYjljZTUtYzA1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c1b9ce5-c056-43ed-b80c-94f33791adce</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 09:04:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Can Fin Homes Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 17, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited standalone financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will also approve the limited review report of the Joint Statutory Central Auditors for the same period. In compliance with the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, the trading window for dealing in the company&apos;s equity shares has been closed since January 01, 2026, and will reopen on January 20, 2026.</p><ul><li>Can Fin Homes Ltd to approve unaudited financial results for Q3 and 9 months of FY2025-26 on January 17, 2026</li><li>The meeting will also approve the limited review report of the Joint Statutory Central Auditors</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the company&apos;s equity shares closed since January 01, 2026, as per SEBI regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2349fdf8-f4a2-4e2f-8100-feda33e944cd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CAN FIN HOMES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ROLLT] Rollatainers Ltd Clarifies Non-Pendency of Price-Sensitive Information</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ROLLATAINERS+LTD.&title=Rollatainers+Ltd+Clarifies+Non-Pendency+of+Price-Sensitive+Information&newsId=f56ea5aa-b52e-4425-860e-e3dd52faa728&token=ZjU2ZWE1YWEtYjUy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f56ea5aa-b52e-4425-860e-e3dd52faa728</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 08:56:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rollatainers Ltd, in response to a clarification sought by BSE Limited, has stated that there is no pending price-sensitive information that could have led to the significant movement in the company&apos;s share price. The company ensures that all required information/announcements will be duly disclosed to the stock exchange(s) as per applicable regulations.</p><ul><li>Rollatainers Ltd clarifies there is no pending price-sensitive information</li><li>The movement in the company&apos;s share price is market-driven</li><li>The company will continue to disclose required information as per applicable regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bbffd4cd-a3bf-4a63-ad76-d0807dcda6e2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ROLLATAINERS LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FRASER] Fraser and Company Ltd confirms non-applicability of Statement of Deviation for Q4 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Fraser+and+Company+Ltd&title=Fraser+and+Company+Ltd+confirms+non-applicability+of+Statement+of+Deviation+for+Q4+2025&newsId=612d1e47-401d-48f6-8f2f-05641ed9c37b&token=NjEyZDFlNDctNDAx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">612d1e47-401d-48f6-8f2f-05641ed9c37b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 08:53:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Fraser and Company Ltd, in accordance with Regulation 32(1) of the SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, confirms that the Statement of Deviation or Variation is not applicable to them for the quarter ended 31/12/2025. This is due to the fact that they have not made any Public Issue, Rights Issue, Preferential Issue, etc. They request the relevant authorities to kindly take this confirmation on record.</p><ul><li>Fraser and Company Ltd confirms non-applicability of Statement of Deviation for Q4 2025</li><li>The company has not made any Public Issue, Rights Issue, Preferential Issue, etc.</li><li>The confirmation is in accordance with Regulation 32(1) of the SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>The confirmation is requested to be taken on record by the relevant authorities</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/abd99644-6f2a-427a-8ec8-5b2f5360f68f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Fraser and Company Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ALKYLAMINE] Alkyl Amines Chemicals Ltd Clarifies on Significant Increase in Share Volume</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ALKYL+AMINES+CHEMICALS+LTD.-%24&title=Alkyl+Amines+Chemicals+Ltd+Clarifies+on+Significant+Increase+in+Share+Volume&newsId=dc7274ff-2212-481e-9aa0-3280a5b2acd2&token=ZGM3Mjc0ZmYtMjIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc7274ff-2212-481e-9aa0-3280a5b2acd2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 08:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Alkyl Amines Chemicals Ltd has clarified on a recent significant increase in volume of the company&apos;s shares across exchanges. The company has made all necessary disclosures as per Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. They are not aware of any information that led to the movement in the volume of the shares.</p><ul><li>Alkyl Amines Chemicals Ltd has clarified on a significant increase in volume of their shares across exchanges.</li><li>The company has made all necessary disclosures as per SEBI regulations.</li><li>They are not aware of any information that led to the movement in the volume of the shares.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a01ec25c-71a7-425a-ad4d-bb2103698851.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ALKYL AMINES CHEMICALS LTD.-$ | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>