<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:54:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[NOVIS] Nova Iron &amp; Steel Ltd to Consider and Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q2 and Q3 of FY 2025-2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NOVA+IRON+%26+STEEL+LTD.&title=Nova+Iron+%26+Steel+Ltd+to+Consider+and+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q2+and+Q3+of+FY+2025-2026&newsId=2ca61dff-8f92-4320-a7ee-31647344a79a&token=MmNhNjFkZmYtOGY5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ca61dff-8f92-4320-a7ee-31647344a79a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:54:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Nova Iron &amp; Steel Ltd has informed BSE that the meeting of the Board of Directors of the Company is scheduled on 26/02/2026. The meeting will consider and approve the Notice in compliance with Regulation 29 of the SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosures Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The Board will inter alia consider the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and half year ended 30/09/2025 and quarter ended 31/12/2025.</p><ul><li>Nova Iron &amp; Steel Ltd scheduled a Board Meeting on 26/02/2026</li><li>The meeting will consider the Notice in compliance with SEBI Regulations</li><li>The Board will consider Unaudited Financial Results for Q2 and Q3 of FY 2025-2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1e5756f6-eadf-4f3b-a2a8-92171e2e0e38.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NOVA IRON & STEEL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NBL] Naapbooks Ltd: Appointment of New Company Secretary &amp; Vacation of Director&apos;s Office</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Naapbooks+Ltd&title=Naapbooks+Ltd%3A+Appointment+of+New+Company+Secretary+%26+Vacation+of+Director%27s+Office&newsId=73a1dbdb-4fec-4fd1-b6ea-a9ad141bf85a&token=NzNhMWRiZGItNGZl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73a1dbdb-4fec-4fd1-b6ea-a9ad141bf85a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:52:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Naapbooks Ltd announced the appointment of Ms. Surbhi Agrawal as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer, following the resignation of Ms. Khushi Golani. The company also noted the vacation of office of Non-Executive &amp; Non-Independent Director, Mr. Siddharth Chandrakant Soni, due to his continuous absence from Board Meetings for 12 months.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Ms. Surbhi Agrawal as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer</li><li>Vacation of office of Mr. Siddharth Chandrakant Soni due to non-attendance of Board Meetings for 12 months</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/29929803-86de-4d0a-868d-8d7fa730225c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Naapbooks Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CYBERMEDIA] Promoter &amp; Promoter Group of Cyber Media India Ltd Increases Shareholding to 67.25% via Rights Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CYBER+MEDIA+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Promoter+%26+Promoter+Group+of+Cyber+Media+India+Ltd+Increases+Shareholding+to+67.25%25+via+Rights+Issue&newsId=3962fe05-38fb-490f-8d34-e81673b0e260&token=Mzk2MmZlMDUtMzhm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3962fe05-38fb-490f-8d34-e81673b0e260</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:52:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>The Promoter &amp; Promoter Group of Cyber Media (India) Limited, led by Pradeep Gupta, have increased their shareholding from 61.79% to 67.25% in the company. This change is due to the allotment of equity shares in the Rights Issue, which led to the conversion of Partly Paid-up Equity Shares into Fully Paid-up Equity Shares. The total share capital of the company has increased from Rs. 15,66,72,420 to Rs. 20,62,06,570, consisting of 1,56,67,242 and 2,06,20,657 Equity Shares of the face value of Rs. 10 each, respectively.</p><ul><li>Promoter &amp; Promoter Group&apos;s shareholding increases from 61.79% to 67.25%</li><li>Allotment of equity shares in Rights Issue</li><li>Conversion of Partly Paid-up Equity Shares into Fully Paid-up Equity Shares</li><li>Total share capital increases from Rs. 15,66,72,420 to Rs. 20,62,06,570</li><li>1,56,67,242 to 2,06,20,657 Equity Shares of the face value of Rs. 10 each</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7a5ad744-1830-46fc-a01b-bebbdaa7faec.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CYBER MEDIA (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BNALTD] B&amp;A Ltd Schedules Extra Ordinary General Meeting on 26th March, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=B+%26+A+LTD.&title=B%26A+Ltd+Schedules+Extra+Ordinary+General+Meeting+on+26th+March%2C+2026&newsId=d6a26f14-f195-4575-84c0-e144fbe340c6&token=ZDZhMjZmMTQtZjE5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6a26f14-f195-4575-84c0-e144fbe340c6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>B&amp;A Ltd has announced an Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) of the Members to be held on Thursday, 26th March, 2026, at the registered office of the Company in Jorhat, Assam. The Notice of the EGM will be sent electronically and by speed post to all the Members who will be holding shares of the Company as on the Record Date, i.e. Friday, 27th February, 2026. The Remote e-voting process will commence on Monday, 23rd March 2026 and end on Wednesday, 25th March, 2026. The cut-off date to determine the Members entitled to remote e-voting as well as e-voting during the proceedings of EGM is 19th March, 2026. The Notice of the EGM will also be available on the Company’s website and on the website of the Stock Exchange i.e. BSE Limited.</p><ul><li>B&amp;A Ltd has scheduled an Extra Ordinary General Meeting on 26th March, 2026</li><li>The meeting will be held at the registered office of the Company in Jorhat, Assam</li><li>Notice of the EGM will be sent to Members holding shares as on 27th February, 2026</li><li>Remote e-voting process will commence on 23rd March, 2026 and end on 25th March, 2026</li><li>The cut-off date to determine the Members entitled to e-voting is 19th March, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5cc30552-13a3-48cf-87ca-5815780cae01.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: B & A LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SILVERTUC] Silver Touch Technologies Receives Purchase Order from Food Safety and Standards Authority of India (FSSAI) for Digital Transformation Engagement</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Silver+Touch+Technologies+Ltd&title=Silver+Touch+Technologies+Receives+Purchase+Order+from+Food+Safety+and+Standards+Authority+of+India+%28FSSAI%29+for+Digital+Transformation+Engagement&newsId=fe9ddbdd-77f5-466b-aa4c-c3184f94576d&token=ZmU5ZGRiZGQtNzdm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe9ddbdd-77f5-466b-aa4c-c3184f94576d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:51:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Silver Touch Technologies Limited, a leading provider of end-to-end IT solutions, has been selected by the FSSAI for a strategic digital transformation engagement. The company will be the Managed Service Provider (MSP) for Application Development, Enhancement, Operations &amp; Maintenance of FSSAI Portals and Applications. The scope of work includes development of new portals and mobile applications, enhancement of existing portals and dashboards, microservices-based architecture upgrades, cloud-based deployment and management, API integrations, payment gateway integrations, AI-enabled Chatbot development, database management and architecture enhancement, and document compression system implementation. This long-term contract provides strong revenue visibility and continuity for the company.</p><ul><li>Silver Touch Technologies receives purchase order from FSSAI for digital transformation engagement</li><li>Company to be Managed Service Provider (MSP) for Application Development, Enhancement, Operations &amp; Maintenance of FSSAI Portals and Applications</li><li>Scope of work includes development of new portals and mobile applications, enhancement of existing portals and dashboards, and more</li><li>Long-term contract provides strong revenue visibility and continuity for the company</li><li>Engagement reinforces Silver Touch&apos;s leadership in strategic government digital transformation programs</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fa4c64c9-9f64-4190-9307-8993c0910780.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Silver Touch Technologies Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[METROBRAND] Metro Brands Ltd Appoints Harshvardhan Chauhan as Chief Marketing Officer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Metro+Brands+Ltd&title=Metro+Brands+Ltd+Appoints+Harshvardhan+Chauhan+as+Chief+Marketing+Officer&newsId=d641abf2-8e0e-4ee3-a71a-6435461f2a0c&token=ZDY0MWFiZjItOGUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d641abf2-8e0e-4ee3-a71a-6435461f2a0c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:44:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Metro Brands Ltd has appointed Mr. Harshvardhan Chauhan as the Chief Marketing Officer and Senior Management Personnel with effect from February 23, 2026. Mr. Chauhan comes with over 18 years of experience in marketing and business leadership across various sectors. He holds a Master’s degree in Business Administration with a specialization in Strategy and Business Management from Symbiosis, Pune, and has completed the Accelerated General Management Program from IIM Ahmedabad. He will be reporting to the CEO, Mr. Nissan Joseph.</p><ul><li>Mr. Harshvardhan Chauhan appointed as Chief Marketing Officer &amp; Senior Management Personnel</li><li>Over 18 years of experience in marketing and business leadership</li><li>Worked in various sectors including retail, fashion, lifestyle, grocery, home, and eCommerce</li><li>Holds a Master’s degree in Business Administration</li><li>Completed the Accelerated General Management Program from IIM Ahmedabad</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4eb22fce-511c-4a1d-a627-6418cedb4aaf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Metro Brands Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HIMFIBP] Rudra Ecovation Ltd: Unanimous Approval for Scheme of Amalgamation with Shiva Texfabs Ltd from Unsecured Creditors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HIMACHAL+FIBRES+LTD.&title=Rudra+Ecovation+Ltd%3A+Unanimous+Approval+for+Scheme+of+Amalgamation+with+Shiva+Texfabs+Ltd+from+Unsecured+Creditors&newsId=746f3bb5-5a9f-4402-a570-c3e61ef993e5&token=NzQ2ZjNiYjUtNWE5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">746f3bb5-5a9f-4402-a570-c3e61ef993e5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:42:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Rudra Ecovation Ltd, formerly known as Himachal Fibres Limited, announced the voting results of the NCLT convened unsecured creditors meeting. The meeting, held on 21st February 2026, was conducted through video conference and other audio-visual means. The company provided facilities for remote e-voting and e-voting at the meeting for the approval of the Scheme of Amalgamation with Shiva Texfabs Ltd. The Scheme was approved unanimously by the unsecured creditors of the Transferor Company. The voting results and scrutinizer&apos;s report are available on the company&apos;s website and on the website of Central Depository Services (India) Limited (CDSL).</p><ul><li>Rudra Ecovation Ltd announced voting results of NCLT convened unsecured creditors meeting.</li><li>Meeting held on 21st February 2026 through video conference and other audio-visual means.</li><li>Company provided facilities for remote e-voting and e-voting at the meeting.</li><li>Scheme of Amalgamation with Shiva Texfabs Ltd approved unanimously by unsecured creditors.</li><li>Voting results and scrutinizer&apos;s report available on the company&apos;s website and on the CDSL website.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d56fb2d8-515b-4ba7-8249-f093bd26b3f6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HIMACHAL FIBRES LTD. | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CYBERMEDIA] Cyber Media India Ltd: Promoters Disclose Securities Holding Changes under SEBI Regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CYBER+MEDIA+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Cyber+Media+India+Ltd%3A+Promoters+Disclose+Securities+Holding+Changes+under+SEBI+Regulations&newsId=f40551b3-6063-47c5-98f2-8a4875d10771&token=ZjQwNTUxYjMtNjA2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f40551b3-6063-47c5-98f2-8a4875d10771</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:42:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cyber Media India Ltd has disclosed changes in securities holdings of its promoters, Mr. Pradeep Gupta and Mr. Dhaval Gupta, in compliance with Regulation 7(2) read with Regulation 6(2) of the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015. Mr. Pradeep Gupta, Promoter, Chairman &amp; Managing Director, acquired 38,07,052 equity shares through the conversion of partly paid-up shares into fully paid-up shares. Mr. Dhaval Gupta, Promoter &amp; Director, acquired 3,80,000 equity shares through the same process. The transactions were executed on 20th February 2026, with the intimation to the company on the same date.</p><ul><li>Cyber Media India Ltd promoters disclose changes in securities holdings</li><li>Mr. Pradeep Gupta acquires 38,07,052 equity shares through conversion</li><li>Mr. Dhaval Gupta acquires 3,80,000 equity shares through conversion</li><li>Transactions executed on 20th February 2026</li><li>Intimation to the company on the same date</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1f718cd1-a890-4372-891e-a6b5f0326cc9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CYBER MEDIA (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SCI] New Director Appointed: Shri Nitin Khamesra Takes Charge as Director (Finance) at Shipping Corporation of India</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHIPPING+CORPORATION+OF+INDIA+LTD.&title=New+Director+Appointed%3A+Shri+Nitin+Khamesra+Takes+Charge+as+Director+%28Finance%29+at+Shipping+Corporation+of+India&newsId=7e160f5b-1dc7-4f28-8943-ffc3c99102a3&token=N2UxNjBmNWItMWRj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7e160f5b-1dc7-4f28-8943-ffc3c99102a3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:42:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shipping Corporation of India (SCl) has announced the appointment of Shri Nitin Khamesra as Director (Finance) on the Board of Directors, effective from 23.02.2026 at 1630 hours. Khamesra, a Chartered Accountant and Cost Accountant, brings over 28 years of experience in financial management, project evaluation, and maritime logistics. He has served in various leadership roles at Indian Oil Corporation Limited (IOCL) and has been instrumental in formulating shipping strategies, chartering policies, and risk management initiatives. His experience in energy trade, treasury operations, and policy frameworks will provide strategic depth to the SCI Board, supporting the Company’s long-term growth and national maritime objectives.</p><ul><li>Shri Nitin Khamesra appointed as Director (Finance) at Shipping Corporation of India</li><li>Khamesra has over 28 years of experience in financial management and maritime logistics</li><li>He has served in various leadership roles at Indian Oil Corporation Limited (IOCL)</li><li>Khamesra has been instrumental in formulating shipping strategies and chartering policies</li><li>His experience will provide strong financial stewardship and strategic depth to the SCI Board</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/15965046-75f2-4231-97f1-c500c9e4b55c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHIPPING CORPORATION OF INDIA LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MOREPENLAB] Morepen Bags ₹2825 Crore Global Deal, Expands into High-Growth CDMO Segment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MOREPEN+LABORATORIES+LTD.&title=Morepen+Bags+%E2%82%B92825+Crore+Global+Deal%2C+Expands+into+High-Growth+CDMO+Segment&newsId=134ea04c-d6c3-4c5b-b8de-3d46db0e2656&token=MTM0ZWEwNGMtZDZj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">134ea04c-d6c3-4c5b-b8de-3d46db0e2656</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 12:41:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Morepen Laboratories Ltd has secured a ₹2825 Crore (USD 91 million) global order from a leading pharma major under a CDMO arrangement. The supplies are expected to commence within the next 4-5 months, with execution scheduled through Q1 of the following fiscal year, subject to customary operational and regulatory approvals. The order is expected to be executed within a period of approximately 12-15 months from the date of award. This international commercial supply contract falls under a CDMO arrangement and is not a related party transaction.</p><ul><li>Morepen Laboratories Ltd secures ₹2825 Crore (USD 91 million) global order from a leading pharma major</li><li>Order awarded under a CDMO arrangement for development and/or manufacturing services</li><li>Supplies expected to commence within the next 4-5 months, with execution through Q1 of the following fiscal year</li><li>Order to be executed within approximately 12-15 months from the date of award</li><li>International commercial supply contract under a CDMO arrangement, not a related party transaction</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9a8adba3-2fdb-4577-863c-2d02aa5cce0d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MOREPEN LABORATORIES LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>