<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:45:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[APIL] Viraaj Pradeep Joshi Acquires Shares of Avi Products India Ltd Through Off-Market Deal</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Avi+Products+India+Ltd&title=Viraaj+Pradeep+Joshi+Acquires+Shares+of+Avi+Products+India+Ltd+Through+Off-Market+Deal&newsId=1ad214be-d0e0-4b79-bef9-b07d0e9326c1&token=MWFkMjE0YmUtZDBl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1ad214be-d0e0-4b79-bef9-b07d0e9326c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:44:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Viraaj Pradeep Joshi has acquired 72,000 shares of Avi Products India Ltd through an off-market deal. The shares, with a face value of Rs.10/-, were acquired from the Target Company- M/s. AVI PRODUCTS INDIA LIMITED. The total equity share capital of the company remains unchanged at Rs. 3,30,68,020/- divided into 33,06,802 equity shares of face value Rs. 10/- each.</p><ul><li>Viraaj Pradeep Joshi acquires 72,000 shares of Avi Products India Ltd</li><li>The acquisition was made through an off-market deal</li><li>The shares have a face value of Rs.10/- each</li><li>The total equity share capital of the company remains unchanged</li><li>The acquisition was made from the Target Company- M/s. AVI PRODUCTS INDIA LIMITED</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8875B2F7_56BB_49AC_B5EC_7CCCF94A1FC3_100401.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Avi Products India Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHYAM] Ventura Guaranty Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results of FY 2025-2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VENTURA+GUARANTY+LTD.&title=Ventura+Guaranty+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+of+FY+2025-2026&newsId=43c48f2b-71b7-4bd8-bb0f-00cdb7c6a7fd&token=NDNjNDhmMmItNzFi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43c48f2b-71b7-4bd8-bb0f-00cdb7c6a7fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ventura Guaranty Ltd has informed the BSE that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on February 13, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results (standalone and consolidated) of the company for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the company is closed from January 1, 2026, and will reopen after 48 hours of declaration of the un-audited financial results. The meeting&apos;s agenda also includes any other business with the permission of the Chair.</p><ul><li>Ventura Guaranty Ltd to consider and approve un-audited financial results for Q3 and nine months of FY 2025-2026</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities closed from January 1, 2026</li><li>Trading window to reopen after 48 hours of un-audited financial results declaration</li><li>Meeting to be held on February 13, 2026</li><li>Agenda includes any other business with the permission of the Chair</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2f50e725-4b9b-4a22-a12a-56b83eebaf9b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VENTURA GUARANTY LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TAVERNIER] Silverstone Consultancy Services Acquires 0.84% Stake in Eforu Entertainment Ltd via Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Tavernier+Resources+Limi&title=Silverstone+Consultancy+Services+Acquires+0.84%25+Stake+in+Eforu+Entertainment+Ltd+via+Open+Market&newsId=d7fa5a38-2d79-485a-81a8-e3335d88e176&token=ZDdmYTVhMzgtMmQ3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7fa5a38-2d79-485a-81a8-e3335d88e176</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Silverstone Consultancy Services Pvt Ltd has acquired 50,000 shares carrying voting rights, equivalent to 0.84% stake, in Eforu Entertainment Ltd. The acquisition was made through the open market on 04.02.2026. The total equity share capital of Eforu Entertainment Ltd remains unchanged at Rs. 5,97,90,000 (59,79,000 Fully Paid Equity Shares of Rs 10/- Each) post the acquisition.</p><ul><li>Silverstone Consultancy Services Pvt Ltd acquires 0.84% stake in Eforu Entertainment Ltd</li><li>The acquisition was made through the open market</li><li>50,000 shares carrying voting rights were acquired</li><li>The transaction took place on 04.02.2026</li><li>Eforu Entertainment Ltd&apos;s equity share capital remains unchanged post acquisition</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/13AEFC24_87C9_43CA_A7D5_F0B37521DE65_101032.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Tavernier Resources Limi | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PREMIERPOL] Promoter Group Company D L Millar &amp; Co Ltd Acquires 0.09% Stake in Premier Polyfilm Ltd via Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PREMIER+POLYFILM+LTD.&title=Promoter+Group+Company+D+L+Millar+%26+Co+Ltd+Acquires+0.09%25+Stake+in+Premier+Polyfilm+Ltd+via+Open+Market&newsId=a349f5a6-2352-4ebb-9f8c-2b5d42d22862&token=YTM0OWY1YTYtMjM1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a349f5a6-2352-4ebb-9f8c-2b5d42d22862</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>On February 4, 2026, D L Millar &amp; Co Ltd, a promoter group company of Premier Polyfilm Ltd, acquired 95,450 equity shares (0.09%) of the target company through the open market. The transaction took place on the Bombay Stock Exchange (BSE) and National Stock Exchange (NSE). The total equity share capital of Premier Polyfilm Ltd is Rs. 10,47,42,475/- i.e., 10,47,42,475 Equity Shares of Rs. 1/- each.</p><ul><li>D L Millar &amp; Co Ltd, a promoter group company, acquired equity shares of Premier Polyfilm Ltd</li><li>0.09% stake was acquired through the open market</li><li>The transaction involved 95,450 equity shares</li><li>The acquisition took place on the Bombay Stock Exchange (BSE) and National Stock Exchange (NSE)</li><li>Premier Polyfilm Ltd&apos;s total equity share capital is Rs. 10,47,42,475/- i.e., 10,47,42,475 Equity Shares of Rs. 1/- each</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1EE87C2C_8AAF_48A0_9671_82B64434DFDC_100705.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PREMIER POLYFILM LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PREMIERPOL] Premier Polyfilm Ltd: D L Millar &amp; Co Ltd Acquires 0.09% Shares of Target Company</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PREMIER+POLYFILM+LTD.&title=Premier+Polyfilm+Ltd%3A+D+L+Millar+%26+Co+Ltd+Acquires+0.09%25+Shares+of+Target+Company&newsId=4dc7032c-efe3-4743-80ed-25548b911ced&token=NGRjNzAzMmMtZWZl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4dc7032c-efe3-4743-80ed-25548b911ced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:37:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>D L Millar &amp; Co Ltd, a promoter group company of Premier Polyfilm Limited, has acquired equity shares of Premier Polyfilm Limited through open market transactions. The acquisition of 95,450 shares represents 0.09% of the total shareholding of the target company.</p><ul><li>D L Millar &amp; Co Ltd, a promoter group company of Premier Polyfilm Limited, has acquired shares of the target company.</li><li>The acquisition represents 0.09% of the total shareholding of Premier Polyfilm Limited.</li><li>The shares were acquired through open market transactions.</li><li>The total number of shares held by D L Millar &amp; Co Ltd after the acquisition is 1,40,40,964.</li><li>The acquisition was made on 04-02-2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6B13E434_8DDE_4039_B424_5D4B665C73F6_100523.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PREMIER POLYFILM LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KPRMILL] SBI Mutual Fund Reduces Stake in K.P.R. Mill Limited by 2%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=K.P.R.+Mill+Limited&title=SBI+Mutual+Fund+Reduces+Stake+in+K.P.R.+Mill+Limited+by+2%25&newsId=138fbc7d-581b-4f12-907c-f79c4d09c01d&token=MTM4ZmJjN2QtNTgx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">138fbc7d-581b-4f12-907c-f79c4d09c01d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:33:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SBI Mutual Fund has sold (net) 3,89,978 shares representing 0.1141% of the paid-up share capital of K.P.R. Mill Limited. The final holding of SBI Mutual Fund, under its various schemes, as at the close of business hours on February 03, 2026, was 1,96,10,169 shares which is 5.7371% of the paid-up share capital of K.P.R. Mill Limited.</p><ul><li>SBI Mutual Fund has decreased its stake in K.P.R. Mill Limited by 2%.</li><li>The sale of shares represents 0.1141% of the paid-up share capital of K.P.R. Mill Limited.</li><li>The final holding of SBI Mutual Fund in K.P.R. Mill Limited is 5.7371%.</li><li>The transaction involved 3,89,978 shares worth Rs. 34,18,14,000.</li><li>The sale was made on the open market on February 03, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/E67115CC_E1D0_4F3A_B66C_08E37AFE0C8A_095944.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: K.P.R. Mill Limited | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[APIL] Neha Sujay Joshi Acquires Shares of Avi Products India Ltd Worth Rs. 3,30,68,020</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Avi+Products+India+Ltd&title=Neha+Sujay+Joshi+Acquires+Shares+of+Avi+Products+India+Ltd+Worth+Rs.+3%2C30%2C68%2C020&newsId=1afa90d1-342f-4127-9ea3-62a6eece9df5&token=MWFmYTkwZDEtMzQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1afa90d1-342f-4127-9ea3-62a6eece9df5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pursuant to Regulation 29(2) of the SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011, Neha Sujay Joshi has disclosed the sale of 52000 shares of face value Rs.10/- each of Avi Products India Ltd. The total value of the shares acquired is Rs. 3,30,68,020. The shares were acquired through an off-market transaction.</p><ul><li>Neha Sujay Joshi acquires shares worth Rs. 3,30,68,020 of Avi Products India Ltd.</li><li>The acquisition was made through an off-market transaction.</li><li>The shares acquired are 52000 in number, with a face value of Rs.10/- each.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/96F21A72_EE7D_4909_BADF_B34B810E6F6E_100205.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Avi Products India Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TREJHARA] Marvis Investments Ltd Acquires Shares in Trejhara Solutions Ltd via Scheme of Amalgamation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Trejhara+Solutions+Ltd&title=Marvis+Investments+Ltd+Acquires+Shares+in+Trejhara+Solutions+Ltd+via+Scheme+of+Amalgamation&newsId=ef8372f4-f49d-4c90-832b-58205511230d&token=ZWY4MzcyZjQtZjQ5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef8372f4-f49d-4c90-832b-58205511230d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Marvis Investments Ltd, along with Kairoleaf Holdings Pte. Ltd and Magnum Advisors Pte. Ltd, have acquired shares in Trejhara Solutions Ltd. The acquisition was made pursuant to a Scheme of Amalgamation between LP Logistics and Trejhara Solutions Ltd, approved by the Hon’ble National Company Law Tribunal, Mumbai bench. The acquirers are exempted from making an open offer under Regulation 10(1)(d)(i). The transaction details include the acquisition of shares from the Transferor Company by the Transferee Company. The acquirers hold a combined 23.59% of the diluted share capital of Trejhara Solutions Ltd post-transaction.</p><ul><li>Marvis Investments Ltd, Kairoleaf Holdings Pte. Ltd, and Magnum Advisors Pte. Ltd acquire shares in Trejhara Solutions Ltd</li><li>Acquisition made pursuant to a Scheme of Amalgamation between LP Logistics and Trejhara Solutions Ltd</li><li>Acquirers exempted from making an open offer under Regulation 10(1)(d)(i)</li><li>Combined 23.59% of the diluted share capital of Trejhara Solutions Ltd held by the acquirers post-transaction</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3A1F9FFE_47BF_423B_8039_16371D05B7EA_094654.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Trejhara Solutions Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AANCHALISP] Mukesh Goel, Promoter of Aanchal Ispat Ltd, Sells Shares Worth 75.00% of Total Voting Capital</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Aanchal+Ispat+Ltd&title=Mukesh+Goel%2C+Promoter+of+Aanchal+Ispat+Ltd%2C+Sells+Shares+Worth+75.00%25+of+Total+Voting+Capital&newsId=23a5b48f-6b21-4e93-aa3c-18d4f9841f60&token=MjNhNWI0OGYtNmIy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23a5b48f-6b21-4e93-aa3c-18d4f9841f60</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mukesh Goel, a promoter of Aanchal Ispat Ltd, has sold shares carrying voting rights through an Offer for Sale conducted on February 03, 2026 and February 04, 2026. The sale resulted in a total acquisition of 21,24,998 shares, which is 75.00% of the total voting capital and 75.00% of the total diluted capital of the company. The shares were sold in two categories: equity shares and warrants/convertible securities. The sale did not involve any encumbered shares or voting rights otherwise than by shares. After the sale, Mukesh Goel&apos;s holding in Aanchal Ispat Ltd includes 75.00% of the shares carrying voting rights, no encumbered shares, and no voting rights otherwise than by shares. The mode of sale was an Offer for Sale.</p><ul><li>Mukesh Goel, a promoter of Aanchal Ispat Ltd, sold shares carrying voting rights.</li><li>The sale resulted in a total acquisition of 21,24,998 shares, which is 75.00% of the total voting capital and 75.00% of the total diluted capital of the company.</li><li>The sale did not involve any encumbered shares or voting rights otherwise than by shares.</li><li>After the sale, Mukesh Goel&apos;s holding in Aanchal Ispat Ltd includes 75.00% of the shares carrying voting rights, no encumbered shares, and no voting rights otherwise than by shares.</li><li>The mode of sale was an Offer for Sale.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1E9439A3_C5C0_4CA8_B932_7F47D583CA9C_094926.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Aanchal Ispat Ltd | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KASTURI] Rajasthan Global Securities Pvt Ltd Sells Shares of Kasturi Metal Composite Ltd on Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kasturi+Metal+Composite+Ltd&title=Rajasthan+Global+Securities+Pvt+Ltd+Sells+Shares+of+Kasturi+Metal+Composite+Ltd+on+Open+Market&newsId=2aa0c32e-273d-4db8-8716-a5e4e0ef0b2a&token=MmFhMGMzMmUtMjcz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2aa0c32e-273d-4db8-8716-a5e4e0ef0b2a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rajasthan Global Securities Pvt Ltd has sold a total of 7,84,000 shares and 3,92,000 warrants/convertible securities of Kasturi Metal Composite Ltd on the open market. This disposal represents 3.77% of the total voting capital of the company. The total equity share capital of Kasturi Metal Composite Ltd remains at 1,03,95,212 shares of Rs. 10 each, both before and after the sale. The disposal was made on 3rd February 2026.</p><ul><li>Rajasthan Global Securities Pvt Ltd sells shares and warrants/convertible securities of Kasturi Metal Composite Ltd</li><li>The sale represents 3.77% of the total voting capital of Kasturi Metal Composite Ltd</li><li>The sale was made on the open market</li><li>The sale was made on 3rd February 2026</li><li>The total equity share capital of Kasturi Metal Composite Ltd remains unchanged at 1,03,95,212 shares of Rs. 10 each</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1E8C3E85_9E55_4B18_B39D_2C2BBAFF9123_094527.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kasturi Metal Composite Ltd | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>