<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 04:07:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SATIN] Satin Creditcare Network Achieves Score of 59 in S&amp;P Global Corporate Sustainability Assessment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Satin+Creditcare+Network+Ltd&title=Satin+Creditcare+Network+Achieves+Score+of+59+in+S%26P+Global+Corporate+Sustainability+Assessment&newsId=7c6ee208-fb4a-43bf-b9f9-c9ee150a1666&token=N2M2ZWUyMDgtZmI0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c6ee208-fb4a-43bf-b9f9-c9ee150a1666</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 03:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Satin Creditcare Network Limited, a leading microfinance institution in India, has achieved a score of 59 in its first-ever S&amp;P Global Corporate Sustainability Assessment. This outcome marks an important milestone in the Company’s sustainability journey and reflects the maturity of its governance, risk and people centric management systems. The S&amp;P Global CSA evaluates companies across a comprehensive range of Environmental, Social and Governance (ESG) parameters, and for SATIN, Human Capital Management, Risk &amp; Crisis Management and Business Ethics emerged as the most material contributors to the Company’s overall score. This achievement reinforces SATIN’s commitment to long-term, stakeholder-centric value creation, positioning the Company as a credible and forward-looking institution in India’s evolving ESG and sustainable finance landscape.</p><ul><li>Satin Creditcare Network achieved a score of 59 in its first-ever S&amp;P Global Corporate Sustainability Assessment</li><li>The assessment evaluated the Company&apos;s performance across a comprehensive range of Environmental, Social and Governance (ESG) parameters</li><li>Human Capital Management, Risk &amp; Crisis Management and Business Ethics were the most material contributors to the Company’s overall score</li><li>This achievement reinforces SATIN’s commitment to long-term, stakeholder-centric value creation</li><li>Satin Creditcare Network is positioned as a credible and forward-looking institution in India’s evolving ESG and sustainable finance landscape</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/be6492c8-8177-4e08-8249-1935e5901219.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Satin Creditcare Network Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JBCHEPHARM] Torrent Pharmaceuticals Acquires 7.44 Million Shares of JB Chemicals &amp; Pharmaceuticals</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=J.B.CHEMICALS+%26+PHARMACEUTICALS+LTD.&title=Torrent+Pharmaceuticals+Acquires+7.44+Million+Shares+of+JB+Chemicals+%26+Pharmaceuticals&newsId=51a2a4b3-2c22-46aa-a4f0-d0ac8b0d6f82&token=NTFhMmE0YjMtMmMy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">51a2a4b3-2c22-46aa-a4f0-d0ac8b0d6f82</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 03:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Torrent Pharmaceuticals Limited has acquired 7,44,81,519 equity shares of JB Chemicals &amp; Pharmaceuticals Limited from Tau Investment Holdings Pte. Ltd. This acquisition was made pursuant to a share purchase agreement dated June 29, 2025, and it includes 1,317 equity shares acquired on December 5, 2025, as part of an open offer. The total equity shares of JB Chemicals &amp; Pharmaceuticals Limited now held by Torrent Pharmaceuticals Limited amount to 47.55% of the total voting capital.</p><ul><li>Torrent Pharmaceuticals has acquired 7,44,81,519 equity shares of JB Chemicals &amp; Pharmaceuticals from Tau Investment Holdings Pte. Ltd.</li><li>The acquisition was made pursuant to a share purchase agreement dated June 29, 2025.</li><li>This acquisition includes 1,317 equity shares acquired on December 5, 2025, as part of an open offer.</li><li>Torrent Pharmaceuticals now holds 47.55% of the total voting capital of JB Chemicals &amp; Pharmaceuticals Limited.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/016FF41C_D21A_4BC2_B08D_CDAD6E292E8E_082828.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: J.B.CHEMICALS & PHARMACEUTICALS LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MEGASOFT] Chintalapati Holdings Pvt Ltd Acquires Major Stake in Sigma Advanced Systems Limited Through Amalgamation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MEGASOFT+LTD.&title=Chintalapati+Holdings+Pvt+Ltd+Acquires+Major+Stake+in+Sigma+Advanced+Systems+Limited+Through+Amalgamation&newsId=e4926e1c-615d-4cf3-a5f3-c31e35ca6b22&token=ZTQ5MjZlMWMtNjE1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e4926e1c-615d-4cf3-a5f3-c31e35ca6b22</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 03:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Chintalapati Holdings Pvt Ltd has acquired a significant stake in Sigma Advanced Systems Limited through the amalgamation of Sigma Advanced Systems Private Limited. The Hon’ble NCLT, Chennai approved the amalgamation on 16th December 2025. Post-amalgamation, Chintalapati Holdings Pvt Ltd has been allotted 8,16,17,788 Equity Shares in Sigma Advanced Systems Limited. This acquisition significantly changes the equity share capital and total voting capital of the company.</p><ul><li>Chintalapati Holdings Pvt Ltd has acquired a significant stake in Sigma Advanced Systems Limited through amalgamation.</li><li>The acquisition was approved by the Hon’ble NCLT, Chennai on 16th December 2025.</li><li>Chintalapati Holdings Pvt Ltd has been allotted 8,16,17,788 Equity Shares in Sigma Advanced Systems Limited.</li><li>This acquisition significantly changes the equity share capital and total voting capital of the company.</li><li>The amalgamation of Sigma Advanced Systems Private Limited into and with Megasoft Limited (Now, Sigma Advanced Systems Limited) was the mode of acquisition.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2F6C6ED0_752A_40FD_9B83_94BBEF54A552_083210.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MEGASOFT LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JBCHEPHARM] Tau Investment Holdings Sells Entire Stake in JB Chemicals &amp; Pharmaceuticals to Torrent Pharmaceuticals</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=J.B.CHEMICALS+%26+PHARMACEUTICALS+LTD.&title=Tau+Investment+Holdings+Sells+Entire+Stake+in+JB+Chemicals+%26+Pharmaceuticals+to+Torrent+Pharmaceuticals&newsId=471a52a1-5c3e-4d87-a6d4-f88db983093d&token=NDcxYTUyYTEtNWMz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">471a52a1-5c3e-4d87-a6d4-f88db983093d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 03:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tau Investment Holdings Pte Ltd has sold its entire stake in JB Chemicals &amp; Pharmaceuticals Ltd to Torrent Pharmaceuticals Limited. The sale, which took place on 21st January 2026, was carried out in accordance with a Share Purchase Agreement (SPA) dated 29th June 2025. Post-transaction, Tau Investment Holdings has been reclassified from the &apos;promoter&apos; category to the &apos;public&apos; category. The transaction marks Torrent Pharmaceuticals&apos; acquisition of control over JB Chemicals &amp; Pharmaceuticals.</p><ul><li>Tau Investment Holdings sells entire stake in JB Chemicals &amp; Pharmaceuticals to Torrent Pharmaceuticals</li><li>Sale carried out in accordance with a Share Purchase Agreement (SPA) dated 29th June 2025</li><li>Tau Investment Holdings reclassified from &apos;promoter&apos; category to &apos;public&apos; category post-transaction</li><li>Torrent Pharmaceuticals acquires control over JB Chemicals &amp; Pharmaceuticals</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/94755156_7831_4320_9ABB_6537AC97CEF8_082622.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: J.B.CHEMICALS & PHARMACEUTICALS LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VGUARD] ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund Increases Shareholding in V-Guard Industries Ltd by 2.03%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=V-GUARD+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=ICICI+Prudential+Mutual+Fund+Increases+Shareholding+in+V-Guard+Industries+Ltd+by+2.03%25&newsId=fbf07c10-aa97-4677-a24b-f1e119ffb1dd&token=ZmJmMDdjMTAtYWE5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fbf07c10-aa97-4677-a24b-f1e119ffb1dd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 02:59:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund has carried out net acquisition of 1,52,059 shares of V-Guard Industries Ltd on January 19, 2026, leading to an increase in their shareholding by more than 2% as compared to their previous disclosure. The Fund under its schemes has acquired a total of 88,84,696 shares of the company from the last filing submitted on October 23, 2025. The holding by schemes of the Fund is from an investment perspective and not with the objective of seeking any controlling interest.</p><ul><li>ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund increases shareholding in V-Guard Industries Ltd by 2.03%</li><li>Net acquisition of 1,52,059 shares on January 19, 2026</li><li>Total acquisition of 88,84,696 shares from the last filing</li><li>Acquisition is for investment purposes, not for controlling interest</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/A36251DC_9735_49F0_8AA9_AA9EC8BA7E0C_082125.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: V-GUARD INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KFINTECH] Wasatch Advisors LP Acquires 0.128% Stake in KFin Technologies Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KFin+Technologies+Ltd&title=Wasatch+Advisors+LP+Acquires+0.128%25+Stake+in+KFin+Technologies+Ltd&newsId=77fa2b2b-51c8-4d9d-abc1-90aaab017869&token=NzdmYTJiMmItNTFj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77fa2b2b-51c8-4d9d-abc1-90aaab017869</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 02:56:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Wasatch Advisors LP, a U.S.-based investment firm, has acquired 220,783 shares carrying voting rights in KFin Technologies Ltd, according to a disclosure under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. This represents 0.128% of the total voting rights in the company. The acquisition was made on January 20, 2026, through open market purchase.</p><ul><li>Wasatch Advisors LP acquires 0.128% stake in KFin Technologies Ltd</li><li>Acquisition made through open market purchase</li><li>220,783 shares carrying voting rights acquired</li><li>Transaction value not disclosed in the document</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/F62EACB3_3E7E_4472_898C_4C7C05262DE9_082415.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KFin Technologies Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SWOEF] Rajesh Nanubhai Jhaveri Acquires 6.05% Stake in Swojas Foods Ltd Through Warrant Conversion</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SWOJAS+ENERGY+FOODS+LTD.&title=Rajesh+Nanubhai+Jhaveri+Acquires+6.05%25+Stake+in+Swojas+Foods+Ltd+Through+Warrant+Conversion&newsId=126e40d3-6852-4f6f-b1e4-cbeac40b42b2&token=MTI2ZTQwZDMtNjg1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">126e40d3-6852-4f6f-b1e4-cbeac40b42b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 02:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>According to a disclosure made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011, Rajesh Nanubhai Jhaveri has acquired 20,00,000 equity shares of Swojas Foods Ltd, formerly known as Swojas Energy Foods Limited, through the conversion of warrants. This acquisition represents 6.05% of the total share and voting capital of the company. The warrants were allotted on 21st January 2026. Prior to this acquisition, Rajesh Nanubhai Jhaveri held 33,21,000 shares, which included encumbrances. Post-acquisition, his holding stands at 20,00,000 shares, 13,21,000 warrants, and no encumbrances, representing a total of 5,69,47,150 equity shares or 33.58% of the total diluted share and voting capital.</p><ul><li>Rajesh Nanubhai Jhaveri acquires 6.05% stake in Swojas Foods Ltd through warrant conversion.</li><li>Acquisition made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</li><li>20,00,000 equity shares acquired at a price of Rs. 10/- each.</li><li>Post-acquisition, Rajesh Nanubhai Jhaveri holds 20,00,000 shares, 13,21,000 warrants, and no encumbrances.</li><li>Acquisition increases Rajesh Nanubhai Jhaveri&apos;s holding to 33.58% of the total diluted share and voting capital.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3B0E3FAD_9ADB_44D8_961E_C82EAFD16896_082014.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SWOJAS ENERGY FOODS LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EVANS] Counter Cyclical Investments Pvt Ltd Acquires 0.16% Additional Shares in Evans Electric Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Evans+Electric+Ltd&title=Counter+Cyclical+Investments+Pvt+Ltd+Acquires+0.16%25+Additional+Shares+in+Evans+Electric+Ltd&newsId=6b0fcd7d-a139-4c96-ab69-66b8146bb3a3&token=NmIwZmNkN2QtYTEz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6b0fcd7d-a139-4c96-ab69-66b8146bb3a3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 02:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Counter Cyclical Investments Pvt Ltd, a Portfolio Manager and Acquirer, has acquired 9,000 shares in Evans Electric Ltd, amounting to 0.16% of the total paid-up share capital. This acquisition increased their total shareholding, along with persons acting in concert, to 5.16%. The acquisition was made through the open market on 19th January 2026.</p><ul><li>Counter Cyclical Investments Pvt Ltd acquired 9,000 shares in Evans Electric Ltd</li><li>The acquisition increased their total shareholding to 5.16%</li><li>The acquisition was made through the open market</li><li>The acquisition happened on 19th January 2026</li><li>Evans Electric Ltd share capital details: 5,488,000 shares after the acquisition</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/559C8B95_810C_4AE6_B1D7_ED621F0CEAC5_081344.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Evans Electric Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DAVANGERE] Arihant Capital Markets Acquires 4.91% Stake in Davangere Sugar Company via Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Davangere+Sugar+Company+Ltd&title=Arihant+Capital+Markets+Acquires+4.91%25+Stake+in+Davangere+Sugar+Company+via+Open+Market&newsId=e2441c69-6637-4109-ade0-375983fcf3fc&token=ZTI0NDFjNjktNjYz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e2441c69-6637-4109-ade0-375983fcf3fc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 02:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Arihant Capital Markets Ltd has acquired a 4.91% stake in Davangere Sugar Company Ltd through the open market. The acquisition was made on 20th January 2026. Arihant Capital Markets Ltd purchased 70,182,674 shares carrying voting rights and 10,588,445 voting rights (VR) otherwise than by shares. The total holding of Arihant Capital Markets Ltd along with PACs before the acquisition was 4.91% and after the acquisition, it increased to 5.65%.</p><ul><li>Arihant Capital Markets Ltd acquires 4.91% stake in Davangere Sugar Company Ltd</li><li>Acquisition made through open market</li><li>70,182,674 shares carrying voting rights acquired</li><li>10,588,445 voting rights (VR) otherwise than by shares acquired</li><li>Post-acquisition holding increases to 5.65%</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/AFABDA0F_AD28_4108_9968_C395B5A99B6C_081904.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Davangere Sugar Company Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GLITTEKG] Acquirers Submit Draft Letter of Offer to Public Shareholders of Glittek Granites Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GLITTEK+GRANITES+LTD.&title=Acquirers+Submit+Draft+Letter+of+Offer+to+Public+Shareholders+of+Glittek+Granites+Ltd&newsId=55f0341f-8efe-40c5-bb53-05b622b5acc0&token=NTVmMDM0MWYtOGVm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55f0341f-8efe-40c5-bb53-05b622b5acc0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 02:47:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Open Offer</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vivro Financial Services Pvt. Ltd, on behalf of the acquirers, has submitted a draft letter of offer to the public shareholders of Glittek Granites Ltd. The acquirers, Maheshkumar Jatashankar Thanki, Bhargav Girjashankar Thanki, Bhavin Harihar Thanki, Kalpana Ashwinkumar Thanki, Hema Bhargay Thanki, and Gautam Aahwinkumar Thanki, along with Rawmin Mining And Industries Private Limited, aim to acquire up to 67,50,000 fully paid-up equity shares of the company, representing 26% of the equity share capital. The offer price is set at Rs. 12.65 per equity share, payable in cash. The offer is not conditional upon any minimum level of acceptance and is not a competing offer. The offer opens on Wednesday, March 4, 2026, and closes on Tuesday, March 17, 2026.</p><ul><li>Acquirers submit draft letter of offer to public shareholders of Glittek Granites Ltd</li><li>Offer to acquire up to 67,50,000 equity shares representing 26% of the company&apos;s equity share capital</li><li>Offer price set at Rs. 12.65 per equity share, payable in cash</li><li>Not conditional upon any minimum level of acceptance</li><li>Offer opens on Wednesday, March 4, 2026, and closes on Tuesday, March 17, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9883B7F4-D103-4073-A51D-E2A075394EF6-081617.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GLITTEK GRANITES LTD. | Category: Open Offer</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>