<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:48:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[INERTIAST] Banganga Paper Industries Ltd. Acquires 78.90% Stake in CMJ Breweries Private Limited for Rs. 2190.44 Lacs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INERTIA+STEEL+LTD.&title=Banganga+Paper+Industries+Ltd.+Acquires+78.90%25+Stake+in+CMJ+Breweries+Private+Limited+for+Rs.+2190.44+Lacs&newsId=0111960f-ec5f-4776-b595-d134de65e090&token=MDExMTk2MGYtZWM1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0111960f-ec5f-4776-b595-d134de65e090</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:46:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Banganga Paper Industries Ltd., now known as Asgard Alcobev Limited, has acquired a 78.90% stake in CMJ Breweries Private Limited. The transaction was completed through a share swap, with the company issuing and allotting up to 15,10,64,917 equity shares of Re. 1/- each at an issue price of Rs. 1.45/- per share, amounting to Rs. 2190.44 Lacs. CMJ Breweries is a leading business group based in Meghalaya, with a strong presence in the alcoholic beverages industry and a modern, high-capacity brewing facility. The acquisition is strategically aimed at diversification and long-term value creation, providing benefits such as business diversification, improved risk management, and entry into a sector with steady demand and long-term growth potential.</p><ul><li>Banganga Paper Industries Ltd. has acquired a 78.90% stake in CMJ Breweries Private Limited.</li><li>The transaction was completed through a share swap, with the company issuing and allotting up to 15,10,64,917 equity shares.</li><li>CMJ Breweries is a leading business group based in Meghalaya, with a strong presence in the alcoholic beverages industry.</li><li>The acquisition is strategically aimed at diversification and long-term value creation.</li><li>The transaction amounted to Rs. 2190.44 Lacs.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b6086b3a-9939-4bf6-b7af-3aa16e2a75a0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INERTIA STEEL LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EMAINDIA] EMA India Ltd Seeks Reclassification of Promoters under SEBI Regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=EMA+INDIA+LTD.&title=EMA+India+Ltd+Seeks+Reclassification+of+Promoters+under+SEBI+Regulations&newsId=ce0941bb-833e-49aa-8931-b3423ff7cdc4&token=Y2UwOTQxYmItODMz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce0941bb-833e-49aa-8931-b3423ff7cdc4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:44:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Reclassification of Shareholding</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>EMA India Ltd has applied to BSE Limited for the reclassification of its promoters from the &apos;Promoter/ Promoter Group&apos; category to the &apos;Public&apos; category. The Board of Directors has approved the request of members of the Promoter/ Promoter Group for reclassification from &apos;Promoter Group Shareholder&apos; to &apos;Public Shareholder&apos; under Regulation 31A of the SEBI (Listing Obligation &amp; Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The reclassification includes members such as Ranjana Bhargava, Rakshita Bhargava, Diatech Tools India Pvt Ltd, and Pradip Kumar Bhargava HUF. The decision is subject to the approval of BSE Limited.</p><ul><li>EMA India Ltd applies for reclassification of promoters</li><li>Board of Directors approves reclassification request</li><li>Reclassification from &apos;Promoter/ Promoter Group&apos; to &apos;Public&apos; category</li><li>Includes members like Ranjana Bhargava, Rakshita Bhargava, Diatech Tools India Pvt Ltd, and Pradip Kumar Bhargava HUF</li><li>Subject to approval from BSE Limited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7969e40d-4713-423a-a731-6de09bd1cae9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: EMA INDIA LTD. | Category: Reclassification of Shareholding</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INERTIAST] Asgard Alcobev Acquires 78.90% Stake in CMJ Breweries for Rs. 2190.44 Lacs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INERTIA+STEEL+LTD.&title=Asgard+Alcobev+Acquires+78.90%25+Stake+in+CMJ+Breweries+for+Rs.+2190.44+Lacs&newsId=de600796-db99-469a-9d22-e3343d5fcbef&token=ZGU2MDA3OTYtZGI5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de600796-db99-469a-9d22-e3343d5fcbef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Asgard Alcobev Limited (Formerly known as Banganga Paper Industries Limited) has acquired 78.90% equity stake in CMJ Breweries Private Limited. The transaction was done through a share swap of 15,10,64,917 equity shares of Re. 1/- each at an issue price of Rs. 1.45/- each. CMJ Breweries is a leading business group based in Meghalaya with a strong presence in the alcoholic beverages industry.</p><ul><li>Asgard Alcobev Limited has acquired 78.90% equity stake in CMJ Breweries Private Limited</li><li>The transaction was done through a share swap of 15,10,64,917 equity shares of Re. 1/- each at an issue price of Rs. 1.45/- each</li><li>CMJ Breweries is a leading business group based in Meghalaya with a strong presence in the alcoholic beverages industry</li><li>The acquisition is strategically aimed at diversification and long-term value creation</li><li>The transaction supports Asgard Alcobev’s vision of evolving into a diversified business group</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8f1ae649-1720-4887-b412-970854c49984.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INERTIA STEEL LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAATVIKGL] Saatvik Green Energy&apos;s Subsidiary Receives Order Worth INR 44.10 Crores from Renowned IPP/EPC Player</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Saatvik+Green+Energy+Ltd&title=Saatvik+Green+Energy%27s+Subsidiary+Receives+Order+Worth+INR+44.10+Crores+from+Renowned+IPP%2FEPC+Player&newsId=f7a6ce56-d417-41d6-bbdc-b021f540cc14&token=ZjdhNmNlNTYtZDQx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7a6ce56-d417-41d6-bbdc-b021f540cc14</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:41:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Saatvik Green Energy Ltd announced that its material subsidiary, Saatvik Solar Industries Private Limited, has received and accepted an order aggregating to INR 44.10 Crores from a renowned Independent Power producer/EPC Player for the supply of solar PV modules. The order is expected to be executed by March 2026.</p><ul><li>Saatvik Solar Industries Private Limited received an order worth INR 44.10 Crores from a renowned IPP/EPC Player.</li><li>The order is for the supply of solar PV modules.</li><li>The order is expected to be executed by March 2026.</li><li>Saatvik Green Energy Ltd is a Saatvik Group Company.</li><li>The order details are provided in Annexure A of the official letter.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0ee78705-2e8e-48b1-9d86-46708616f783.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Saatvik Green Energy Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INERTIAST] Asgard Alcobev Acquires 78.90% Stake in CMJ Breweries for Rs. 2190.44 Lacs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INERTIA+STEEL+LTD.&title=Asgard+Alcobev+Acquires+78.90%25+Stake+in+CMJ+Breweries+for+Rs.+2190.44+Lacs&newsId=e3e35838-f631-4ce8-9b12-defad01ae566&token=ZTNlMzU4MzgtZjYz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3e35838-f631-4ce8-9b12-defad01ae566</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Asgard Alcobev Limited (Formerly known as Banganga Paper Industries Limited) has acquired a 78.90% stake in CMJ Breweries Private Limited. The acquisition was done through the issuance and allotment of up to 15,10,64,917 equity shares of Re. 1/- each of the Company at an issue price of Rs. 1.45/- per share, amounting to Rs. 2190.44/- Lacs. CMJ Breweries is a leading business group based in Meghalaya, dedicated to the production of beer and operating a modern, high-capacity brewing facility. The acquisition is strategically aimed at diversification and long-term value creation.</p><ul><li>Asgard Alcobev Limited has acquired a 78.90% stake in CMJ Breweries Private Limited.</li><li>The acquisition was done through the issuance and allotment of equity shares worth Rs. 2190.44/- Lacs.</li><li>CMJ Breweries is a leading business group based in Meghalaya, dedicated to the production of beer.</li><li>The acquisition is strategically aimed at diversification and long-term value creation.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b91ded1b-2a91-43d4-96d3-4bedd2211f87.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INERTIA STEEL LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BCG] Brightcom Group Ltd to Host Shareholder Conference Call on 21st February 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Brightcom+Group+Ltd&title=Brightcom+Group+Ltd+to+Host+Shareholder+Conference+Call+on+21st+February+2026&newsId=b2fd4721-fecf-4c65-8381-fed6852210dd&token=YjJmZDQ3MjEtZmVj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b2fd4721-fecf-4c65-8381-fed6852210dd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:41:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Brightcom Group Ltd has announced a Shareholder Conference Call on Saturday, 21st February 2026, to discuss the Unaudited Financial Results for the Quarter ended 31st December 2025 and to provide business updates. The conference call will be hosted on the Company’s website closer to the date. Senior management will address the financial performance and operational developments, followed by an interactive session with the shareholders.</p><ul><li>Brightcom Group Ltd to host a Shareholder Conference Call on 21st February 2026</li><li>The call is to discuss the Unaudited Financial Results for the Quarter ended 31st December 2025</li><li>The conference call will be hosted on the Company’s website closer to the date</li><li>Senior management will address the financial performance and operational developments</li><li>An interactive session with the shareholders will follow the discussion</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c5b93320-fc1b-4638-81ea-76d2ea57cdb2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Brightcom Group Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VALECHAENG] Valecha Engineering Ltd. Approves Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended 31.12.2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Valecha+Engineering+Ltd-%24&title=Valecha+Engineering+Ltd.+Approves+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+31.12.2025&newsId=12b8b128-71bf-4d36-8322-0abbd94f0e2d&token=MTJiOGIxMjgtNzFi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12b8b128-71bf-4d36-8322-0abbd94f0e2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Valecha Engineering Ltd. has approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31.12.2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 13.31 crores for the quarter and 31.55 crores for the nine months ended period. The total income for the quarter is 44.86 crores and 52.70 crores for the nine months ended period. The company&apos;s net profit attributable to shareholders for the quarter is 11.19 crores and 437.37 crores for the nine months ended period. The EPS for the quarter is (0.26) and 4.97 for the nine months ended period.</p><ul><li>Valecha Engineering Ltd. has approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31.12.2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 13.31 crores for the quarter and 31.55 crores for the nine months ended period.</li><li>The total income for the quarter is 44.86 crores and 52.70 crores for the nine months ended period.</li><li>The company&apos;s net profit attributable to shareholders for the quarter is 11.19 crores and 437.37 crores for the nine months ended period.</li><li>The EPS for the quarter is (0.26) and 4.97 for the nine months ended period.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d68e75ec-9d5b-47cd-a7d3-345b2613242e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Valecha Engineering Ltd-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SPANDANA] Spandana Sphoorty Financial Ltd Appoints Avinash Yadav as Chief Information Officer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Spandana+Sphoorty+Financial+Ltd&title=Spandana+Sphoorty+Financial+Ltd+Appoints+Avinash+Yadav+as+Chief+Information+Officer&newsId=d19875e6-3018-4849-89be-044638591921&token=ZDE5ODc1ZTYtMzAx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d19875e6-3018-4849-89be-044638591921</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Spandana Sphoorty Financial Ltd has approved the appointment of Mr. Avinash Yadav as the Chief Information Officer of the Company. Mr. Yadav is a visionary technology leader with expertise in leading high impact technology projects, AI/ML models, technical operations and IT governance. He has been awarded as top 50 tech leaders in NBFC by ET-Edge and as best CTO/CIO of the year 2025 by UBS Forums. His appointment will be effective from February 17, 2026. Mr. Yadav is not related to any Director on the Board of the Company.</p><ul><li>Spandana Sphoorty Financial Ltd has appointed Mr. Avinash Yadav as the Chief Information Officer</li><li>Mr. Yadav is a visionary technology leader with expertise in leading high impact technology projects, AI/ML models, technical operations and IT governance</li><li>He has been awarded as top 50 tech leaders in NBFC by ET-Edge and as best CTO/CIO of the year 2025 by UBS Forums</li><li>His appointment will be effective from February 17, 2026</li><li>Mr. Yadav is not related to any Director on the Board of the Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/01d87c6e-e595-4087-b24b-e3aa8c9703c6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Spandana Sphoorty Financial Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CEINSYSTECH] Ceinsys Tech Ltd Receives Listing Approval from National Stock Exchange of India Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ceinsys+Tech+Ltd&title=Ceinsys+Tech+Ltd+Receives+Listing+Approval+from+National+Stock+Exchange+of+India+Limited&newsId=3b7efd0e-d124-452d-a3e2-0de4e1282c54&token=M2I3ZWZkMGUtZDEy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b7efd0e-d124-452d-a3e2-0de4e1282c54</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ceinsys Tech Ltd has announced that it has received approval for listing its Equity Shares on the National Stock Exchange of India Limited (NSE). The approval is for the listing of 1,78,41,146 Equity Shares with a face value of Rs. 10/- each. The shares will be listed and admitted to dealings on NSE under the Symbol &apos;CEINSYS&apos; from February 19, 2026. The company is requested to submit all important information and filings through &apos;NEAPS&apos; — NSE Electronic Application Processing System.</p><ul><li>Ceinsys Tech Ltd receives listing approval from NSE</li><li>1,78,41,146 Equity Shares of Rs. 10/- each to be listed</li><li>Listing and dealings to commence from February 19, 2026</li><li>Symbol for the shares is &apos;CEINSYS&apos;</li><li>Company to submit all filings through &apos;NEAPS&apos; portal</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dbc060cc-944d-43d7-99fe-9a6bbb377f03.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ceinsys Tech Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CERA] Cera Sanitaryware Ltd Announces Exercise of Stock Options under ESOS 2024</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CERA+SANITARYWARE+LTD.&title=Cera+Sanitaryware+Ltd+Announces+Exercise+of+Stock+Options+under+ESOS+2024&newsId=c8636ccb-e65d-4bff-845a-3dfef75d2990&token=Yzg2MzZjY2ItZTY1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c8636ccb-e65d-4bff-845a-3dfef75d2990</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 15:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>ESOP</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cera Sanitaryware Ltd has announced the exercise of stock options under the Cera Sanitaryware - Employee Stock Option Scheme 2024 (ESOS 2024). Eligible employees have exercised their rights to 170 options granted on 5th June 2024 and vested on 5th June 2025. The CERA Sanitaryware Employees Welfare Trust is in process of transferring equity shares to the option grantee. The exercise of options will not result in any change in the paid-up equity share capital of the Company as the shares have been sourced from the secondary market.</p><ul><li>170 options exercised under ESOS 2024</li><li>Options granted on 5th June 2024 and vested on 5th June 2025</li><li>Shares sourced from the secondary market</li><li>No change in the paid-up equity share capital of the Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dad90648-cc83-460e-9a15-ce2a7bf06abe.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CERA SANITARYWARE LTD. | Category: ESOP</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>