<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:55:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ADCINDIA] ADC India Communications Ltd: Resignation of Two Directors Following Amphenol Corporation&apos;s Acquisition of CCS Business</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADC+India+Communications+Limited-%24&title=ADC+India+Communications+Ltd%3A+Resignation+of+Two+Directors+Following+Amphenol+Corporation%27s+Acquisition+of+CCS+Business&newsId=e8f82c86-b398-4a80-8dc3-7c4d3d71e854&token=ZThmODJjODYtYjM5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e8f82c86-b398-4a80-8dc3-7c4d3d71e854</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:52:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>ADC India Communications Ltd announced the resignation of two non-executive non-independent directors, Mr. Rakesh Kishore Bhanushali and Mr. Jonathan Niall Murphy, with effect from the conclusion of the board meeting held on 10th February 2026. The resignations were a consequence of Amphenol Corporation&apos;s acquisition of the CCS business from Vistance Networks, Inc., which required the directors to step down from the board.</p><ul><li>ADC India Communications Ltd announced the resignation of two directors, Mr. Rakesh Kishore Bhanushali and Mr. Jonathan Niall Murphy.</li><li>The resignations were a consequence of Amphenol Corporation&apos;s acquisition of the CCS business from Vistance Networks, Inc.</li><li>Mr. Rakesh Kishore Bhanushali and Mr. Jonathan Niall Murphy were non-executive non-independent directors of the company.</li><li>The resignations took effect from the conclusion of the board meeting held on 10th February 2026.</li><li>Amphenol Corporation had completed the acquisition of the CCS business from Vistance Networks, Inc. on 9th January 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cc8e0450-698f-479e-ae84-740971c81061.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADC India Communications Limited-$ | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HINDUNILVR] Hindustan Unilever Ltd Approves Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HINDUSTAN+UNILEVER+LTD.&title=Hindustan+Unilever+Ltd+Approves+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025&newsId=70d54ed8-2922-4b94-ad7f-1e2f567e60ad&token=NzBkNTRlZDgtMjky</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70d54ed8-2922-4b94-ad7f-1e2f567e60ad</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hindustan Unilever Ltd has approved the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at Rs. 16,197 crores for the quarter and Rs. 47,464 crores for the nine months period. The profit before tax for the quarter is Rs. 10,370 crores and Rs. 14,081 crores for the nine months period. The company also reported a profit for the period from continuing operations at Rs. 7,650 crores for the quarter and Rs. 10,680 crores for the nine months period.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter is Rs. 16,197 crores</li><li>Profit before tax for the quarter is Rs. 10,370 crores</li><li>Profit for the period from continuing operations is Rs. 7,650 crores for the quarter</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/65359d81-bc70-4424-9a65-811a998b5e4a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HINDUSTAN UNILEVER LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASHOKLEY] Ashok Leyland Ltd Clarifies Position on Recent Speculations and Share Price Fluctuations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ASHOK+LEYLAND+LTD.&title=Ashok+Leyland+Ltd+Clarifies+Position+on+Recent+Speculations+and+Share+Price+Fluctuations&newsId=d3931a3d-ac8d-4fd5-a165-c57b4d7ad212&token=ZDM5MzFhM2QtYWM4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3931a3d-ac8d-4fd5-a165-c57b4d7ad212</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:43:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In response to a recent news article in Economic Times dated February 11, 2026, Ashok Leyland Ltd has clarified that it does not respond to speculations. The company also stated that there is no connection between the share price change during the day and this speculation. The company promptly discloses any material information as required by regulatory authorities and will continue to do so in the future.</p><ul><li>Ashok Leyland Ltd does not respond to speculations</li><li>There is no connection between the share price change and the speculation</li><li>Company promptly discloses material information as required by regulatory authorities</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0c8913e6-a07d-491d-9c7e-4a749475a783.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ASHOK LEYLAND LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZAGGLE] Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd Enters Agreement with Rebel Foods Private Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Zaggle+Prepaid+Ocean+Services+Ltd&title=Zaggle+Prepaid+Ocean+Services+Ltd+Enters+Agreement+with+Rebel+Foods+Private+Limited&newsId=38fbd788-6ac3-4f98-b226-955cb1413d83&token=MzhmYmQ3ODgtNmFj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">38fbd788-6ac3-4f98-b226-955cb1413d83</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Limited has entered into an agreement with Rebel Foods Private Limited. Zaggle will provide the Zaggle Zoyer Platform to Rebel Foods Private Limited. The agreement does not involve any related party transactions. The consideration or size of the order is not specified in the document.</p><ul><li>Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd has entered into an agreement with Rebel Foods Private Limited</li><li>Zaggle will provide the Zaggle Zoyer Platform to Rebel Foods Private Limited</li><li>The agreement does not involve any related party transactions</li><li>The consideration or size of the order is not specified</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2d1d2f7d-f94b-4275-ad85-b1ffb921e57a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[POLYCAB] Polycab India Ltd Schedules Institutional Investor Meet</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Polycab+India+Ltd&title=Polycab+India+Ltd+Schedules+Institutional+Investor+Meet&newsId=2377c504-e936-41e9-babd-016f3568a9dc&token=MjM3N2M1MDQtZTkz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2377c504-e936-41e9-babd-016f3568a9dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:27:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Polycab India Ltd has announced an Institutional Investor(s) / Analyst(s) meet on February 17, 2026. The meeting will be physical and held in Mumbai. The presentation will include corporate and earnings information as hosted on the company&apos;s website and other publicly available information.</p><ul><li>Polycab India Ltd has scheduled an Institutional Investor(s) / Analyst(s) meet for February 17, 2026.</li><li>The meeting will be held physically in Mumbai.</li><li>Batlivala &amp; Karani Securities are expected to be present.</li><li>Corporate and earnings presentation will be shared, based on information hosted on the company&apos;s website and publicly available information.</li><li>The meeting is subject to changes if any.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e7436702-abff-4ded-926b-bb521508f2cf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Polycab India Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KALLAM] NCLT Amravati Bench Receives Application/Petition Against Kallam Textiles Ltd by Union Bank Of India</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kallam+Textiles+Ltd-%24&title=NCLT+Amravati+Bench+Receives+Application%2FPetition+Against+Kallam+Textiles+Ltd+by+Union+Bank+Of+India&newsId=d17c76f3-4579-4c2b-a204-432264dff45d&token=ZDE3Yzc2ZjMtNDU3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d17c76f3-4579-4c2b-a204-432264dff45d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 04:23:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kallam Textiles Ltd has received a mail communication dated 11-02-2026 from NCLT AMARAVATI BENCH regarding the Application/Petition registered with Case No: C.P. (IB)/3(AM)2026 by Union Bank Of India. The case is filed at NCLT (Amravati) and allotted case Number :AM C.P. (IB) 3 2026. The company will continue to update the Exchange(s) for any further developments in this regard.</p><ul><li>NCLT Amravati Bench received an Application/Petition from Union Bank Of India against Kallam Textiles Ltd.</li><li>The case is filed at NCLT (Amravati) and allotted case Number :AM C.P. (IB) 3 2026.</li><li>Kallam Textiles Ltd will continue to update the Exchange(s) for any further developments.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1183ca28-89b5-4d55-a179-acd880ca18a7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kallam Textiles Ltd-$ | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GARUDA] Garuda Construction and Engineering Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Garuda+Construction+and+Engineering+Ltd&title=Garuda+Construction+and+Engineering+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025&newsId=3a9a898c-def2-4215-bf5e-76edb90d7808&token=M2E5YTg5OGMtZGVm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a9a898c-def2-4215-bf5e-76edb90d7808</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:57:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Garuda Construction and Engineering Ltd has announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 14,005.41 lakhs for the quarter and 38,166.68 lakhs for the nine months. The profit before tax for the quarter is 2,147.61 lakhs and for the nine months is 4,315.64 lakhs. The earnings per share (EPS) for the quarter is 5.608.85 and for the nine months is 11.233.34. The company operates in a single business segment, which is construction activity, and conducts its business in only one geographical segment, India.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter is 14,005.41 lakhs</li><li>Profit before tax for the quarter is 2,147.61 lakhs</li><li>Earnings per share (EPS) for the quarter is 5.608.85</li><li>The company operates in a single business segment - construction activity</li><li>The company conducts its business in only one geographical segment - India</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b8601a0a-573c-428d-b40b-a6a8a0f6beb2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Garuda Construction and Engineering Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GARUDA] Garuda Construction and Engineering Ltd Approves Q3 Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Garuda+Construction+and+Engineering+Ltd&title=Garuda+Construction+and+Engineering+Ltd+Approves+Q3+Results+for+2025&newsId=9ef893a1-f36c-4723-b85f-4ad89ab9e5fc&token=OWVmODkzYTEtZjM2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ef893a1-f36c-4723-b85f-4ad89ab9e5fc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Garuda Construction and Engineering Ltd has approved the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The company operates in the construction sector and is based in Mumbai, Maharashtra. The results were reviewed by Agarwal Tibrewal &amp; Co Chartered Accountants.</p><ul><li>Garuda Construction and Engineering Ltd has approved the Unaudited Standalone Financial Results for Q3 2025.</li><li>The company has also approved the Unaudited Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 2025.</li><li>The results were reviewed by Agarwal Tibrewal &amp; Co Chartered Accountants.</li><li>The company operates in the construction sector.</li><li>The registered office of the company is in Mumbai, Maharashtra.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cd11588d-6026-4d5b-951f-34afde0100a2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Garuda Construction and Engineering Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BBOX] Black Box Ltd Reports Q3 FY26 Results with 11% Revenue Growth and Strategic Expansion</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Black+Box+Ltd&title=Black+Box+Ltd+Reports+Q3+FY26+Results+with+11%25+Revenue+Growth+and+Strategic+Expansion&newsId=4e8d910a-29b1-46a0-8980-5135c925661d&token=NGU4ZDkxMGEtMjli</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4e8d910a-29b1-46a0-8980-5135c925661d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:23:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Black Box Limited, a leading provider of digital infrastructure solutions, announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The Company delivered sustained growth, with improvements across revenue and operating profit, driven by broad-based performance across its key markets. The Company executed a definitive agreement to acquire Brazil based 2S Inovagdes Tecnoldgicas. The Company is firmly positioned for a growth trajectory in the quarters ahead with consolidated revenue for Q3 FY26 at 1,660 crore, representing a 11% year-on-year growth, and EBITDA at 147 crore, representing a 10% year-on-year growth.</p><ul><li>Revenue up 11% YoY and EBITDA up 10% YoY</li><li>Executed definitive agreement to acquire Brazil based 2S Inovagdes Tecnoldgicas</li><li>Order backlog projected at approximately $800 million by FY26 end</li><li>Improved execution and increased momentum in Q3 FY26</li><li>Expected to add around %500 crore of revenue in FY27 from the acquisition of 2S</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3836be80-521a-4286-ab16-9b2aa614c253.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Black Box Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WABAG] VA Tech Wabag Ltd. Granted Interim Stay on GST-Related Orders by Karnataka High Court</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VA+TECH+WABAG+LTD.&title=VA+Tech+Wabag+Ltd.+Granted+Interim+Stay+on+GST-Related+Orders+by+Karnataka+High+Court&newsId=cc46c54c-3f4a-43eb-a6ce-082a3e9f5a07&token=Y2M0NmM1NGMtM2Y0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cc46c54c-3f4a-43eb-a6ce-082a3e9f5a07</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 03:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>VA Tech Wabag Ltd. has received an interim stay order from the Karnataka High Court on two GST-related orders issued by the GST Commissionerate, Bengaluru. The first order involves alleged wrong classification and short payment of GST for supply of Works Contract services amounting to INR 1,20,38,078/- plus applicable interest and a penalty of INR 1,20,38,078/-. The second order is the outcome of a routine GST compliance audit under Section 65 of the CGST Act, 2017 for the period from FY 2018-19 to 2022-23 amounting to INR 23,21,411/-. The High Court granted the interim stay on February 11, 2026, and the Company will inform further developments in due course.</p><ul><li>VA Tech Wabag Ltd. received interim stay orders from the Karnataka High Court on two GST-related matters.</li><li>The first order involves alleged wrong classification and short payment of GST for supply of Works Contract services amounting to INR 1,20,38,078/- plus applicable interest and a penalty of INR 1,20,38,078/-.</li><li>The second order is the outcome of a routine GST compliance audit under Section 65 of the CGST Act, 2017 for the period from FY 2018-19 to 2022-23 amounting to INR 23,21,411/-.</li><li>The High Court granted the interim stay on February 11, 2026.</li><li>The Company will inform further developments in due course.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/15bee686-9898-4493-9060-d5e65fb50140.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VA TECH WABAG LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>