<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:30:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ASTEC] Astec Lifesciences Reports Q3FY26 Financial Results: Revenue Growth, Improved Margins, and Positive EBITDA</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ASTEC+LIFESCIENCES+LIMITED&title=Astec+Lifesciences+Reports+Q3FY26+Financial+Results%3A+Revenue+Growth%2C+Improved+Margins%2C+and+Positive+EBITDA&newsId=054f9e97-7101-4ba1-94d6-c8f3e737212c&token=MDU0ZjllOTctNzEw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">054f9e97-7101-4ba1-94d6-c8f3e737212c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Astec Lifesciences Limited has announced its financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company reported consolidated total income of Rs. 125.5 crore in Q3FY26, representing a 31% increase from Q3FY25. The company&apos;s EBITDA stood at Rs. 4.8 crore in Q3FY26, compared to an EBITDA loss of Rs. 3.8 crore in Q3 FY25. The company reported a loss of Rs. 15.7 crore in Q3FY26, an improvement from the loss of Rs. 40.4 crore in Q3FY25. For the nine-month period ended December 31, 2025, the company reported a loss of Rs. 73.1 crore, compared to a loss of Rs. 118.6 crore in the same period last year.</p><ul><li>1.3x growth in revenue over Q3 FY25, driven by higher Enterprise volumes and improved Contract Manufacturing segment off-take.</li><li>Sequential revenue increase of 1.7x over Q2 FY26, primarily due to CDOMO off-take.</li><li>Improvement in Enterprise margins and higher COMO volume off-take contributing to overall margin improvement.</li><li>Positive EBITDA of Rs. 4.8 crore in Q3 FY26.</li><li>Loss reduction in Q3FY26 to Rs. 15.7 crore from Rs. 40.4 crore in Q3FY25.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d0fa0c79-3a86-41d7-892b-5114a03f83df.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ASTEC LIFESCIENCES LIMITED | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[QUINT] Quint Digital Ltd. Proposes Amendments to Memorandum and Articles of Association</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Quint+Digital+Media+Ltd&title=Quint+Digital+Ltd.+Proposes+Amendments+to+Memorandum+and+Articles+of+Association&newsId=d3908036-bd26-455e-a438-74fc087280ef&token=ZDM5MDgwMzYtYmQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3908036-bd26-455e-a438-74fc087280ef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:21:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Quint Digital Ltd. announced that its Board of Directors, in a meeting held on January 30, 2026, proposed amendments to the company&apos;s Memorandum and Articles of Association. The proposed amendments are subject to the approval of the members of the company. The amendments to the Memorandum of Association include a re-classification of the existing authorized share capital, while the Articles of Association will be updated to align with the evolving regulatory and legal requirements prescribed by SEBI and the MCA. The company&apos;s internal management framework and policies will also be realigned with these requirements, aiming to strengthen corporate governance and enhance operational flexibility.</p><ul><li>Proposed amendments to the Memorandum and Articles of Association of Quint Digital Ltd.</li><li>Subject to the approval of the members of the company.</li><li>Re-classification of the existing authorized share capital.</li><li>Update of the Articles of Association to align with SEBI and MCA requirements.</li><li>Aim to strengthen corporate governance and enhance operational flexibility.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/db6b23f3-42cd-4b50-842f-45853c1a8da5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Quint Digital Media Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SICALLOG] Sical Logistics Ltd. Postpones Board Meeting to Approve Rights Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SICAL+LOGISTICS+LTD.&title=Sical+Logistics+Ltd.+Postpones+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Rights+Issue&newsId=fb4a8480-3d56-455c-bcae-e984a3bc9e6c&token=ZmI0YTg0ODAtM2Q1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fb4a8480-3d56-455c-bcae-e984a3bc9e6c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:21:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sical Logistics Ltd. has informed the BSE that the meeting of the Board of Directors, originally scheduled for January 30, 2026, has been rescheduled to February 3, 2026. The postponement is due to the Stock Exchanges considering the Draft Letter of Offer and raising queries, which the company is in the process of replying. The meeting will discuss and decide various matters in connection with the Rights Issue, including the specific terms such as the Rights Issue price, rights entitlement ratio, the record date, timing of the Rights Issue, and other terms and conditions. The Rights Issue is for an amount not exceeding Rs. 11,000 Lakhs and will be offered to the eligible equity shareholders by way of a rights issue, in accordance with the Companies Act, 2013, as amended and the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Issue of Capital and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2018, as amended.</p><ul><li>Sical Logistics Ltd. postpones Board meeting to February 3, 2026</li><li>Postponement due to Stock Exchanges considering Draft Letter of Offer and raising queries</li><li>Company is in the process of replying to the queries</li><li>Meeting will discuss various matters in connection with the Rights Issue</li><li>Rights Issue for an amount not exceeding Rs. 11,000 Lakhs</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/881975ad-67bf-4d92-b572-cc6851fb11ea.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SICAL LOGISTICS LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EXATO] Exato Technologies Participates in Acumatica Partner Summit 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Exato+Technologies+Ltd&title=Exato+Technologies+Participates+in+Acumatica+Partner+Summit+2026&newsId=e8b54fb9-181c-4e2f-b29d-73e10fb0b7ca&token=ZThiNTRmYjktMTgx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e8b54fb9-181c-4e2f-b29d-73e10fb0b7ca</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Exato Technologies Ltd, with scrip code 544626, recently participated in the Acumatica Partner Summit 2026 held in Seattle, USA. The summit, organized by Acumatica, a global provider of cloud-based Enterprise Resource Planning (ERP) solutions, emphasized a partner-centric ecosystem approach. The event highlighted the importance of collaboration among Value-Added Resellers (VARs), Independent Software Vendors (ISVs), and alliance partners for innovation, go-to-market execution, and enhanced customer success. The Company&apos;s participation aligns with its long-term strategic objectives and supports ecosystem-led growth and customer value creation. This disclosure does not involve any material financial or contractual commitment.</p><ul><li>Exato Technologies participated in Acumatica Partner Summit 2026</li><li>Summit emphasized a partner-centric ecosystem approach</li><li>Collaboration among VARs, ISVs, and alliance partners for innovation</li><li>Participation aligns with Exato&apos;s long-term strategic objectives</li><li>Supports ecosystem-led growth and customer value creation</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8d3da3f1-9db4-47de-84f4-c863ab05cb57.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Exato Technologies Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SIMMOND] Simmonds Marshall Ltd to Announce Q4 Results on Feb 06, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SIMMONDS+MARSHALL+LTD.&title=Simmonds+Marshall+Ltd+to+Announce+Q4+Results+on+Feb+06%2C+2026&newsId=dc6e5759-849f-445b-a7d1-8606e8d354b3&token=ZGM2ZTU3NTktODQ5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc6e5759-849f-445b-a7d1-8606e8d354b3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Simmonds Marshall Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 06, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the company has been closed from January 01, 2026, and will remain closed till 48 hours after the announcement of the Un-Audited Financial Results to the stock exchange.</p><ul><li>Simmonds Marshall Ltd to announce Q4 results on Feb 06, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve Unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the securities of the company has been closed from January 01, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ae5671b7-e499-492e-bc3e-589c85b078df.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SIMMONDS MARSHALL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUGSLLOYD] Sugs Lloyd Ltd Secures Rs. ¥84.36 Crore Network Maintenance Contract from BSES Yamuna Power Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sugs+Lloyd+Ltd&title=Sugs+Lloyd+Ltd+Secures+Rs.+%C2%A584.36+Crore+Network+Maintenance+Contract+from+BSES+Yamuna+Power+Limited&newsId=8e95f334-1e33-4d86-8d6b-95d62c3e577f&token=OGU5NWYzMzQtMWUz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8e95f334-1e33-4d86-8d6b-95d62c3e577f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:21:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Sugs Lloyd Ltd has received a Letter of Award from BSES Yamuna Power Limited for a Network Maintenance Contract (NMC) of Electricity Distribution Network in Central Circle of BYPL, Delhi. The order value, including GST, is Rs. ¥84.3629298 crore. The contract includes maintenance of EHV Grids, 11 KV Network, Streetlight, and other related works.</p><ul><li>Sugs Lloyd Ltd secures a Network Maintenance Contract from BSES Yamuna Power Limited worth Rs. ¥84.36 crore</li><li>The contract includes maintenance of EHV Grids, 11 KV Network, Streetlight, and other related works</li><li>The contract period is from 01.02.2026 to 31.01.2029 (Three Years)</li><li>The order value includes GST</li><li>The contract is a Domestic Entity awarded by a domestic entity</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5136bbc8-d109-4779-97ab-04d402f75660.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sugs Lloyd Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MITSU] Mitsu Chem Plast Limited Announces 217.03% YoY Net Profit Growth in Q3 FY26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Mitsu+Chem+Plast+Ltd&title=Mitsu+Chem+Plast+Limited+Announces+217.03%25+YoY+Net+Profit+Growth+in+Q3+FY26&newsId=243df120-a091-4c2f-9062-45c643355f52&token=MjQzZGYxMjAtYTA5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">243df120-a091-4c2f-9062-45c643355f52</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Mitsu Chem Plast Limited, a leading global manufacturer of Blow Molded &amp; Injection Molded products, has reported a robust performance for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s net profit surged by 217.03% YoY, and the EBITDA margin increased by 73% YoY. The total income stood at ₹ 2,640,503 Lakhs. The company is expanding its capacity by adding ~655 MT per annum, taking the total capacity to ~29,000+ MT per annum. This capacity expansion is expected to support growth, rising demand, and improved customer service.</p><ul><li>Net profit surged by 217.03% YoY</li><li>EBITDA margin increased by 73% YoY</li><li>Total income stood at ₹ 2,640,503 Lakhs</li><li>Planned addition of ~655 MT per annum, taking total capacity to ~29,000+ MT per annum</li><li>Capacity expansion to support growth and demand</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/88c2f1fc-d57b-47a2-a5ea-7b6b802bbeac.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Mitsu Chem Plast Ltd | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SANCF] Sanchay Finvest Ltd. Proposes Capital Increase &amp; Additional Preferential Allotment of 61,00,000 Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SANCHAY+FINVEST+LTD.&title=Sanchay+Finvest+Ltd.+Proposes+Capital+Increase+%26+Additional+Preferential+Allotment+of+61%2C00%2C000+Equity+Shares&newsId=fe91e22c-48e6-43b6-a70f-0f3b27c79281&token=ZmU5MWUyMmMtNDhl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe91e22c-48e6-43b6-a70f-0f3b27c79281</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:03:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sanchay Finvest Ltd. announced that its Board of Directors held a meeting on Friday, 30th January 2026, and proposed to increase the company&apos;s authorized capital from Rs. 8,00,00,000 to Rs. 14,00,00,000, after receiving necessary approvals in the ensuing EGM. The company also announced an additional preferential allotment of 61,00,000 equity shares at a price of Rs. 10/- per equity share, following a formal intimation from one of the proposed preferential allottees, Mr. Sagar Tilokchand Kothari.</p><ul><li>Proposed increase in the authorized capital of Sanchay Finvest Ltd. from Rs. 8,00,00,000 to Rs. 14,00,00,000</li><li>Additional preferential allotment of 61,00,000 equity shares at a price of Rs. 10/- per equity share</li><li>Involvement of Mr. Sagar Tilokchand Kothari in the preferential allotment</li><li>The company requires adequate capital to accommodate the additional fresh issue of proposed preferential allotment</li><li>The proposed allotment is subject to the approval of the Members of the Company and applicable regulatory/statutory authorities</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e98d3bc2-e3b5-4c66-ad38-6a462adab339.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SANCHAY FINVEST LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CHANDNIMACH] Chandni Machines Ltd Approves Preferential Allotment of Equity Shares &amp; Convertible Warrants</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Chandni+Machines+Ltd&title=Chandni+Machines+Ltd+Approves+Preferential+Allotment+of+Equity+Shares+%26+Convertible+Warrants&newsId=4979ae15-bd02-48f4-aee2-799988fe2319&token=NDk3OWFlMTUtYmQw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4979ae15-bd02-48f4-aee2-799988fe2319</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 14:57:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Chandni Machines Ltd has approved the allotment of 38,10,900 equity shares and 40,00,000 fully convertible warrants on a preferential basis. The equity shares are priced at Rs. 52.50 (including a premium of Rs. 42.50) each and the warrants are convertible into equity shares at the same price within a maximum period of 18 months from the date of allotment. The company has received 25% of the warrant issue price from the allottees. The allotment of 3,73,100 equity shares could not be made due to non-receipt of allotment money.</p><ul><li>Chandni Machines Ltd approves preferential allotment of equity shares and convertible warrants.</li><li>38,10,900 equity shares priced at Rs. 52.50 each to be issued.</li><li>40,00,000 fully convertible warrants to be issued, each convertible into an equity share at Rs. 52.50.</li><li>25% of the warrant issue price received from the allottees.</li><li>Allotment of 3,73,100 equity shares cancelled due to non-receipt of allotment money.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e9d98027-67c9-4cc1-96c1-aa30f37aeca7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Chandni Machines Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ESAFSFB] ESAF Small Finance Bank Delivers Strong Turnaround in Q3 FY26: MARG Strategy Drives Performance</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ESAF+Small+Finance+Bank+Ltd&title=ESAF+Small+Finance+Bank+Delivers+Strong+Turnaround+in+Q3+FY26%3A+MARG+Strategy+Drives+Performance&newsId=5d04a0b1-2433-4010-9d83-929efba40b7a&token=NWQwNGEwYjEtMjQz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d04a0b1-2433-4010-9d83-929efba40b7a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 14:54:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>ESAF Small Finance Bank announced its financial results for the third quarter of FY26, marking a return to profitability, strong growth in its MARG portfolio, and a significant improvement in asset quality. The Bank reported a net profit of ¥7 crore for Q3 FY26, as against a loss of ¥211 crore in the same quarter last year. Total business stood at ¥44,686 crore, registering a year-on-year growth of 10%. Gross advances grew by 13.1% to ¥20,679 crore, while deposits increased by 7.1% to ¥24,006 crore. Secured loan disbursements surged by 149% year-on-year to ¥10,530 crore during the quarter. Asset quality saw a meaningful turnaround during the quarter, with Gross NPA reducing to 5.6% from 8.5% in the previous quarter and Net NPA declining to 2.7% from 3.8%.</p><ul><li>Return to profitability in Q3 FY26 with a net profit of ¥7 crore</li><li>10% year-on-year growth in total business</li><li>13.1% growth in gross advances and 7.1% growth in deposits</li><li>149% year-on-year surge in secured loan disbursements</li><li>Meaningful turnaround in asset quality with reduced Gross and Net NPA</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3840f29b-f464-4774-9f6b-eab769b16d0c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ESAF Small Finance Bank Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>