<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:47:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[KWIL] Kwality Walls Receives Draft Letter of Offer from Magnum under SEBI Regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KWIL&title=Kwality+Walls+Receives+Draft+Letter+of+Offer+from+Magnum+under+SEBI+Regulations&newsId=d5b25386-594e-4263-9e46-f2390cdfe1dd&token=ZDViMjUzODYtNTk0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5b25386-594e-4263-9e46-f2390cdfe1dd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:46:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Kwality Walls (India) Limited has received a copy of the detailed public statement issued by Kotak Mahindra Capital Company Limited. The statement is in respect of an open offer made by The Magnum Ice Cream Company HoldCo 1 Netherlands B.V. together with Magnum ICC Finance B.V. and The Magnum Ice Cream Company N.V. The offer is made to the public shareholders of the Company pursuant to and in compliance with requirements under the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</p><ul><li>Kwality Walls (India) Limited has received a Draft Letter of Offer from Magnum under SEBI regulations.</li><li>The offer is made by The Magnum Ice Cream Company HoldCo 1 Netherlands B.V. together with Magnum ICC Finance B.V. and The Magnum Ice Cream Company N.V.</li><li>The offer is pursuant to and in compliance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</li><li>The offer is made to the public shareholders of the Company.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1e501e18-8e5c-47a1-89cf-4a5ef39275b1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KWIL | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TRU] Interim order maintained in TruCap Finance&apos;s open offer case by Securities Appellate Tribunal</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TruCap+Finance+Ltd&title=Interim+order+maintained+in+TruCap+Finance%27s+open+offer+case+by+Securities+Appellate+Tribunal&newsId=e0c1efe8-6708-4330-bc18-245e298900be&token=ZTBjMWVmZTgtNjcw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0c1efe8-6708-4330-bc18-245e298900be</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:44:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sundae Capital Advisors Pvt Ltd, the Manager to the Offer, has informed BSE about the interim order of the Hon&apos;ble Securities Appellate Tribunal in the matter of the open offer given by Marwadi Chandarana Intermediaries Brokers Private Limited to the shareholders of Trucap Finance Limited. The Tribunal had previously passed an interim order to maintain status quo till the next hearing, and in the hearing held on February 20, 2026, it allowed the respondent a time of two weeks to file a reply. The interim order continues till the next date of listing, which is March 25, 2026. The appeal is listed for the next hearing on the same date.</p><ul><li>Interim order maintained in TruCap Finance&apos;s open offer case by Securities Appellate Tribunal</li><li>Respondent allowed two weeks to file reply, rejoinder to be filed within two weeks thereafter</li><li>Interim order to continue till the next date of listing</li><li>Next hearing scheduled for March 25, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0861072C-2994-4135-A18B-8784C64C776E-180838.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TruCap Finance Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BRIGADE] Brigade Group Launches &apos;Brigade Stellaris&apos; in Chennai with 1,700 Crores GDV</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BRIGADE+ENTERPRISES+LTD.&title=Brigade+Group+Launches+%27Brigade+Stellaris%27+in+Chennai+with+1%2C700+Crores+GDV&newsId=f4a03c3f-341b-45eb-8ddb-e2857f21bb00&token=ZjRhMDNjM2YtMzQx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4a03c3f-341b-45eb-8ddb-e2857f21bb00</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:42:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Brigade Group has announced the launch of its residential project, Brigade Stellaris in Chennai. The project is located on a prime 5.19 acre land parcel on Velachery Road, Chennai, owned by the Company and has an estimated Gross Development Value (GDV) of approximately 1,700 Crores. The development will house an exclusive collection of &apos;Signature Residences,&apos; emphasizing modern functionality and world-class amenities. By integrating sustainable design with high-end architecture, Brigade Stellaris aims to provide a sanctuary for urban professionals and families who seek luxury without compromising on proximity to the city’s major employment and commercial hubs.</p><ul><li>Brigade Group launches a new residential project &apos;Brigade Stellaris&apos; in Chennai.</li><li>The project is located on a 5.19 acre prime land parcel on Velachery Road, Chennai.</li><li>The estimated Gross Development Value (GDV) is approximately 1,700 Crores.</li><li>The project will feature an exclusive collection of &apos;Signature Residences&apos; with modern functionality and world-class amenities.</li><li>Brigade Group is known for delivering high-quality construction and sustainable designs.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/12fb3d8f-2e4d-447b-add3-027f3d4a9440.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BRIGADE ENTERPRISES LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TATACOMM] Tata Communications Ltd Grants 24,654 Employee Stock Options Under &apos;Tata Communications Limited - Stock Unit Plan 2023&apos;</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TATA+COMMUNICATIONS+LTD.&title=Tata+Communications+Ltd+Grants+24%2C654+Employee+Stock+Options+Under+%27Tata+Communications+Limited+-+Stock+Unit+Plan+2023%27&newsId=aba7c7e3-fee3-4ebd-903f-aff1d2df119d&token=YWJhN2M3ZTMtZmVl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aba7c7e3-fee3-4ebd-903f-aff1d2df119d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:42:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tata Communications Ltd has granted 24,654 employee stock options under &apos;Tata Communications Limited - Stock Unit Plan 2023&apos;. The grant was approved by the Nomination and Remuneration Committee (NRC) on February 26, 2026, with an effective date of March 1, 2026. The RSUs are exercisable into not more than 7,812 equity shares of face value of INR 10 each fully paid up. The RSUs shall vest with the employee on the satisfaction of a time-based and a performance-based vesting criteria, within a period of 1 to 3 years from the grant date.</p><ul><li>Tata Communications Ltd grants 24,654 employee stock options under &apos;Tata Communications Limited - Stock Unit Plan 2023&apos;</li><li>The grant was approved by the Nomination and Remuneration Committee (NRC) on February 26, 2026</li><li>The RSUs are exercisable into not more than 7,812 equity shares</li><li>The RSUs shall vest with the employee on the satisfaction of a time-based and a performance-based vesting criteria</li><li>The vesting period is within 1 to 3 years from the grant date</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/82f64851-e605-4ee2-a8a1-9bd570be65f6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TATA COMMUNICATIONS LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MINDACORP] Minda Corporation Revises Commercial Paper Maturity Date Due to Bank Holiday Change</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Minda+Corporation+Ltd&title=Minda+Corporation+Revises+Commercial+Paper+Maturity+Date+Due+to+Bank+Holiday+Change&newsId=ac9a514b-e275-484a-88a1-b5aa11a30735&token=YWM5YTUxNGItZTI3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac9a514b-e275-484a-88a1-b5aa11a30735</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Minda Corporation Limited has updated the maturity date of its Commercial Paper(s) from 03.03.2026 to 02.03.2026 due to a change in the bank holiday from 04.03.2026 to 03.03.2026. This change is in accordance with the SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/DDHS/PoD1/P/CIR/2024/54 dated May 22, 2024, and FIMMDA guidelines. The revised maturity date applies to a Commercial Paper of ₹ 100 crore issued by Minda Corporation Limited.</p><ul><li>Minda Corporation Limited revises the maturity date of its Commercial Paper(s) due to a change in bank holiday</li><li>The original maturity date was 03.03.2026, which has been revised to 02.03.2026</li><li>The change is in accordance with SEBI and FIMMDA guidelines</li><li>The revised maturity date applies to a ₹ 100 crore Commercial Paper issued by Minda Corporation Limited</li><li>HDFC Bank will process the CP redemption on 02.03.2026 as per the updated maturity date</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/302da95f-de7e-4af7-945e-cc373a3d3b61.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Minda Corporation Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SOFTBPO] IDream Film Infrastructure Receives SEBI Observation Letter for Open Offer from Northvale Capital Partners</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SOFTBPO+GLOBAL+SERVICES+LTD.&title=IDream+Film+Infrastructure+Receives+SEBI+Observation+Letter+for+Open+Offer+from+Northvale+Capital+Partners&newsId=66c07dca-9327-41b2-a83d-214769610ee7&token=NjZjMDdkY2EtOTMy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66c07dca-9327-41b2-a83d-214769610ee7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:41:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>IDream Film Infrastructure Company Limited has received an Observation Letter from the Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) in relation to the Draft Letter of Offer filed by Northvale Capital Partners PTE Limited for the acquisition of up to 7,03,43,853 equity shares. This offer, if successful, would result in a change in control of the Target Company in favor of the Acquirer. The Manager to the Offer will initiate subsequent actions as per the SAST Regulations and SEBI&apos;s directions. The Company will keep the Stock Exchange informed of further developments.</p><ul><li>IDream Film Infrastructure has received an Observation Letter from SEBI for an Open Offer by Northvale Capital Partners.</li><li>Northvale Capital Partners aim to acquire up to 7,03,43,853 equity shares of IDream Film Infrastructure.</li><li>The acquisition would result in a change in control of the Target Company in favor of the Acquirer.</li><li>The Manager to the Offer will initiate actions as per SAST Regulations and SEBI&apos;s directions.</li><li>The Company will keep the Stock Exchange informed of further developments.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/34333a30-8131-4309-8a90-c73d0e3b8265.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SOFTBPO GLOBAL SERVICES LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TIL] TIL Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Rights Issue of Equity Shares Up to Rs. 200 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TIL+LTD.&title=TIL+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Rights+Issue+of+Equity+Shares+Up+to+Rs.+200+Crores&newsId=893a4aba-8c62-4f52-a2d0-771de1df9eba&token=ODkzYTRhYmEtOGM2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">893a4aba-8c62-4f52-a2d0-771de1df9eba</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Right Issue</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>TIL Ltd has informed the BSE that the company&apos;s Board of Directors will meet on 05/03/2026 to consider and approve a letter attached to the notice. The meeting will also seek approval from the Rights Issue Committee of the Board to fix the record date, price, and entitlement ratio for the Rights Issue of Equity Shares for an amount not exceeding Rs. 200 Crores, which was previously approved by the Board of Directors on February 23, 2026. The approval is subject to receipt of necessary approvals from stock exchanges and other regulatory authorities.</p><ul><li>TIL Ltd schedules Board Meeting on 05/03/2026 to consider and approve a letter attached to the notice.</li><li>The company seeks approval from the Rights Issue Committee to fix the record date, price, and entitlement ratio for the Rights Issue of Equity Shares.</li><li>Rights Issue of Equity Shares is for an amount not exceeding Rs. 200 Crores, as previously approved by the Board of Directors on February 23, 2026.</li><li>Approval from stock exchanges and other regulatory authorities is required before proceeding with the Rights Issue.</li><li>The Rights Issue is subject to necessary approvals and regulations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f32edf97-145a-4826-b317-d9d2a77be101.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TIL LTD. | Category: Right Issue</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DABUR] Dabur India Ltd: SEBI Regulation 30 Update; Orders for Tax Demand of Rs. 3,12,74,277 Set Aside</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DABUR+INDIA+LTD.&title=Dabur+India+Ltd%3A+SEBI+Regulation+30+Update%3B+Orders+for+Tax+Demand+of+Rs.+3%2C12%2C74%2C277+Set+Aside&newsId=6efbab7a-832d-46d4-817e-f90113a3b16c&token=NmVmYmFiN2EtODMy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6efbab7a-832d-46d4-817e-f90113a3b16c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:41:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dabur India Ltd has submitted an update under Regulation 30 of the SEBI Listing Regulations regarding disclosures dated February 4, 2025 and October 3, 2025. The update pertains to orders passed by the Joint Commissioner, State Tax, Circle-C, Alwar, Rajasthan for a total demand of Rs. 3,12,74,277 (including interest and penalty) due to a product classification issue for financial years 2017-18, 2018-19, and 2019-20. The tax demand amounted to Rs. 97,28,014, the interest to Rs. 1,18,18,249, and the penalty to Rs. 97,28,014. The Company had filed appeals before the 1st Appellate Authority State Tax, Alwar, Rajasthan for each of the financial years. The Ld. Appellate Authority has set aside the aforementioned demand, including interest and penalty. The order was received on February 26, 2026, and there is no impact on the Company&apos;s operations or other activities.</p><ul><li>Dabur India Ltd submits update under SEBI Regulation 30</li><li>Orders passed by Joint Commissioner, State Tax, Alwar, Rajasthan for a total demand of Rs. 3,12,74,277</li><li>Demand pertains to product classification issue for financial years 2017-18, 2018-19, and 2019-20</li><li>Company filed appeals before the 1st Appellate Authority State Tax, Alwar, Rajasthan</li><li>Appellate Authority set aside the demand, including interest and penalty</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b0fb88ce-6cdc-4378-b224-7f3c7525c617.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DABUR INDIA LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[COSMOFIRST] Cosmo First Ltd Announces Resignation of Business Head-Speciality Chemicals, Mr. Raj Sharma</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Cosmo+First+Ltd&title=Cosmo+First+Ltd+Announces+Resignation+of+Business+Head-Speciality+Chemicals%2C+Mr.+Raj+Sharma&newsId=586230c0-8b70-480d-9d09-76dc295cfcac&token=NTg2MjMwYzAtOGI3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">586230c0-8b70-480d-9d09-76dc295cfcac</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cosmo First Ltd, in accordance with Regulation 30 of SEBI Listing Regulations, has announced the resignation of Mr. Raj Sharma, Business Head-Speciality Chemicals, due to personal reasons. His resignation was accepted and he was relieved from his duties with effect from the close of business hours on February 28, 2026. Mr. Sharma has expressed his gratitude for the opportunity to lead the business during his tenure.</p><ul><li>Mr. Raj Sharma, Business Head-Speciality Chemicals, resigns from Cosmo First Ltd.</li><li>Resignation accepted by the company with effect from February 28, 2026.</li><li>Mr. Sharma expresses gratitude for the opportunity to lead the business.</li><li>Company to maintain business momentum during the transition period.</li><li>Personal reasons cited as the reason for resignation.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cb393717-b64e-4d9d-b9ae-d598d0f937ba.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Cosmo First Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NXST] Nexus Select Trust Discloses Material Issue in Meeting with Institutional Investor</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Nexus+Select+Trust&title=Nexus+Select+Trust+Discloses+Material+Issue+in+Meeting+with+Institutional+Investor&newsId=f27f7786-6711-4086-9b90-61a1149727b3&token=ZjI3Zjc3ODYtNjcx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f27f7786-6711-4086-9b90-61a1149727b3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 12:41:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Nexus Select Trust, managed by Nexus Select Mall Management Private Limited, held a meeting with an Institutional Investor on February 27, 2026. The meeting was attended by senior management personnel from Nexus Select Mall Management Private Limited. The details of the meeting have been disclosed by the trust.</p><ul><li>Nexus Select Trust discloses material issue in a meeting with an Institutional Investor</li><li>Meeting held on February 27, 2026</li><li>Attended by senior management personnel from Nexus Select Mall Management Private Limited</li><li>Disclosed by the trust</li><li>Nexus Select Mall Management Private Limited is the Manager to Nexus Select Trust</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d2a5558e-68c3-40e4-be2d-6aaeee4b05fe.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Nexus Select Trust | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>