<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:38:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SYSTMTXC] Systematix Group: Q3 FY26 &amp; 9M FY26 Updates, Investments Re-defined</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SYSTEMATIX+CORPORATE+SERVICES+LTD.&title=Systematix+Group%3A+Q3+FY26+%26+9M+FY26+Updates%2C+Investments+Re-defined&newsId=ff69d505-82d1-497b-9f86-2a0a2db7ce84&token=ZmY2OWQ1MDUtODJk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff69d505-82d1-497b-9f86-2a0a2db7ce84</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:47:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Systematix Group has reported a total income from operation of 33.60 cr for Q3 FY26, a decrease of 23% YoY. However, the total income for 9M FY26 is 122.67 cr, an increase of 12% YoY. The financial highlights for Q3 FY26 &amp; 9M FY26 show an adjusted PBT of 5 cr for Q3 FY26 and 16.5 cr for 9M FY26. The Group has re-defined its investments strategy, but details are not provided in the presentation.</p><ul><li>Total income from operation decreased by 23% YoY for Q3 FY26</li><li>Total income from operation increased by 12% YoY for 9M FY26</li><li>Adjusted PBT for Q3 FY26 is 5 cr</li><li>Adjusted PBT for 9M FY26 is 16.5 cr</li><li>Systematix Group has re-defined its investments strategy</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cbec1eb0-8c6c-4dc5-be5d-8d28b069ba97.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SYSTEMATIX CORPORATE SERVICES LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JARO] Jaro Institute Announces Re-Appointment of Independent Director and Approval of ESOP Scheme 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jaro+Institute+of+Technology+Management+and+Research+Ltd&title=Jaro+Institute+Announces+Re-Appointment+of+Independent+Director+and+Approval+of+ESOP+Scheme+2026&newsId=3628265a-90f6-4bc1-9a98-3a214b26a44d&token=MzYyODI2NWEtOTBm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3628265a-90f6-4bc1-9a98-3a214b26a44d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:41:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jaro Institute of Technology Management and Research Ltd has announced the re-appointment of Mr. Ishan Baveja as an Independent Director for a second term of 5 years, subject to approval of shareholders. The company also approved the Jaro Education Employees Stock Option Plan 2026 (ESOP Scheme 2026) for the grant of options to eligible employees, which will be implemented through the Trust Route. The company will seek approval of shareholders for the scheme through a Postal Ballot.</p><ul><li>Re-appointment of Mr. Ishan Baveja as an Independent Director</li><li>Approval of Jaro Education Employees Stock Option Plan 2026 (ESOP Scheme 2026)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8fe427b8-81dd-4958-b5e6-35900e065086.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jaro Institute of Technology Management and Research Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[YESBANK] YES Bank Re-appoints Dr. Rajan Pental as Executive Director till July 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=YES+BANK+LTD.&title=YES+Bank+Re-appoints+Dr.+Rajan+Pental+as+Executive+Director+till+July+2026&newsId=b08c8e1e-d35a-438c-bd96-ee91de425150&token=YjA4YzhlMWUtZDM1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b08c8e1e-d35a-438c-bd96-ee91de425150</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:32:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>YES Bank Ltd has received approval from the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) for the re-appointment of Dr. Rajan Pental as Executive Director for a further period of six months, effective from February 2, 2026, until his superannuation date, July 31, 2026. His re-appointment is subject to the approval of the bank&apos;s shareholders. Dr. Pental has a rich experience of 3 decades in the financial services industry and currently serves as the Executive Director at YES BANK, overseeing various portfolios including Branch Banking, Retail Assets, SME Banking, and Corporate Social Responsibility. He has been instrumental in setting up and institutionalizing the Retail Assets Business for HDFC Bank in the Northern region and has held positions of increasing responsibilities in HDFC Bank from Jun 2001 to Oct 2015.</p><ul><li>YES Bank receives RBI approval for Dr. Rajan Pental&apos;s re-appointment as Executive Director.</li><li>Dr. Pental&apos;s re-appointment is effective from February 2, 2026, until July 31, 2026.</li><li>His re-appointment is subject to shareholder approval.</li><li>Dr. Pental has 3 decades of experience in the financial services industry.</li><li>He currently oversees various portfolios at YES BANK and has a proven track record in Retail Banking and building new businesses.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1a55c4cf-59d2-469d-b569-be60dcc34bb3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: YES BANK LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JARO] Jaro Institute Announces Re-Appointment of Independent Director and Approval of ESOP Scheme 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jaro+Institute+of+Technology+Management+and+Research+Ltd&title=Jaro+Institute+Announces+Re-Appointment+of+Independent+Director+and+Approval+of+ESOP+Scheme+2026&newsId=530166d6-d429-41d9-bd46-f9f0a344b477&token=NTMwMTY2ZDYtZDQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">530166d6-d429-41d9-bd46-f9f0a344b477</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:32:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jaro Institute of Technology Management and Research Ltd has announced the re-appointment of Mr. Ishan Baveja as an Independent Director for a second term of 5 years, subject to shareholders&apos; approval. The company also approved the Jaro Education Employees Stock Option Plan 2026 (ESOP Scheme 2026) for the grant of options to eligible employees, which will be implemented through the Trust Route. The company will seek approval of shareholders for the scheme through a Postal Ballot.</p><ul><li>Re-appointment of Mr. Ishan Baveja as an Independent Director</li><li>Approval of Jaro Education Employees Stock Option Plan 2026 (ESOP Scheme 2026)</li><li>Implementation of the scheme through Trust Route</li><li>Seeking shareholders&apos; approval for the scheme through a Postal Ballot</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4e13f39b-fea0-4815-b5e8-5d52dc17f08b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jaro Institute of Technology Management and Research Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JARO] Jaro Institute of Technology Management and Research Ltd Approves Employee Stock Option Plan 2026 and Re-Appoints Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jaro+Institute+of+Technology+Management+and+Research+Ltd&title=Jaro+Institute+of+Technology+Management+and+Research+Ltd+Approves+Employee+Stock+Option+Plan+2026+and+Re-Appoints+Independent+Director&newsId=8b72cd75-f66a-44be-8f3b-19035bbe2745&token=OGI3MmNkNzUtZjY2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b72cd75-f66a-44be-8f3b-19035bbe2745</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jaro Institute of Technology Management and Research Ltd has approved the Jaro Education Employee Stock Option Plan 2026 (ESOP Scheme 2026) and seeks shareholders&apos; approval for the same. The scheme will be implemented through the Trust route. The company has also approved the re-appointment of Mr. Ishan Baveja as an Independent Director for a second term of 5 years. Mr. Baveja is a practicing chartered accountant and has over 12 years of experience in the accounting sector.</p><ul><li>Approval of Jaro Education Employees Stock Option Plan 2026</li><li>Implementation through Trust Route</li><li>Seeking Shareholders&apos; approval for the Scheme through a Postal Ballot</li><li>Re-Appointment of Mr. Ishan Baveja as an Independent Director for a second term of 5 years</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8d3a9cef-8e45-4641-a4fb-abac2a12531e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jaro Institute of Technology Management and Research Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NDTV] New Delhi Television Ltd Surrenders Permission for Three HD News Channels</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NEW+DELHI+TELEVISION+LTD.&title=New+Delhi+Television+Ltd+Surrenders+Permission+for+Three+HD+News+Channels&newsId=13ee7f55-6420-4bb5-b46b-d3860c610065&token=MTNlZTdmNTUtNjQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13ee7f55-6420-4bb5-b46b-d3860c610065</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Other</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>New Delhi Television Ltd has voluntarily surrendered the permission granted by the Ministry of Information &amp; Broadcasting for the uplinking and downlinking of the proposed News and Current Affairs Channel namely NDTV INDIA HD. The decision was made based on an internal strategic assessment, as the company has decided not to proceed with the launch of the proposed channels: NDTV INDIA HD, NDTV 24x7 HD, and NDTV PROFIT HD. Since the channels were non-operational, the surrender of permission does not have any material impact on the Company’s business operations or financial position.</p><ul><li>New Delhi Television Ltd surrenders permission for three HD News Channels</li><li>Permission was granted by the Ministry of Information &amp; Broadcasting</li><li>Channels include NDTV INDIA HD, NDTV 24x7 HD, and NDTV PROFIT HD</li><li>Decision based on internal strategic assessment</li><li>Surrender of permission has no material impact on business operations or financial position</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/994e839b-8519-48f8-9205-f703c3667f6e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NEW DELHI TELEVISION LTD. | Category: Other</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LEMONTREE] Lemon Tree Hotels Announces Composite Scheme of Arrangement</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Lemon+Tree+Hotels+Ltd&title=Lemon+Tree+Hotels+Announces+Composite+Scheme+of+Arrangement&newsId=85b1c2a0-b92f-4f8c-aa4a-f38f5a7c7215&token=ODViMWMyYTAtYjky</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85b1c2a0-b92f-4f8c-aa4a-f38f5a7c7215</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Reorganization</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Lemon Tree Hotels Limited, a leading hotel chain in India, has announced a Composite Scheme of Arrangement. This scheme will result in two distinct businesses: Lemon Tree Hotels, a pure-play asset-light company, and Fleur Hotels, a large-scale hotel ownership/leasing platform. The reorganization is expected to be completed in 12-15 months. Post reorganization, Lemon Tree will be debt-free, high-margin, and high ROCE, generating strong free cash flows. Fleur Hotels will consolidate ownership of existing hotels and pursue growth through development, acquisitions, and enhancing asset level performance.</p><ul><li>Lemon Tree Hotels to become a pure-play asset-light company focused on hotel management, brand, loyalty distribution, and digital services.</li><li>Fleur Hotels to operate as a large-scale hotel ownership/leasing platform with end-to-end in-house development capabilities.</li><li>Post reorganization, Lemon Tree will be debt-free, high-margin, and high ROCE, generating strong free cash flows.</li><li>Fleur Hotels will consolidate ownership of existing hotels and pursue growth through development, acquisitions, and enhancing asset level performance.</li><li>The reorganization is expected to be completed in 12-15 months.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/098527b9-fd65-4aa9-9c6d-1ac184b2eda0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Lemon Tree Hotels Ltd | Category: Reorganization</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JARO] Jaro Institute Board Approves Stock Option Plan, Re-Appointment of Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jaro+Institute+of+Technology+Management+and+Research+Ltd&title=Jaro+Institute+Board+Approves+Stock+Option+Plan%2C+Re-Appointment+of+Director&newsId=92140866-0600-4cac-aab7-2b8b9d0b01ab&token=OTIxNDA4NjYtMDYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">92140866-0600-4cac-aab7-2b8b9d0b01ab</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:24:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Jaro Institute of Technology Management and Research Ltd. approved the Jaro Education Employees Stock Option Plan 2026 (ESOP Scheme 2026) and the re-appointment of Mr. Ishan Baveja as an Independent Director for a second term of 5 years. The ESOP Scheme 2026, subject to shareholders&apos; approval, will allow the company to grant options to eligible employees for acquiring up to 10,00,000 (Ten Lakhs) equity shares. The re-appointment of Mr. Baveja, who is not debarred from holding the office of the Director, will be effective from February 4, 2026.</p><ul><li>Approval of Jaro Education Employees Stock Option Plan 2026 (ESOP Scheme 2026)</li><li>Re-appointment of Mr. Ishan Baveja as an Independent Director for a second term of 5 years</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/65a4b07c-53f4-4aac-9074-f7e3ea9bbed8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jaro Institute of Technology Management and Research Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SYSTMTXC] Systematix Corporate Services Ltd Appoints New Independent Director and Approves Quarterly Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SYSTEMATIX+CORPORATE+SERVICES+LTD.&title=Systematix+Corporate+Services+Ltd+Appoints+New+Independent+Director+and+Approves+Quarterly+Financial+Results&newsId=0d681b3a-b307-4fda-bba9-8d6d15bd2ca6&token=MGQ2ODFiM2EtYjMw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d681b3a-b307-4fda-bba9-8d6d15bd2ca6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:52:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Systematix Corporate Services Ltd has announced the appointment of Mr. Vijaykumar Gautam as an Additional Non-Executive Independent Director, following the recommendation of the Nomination and Remuneration Committee. Mr. Gautam will hold office till the ensuing General Meeting and thereafter subject to approval of Members, to be appointed as a Non-Executive Independent Director for a 5-year term starting from January 21, 2026. The company has also approved the standalone and consolidated un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Vijaykumar Gautam as Additional Non-Executive Independent Director</li><li>Mr. Gautam to serve as a Non-Executive Independent Director for a 5-year term</li><li>Approval of standalone and consolidated un-audited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3a5359db-1146-46af-a354-1d24a988990a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SYSTEMATIX CORPORATE SERVICES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CUPID] Cupid Ltd to Invest Rs. 331 Crores in Baazar Style Retail Ltd; Expanding FMCG Product Portfolio and Consumer Reach</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CUPID+LTD.-%24&title=Cupid+Ltd+to+Invest+Rs.+331+Crores+in+Baazar+Style+Retail+Ltd%3B+Expanding+FMCG+Product+Portfolio+and+Consumer+Reach&newsId=7a239d73-28bc-4516-b18a-84d232679291&token=N2EyMzlkNzMtMjhi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7a239d73-28bc-4516-b18a-84d232679291</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:52:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Cupid Limited has informed BSE about the outcome of its Board Meeting held on 21st January, 2026. The Board approved a strategic investment in Preferential Warrants Convertible in to Equity Shares of Baazar Style Retail Limited, a company listed on BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange of India, amounting to Rs. 331,53,25,000 (Rupees Three Hundred and Thirty-one Crores Fifty-Three Lakhs and Twenty-five Thousand only). This investment will provide Cupid&apos;s FMCG product portfolio with a strong platform to scale across key regional markets, with the store network expected to expand to over 500 locations within the next 3 years. The preferential warrants will be converted into equity shares within the timelines as per ICDR regulations, 2018, with 25% of the issue amount paid at the time of allotment and the balance 75% at the time of exercise of the right of conversion.</p><ul><li>Cupid Limited to invest Rs. 331 Crores in Baazar Style Retail Limited</li><li>Strategic investment to strengthen Cupid&apos;s retail presence and expand consumer reach</li><li>Baazar Style Retail Limited operates over 250 stores and aims to expand to 500 locations within the next 3 years</li><li>Cupid&apos;s FMCG product portfolio will be an integral part of the store network&apos;s growth</li><li>Preferential warrants to be converted into equity shares within the timelines as per ICDR regulations, 2018</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/30134a8f-5e21-4dd4-a16b-50a769a83a48.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CUPID LTD.-$ | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>