<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 21:20:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[TCIEXP*] TCI Express Ltd. May Recommend Interim Dividend for FY 25-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TCI+Express+Ltd&title=TCI+Express+Ltd.+May+Recommend+Interim+Dividend+for+FY+25-26&newsId=ebeeb2c3-ea44-473f-9de8-0f433e44b277&token=ZWJlZWIyYzMtZWE0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ebeeb2c3-ea44-473f-9de8-0f433e44b277</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>TCI Express Ltd. is set to convene a Board of Directors meeting on February 03, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The Board may also consider/recommend an interim dividend for the financial year 2025-26. The record date for the dividend, if declared, would be Saturday, February 07, 2026. The trading window for dealing in the equity shares of the Company will remain closed from Thursday, January 1, 2026, to 48 hours after the communication of the financial results.</p><ul><li>TCI Express Ltd. to consider interim dividend for FY 25-26</li><li>Board meeting scheduled for February 03, 2026</li><li>Un-audited financial results for Q3 and nine months ending December 31, 2025, to be approved</li><li>Record date for dividend payment set for Saturday, February 07, 2026</li><li>Trading window for equity shares closed from January 1, 2026, to 48 hours post financial results communication</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7ed374f4-c6c2-49aa-8d5a-5d9d0a53ed2a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TCI Express Ltd | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ALLTIME] EU Suspends GSP Benefits on Plastic Products for All Time Plastics Ltd Until 2028</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=All+Time+Plastics+Ltd&title=EU+Suspends+GSP+Benefits+on+Plastic+Products+for+All+Time+Plastics+Ltd+Until+2028&newsId=fd386b5b-e3b2-43f4-9d43-f28317f322be&token=ZmQzODZiNWItZTNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd386b5b-e3b2-43f4-9d43-f28317f322be</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>All Time Plastics Ltd has clarified the suspension of European Union (EU) Generalised Scheme of Preferences (GSP) benefits for certain product sections, including Section S-7a — Plastics and articles thereof, for India. The suspension, which started on 1 January 2023, has been extended until 31 December 2028. Plastic products exported by the Company fall under Section S-7a, and accordingly, GSP tariff benefits for such products have not been available since 1 January 2023. The Company confirms that there is no change in applicable duty rates or pricing arrangements for its EU customers.</p><ul><li>EU suspended GSP tariff preferences for certain product sections, including Section S-7a — Plastics and articles thereof, for India until 2028</li><li>Plastic products exported by All Time Plastics Ltd fall under Section S-7a and are not eligible for GSP tariff benefits since 1 January 2023</li><li>There is no change in applicable duty rates or pricing arrangements for the Company&apos;s EU customers</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e5456f96-3d02-48dd-ba29-1204ff364d45.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: All Time Plastics Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TCIEXP*] TCI Express Ltd. to Consider Interim Dividend in February 2026 Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TCI+Express+Ltd&title=TCI+Express+Ltd.+to+Consider+Interim+Dividend+in+February+2026+Board+Meeting&newsId=68a7696a-c501-41b9-b6c6-505e9cb1da99&token=NjhhNzY5NmEtYzUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68a7696a-c501-41b9-b6c6-505e9cb1da99</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>TCI Express Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 3, 2026, to consider and approve the recommendation of an interim dividend for the financial year 2025-26. The meeting will also consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. If declared, the record date for the purpose would be February 7, 2026. The trading window for dealing in the equity shares of the Company will remain closed from January 1, 2026, to 48 hours after the communication of the said financial results.</p><ul><li>TCI Express Ltd. to consider interim dividend for the financial year 2025-26</li><li>Board meeting scheduled on February 3, 2026, to consider and approve un-audited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Record date for interim dividend set for February 7, 2026</li><li>Trading window for equity shares to remain closed from January 1, 2026, to 48 hours after financial results communication</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9b0cb9d9-f454-4ed8-8f91-c81abd11701f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TCI Express Ltd | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TCIEXP*] TCI Express Ltd. May Declare Interim Dividend for FY 25-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TCI+Express+Ltd&title=TCI+Express+Ltd.+May+Declare+Interim+Dividend+for+FY+25-26&newsId=9cb3b1cc-5f04-4cf9-a0c0-ec9d9fbd9f96&token=OWNiM2IxY2MtNWYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9cb3b1cc-5f04-4cf9-a0c0-ec9d9fbd9f96</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>TCI Express Ltd. is set to convene a Board of Directors meeting on February 03, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The Board may also consider/recommend an interim dividend on the equity shares of the Company for the financial year 2025-26. The record date for the purpose would be Saturday, February 07, 2026. The trading window for dealing in the equity shares of the Company will be closed from Thursday, January 1, 2026, to 48 hours after the communication of the financial results. This disclosure is as per the SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirements) Regulation, 2015.</p><ul><li>TCI Express Ltd. to consider interim dividend for FY 25-26</li><li>Board meeting scheduled on February 03, 2026</li><li>Record date set for Saturday, February 07, 2026</li><li>Trading window for equity shares to close on January 1, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2efe21be-d679-4a53-afa5-a9b47bdd1802.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TCI Express Ltd | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TCIEXP*] TCI Express Completes Acquisition of TCI Global (Singapore) Pte. Ltd. for SGD 18,000</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TCI+Express+Ltd&title=TCI+Express+Completes+Acquisition+of+TCI+Global+%28Singapore%29+Pte.+Ltd.+for+SGD+18%2C000&newsId=f5001aa0-15f7-4855-9e4f-1a809f0e09be&token=ZjUwMDFhYTAtMTVm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f5001aa0-15f7-4855-9e4f-1a809f0e09be</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>TCI Express Ltd has completed the acquisition of 100% equity shares of TCI Global (Singapore) Pte. Ltd. from TCI Holdings Asia Pacific Pte. Ltd. The transaction, valued at SGD 18,000, was completed in cash and TCI Global (Singapore) Pte. Ltd. has become a step-down wholly owned subsidiary of TCI Express Limited. TCI Global (Singapore) Pte. Ltd., incorporated in 2006, is engaged in the business of transport, logistics, and related services.</p><ul><li>TCI Express Ltd completes acquisition of TCI Global (Singapore) Pte. Ltd.</li><li>Transaction valued at SGD 18,000</li><li>TCI Global (Singapore) Pte. Ltd. becomes a step-down wholly owned subsidiary of TCI Express Limited</li><li>TCI Global (Singapore) Pte. Ltd. incorporated in 2006 and engaged in transport, logistics, and related services</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f457a3fd-5af1-4dde-b390-9fe9316ab81e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TCI Express Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[COFORGE] Coforge and Innovaccer Partner to Accelerate AI Transformation in Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Coforge+Ltd&title=Coforge+and+Innovaccer+Partner+to+Accelerate+AI+Transformation+in+Healthcare&newsId=0ef19da7-1f42-4c5c-9723-44860e961aed&token=MGVmMTlkYTctMWY0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ef19da7-1f42-4c5c-9723-44860e961aed</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Partnership</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Coforge, a global digital services and solutions provider, and Innovaccer, a leading healthcare AI company, have announced a strategic partnership to improve care delivery and patient outcomes. The partnership combines Coforge&apos;s domain expertise in driving organizational transformation with Innovaccer’s AI infrastructure and data platform, aiming to drive measurable improvements in clinical, financial and administrative results for healthcare organizations. The two firms have launched G-Forge, a joint initiative to help healthcare organizations scale AI, integrate siloed data, and improve enterprise decision-making.</p><ul><li>Strategic partnership between Coforge and Innovaccer to improve care delivery and patient outcomes in the healthcare ecosystem.</li><li>Combination of Coforge&apos;s domain expertise and Innovaccer’s AI infrastructure and data platform to drive measurable improvements in clinical, financial and administrative results for healthcare organizations.</li><li>Launch of G-Forge, a joint initiative to help healthcare organizations scale AI, integrate siloed data, and improve enterprise decision-making.</li><li>Coforge as the preferred platinum implementation partner for Innovaccer’s Gravity AI platform, establishing a Healthcare AI Center of Excellence.</li><li>Development of industry-specific accelerators and solutions in the areas of member and provider experience, care management, and revenue cycle management.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b136a5f0-8783-422e-b2c0-e92d9a791a18.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Coforge Ltd | Category: Partnership</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IFGLEXPOR] IFGL Refractories&apos; UK Subsidiary Appoints New Statutory Auditors, Hebblethwaites</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IFGL+Refractories+Ltd&title=IFGL+Refractories%27+UK+Subsidiary+Appoints+New+Statutory+Auditors%2C+Hebblethwaites&newsId=f38453bc-3f0e-4615-8773-a59cc52ef9ab&token=ZjM4NDUzYmMtM2Yw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f38453bc-3f0e-4615-8773-a59cc52ef9ab</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 16:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Further to a previous announcement, IFGL Refractories Ltd&apos;s material subsidiary, M/s Sheffield Refractories Ltd, UK, has appointed Hebblethwaites, Chartered Accountants and Registered Auditors as their Statutory Auditors. Hebblethwaites is a well-established firm based in Sheffield, South Yorkshire, offering a range of professional services including audit, accounting, tax, and business advisory. This disclosure is in accordance with applicable laws, rules, and regulations of the United Kingdom and is also available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>IFGL Refractories&apos; UK subsidiary appoints new Statutory Auditors</li><li>New auditors, Hebblethwaites, are a well-established firm of Chartered Accountants and Registered Auditors based in Sheffield, South Yorkshire</li><li>Hebblethwaites provide a range of professional services including audit, accounting, tax, and business advisory</li><li>Appointment is in accordance with applicable laws, rules, and regulations of the United Kingdom</li><li>Disclosure is available on the company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e40a7428-dd67-452e-9445-92357d1a2afe.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IFGL Refractories Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STALLION] Stallion India Fluorochemicals Ltd to Consider and Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months of FY2025-2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Stallion+India+Fluorochemicals+Ltd&title=Stallion+India+Fluorochemicals+Ltd+to+Consider+and+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+nine+months+of+FY2025-2026&newsId=8c6f18b6-344b-4bf9-bcbe-360311c8a674&token=OGM2ZjE4YjYtMzQ0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c6f18b6-344b-4bf9-bcbe-360311c8a674</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Stallion India Fluorochemicals Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 29th January 2026 to consider and approve the unaudited financial results (standalone and consolidated) for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December 2025. This is in accordance with the Regulation 29 of SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, as amended from time to time.</p><ul><li>Stallion India Fluorochemicals Ltd to consider and approve unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months of FY2025-2026</li><li>The meeting is scheduled on 29th January 2026</li><li>The financial results are for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December 2025</li><li>The consideration and approval is in accordance with the Regulation 29 of SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, as amended from time to time</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2b95d91b-b609-4968-a2de-e4e5cbf176cc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Stallion India Fluorochemicals Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RCL] Radhagobind Commercial LTD Receives Provisional List of Expressions of Interest</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Radhagobind+Commercial+Ltd&title=Radhagobind+Commercial+LTD+Receives+Provisional+List+of+Expressions+of+Interest&newsId=c04d32f3-2d76-4990-8f92-d9181a3aed95&token=YzA0ZDMyZjMtMmQ3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c04d32f3-2d76-4990-8f92-d9181a3aed95</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:51:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Radhagobind Commercial Ltd has submitted a provisional list of Expressions of Interest (EOIs) for Section 25(2)(h) of the IBC in compliance with SEBI regulations. The list includes Anuj Jalan, Bhawarlal Camellia Tradex Private Limited, Madhusudhana Reddy, M Dynamic Services and Security Limited, and several other applicants. This compilation is provisional, subject to further verification and updates, and has been filed in good faith to ensure transparency and adherence to regulatory timelines.</p><ul><li>Radhagobind Commercial LTD submits provisional EOIs for Section 25(2)(h) of the IBC.</li><li>List includes Anuj Jalan, Bhawarlal Camellia Tradex Private Limited, Madhusudhana Reddy, and M Dynamic Services and Security Limited among others.</li><li>Compilation is provisional and subject to further verification and updates.</li><li>Filed in good faith to ensure transparency and adherence to regulatory timelines.</li><li>Includes various individual applicants, consortiums, and joint ventures.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2d9a1fc3-ef43-405f-90e9-32f95b060db4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Radhagobind Commercial Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MARCLOIRE] Marc Loire Fashions Ltd Opens New Store, Total Count Now 4</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Marc+Loire+Fashions+Ltd&title=Marc+Loire+Fashions+Ltd+Opens+New+Store%2C+Total+Count+Now+4&newsId=59cb6aed-429d-4c69-9851-16cfa3e38157&token=NTljYjZhZWQtNDI5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59cb6aed-429d-4c69-9851-16cfa3e38157</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:11:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pursuant to Regulation 30 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, Marc Loire Fashions Ltd has announced the opening of a new store in Delhi- 110033. This brings the total number of stores to 4.</p><ul><li>Marc Loire Fashions Ltd has opened a new store</li><li>The new store is located at B-12/B, Majlis Park, Adarsh Nagar, Delhi- 110033</li><li>This brings the total number of stores to 4</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0bc909d2-afe4-431c-a9fa-ca7722153f0a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Marc Loire Fashions Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>