<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 09:26:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[PLASTIBLEN] Plastiblends India Ltd Announces Q3 Financial Results with 7.01% EBITDA Margin</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PLASTIBLENDS+INDIA+LTD.-%24&title=Plastiblends+India+Ltd+Announces+Q3+Financial+Results+with+7.01%25+EBITDA+Margin&newsId=757294be-d5e5-4582-b0ef-6875d4c14889&token=NzU3Mjk0YmUtZDVl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">757294be-d5e5-4582-b0ef-6875d4c14889</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 09:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Plastiblends India Ltd, a leading Masterbatch Manufacturing Company, announced its financial results for the third quarter ended 31st December 2025. The company reported a revenue from operations of Rs. 18,580 lakhs for the quarter and Rs. 57,804 lakhs for the nine months ended 31st December 2025. The EBITDA margin for the quarter was 7.01%. The company continues to enjoy market and brand leadership.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter is Rs. 18,580 lakhs</li><li>EBITDA for the quarter is Rs. 1,302 lakhs</li><li>PAT for the quarter is Rs. 647 lakhs</li><li>GST rationalization reforms in automobiles and consumer durable segments are expected to boost revenue</li><li>Rupee weakening raised input cost</li><li>Multiple geopolitical tensions impacted the export market</li><li>Expansion of engineering plastic division was undertaken</li><li>Augmentation of solar capacity by 5 MW is progressing well</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ddf01fac-fe45-4ee4-9621-f1392e183e87.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PLASTIBLENDS INDIA LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WONDERLA] Wonderla Holidays Ltd to Approve Q3 FY2025-26 Financial Results on Feb 4, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Wonderla+Holidays+Ltd&title=Wonderla+Holidays+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+FY2025-26+Financial+Results+on+Feb+4%2C+2026&newsId=37d31c3f-e609-4787-9592-b9e62ca14f77&token=MzdkMzFjM2YtZTYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37d31c3f-e609-4787-9592-b9e62ca14f77</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 09:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Wonderla Holidays Ltd has announced a Board of Directors meeting on February 4, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. This meeting is in accordance with Regulation 29 of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Wonderla Holidays Ltd scheduled a Board of Directors meeting on February 4, 2026.</li><li>The meeting aims to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for Q3 FY2025-26.</li><li>The quarter ended on December 31, 2025.</li><li>The announcement is in accordance with Regulation 29 of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2d10d7b8-f39f-431a-b837-df367d6a9100.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Wonderla Holidays Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PTL] PTL Enterprises Ltd. Reports on Transfer Request of Physical Shares Under SEBI Special Window</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PTL+ENTERPRISES+LTD.-%24&title=PTL+Enterprises+Ltd.+Reports+on+Transfer+Request+of+Physical+Shares+Under+SEBI+Special+Window&newsId=f3972775-7f0f-432f-b78d-c339d3ef20b2&token=ZjM5NzI3NzUtN2Yw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3972775-7f0f-432f-b78d-c339d3ef20b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 09:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>PTL Enterprises Ltd. has submitted a report from its Registrar and Transfer Agent, Alankit Assignments Limited, regarding transfer requests for physical shares that were re-lodged for transfer cum demat during the period from November 01, 2025 to January 06, 2026. The report, which is in accordance with SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97, provides the status of these requests as of January 6th, 2026.</p><ul><li>PTL Enterprises Ltd. has reported on transfer requests of physical shares under the special window provided by the SEBI Circular.</li><li>The report is based on the period from November 01, 2025 to January 06, 2026.</li><li>The status of these requests is provided as of January 6th, 2026.</li><li>The report is in accordance with SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97.</li><li>The report was submitted by the company&apos;s Registrar and Transfer Agent, Alankit Assignments Limited.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/efa2bc85-969a-4d34-b6dc-f6af25e85881.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PTL ENTERPRISES LTD.-$ | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDBANK] Indbank Merchant Banking Services Ltd Announces Q3 Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDBANK+MERCHANT+BANKING+SERVICES+LTD.&title=Indbank+Merchant+Banking+Services+Ltd+Announces+Q3+Results+for+2025&newsId=6704b250-b792-4f09-a8b1-5b7fe87a6e46&token=NjcwNGIyNTAtYjc5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6704b250-b792-4f09-a8b1-5b7fe87a6e46</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 09:13:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indbank Merchant Banking Services Ltd, a subsidiary of Indian Bank, announced its financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at Rs. 258.19 lakhs, with a profit before tax of Rs. 591.11 lakhs. The company operates at one segment as per IND-AS. The financial results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations stands at Rs. 258.19 lakhs</li><li>Profit before tax is Rs. 591.11 lakhs</li><li>The company operates at one segment as per IND-AS</li><li>Financial results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee</li><li>Approved by the Board of Directors</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2026ac90-2fe7-4f0e-b2e8-2ef2b3d3d58e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDBANK MERCHANT BANKING SERVICES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUNPHARMA] Life Insurance Corporation of India Acquires 0.008% Shares in Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SUN+PHARMACEUTICAL+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Life+Insurance+Corporation+of+India+Acquires+0.008%25+Shares+in+Sun+Pharmaceutical+Industries+Ltd&newsId=b9a060d3-8209-4551-bdd6-00cb38fb047f&token=YjlhMDYwZDMtODIw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b9a060d3-8209-4551-bdd6-00cb38fb047f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 09:13:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC) has acquired 2,02,500 shares carrying voting rights in Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd. This represents 0.008% of the total shares of the company. The acquisition was made on 13th January 2026. Post-acquisition, LIC holds 12,00,79,148 shares carrying voting rights, which is 5.004% of the total shares of Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd.</p><ul><li>Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC) acquires 0.008% shares in Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd</li><li>LIC acquires 2,02,500 shares carrying voting rights in Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd</li><li>Post-acquisition, LIC holds 5.004% shares in Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd</li><li>The acquisition was made on 13th January 2026</li><li>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd is listed on BSE and NSE</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/48184219_AD41_423D_82AB_63E0EDAD0DF0_144144.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SUN PHARMACEUTICAL INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DEEPAKFERT] Deepak Fertilisers &amp; Petrochemicals Corporation Ltd. Receives Order for Penalty Reduction</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DEEPAK+FERTILISERS+%26+PETROCHEMICALS+CORPORATION+LTD.&title=Deepak+Fertilisers+%26+Petrochemicals+Corporation+Ltd.+Receives+Order+for+Penalty+Reduction&newsId=84e35ce0-e88f-4fe1-b23e-76a6d3b0d7c8&token=ODRlMzVjZTAtZTg4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">84e35ce0-e88f-4fe1-b23e-76a6d3b0d7c8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 09:10:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Deepak Fertilisers &amp; Petrochemicals Corporation Ltd. has received an order from the Joint Commissioner of State Tax (JC- Appeals) authority in Pune, reducing the tax demand and penalty imposed on the company. The order, passed on 13th January 2026, reduces the total demand from Rs.95,60,58,493/- to Rs.95,20,58,543/-. The company does not admit to any violation or contravention, but the Department has disallowed the input tax credit claimed due to non-reflection in GSTR2A and ineligible credit. The company has taken a legal view that the demand is not tenable and is liable to be set aside in appeal. The company will challenge the order at an appropriate forum.</p><ul><li>Deepak Fertilisers &amp; Petrochemicals Corporation Ltd. receives an order from the JC- Appeals authority in Pune</li><li>The order reduces the total tax demand from Rs.95,60,58,493/- to Rs.95,20,58,543/-</li><li>The company does not admit to any violation or contravention</li><li>The company will challenge the order at an appropriate forum</li><li>The decision is not expected to have a material impact on the company&apos;s financials or operations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ef3eaa29-b763-4051-ac1a-61dbc4c11679.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DEEPAK FERTILISERS & PETROCHEMICALS CORPORATION LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KARURVYSYA] Karur Vysya Bank Schedules Conference Call for Q3 2025 Results Disclosure</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KARUR+VYSYA+BANK+LTD.&title=Karur+Vysya+Bank+Schedules+Conference+Call+for+Q3+2025+Results+Disclosure&newsId=d0036e57-e932-49a0-9149-7074e3a81670&token=ZDAwMzZlNTctZTkz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d0036e57-e932-49a0-9149-7074e3a81670</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 09:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Karur Vysya Bank Ltd has announced a conference call for investors and analysts to discuss the bank&apos;s unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The conference call is scheduled for Friday, January 23, 2026, at 6.00 P.M. IST.</p><ul><li>Bank to disclose unaudited financial results for Q3 2025</li><li>Conference call scheduled for January 23, 2026, at 6.00 P.M. IST</li><li>Conference dial-in details provided for domestic and international participants</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4B7BE89A-5D44-4E93-A41F-4ABA4C961CA7-143219.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KARUR VYSYA BANK LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HDFCAMC] HDFC Asset Management Company Ltd Announces Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HDFC+Asset+Management+Company+Ltd&title=HDFC+Asset+Management+Company+Ltd+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=6c33e4ea-4268-4ebb-85e5-8a5cbc213d05&token=NmMzM2U0ZWEtNDI2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c33e4ea-4268-4ebb-85e5-8a5cbc213d05</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 09:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>HDFC Asset Management Company Ltd announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 1,074.25 crore for the quarter and 3,068.05 crore for the nine months period. The total income for the quarter is 1,233.23 crore and 3,555.59 crore for the nine months period. The company&apos;s profit before tax stands at 1,014.6 crore and the profit after tax is 770 crore. The earnings per equity share (Face value of 5 each) for the quarter is 17.98 and 52.25 for the nine months period.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter is 1,074.25 crore</li><li>Total income for the quarter is 1,233.23 crore</li><li>Profit before tax for the quarter is 1,014.6 crore</li><li>Profit after tax for the quarter is 770 crore</li><li>Earnings per equity share for the quarter is 17.98</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9fefce17-b29a-47ca-9521-1e478c3b200f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HDFC Asset Management Company Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDBANK] Indbank Merchant Banking Services Ltd Approves Q3 Results for FY2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDBANK+MERCHANT+BANKING+SERVICES+LTD.&title=Indbank+Merchant+Banking+Services+Ltd+Approves+Q3+Results+for+FY2025-26&newsId=4c486343-6cd4-45f0-965e-23ed4568f4bd&token=NGM0ODYzNDMtNmNk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4c486343-6cd4-45f0-965e-23ed4568f4bd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 09:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indbank Merchant Banking Services Ltd, a subsidiary of Indian Bank, announced its un-audited financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The meeting was held on 14.01.2026 and the results were approved by the Board of Directors. The company operates at one segment as per IND-AS. The financial results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and the statutory auditors have issued an unmodified audit opinion.</p><ul><li>Q3 results for FY2025-26 approved</li><li>Revenue from operations stands at Rs. 258.19 Lakhs</li><li>Profit for the period from continuing operations is Rs. 4,437.82 Lakhs</li><li>Earnings per equity share - Basic and Diluted is Rs. 117.39</li><li>Reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3d238cc3-149e-4f18-ad7a-27882853e42c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDBANK MERCHANT BANKING SERVICES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SANGAMIND] Sangam India Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Unaudited Financial Results on January 21, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SANGAM+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Sangam+India+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Unaudited+Financial+Results+on+January+21%2C+2026&newsId=494b807d-a743-4d85-96ec-90516fcb43dc&token=NDk0YjgwN2QtYTc0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">494b807d-a743-4d85-96ec-90516fcb43dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 09:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sangam India Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 21, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results (Standalone and Consolidated) for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The meeting is scheduled in accordance with Regulation 29 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The trading window for dealing in the equity shares of the Company was closed for the designated persons from 1st January, 2026 till the expiry of 48 hours after the declaration of Unaudited Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Sangam India Ltd to approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December, 2025</li><li>Meeting of the Board of Directors scheduled on 21st January, 2026</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the equity shares of the Company closed for designated persons from 1st January, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6f80f837-4277-4177-a22f-faa62bf9d389.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SANGAM (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>