<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 12:38:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SUDARSHAN] SEBI Regulation 30: GST Department Initiates Inspection, Search, and Seizure at Sudarshan Pharma Industries Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sudarshan+Pharma+Industries+Ltd&title=SEBI+Regulation+30%3A+GST+Department+Initiates+Inspection%2C+Search%2C+and+Seizure+at+Sudarshan+Pharma+Industries+Ltd&newsId=670101b2-9d19-4a70-a904-c0db6d037299&token=NjcwMTAxYjItOWQx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">670101b2-9d19-4a70-a904-c0db6d037299</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 12:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sudarshan Pharma Industries Ltd, under SEBI Regulation 30, has confirmed an inspection, search, and seizure operation initiated by the Goods &amp; Service Tax Department, Mumbai Maharashtra, at their registered office. The company is fully cooperating with the GST Department and is in the process of collecting and responding to all queries. Upon conclusion of the event, any material developments will be intimated in due course. The business operations of the company continued as usual during the said event.</p><ul><li>SEBI Regulation 30 confirmation from Sudarshan Pharma Industries Ltd</li><li>GST Department inspection, search, and seizure operation initiated</li><li>Company is fully cooperating with the GST Department</li><li>Material developments to be intimated upon conclusion of the event</li><li>Business operations remained unaffected during the event</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1db1740b-330f-4c04-abed-197ed20121e1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sudarshan Pharma Industries Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STYLEBAAZA] Baazar Style Retail Ltd Opens New Store in Jharkhand, Expanding Retail Footprint to 258 Outlets</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Baazar+Style+Retail+Ltd&title=Baazar+Style+Retail+Ltd+Opens+New+Store+in+Jharkhand%2C+Expanding+Retail+Footprint+to+258+Outlets&newsId=12274189-e7a4-4e64-b88b-19fa354bc204&token=MTIyNzQxODktZTdh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12274189-e7a4-4e64-b88b-19fa354bc204</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 07:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Baazar Style Retail Ltd, formerly known as Baazar Style Retail Pvt. Ltd., has announced the opening of a new Style Baazar store in Morabadi, Jharkhand. This addition expands the company&apos;s total number of stores to 258, as of the date of this announcement. The company is committed to complying with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Baazar Style Retail Ltd has opened a new Style Baazar store in Morabadi, Jharkhand.</li><li>The company now has a total of 258 stores across various locations.</li><li>This announcement is in compliance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6ebce6d0-a861-4edf-ae74-59281ee8ba86.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Baazar Style Retail Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ICICIBANK] ICICI Bank Faces Rs. 50,38 Crore Tax Demand from Maharashtra GST Department</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ICICI+BANK+LTD.&title=ICICI+Bank+Faces+Rs.+50%2C38+Crore+Tax+Demand+from+Maharashtra+GST+Department&newsId=12ff3795-8524-4c38-966a-08791b22005b&token=MTJmZjM3OTUtODUy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12ff3795-8524-4c38-966a-08791b22005b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 06:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>On January 4, 2025, ICICI Bank Ltd received an order in original (OIO) from the Maharashtra Goods and Services Tax (GST) Department for a tax demand of Rs. 50,38,09,792/- and an equivalent amount of penalty and interest. The Bank filed an appeal against the OIO. On February 21, 2026, the Bank received an Order in Appeal (OIA) under Section 107 of the Central Goods and Services Tax Act, 2017 from the Maharashtra GST Department, maintaining the tax demand and penalty. The Bank plans to contest the OIA through a further appeal within prescribed timelines.</p><ul><li>ICICI Bank received an OIO from Maharashtra GST Department for a tax demand of Rs. 50,38 crore</li><li>The Bank filed an appeal against the OIO</li><li>Bank received an OIA under Section 107 of the Central Goods and Services Tax Act, 2017</li><li>OIA maintained the tax demand and penalty</li><li>ICICI Bank to contest the OIA through a further appeal</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9d4e04ee-0f4e-4f41-a2e7-17c86f3a6c45.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ICICI BANK LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[QUADRANT] Quadrant Televentures Ltd Extends Invitation for Expression of Interest</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Quadrant+Televentures+Limited-%24&title=Quadrant+Televentures+Ltd+Extends+Invitation+for+Expression+of+Interest&newsId=f2a9fd97-95e8-4409-b218-bbe59b9fded1&token=ZjJhOWZkOTctOTVl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f2a9fd97-95e8-4409-b218-bbe59b9fded1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 05:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Invitation for Expression of Interest</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Quadrant Televentures Ltd, a telecommunication and broadband services provider in Punjab and adjoining areas, has extended the last date for receipt of Expression of Interest (EOI) to 02.03.2026. The company, which reported a revenue of Rs. 273.97 Crores in FY 2024-2025, has a total of 1222 employees and its equity shares are listed with BSE. The last available financial statements and other relevant details can be obtained from the company&apos;s website or by sending an email to gtl.ibc@gmail.com. The eligibility criteria for resolution applicants are also available at the same location. The last date for submission of objections to the provisional list of prospective resolution applicants is now 17.03.2026.</p><ul><li>Quadrant Televentures Ltd extends last date for EOI to 02.03.2026</li><li>Company reported revenue of Rs. 273.97 Crores in FY 2024-2025</li><li>Total of 1222 employees</li><li>Equity shares listed with BSE</li><li>Last date for submission of objections to provisional list extended to 17.03.2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1461cfb0-3ed5-4ca0-9d67-77d3c441ebe7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Quadrant Televentures Limited-$ | Category: Invitation for Expression of Interest</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MINDSPACE] Mindspace EcoRun 2.0 Returns for Second Year with Over 4200 Runners in Hyderabad</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Mindspace+Business+Parks+REIT&title=Mindspace+EcoRun+2.0+Returns+for+Second+Year+with+Over+4200+Runners+in+Hyderabad&newsId=31f44fb1-0b90-49b4-b8fc-97cea2484487&token=MzFmNDRmYjEtMGI5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">31f44fb1-0b90-49b4-b8fc-97cea2484487</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 04:01:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mindspace Business Parks REIT, in association with Mirchi, successfully hosted the second edition of &apos;Mindspace EcoRun 2.0&apos; on February 22, 2026, at Mindspace Madhapur, Hyderabad. The sustainability-led marathon saw participation from over 4200 runners across different age groups. The event was designed around a planet-friendly experience, featuring eco-conscious race kits and waste management practices. Post-event, the waste collected will be upcycled into functional chairs for school children associated with the NGO partner Nirmaan.</p><ul><li>Mindspace REIT and Mirchi successfully hosted the second edition of Mindspace EcoRun 2.0 with over 4200 runners in Hyderabad.</li><li>The event was designed around a planet-friendly experience, incorporating eco-conscious race kits and waste management practices.</li><li>The waste collected post-event will be upcycled into functional chairs for school children associated with the NGO partner Nirmaan.</li><li>The marathon welcomed participants from different age groups, fostering a strong community turnout across Hyderabad’s workplace and neighbourhood ecosystem.</li><li>The second edition of Mindspace EcoRun reflects Mindspace REIT’s continued commitment to integrating sustainability into every aspect of their developments.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cf5725d1-b608-434a-b077-adcc43851200.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Mindspace Business Parks REIT | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IDFCFIRSTB] IDFC First Bank Ltd Identifies Fraudulent Activities of Approximately INR 590 Crore in a Chandigarh Branch</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IDFC+First+Bank+Ltd&title=IDFC+First+Bank+Ltd+Identifies+Fraudulent+Activities+of+Approximately+INR+590+Crore+in+a+Chandigarh+Branch&newsId=ad13fcdd-347c-45d0-9e72-1905abf28921&token=YWQxM2ZjZGQtMzQ3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad13fcdd-347c-45d0-9e72-1905abf28921</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 04:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>IDFC First Bank Ltd has identified unauthorized and fraudulent activities by certain employees at a particular branch in Chandigarh. The fraud involves accounts held by certain departments of the Government of Haryana and potentially other individuals/entities. The preliminary internal assessment shows an approximate reconciliation amount of INR 590 crore. The bank has taken actions including placing suspected officials under suspension, pursuing strict disciplinary, civil, and criminal actions, and cooperating with investigating agencies. An independent external agency has been appointed to conduct a forensic audit.</p><ul><li>IDFC First Bank Ltd identified fraudulent activities in a Chandigarh branch involving Government of Haryana accounts.</li><li>The preliminary internal assessment shows an approximate reconciliation amount of INR 590 crore.</li><li>Four suspected officials have been placed under suspension pending investigation.</li><li>An independent external agency has been appointed to conduct a forensic audit.</li><li>The bank has filed a complaint with the Police authorities and will extend full cooperation to the investigating agencies.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f52c7126-9362-4f4e-9110-09f1efe0f610.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IDFC First Bank Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UNIABEXAL] Uni Abex Alloy Products Ltd Receives Rs. 257.88 Crore from Land Sale in Thane</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=UNI+ABEX+ALLOY+PRODUCTS+LTD.&title=Uni+Abex+Alloy+Products+Ltd+Receives+Rs.+257.88+Crore+from+Land+Sale+in+Thane&newsId=bc9d4941-7e7d-4729-a639-fcc0ecfb4ea0&token=YmM5ZDQ5NDEtN2U3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc9d4941-7e7d-4729-a639-fcc0ecfb4ea0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 17:11:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Sale</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Uni Abex Alloy Products Ltd has informed about the completion of the sale of its land at Thane. The company has received the entire sale proceeds of approximately Rs. 257.88 crore, which includes an advance amount of Rs. 48.85 crore and an additional amount of Rs. 13.65 crore for an additional area of 2,008 sq mts. Post this sale, the company now holds only a marginal area of 2,520 sq mtrs of Thane Land.</p><ul><li>Uni Abex Alloy Products Ltd has completed the sale of its land at Thane</li><li>The company has received the entire sale proceeds of approximately Rs. 257.88 crore</li><li>This includes an advance amount of Rs. 48.85 crore and an additional amount of Rs. 13.65 crore for an additional area of 2,008 sq mts</li><li>Post sale, the company now holds only a marginal area of 2,520 sq mtrs of Thane Land</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/367ba6f9-5ece-44b4-a69e-e91c25ff5654.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: UNI ABEX ALLOY PRODUCTS LTD. | Category: Sale</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HEG] HEG Ltd. Violates SEBI Regulations: Designated Persons&apos; Trading Infringements</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HEG+LTD.&title=HEG+Ltd.+Violates+SEBI+Regulations%3A+Designated+Persons%27+Trading+Infringements&newsId=bbdc79e0-7358-43e0-b5ee-811a5604994e&token=YmJkYzc5ZTAtNzM1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bbdc79e0-7358-43e0-b5ee-811a5604994e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 17:02:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>HEG Ltd. has reported violations of the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, and its Code of Conduct for Regulating, Monitoring &amp; Reporting Trading by Insiders. The violations were committed by designated persons in accordance with SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/ISD/ISD/CIR/P/2020/135 dated July 23, 2020. The violations include trading without pre-clearance, contra trade, and non-disclosure of transactions to the Company. The Company has advised the concerned persons to sell their entire equity shares of HEG Limited and deposit the sale proceeds into the designated account of the SEBI. The Company has also directed the concerned persons to inform their Portfolio Management Services (PMS) provider or broker to place the scrip of HEG Limited on the restricted/negative list.</p><ul><li>HEG Ltd. reports violations of SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, and its Code of Conduct for Regulating, Monitoring &amp; Reporting Trading by Insiders.</li><li>Designated persons committed violations involving trading without pre-clearance, contra trade, and non-disclosure of transactions to the Company.</li><li>Company directs concerned persons to sell their entire equity shares of HEG Limited and deposit the sale proceeds into the designated account of the SEBI.</li><li>Company advises concerned persons to inform their PMS provider or broker to place the scrip of HEG Limited on the restricted/negative list.</li><li>Corrective and preventive measures are taken to ensure regulatory compliance, uphold corporate governance, and maintain market integrity.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e9c28a64-1874-4479-b328-142d19838066.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HEG LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GRERENEW] GRE Renew Enertech Ltd Appoints M/s Vivek J. Vakharia &amp; Associates as Secretarial Auditor for Five Financial Years</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GRE+Renew+Enertech+Ltd&title=GRE+Renew+Enertech+Ltd+Appoints+M%2Fs+Vivek+J.+Vakharia+%26+Associates+as+Secretarial+Auditor+for+Five+Financial+Years&newsId=d985c883-f0e2-4e80-a24b-d1d10f932c87&token=ZDk4NWM4ODMtZjBl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d985c883-f0e2-4e80-a24b-d1d10f932c87</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:41:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Expansion</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>GRE Renew Enertech Ltd has appointed M/s Vivek J. Vakharia &amp; Associates, Practicing Company Secretaries, as the Secretarial Auditor of the Company for one term of five (5) consecutive financial years, i.e., from FY 2025-26 to FY 2029-30. The appointment is subject to approval of the Members of the Company at the ensuing Annual General Meeting. M/s Vivek J. Vakharia &amp; Associates is a Peer Reviewed Firm of Practicing Company Secretaries with extensive experience in Corporate, Securities and Regulatory laws.</p><ul><li>GRE Renew Enertech Ltd appoints M/s Vivek J. Vakharia &amp; Associates as Secretarial Auditor</li><li>The appointment is for a term of five (5) consecutive financial years from FY 2025-26 to FY 2029-30</li><li>The appointment is subject to approval of the Members at the ensuing Annual General Meeting</li><li>M/s Vivek J. Vakharia &amp; Associates is a Peer Reviewed Firm of Practicing Company Secretaries</li><li>The firm specializes in listing of securities on recognized stock exchanges and provides periodic and event-based compliances under various SEBI regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ae52d307-4190-4264-8b23-8d2dbf724cca.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GRE Renew Enertech Ltd | Category: Expansion</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VADILALIND] Vadilal Industries Independent Director, Shivakumar Dega, Resigns Over Non-Compliance with Minimum Wage Act</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VADILAL+INDUSTRIES+LTD.-%24&title=Vadilal+Industries+Independent+Director%2C+Shivakumar+Dega%2C+Resigns+Over+Non-Compliance+with+Minimum+Wage+Act&newsId=021cc1da-d2a1-49bb-a58a-2c023162d54e&token=MDIxY2MxZGEtZDJh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">021cc1da-d2a1-49bb-a58a-2c023162d54e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Vadilal Industries Ltd. announced the resignation of its independent director, Mr. Shivakumar Dega, due to the company&apos;s non-compliance with the Minimum Wages Act 1948 and Code of Wages 2019. Mr. Dega expressed his concerns in his resignation letter dated February 17, 2026, stating that the company has been paying its factory workers less than the minimum wage, which is a serious offence under Indian law. This violation has resulted in potential legal action for forced labour under Article 23 of the Indian Constitution. Despite raising the issue in several meetings and putting it down in writing, the board has not acted in the interests of all shareholders and the factory workers. The company is trying to stretch this liability over 2 to 4 years, which Mr. Dega strongly opposes. The board, however, seems unhappy with Mr. Dega for raising the minimum wage issue.</p><ul><li>Vadilal Industries independent director, Mr. Shivakumar Dega, resigns over non-compliance with Minimum Wages Act 1948 and Code of Wages 2019.</li><li>Company has been paying its factory workers less than the minimum wage, a serious offence under Indian law.</li><li>Potential legal action for forced labour under Article 23 of the Indian Constitution.</li><li>Despite raising the issue in several meetings, the board has not acted in the interests of all shareholders and the factory workers.</li><li>Company trying to stretch this liability over 2 to 4 years, which Mr. Dega strongly opposes.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b0290b9a-88bf-421a-8657-a3a1ad0ffb5f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VADILAL INDUSTRIES LTD.-$ | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>