<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:59:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[BECTORFOOD] Mrs. Bectors Food Specialities Ltd. Reports Utilization of QIP Proceeds for December 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Mrs.+Bectors+Food+Specialities+Ltd&title=Mrs.+Bectors+Food+Specialities+Ltd.+Reports+Utilization+of+QIP+Proceeds+for+December+2025&newsId=6d634aaa-ab9d-41a7-ac3d-600c299138fd&token=NmQ2MzRhYWEtYWI5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d634aaa-ab9d-41a7-ac3d-600c299138fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mrs. Bectors Food Specialities Ltd. has submitted a final monitoring agency report regarding the utilization of proceeds from their Qualified Institutional Placement (QIP). The report, prepared by ICRA Limited, shows that the issuance proceeds have been used in line with the objects of the issue, with no material deviations. The company has utilized funds for the Khopoli Expansion Project, financing Bakebest Foods I&apos;Drivat.ce Limited, and general corporate purposes. The total original cost was INR 388.062 Crore, but due to lower actual offer-related expenses, the actual net proceeds were revised to INR 388.673 Crore.</p><ul><li>Mrs. Bectors Food Specialities Ltd. has utilized QIP proceeds as per the objects of the issue</li><li>The total original cost was INR 388.062 Crore, but actual net proceeds were revised to INR 388.673 Crore</li><li>Funds have been used for the Khopoli Expansion Project, financing Bakebest Foods I&apos;Drivat.ce Limited, and general corporate purposes</li><li>No material deviations in the utilization of proceeds have been observed</li><li>All necessary Government approvals are available for Bectors and Pollution, Power &amp; Fire consent of New Plant is available for Bakebest</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3bb2fa15-ecfa-481a-b379-c61358e67ac6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Mrs. Bectors Food Specialities Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KSHITIJ] Kshitij Investments Ltd Approves Q3 Results, Avails Loans from Central Bank of India and State Bank of India</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kshitij+Investments+Ltd&title=Kshitij+Investments+Ltd+Approves+Q3+Results%2C+Avails+Loans+from+Central+Bank+of+India+and+State+Bank+of+India&newsId=89aa6d50-89d7-410d-adb3-549364d24b4f&token=ODlhYTZkNTAtODlk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">89aa6d50-89d7-410d-adb3-549364d24b4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kshitij Investments Ltd, formerly known as Manglam Global Corporations Limited, has approved and taken on record the unaudited Financial Results for the quarter ended on 31st December, 2025. The company has availed a WHR Loan/Credit Facilities from Central Bank of India for an amount of INR 10,00,00,000 and Loan/Credit Facilities from State Bank of India for an amount of INR 7,00,00,000. The trading window for dealing in the shares of the company for Designated Persons shall remain closed until Sunday, 15th February, 2026. The company&apos;s audit committee has reviewed the financial results, and there are no qualifications in the limited review report.</p><ul><li>Kshitij Investments Ltd approves and takes on record the unaudited Financial Results for Q3 2025</li><li>The company has availed a WHR Loan/Credit Facilities from Central Bank of India for INR 10,00,00,000</li><li>Kshitij Investments Ltd has also availed Loan/Credit Facilities from State Bank of India for INR 7,00,00,000</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the shares of the company for Designated Persons remains closed until Sunday, 15th February, 2026</li><li>No qualifications in the limited review report</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/95fae194-ca6e-4a1d-b88c-3403e73fb020.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kshitij Investments Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TRU] TruCap Finance Ltd Reports Q3 &amp; Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TruCap+Finance+Ltd&title=TruCap+Finance+Ltd+Reports+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=4e1ffb1b-d543-440f-b0c7-f5f955c5a871&token=NGUxZmZiMWItZDU0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4e1ffb1b-d543-440f-b0c7-f5f955c5a871</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:58:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>TruCap Finance Ltd has reported its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 1509.96 lakhs for the quarter and 2279.31 lakhs for the nine months period. The company has not raised any fresh funds or through issue of non-convertible securities during the quarter. The company was not in compliance with certain financial covenants under its financing arrangements, which may adversely impact its financial position. The management is actively addressing these matters and pursuing measures to enhance the company&apos;s liquidity and financial flexibility.</p><ul><li>TruCap Finance Ltd has reported its financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 1509.96 lakhs for the quarter and 2279.31 lakhs for the nine months period.</li><li>The company did not raise any fresh funds or through issue of non-convertible securities during the quarter.</li><li>TruCap Finance Ltd was not in compliance with certain financial covenants under its financing arrangements.</li><li>The management is actively addressing these matters and pursuing measures to enhance the company&apos;s liquidity and financial flexibility.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fecec031-5ac3-4e8b-8fe3-a16d2b687ca5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TruCap Finance Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AMARAJABAT] Amara Raja Energy &amp; Mobility Ltd Announces Q3 9M FY26 Financial Results with Exceptional Items</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AMARA+RAJA+BATTERIES+LTD.&title=Amara+Raja+Energy+%26+Mobility+Ltd+Announces+Q3+9M+FY26+Financial+Results+with+Exceptional+Items&newsId=90bb720b-b159-4812-a204-9f97be543c25&token=OTBiYjcyMGItYjE1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90bb720b-b159-4812-a204-9f97be543c25</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:57:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Amara Raja Energy &amp; Mobility Ltd, formerly known as Amara Raja Batteries Limited, announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 3,350.84 crores for the quarter and 10,088.94 crores for the nine-month period. The total income for the quarter is 3,377.18 crores and 10,153.30 crores for the nine-month period. The company&apos;s expenses for the quarter are 3,377.18 crores and 10,153.30 crores for the nine-month period. The net profit after tax for the quarter is 963.90 crores and 2,742.37 crores for the nine-month period. The company has presented an incremental impact of 43.80 crores as an &apos;Exceptional Item&apos; in the Standalone financial results for the quarter and nine-months ended December 31, 2025, due to the implications of the Labour Codes. The company continues to monitor the finalisation of central/state rules and other developments pertaining to labour codes.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter is 3,350.84 crores.</li><li>Total income for the quarter is 3,377.18 crores.</li><li>Net profit after tax for the quarter is 963.90 crores.</li><li>An exceptional item of 43.80 crores has been presented due to the implications of the Labour Codes.</li><li>The company continues to monitor the finalisation of central/state rules and other developments pertaining to labour codes.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3f8525f9-2a88-478d-9ead-dc1054527716.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AMARA RAJA BATTERIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PROTEAN] Protean eGov Technologies Ltd. Approves Q3FY26 Unaudited Financial Results and Announces Independent Director&apos;s Term Completion</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Protean+eGov+Technologies+Ltd&title=Protean+eGov+Technologies+Ltd.+Approves+Q3FY26+Unaudited+Financial+Results+and+Announces+Independent+Director%27s+Term+Completion&newsId=57692c7f-8e90-413a-941b-f1a7937638c8&token=NTc2OTJjN2YtOGU5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57692c7f-8e90-413a-941b-f1a7937638c8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Protean eGov Technologies Limited announced the approval of its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The Board Meeting, held on February 11, 2026, also resulted in the conclusion of Ms. Preeti Mehta&apos;s term as an Independent Director, who will cease to be a member of all the Committees of the Board from February 14, 2026. The financial results and other required disclosures are provided in the document.</p><ul><li>Protean eGov Technologies Ltd. approved the unaudited financial results for Q3FY26.</li><li>Ms. Preeti Mehta will complete her term as an Independent Director on February 14, 2026.</li><li>Ms. Preeti Mehta will cease to be a member of all the Committees of the Board from February 14, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/319e87c6-1a60-4f88-839f-54f77d330b49.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Protean eGov Technologies Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ABCOTS] A B Cotspin India Ltd Announces Q3 FY 2025-26 Results: 30.37% YoY Revenue Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=A+B+Cotspin+India+Ltd&title=A+B+Cotspin+India+Ltd+Announces+Q3+FY+2025-26+Results%3A+30.37%25+YoY+Revenue+Growth&newsId=1cf5ac78-30e2-46f5-8f65-2d1c0b245ad1&token=MWNmNWFjNzgtMzBl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1cf5ac78-30e2-46f5-8f65-2d1c0b245ad1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:55:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>A B Cotspin India Ltd, a leading textile manufacturer, announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 FY 2025-26. The company reported a revenue from operations of 194.66 cr, a YoY increase of 30.37%. The EBITDA stands at 32.77 cr, a significant increase of 37.98% YoY. The company has also expanded its operational capacity and solar power capacity, and announced a major expansion plan. The US has reduced import tariffs on select Indian products, which could potentially benefit Indian textile exporters, including A B Cotspin.</p><ul><li>Revenue from Operations increased by 30.37% YoY</li><li>EBITDA increased by 37.98% YoY</li><li>Expanded operational capacity to 50,832 spindles</li><li>Enhanced solar power footprint to 3,131 KW</li><li>Announced capacity expansion up to X1,500 crores</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c6e68d9a-0a83-43af-84b3-bbbb56398b39.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: A B Cotspin India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PARLEIND] Parle Industries Ltd to Approve Q3 Financial Results on Feb 14, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Parle+Industries+Ltd&title=Parle+Industries+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+Financial+Results+on+Feb+14%2C+2026&newsId=390225c5-8dc0-43a4-baf0-8bd59c9170a8&token=MzkwMjI1YzUtOGRj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">390225c5-8dc0-43a4-baf0-8bd59c9170a8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Parle Industries Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 14, 2026, to consider and approve the standalone and consolidated un-audited financial results for the third quarter ended 31 December, 2025. The meeting will also take note of the Limited Review Report for the same period. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company was closed from 01 January, 2026 till the expiration of 48 hours after the declaration of the un-audited financial results for the third quarter ended 31 December, 2025 i.e. 16™ February, 2026 for the Company&apos;s Directors, Officers, designated employees and other connected persons of the Company.</p><ul><li>Parle Industries Ltd to consider and approve Q3 financial results for the period ending 31 December, 2025</li><li>The meeting is scheduled on 14th February, 2026</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company was closed from 01 January, 2026 till the expiration of 48 hours after the declaration of the un-audited financial results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bc766792-58f5-4817-80b6-641c5376d17d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Parle Industries Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RAMSONS] Ramsons Projects Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Unaudited Standalone Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RAMSONS+PROJECTS+LTD.&title=Ramsons+Projects+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Unaudited+Standalone+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=5465f465-32b2-4b3e-9db9-80da6b77febf&token=NTQ2NWY0NjUtMzJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5465f465-32b2-4b3e-9db9-80da6b77febf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ramsons Projects Ltd has announced its unaudited standalone financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s total income stands at ₹ 692.48 lakhs, with a profit before tax of ₹ 51.85 lakhs. The Board of Directors approved these results in a meeting held on February 11, 2026. The review report submitted by the independent auditor, NVM &amp; Company, states that nothing has come to their attention that would cause them to believe that the financial statements contain any material misstatement.</p><ul><li>Ramsons Projects Ltd reported a total income of ₹ 692.48 lakhs for the nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s profit before tax stands at ₹ 51.85 lakhs for the same period.</li><li>The independent auditor, NVM &amp; Company, has issued a review report stating that the financial statements are free from material misstatement.</li><li>The Board of Directors approved the unaudited standalone financial results in a meeting held on February 11, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8f8adffa-b4f1-488b-bccf-d08bbde937ed.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RAMSONS PROJECTS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STARHEALTH] Star Health and Allied Insurance Appoints Mr. Himanshu Walia and Mr. Amitabh Jain as Whole-time Directors and Key Managerial Personnel</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Star+Health+and+Allied+Insurance+Company+Ltd&title=Star+Health+and+Allied+Insurance+Appoints+Mr.+Himanshu+Walia+and+Mr.+Amitabh+Jain+as+Whole-time+Directors+and+Key+Managerial+Personnel&newsId=144029c3-54d1-4d88-a8f6-6ea7da8fac61&token=MTQ0MDI5YzMtNTRk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">144029c3-54d1-4d88-a8f6-6ea7da8fac61</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:54:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Star Health and Allied Insurance Company Limited has informed the exchange about the appointment of Mr. Himanshu Walia and Mr. Amitabh Jain as Whole-time Directors and Key Managerial Personnel. The appointments are for a period of five years with effect from February 11, 2026, following the approval by the IRDAI and the Board of Directors and Shareholders. Both appointees are experienced professionals in the insurance industry, with Mr. Walia serving as Chief Marketing Officer at Star Health and Mr. Jain being a founding member of ICICI Lombard and serving as Chief Operating Officer at Star Health.</p><ul><li>Star Health and Allied Insurance Company Limited appoints Mr. Himanshu Walia and Mr. Amitabh Jain as Whole-time Directors and Key Managerial Personnel.</li><li>The appointments are for a period of five years with effect from February 11, 2026.</li><li>The appointments follow the approval by the IRDAI, Board of Directors, and Shareholders.</li><li>Mr. Himanshu Walia is an experienced professional in the insurance industry and currently serves as Chief Marketing Officer at Star Health.</li><li>Mr. Amitabh Jain is a founding member of ICICI Lombard and currently serves as Chief Operating Officer at Star Health.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8e6b5ebe-7132-408c-97de-749f81696c91.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Star Health and Allied Insurance Company Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KALYANIFRG] Kalyani Forge Ltd Appoints Jagdish Baheti as Chief Financial Officer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KALYANI+FORGE+LTD.&title=Kalyani+Forge+Ltd+Appoints+Jagdish+Baheti+as+Chief+Financial+Officer&newsId=2435f416-b73a-4d17-950c-8a8573cff42b&token=MjQzNWY0MTYtYjcz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2435f416-b73a-4d17-950c-8a8573cff42b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kalyani Forge Limited has announced the appointment of Mr. Jagdish Baheti as the Chief Financial Officer and Key Managerial Personnel of the company. The appointment is in accordance with the SEBI Listing Regulations and will take effect from February 11, 2026. Baheti is a Chartered Accountant with an MBA in Finance and has over 15 years of experience in the manufacturing industry. He has previously worked with Delfingen (French Automotive Group) and Hirschvogel Components India (A German Automotive Group). His expertise lies in budgeting, forecasting, taxation, treasury, and project finance.</p><ul><li>Jagdish Baheti appointed as Chief Financial Officer and Key Managerial Personnel</li><li>Appointment effective from February 11, 2026</li><li>Baheti is a Chartered Accountant with an MBA in Finance</li><li>Over 15 years of experience in the manufacturing industry</li><li>Expertise in budgeting, forecasting, taxation, treasury, and project finance</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ec7cdc03-5a88-46cb-ae23-9771f3714309.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KALYANI FORGE LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>