<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 09:31:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[WAAREERTL] Waaree Renewable Technologies to Acquire 55% Stake in Associated Power Structures for INR 1,225 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Waaree+Renewable+Technologies+Ltd&title=Waaree+Renewable+Technologies+to+Acquire+55%25+Stake+in+Associated+Power+Structures+for+INR+1%2C225+Crores&newsId=da3af27e-5c78-421e-bcd3-631c6cec7ddd&token=ZGEzYWYyN2UtNWM3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">da3af27e-5c78-421e-bcd3-631c6cec7ddd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 09:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd. has approved the acquisition of approximately 55% of the stake in Associated Power Structures Ltd. (ASPL) for a total consideration of INR 1,225 crores. The acquisition is a mix of primary and secondary shares. ASPL, established in 1996, is in the business of power transmission and distribution into the infrastructure sector. Post-acquisition, ASPL will become a subsidiary of Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd. The transaction is not a related party transaction and none of the promoter/promoter group/group companies have any interest in the entity being acquired. The acquisition is part of Waaree&apos;s strategic initiative to expand its presence and strengthen its capabilities across the renewable energy and energy efficiency ecosystem.</p><ul><li>Waaree Renewable Technologies to acquire approximately 55% stake in Associated Power Structures Limited</li><li>Total consideration of INR 1,225 crores (mix of primary and secondary shares)</li><li>ASPL operates in the power transmission and distribution sector</li><li>Acquisition to strengthen Waaree&apos;s capabilities across the renewable energy ecosystem</li><li>ASPL to become a subsidiary of Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bcd09c5e-51a1-4daf-83e9-8310b05fa8a3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WAAREERTL] Waaree Renewable Technologies to Acquire 55% Stake in Associated Power Structures for INR 1,225 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Waaree+Renewable+Technologies+Ltd&title=Waaree+Renewable+Technologies+to+Acquire+55%25+Stake+in+Associated+Power+Structures+for+INR+1%2C225+Crores&newsId=48a4b8bc-c40f-4907-ae5c-f83f40373550&token=NDhhNGI4YmMtYzQw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48a4b8bc-c40f-4907-ae5c-f83f40373550</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 09:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd. has approved a term sheet for the proposed acquisition of 55% stake in Associated Power Structures Limited (ASPL) for a total consideration of INR 1,225 crores. The acquisition is a mix of primary and secondary shares. ASPL, established in 1996, is in the business of Power transmission and distribution into the infrastructure sector. The acquisition will make ASPL a subsidiary of Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd. The transaction is not a related party transaction and none of the promoter/promoter group/group companies have any interest in the entity being acquired. The acquisition is part of WRITL’s strategic initiative to expand its presence and strengthen its capabilities across the renewable energy and energy efficiency ecosystem.</p><ul><li>Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd. to acquire 55% stake in Associated Power Structures Limited</li><li>Total consideration of INR 1,225 crores</li><li>ASPL to become a subsidiary of Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd.</li><li>ASPL established in 1996, in the business of Power transmission and distribution</li><li>Transaction is not a related party transaction</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ed200c08-af3d-4db7-9a1a-32b5dddb6242.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AIRFLOA] Airfloa Rail Technology Ltd Teams Up with Janatics for Automatic Door Systems in Railway Coaches</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Airfloa+Rail+Technology+Ltd&title=Airfloa+Rail+Technology+Ltd+Teams+Up+with+Janatics+for+Automatic+Door+Systems+in+Railway+Coaches&newsId=f876e256-d585-4dd1-a653-4f58b1eb814b&token=Zjg3NmUyNTYtZDU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f876e256-d585-4dd1-a653-4f58b1eb814b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 08:55:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>MoU</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Airfloa Rail Technology Ltd, a leading manufacturer of railway rolling stock components and turnkey interior solutions, has signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with Janatics Industrial Automation Private Limited for the development and supply of Automatic Door Systems for railway applications. The MoU covers Automatic Door Systems for modern railway coaches, including Freight EMU and Vande Bharat platforms. The product scope includes Double Leaf Plug Doors, Automatic Single Leaf Plug Doors, Pocket Sliding Doors, and Automatic Fire Barrier Doors. Airfloa will lead tender participation, customer engagement, and project execution. This strategic partnership strengthens Airfloa’s capabilities in a specialised subsystem that is increasingly becoming standard across new-generation railway coaches and upgrades.</p><ul><li>Airfloa Rail Technology Ltd has signed an MoU with Janatics Industrial Automation Private Limited for the development and supply of Automatic Door Systems for railway applications.</li><li>The MoU covers Automatic Door Systems for modern railway coaches, including Freight EMU and Vande Bharat platforms.</li><li>The product scope includes Double Leaf Plug Doors, Automatic Single Leaf Plug Doors, Pocket Sliding Doors, and Automatic Fire Barrier Doors.</li><li>Airfloa will lead tender participation, customer engagement, and project execution.</li><li>This strategic partnership strengthens Airfloa’s capabilities in a specialised subsystem that is increasingly becoming standard across new-generation railway coaches and upgrades.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0e7289ca-0217-4573-adeb-6a35262c3a3c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Airfloa Rail Technology Ltd | Category: MoU</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AIRFLOA] Airfloa Rail Technology Ltd Teams Up with Janatics for Automatic Door Systems in Railway Coaches</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Airfloa+Rail+Technology+Ltd&title=Airfloa+Rail+Technology+Ltd+Teams+Up+with+Janatics+for+Automatic+Door+Systems+in+Railway+Coaches&newsId=aca46701-6bf2-481e-ae30-7928fd59f9e9&token=YWNhNDY3MDEtNmJm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aca46701-6bf2-481e-ae30-7928fd59f9e9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 08:51:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>MoU</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Airfloa Rail Technology Ltd, a leading manufacturer of railway rolling stock components and turnkey interior solutions, has signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with Janatics Industrial Automation Private Limited for the development and supply of Automatic Door Systems for railway applications. The MoU covers Automatic Door Systems for modern railway coaches, including Freight EMU and Vande Bharat platforms. The product scope includes Double Leaf Plug Doors, Automatic Single Leaf Plug Doors, Pocket Sliding Doors, and Automatic Fire Barrier Doors. Airfloa will lead tender participation, customer engagement, and project execution. This strategic partnership strengthens Airfloa’s capabilities in a specialised subsystem that is increasingly becoming standard across new-generation railway coaches and upgrades.</p><ul><li>Airfloa Rail Technology Ltd has signed an MoU with Janatics Industrial Automation Private Limited for the development and supply of Automatic Door Systems for railway applications.</li><li>The MoU covers Automatic Door Systems for modern railway coaches, including Freight EMU and Vande Bharat platforms.</li><li>The product scope includes Double Leaf Plug Doors, Automatic Single Leaf Plug Doors, Pocket Sliding Doors, and Automatic Fire Barrier Doors.</li><li>Airfloa will lead tender participation, customer engagement, and project execution.</li><li>This partnership strengthens Airfloa’s capabilities in a specialised subsystem that is increasingly becoming standard across new-generation railway coaches and upgrades.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/001972af-ca4b-4a64-88dc-98976208583a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Airfloa Rail Technology Ltd | Category: MoU</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BAMPSL] Bampsl Securities Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Unaudited Quarterly Results for December 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BAMPSL+SECURITIES+LTD.&title=Bampsl+Securities+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Unaudited+Quarterly+Results+for+December+2025&newsId=7804f320-66a6-4cdc-b980-cf303cfc312f&token=NzgwNGYzMjAtNjZh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7804f320-66a6-4cdc-b980-cf303cfc312f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 08:49:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bampsl Securities Ltd has informed the BSE that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled for 09/02/2026. The meeting will inter alia consider and approve the Un-Audited Financial Results of the Company for the Quarter ended 31st December, 2025. The Company also mentioned that trading by Directors, Promoters, and Designated Persons will be regulated, monitored, and reported 48 hours after the results are made public on 31st December.</p><ul><li>Bampsl Securities Ltd scheduled a Board Meeting for 09/02/2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the Un-Audited Financial Results for the Quarter ended 31st December, 2025</li><li>Trading by Directors, Promoters, and Designated Persons will be regulated, monitored, and reported 48 hours after the results are made public</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/abc35d88-133b-4d74-ba28-a35329490212.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BAMPSL SECURITIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PVR] PVR INOX divests 4700BC to Marico for INR 226.8 crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PVR+LTD.&title=PVR+INOX+divests+4700BC+to+Marico+for+INR+226.8+crore&newsId=ddd46f10-1944-4b90-87c8-f16388ff367d&token=ZGRkNDZmMTAtMTk0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ddd46f10-1944-4b90-87c8-f16388ff367d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 08:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Divestment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>PVR INOX Limited has entered into definitive agreements to monetise its entire stake in Zea Maize Private Limited, one of India’s leading premium snacking companies operating under the 4700BC brand, to Marico Limited for a total consideration of INR 226.8 crore. This transaction is expected to be accretive to PVR INOX’s profit, free cash flow, and return ratios.</p><ul><li>PVR INOX divests its entire stake in Zea Maize Private Limited to Marico Limited for INR 226.8 crore.</li><li>4700BC is one of India’s leading premium snacking companies with a strong multi-channel presence across modern retail, digital commerce, and institutional channels.</li><li>The transaction enables 4700BC to benefit from Marico’s sharper FMCG focus, deeper distribution reach, and accelerated new product launches.</li><li>PVR INOX will continue to focus on its core cinema exhibition business after the divestment.</li><li>Axis Capital acted as the exclusive financial advisor and Shardul Amarchand Mangaldas &amp; Co acted as the legal advisor to PVR INOX for this transaction.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/96dab1fa-2450-430f-acc1-10df518fbde2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PVR LTD. | Category: Divestment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PINELABS] Pine Labs Partners with Wio Bank to Modernize UAE Merchant Acquiring Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Pine+Labs+Ltd&title=Pine+Labs+Partners+with+Wio+Bank+to+Modernize+UAE+Merchant+Acquiring+Infrastructure&newsId=dca3af57-482a-4643-86bd-6807c6754652&token=ZGNhM2FmNTctNDgy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dca3af57-482a-4643-86bd-6807c6754652</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 08:38:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Partnership</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Pine Labs, a global fintech platform, has partnered with Wio Bank, the Middle East’s leading digital financial platform, to build a modern acquiring infrastructure with no legacy tech dependency. The collaboration aims to enable faster merchant onboarding, real-time settlement capabilities, and seamless multi-mode payment acceptance at scale. Wio Bank will deploy Credit+, Pine Labs’ modular, API-first acquiring platform, to power its core acquiring operations.</p><ul><li>Pine Labs and Wio Bank partner to modernize merchant acquiring infrastructure in UAE.</li><li>Collaboration aims to enable faster merchant onboarding, real-time settlement, and seamless multi-mode payment acceptance at scale.</li><li>Wio Bank to deploy Credit+, Pine Labs’ modular, API-first acquiring platform for core acquiring operations.</li><li>Credit+ supports intelligent rule-based workflows, data-driven decisioning, and optimisation of payment acceptance rates.</li><li>Cloud-native, microservices-based framework ensures high availability, enterprise-grade security, and regulatory compliance.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/06407ddf-d0f3-40dc-b26a-112132ed0dc4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Pine Labs Ltd | Category: Partnership</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MARICO] Marico Ltd to Acquire 93.27% Stake in Premium Gourmet Snacking Brand &apos;4700BC&apos;</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MARICO+LTD.&title=Marico+Ltd+to+Acquire+93.27%25+Stake+in+Premium+Gourmet+Snacking+Brand+%274700BC%27&newsId=63c4b3ed-b537-4e60-b7ed-081d21fbc6a8&token=NjNjNGIzZWQtYjUz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63c4b3ed-b537-4e60-b7ed-081d21fbc6a8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 08:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Marico Ltd has entered into definitive agreements to acquire 93.27% of Zea Maize Private Limited, the company that owns the brand &apos;4700BC&apos; - one of India’s leading premium gourmet snacking brands. The acquisition is expected to be completed within 30 days, subject to customary closing conditions and terms of the definitive agreements. The acquisition will expand Marico’s total addressable market in value-added foods categories and make Zea Maize a subsidiary of the Company upon completion of the transaction.</p><ul><li>Marico Ltd to acquire 93.27% of Zea Maize Private Limited, owner of the brand &apos;4700BC&apos;.</li><li>The acquisition is expected to be completed within 30 days.</li><li>The acquisition will expand Marico’s total addressable market in value-added foods categories.</li><li>Zea Maize will become a subsidiary of Marico upon completion of the transaction.</li><li>Founder of Zea Maize to retain stake and continue leading the business.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1e497d48-0c27-4c5b-811c-7658d2bfbf12.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MARICO LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PVR] PVR INOX to Divest Entire Shareholding in Subsidiary Zea Maize Private Limited to Marico Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PVR+LTD.&title=PVR+INOX+to+Divest+Entire+Shareholding+in+Subsidiary+Zea+Maize+Private+Limited+to+Marico+Limited&newsId=8a2bbd86-7668-43f1-bf44-7edd8558ab4c&token=OGEyYmJkODYtNzY2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a2bbd86-7668-43f1-bf44-7edd8558ab4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 08:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Divestment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>PVR INOX Limited has approved the sale of its entire shareholding in its subsidiary, Zea Maize Private Limited (&apos;ZMPL&apos;), to Marico Limited. The sale includes 93.27% of the paid-up equity share capital of ZMPL, which owns the brand ‘4700BC’. The divestment is expected to be completed within 30 days, subject to customary closing conditions and terms of the definitive agreements. ZMPL is neither a material subsidiary of the Company nor listed on any stock exchange.</p><ul><li>PVR INOX to divest its entire shareholding in subsidiary Zea Maize Private Limited</li><li>93.27% of the paid-up equity share capital of ZMPL to be sold to Marico Limited</li><li>ZMPL owns the brand ‘4700BC’</li><li>Expected to be completed within 30 days</li><li>ZMPL is not a material subsidiary of the Company nor listed on any stock exchange</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5f9b6a89-c687-4dea-a638-47d75d1cc765.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PVR LTD. | Category: Divestment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AXISBANK] Axis Bank Announces Strong QOQ Growth in Deposits and Advances; Core Operating Profit Up 9%, PAT Up 28% in Q3FY26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AXIS+BANK+LTD.&title=Axis+Bank+Announces+Strong+QOQ+Growth+in+Deposits+and+Advances%3B+Core+Operating+Profit+Up+9%25%2C+PAT+Up+28%25+in+Q3FY26&newsId=97cff7a2-a5b0-4f1e-a994-f18da20bac56&token=OTdjZmY3YTItYTVi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97cff7a2-a5b0-4f1e-a994-f18da20bac56</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 08:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Axis Bank has reported a strong YoY deposits and advances growth of 15% and 14% respectively, and a 9% QoQ growth in core operating profit and 28% in PAT for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The bank&apos;s total deposits have grown 15% YoY and 12% QoQ, with term deposits up 16% YoY and 14% QoQ. The bank&apos;s SME loans have grown 22% YoY and 6% QoQ, while corporate loans have grown 27% YoY and 7% QoQ. The bank&apos;s cost to assets stands at 2.33%, down 15 bps YoY and 5 bps QoQ. The bank&apos;s GNPA% stands at 1.40%, down 6 bps QoQ and YOY. Axis Bank has acquired approximately 1 million cards in Q3FY26 and maintains a market share of ~14% on cards in force. The bank has also maintained a leading position in UPI Payer PSP, with a market share of ~39% and the lowest technical declines for 9MFY26.</p><ul><li>Strong YoY deposits and advances growth of 15% and 14% respectively</li><li>Core operating profit up 9% QoQ, PAT up 28% QoQ</li><li>SME loans up 22% YoY, Corporate loans up 27% YoY</li><li>Cost to assets at 2.33%, declined 15 bps YOY and 5 bps QOQ</li><li>GNPA% at 1.40% down 6 bps QOQ and YOY, Net NPA at 0.42% down 2 bps QoQ</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e72efa17-3dbc-4cf2-a16f-f355f9c5849c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AXIS BANK LTD. | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>