<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:55:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[KIRLOSBROS] Kirloskar Brothers Ltd Receives &apos;Aspiring&apos; ESG Rating of 67 for FY 2024-25</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KIRLOSKAR+BROTHERS+LTD.-%24&title=Kirloskar+Brothers+Ltd+Receives+%27Aspiring%27+ESG+Rating+of+67+for+FY+2024-25&newsId=eb165bd9-ee0c-46bd-920d-be0c82e1f275&token=ZWIxNjViZDktZWUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eb165bd9-ee0c-46bd-920d-be0c82e1f275</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:54:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kirloskar Brothers Ltd has been assigned an overall Environmental, Social and Governance (ESG) Rating of 67 under the category &apos;Aspiring&apos; by NSE Sustainability Ratings &amp; Analytics Limited. This rating is based on the disclosures of FY 2024-25 and reflects the company&apos;s performance on ESG parameters as assessed by the rating agency. Notably, the company has not engaged NSE Sustainability for ESG Rating, and the report has been independently prepared by the agency based on data available in the public domain.</p><ul><li>Kirloskar Brothers Ltd receives an ESG rating of 67 under the category &apos;Aspiring&apos; for FY 2024-25</li><li>Rating assigned by NSE Sustainability Ratings &amp; Analytics Limited based on public domain data</li><li>Company has not engaged NSE Sustainability for ESG Rating</li><li>Rating reflects the company&apos;s performance on Environmental, Social and Governance parameters</li><li>NSE Sustainability publishes the rating on its website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/29d91514-050a-49f6-85ba-8f8d552f7824.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KIRLOSKAR BROTHERS LTD.-$ | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PANORAMA] Panorama Studios International Ltd Assigns Airborne Rights of &apos;Like Aani Subscribe&apos; to Nitin Vaidya Productions LLP and Abhishek Merukar Productions LLP</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Panorama+Studios+International+Ltd&title=Panorama+Studios+International+Ltd+Assigns+Airborne+Rights+of+%27Like+Aani+Subscribe%27+to+Nitin+Vaidya+Productions+LLP+and+Abhishek+Merukar+Productions+LLP&newsId=80784566-3a79-4fa6-86d7-c22815061179&token=ODA3ODQ1NjYtM2E3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80784566-3a79-4fa6-86d7-c22815061179</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:51:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Panorama Studios Inflight, a subsidiary of Panorama Studios International Ltd, has executed an Assignment Agreement with Nitin Vaidya Productions LLP and Abhishek Merukar Productions LLP. This agreement grants the latter the exclusive Airborne Rights for the cinematographic film &apos;Like Aani Subscribe&apos; starring Amey Wagh, Amruta Khanvilkar, and directed by Abhishek Merukar. The film will be exploited on a global scale, including India.</p><ul><li>Panorama Studios Inflight has assigned Airborne Rights of the film &apos;Like Aani Subscribe&apos; to Nitin Vaidya Productions LLP and Abhishek Merukar Productions LLP</li><li>The film stars Amey Wagh and Amruta Khanvilkar</li><li>Abhishek Merukar is the director of the film</li><li>The Airborne Rights are granted on an exclusive basis for the entire world including India</li><li>This information is shared as per Regulation 30 read with Schedule III of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b07dfddd-ed9e-4b8c-9782-46a330dda8c5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Panorama Studios International Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[REPONO] Repono Ltd to Incorporate Subsidiary and Transfer Funds in Board Meeting on 24/02/2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Repono+Ltd&title=Repono+Ltd+to+Incorporate+Subsidiary+and+Transfer+Funds+in+Board+Meeting+on+24%2F02%2F2026&newsId=ad4dc098-0a20-4012-a1fc-87623d24dff6&token=YWQ0ZGMwOTgtMGEy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad4dc098-0a20-4012-a1fc-87623d24dff6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:51:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Repono Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 24th February 2026 to consider and approve the incorporation of a subsidiary. The company will also transfer funds towards the subscription amount. The meeting is in accordance with Regulation 29 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Repono Ltd to incorporate a subsidiary</li><li>Transfer of funds towards subscription amount</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1c8ced56-5d18-4a45-9dda-86c49d5bd049.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Repono Ltd | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CRESSAN] Cressanda Railway Solutions Ltd: Executive Director, Mr. Pankaj Agarwal, Resigns</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CRESSANDA+SOLUTIONS+LTD.&title=Cressanda+Railway+Solutions+Ltd%3A+Executive+Director%2C+Mr.+Pankaj+Agarwal%2C+Resigns&newsId=dd3a2c50-26e3-4fc1-b7da-86743f1090bd&token=ZGQzYTJjNTAtMjZl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd3a2c50-26e3-4fc1-b7da-86743f1090bd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:51:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cressanda Railway Solutions Ltd has announced the resignation of its Executive Director, Mr. Pankaj Agarwal, with effect from 19th February, 2026. The resignation is in accordance with the SEBI Listing Regulations. Mr. Agarwal will also cease to be a Member of the Corporate Social Responsibility and Risk Management Committee. The Board of Directors have expressed their gratitude for his contributions and guidance during his tenure.</p><ul><li>Mr. Pankaj Agarwal has resigned as Executive Director of Cressanda Railway Solutions Ltd.</li><li>His resignation will be effective from 19th February, 2026.</li><li>He will also cease to be a Member of the Corporate Social Responsibility and Risk Management Committee.</li><li>The resignation is in accordance with the SEBI Listing Regulations.</li><li>The Board of Directors have appreciated his contributions and guidance.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2538c1a3-7078-4ac7-aa88-8826ad54ebbb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CRESSANDA SOLUTIONS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PANORAMA] Panorama Studios International Ltd Executes Assignment Agreement with Take Pictures for Film &apos;Kaisi Ye Paheli&apos;</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Panorama+Studios+International+Ltd&title=Panorama+Studios+International+Ltd+Executes+Assignment+Agreement+with+Take+Pictures+for+Film+%27Kaisi+Ye+Paheli%27&newsId=77b465c8-dc34-42ad-bbbd-797fbc8d8dfc&token=NzdiNDY1YzgtZGMz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77b465c8-dc34-42ad-bbbd-797fbc8d8dfc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Panorama Studios International Ltd has announced that its subsidiary, Panorama Studios Inflight, has entered into an Assignment Agreement with Take Pictures. This agreement grants Take Pictures the exclusive rights to exploit the Airborne Rights for the cinematographic film &apos;Kaisi Ye Paheli&apos; worldwide, including India. The film stars Sukant Goel, Sadhana Singh, Rajit Kapoor, and is directed by Ananyabrata Chakravorty.</p><ul><li>Panorama Studios International Ltd&apos;s subsidiary, Panorama Studios Inflight, has signed an agreement with Take Pictures</li><li>Take Pictures granted exclusive Airborne Rights for the film &apos;Kaisi Ye Paheli&apos;</li><li>The film stars Sukant Goel, Sadhana Singh, and Rajit Kapoor</li><li>Directed by Ananyabrata Chakravorty</li><li>Agreement covers worldwide exploitation, including India</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d8dd6921-bc4c-45a4-b942-84e3bf50a8c5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Panorama Studios International Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LTTS] L&amp;T Technology Services&apos; Chief Delivery Officer, Dr. Narayanan Ramanathan, Resigns Effective February 19, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=L%26T+Technology+Services+Ltd&title=L%26T+Technology+Services%27+Chief+Delivery+Officer%2C+Dr.+Narayanan+Ramanathan%2C+Resigns+Effective+February+19%2C+2026&newsId=ce246a92-8f3c-4e76-b545-60704273416d&token=Y2UyNDZhOTItOGYz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce246a92-8f3c-4e76-b545-60704273416d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:51:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>L&amp;T Technology Services Ltd announced the resignation of Dr. Narayanan Ramanathan as Chief Delivery Officer (Senior Management Personnel) due to personal reasons. His resignation will be effective from close of business hours on February 19, 2026. The company has made the necessary disclosures as per the SEBI Listing Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Dr. Narayanan Ramanathan has resigned from his position as Chief Delivery Officer at L&amp;T Technology Services Ltd due to personal reasons.</li><li>His resignation will be effective from close of business hours on February 19, 2026.</li><li>The company has made the necessary disclosures as per the SEBI Listing Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b58c4920-2826-4fe0-b0f9-fbcd009f5f3d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: L&T Technology Services Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RLFL] Ramchandra Leasing &amp; Finance Ltd Issues Corrigendum for EGM: Changes in Name and Preferential Issue of Convertible Warrants</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ramchandra+Leasing+%26+Finance+Ltd&title=Ramchandra+Leasing+%26+Finance+Ltd+Issues+Corrigendum+for+EGM%3A+Changes+in+Name+and+Preferential+Issue+of+Convertible+Warrants&newsId=57a79460-5a30-4b4b-861d-e16860811121&token=NTdhNzk0NjAtNWEz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57a79460-5a30-4b4b-861d-e16860811121</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:44:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ramchandra Leasing &amp; Finance Ltd has issued a corrigendum for the Extraordinary General Meeting (EGM) held on November 21, 2025. The corrigendum addresses some inadvertent omissions and mistakes in the original notice. The changes include the availability of the PCA Certificate for the proposed name change to &apos;RAAMA FINANCE LIMITED&apos; and the preferential issue of 11,40,00,000 Convertible Warrants. The corrigendum also provides updated details on the current and proposed status of allottees post the preferential issues.</p><ul><li>Issuance of corrigendum for EGM held on November 21, 2025</li><li>Availability of PCA Certificate for the proposed name change</li><li>Preferential issue of 11,40,00,000 Convertible Warrants</li><li>Updated details on the current and proposed status of allottees post the preferential issues</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bae61d65-2318-4def-9178-dd2158f3d374.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ramchandra Leasing & Finance Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RVNL] Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd Executes Strategic Joint Venture Agreement with Texmaco Rail &amp; Engineering Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Rail+Vikas+Nigam+Ltd&title=Rail+Vikas+Nigam+Ltd+Executes+Strategic+Joint+Venture+Agreement+with+Texmaco+Rail+%26+Engineering+Limited&newsId=452c8ae5-0cd5-4fd8-be75-e18541338f42&token=NDUyYzhhZTUtMGNk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">452c8ae5-0cd5-4fd8-be75-e18541338f42</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:44:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd has executed a Strategic Joint Venture Shareholders’ Agreement with Texmaco Rail &amp; Engineering Limited. The agreement is for the incorporation and operation of a joint venture company. This information is provided for record purposes, following earlier communications on 29.05.2025 and 27.08.2025.</p><ul><li>Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd and Texmaco Rail &amp; Engineering Limited have executed a Strategic Joint Venture Shareholders’ Agreement.</li><li>The agreement is for the incorporation and operation of a joint venture company.</li><li>This development follows earlier communications on 29.05.2025 and 27.08.2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d0d81554-60f1-42dc-b9fd-3795c4e7b037.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Rail Vikas Nigam Ltd | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EUROPRATIK] Euro Pratik Launches Canfor 2 and Chisel 2026, Offering Smarter and More Accessible Wall Panel Designs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Euro+Pratik+Sales+Ltd&title=Euro+Pratik+Launches+Canfor+2+and+Chisel+2026%2C+Offering+Smarter+and+More+Accessible+Wall+Panel+Designs&newsId=ccdd9048-dea2-418b-ba48-4978ede2befb&token=Y2NkZDkwNDgtZGVh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ccdd9048-dea2-418b-ba48-4978ede2befb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:44:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Euro Pratik, one of India’s leading decorative wall panel brands, has announced the launch of two new product ranges for 2026 — Canfor 2 and Chisel 2026. These new launches are aimed at elevating personal spaces at practical price points, blending versatile surface solutions with aesthetics. The Canfor 2 range comes in 70 new designs and colour options, inspired from materials such as cork, metal, pastels, wood, stone, marble, and fabric. The Chisel 2026 range presents pre-finished, ready-to-install wall panels that are designed for hassle-free installation with striking visual impact. Made from recyclable, eco-friendly materials, they suit residential and commercial spaces, delivering cohesive, contemporary interiors.</p><ul><li>Launch of two new product ranges: Canfor 2 and Chisel 2026</li><li>Affordable prices starting from %120—%150 per sq. ft</li><li>Canfor 2 comes in 70 new designs and colour options</li><li>Chisel 2026 presents pre-finished, ready-to-install wall panels</li><li>Made from recyclable, eco-friendly materials</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/874b19ca-2b40-438b-a6f4-9d6118456543.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Euro Pratik Sales Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RMC] RMC Switchgears Ltd: Promoter-to-Promoter Share Transfer Completed</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RMC+Switchgears+Ltd&title=RMC+Switchgears+Ltd%3A+Promoter-to-Promoter+Share+Transfer+Completed&newsId=b5770b21-0dca-4122-897a-f2ce3b901d7e&token=YjU3NzBiMjEtMGRj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5770b21-0dca-4122-897a-f2ce3b901d7e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 12:42:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>RMC Switchgears Ltd has announced an inter-se transfer of shares between promoters and promoter group. The transfer was done through gift within the family and falls under the exemption of Regulation 10(1)(a)(ii) of SEBI (SAST) Regulations, 2011. The total holding of promoter and promoter group remains the same before and after the transaction. The transfer involved 7,50,900 shares from Vitthal Das Agarwal HUF to Ankit Agrawal and 94,800 shares from Vitthal Das Agrawal to Ankit Agrawal.</p><ul><li>Inter-se transfer of shares between promoters and promoter group</li><li>Transfer done through gift within the family</li><li>Falls under the exemption of Regulation 10(1)(a)(ii) of SEBI (SAST) Regulations, 2011</li><li>Total holding of promoter and promoter group remains the same</li><li>Involved 7,50,900 shares from Vitthal Das Agarwal HUF to Ankit Agrawal and 94,800 shares from Vitthal Das Agrawal to Ankit Agrawal</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a9a1b7c7-00ea-4293-ba1e-b87f85939d83.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RMC Switchgears Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>