<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:50:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SHRICON] Shricon Industries Ltd. Approves Un-Audited Standalone Financial Results for Q3 &amp; Nine Months Ended Dec 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHRICON+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Shricon+Industries+Ltd.+Approves+Un-Audited+Standalone+Financial+Results+for+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Ended+Dec+31%2C+2025&newsId=2c5e8974-d069-4714-9d2e-85d077963abc&token=MmM1ZTg5NzQtZDA2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2c5e8974-d069-4714-9d2e-85d077963abc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:50:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shricon Industries Ltd. announced the outcome of its Board of Directors meeting held on February 06, 2026. The Board approved the Un-Audited Standalone Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The financial results were reviewed by R S Dani &amp; Co., Statutory Auditors of the Company. The company also considered the quarterly integrated corporate governance report, Investor Grievance Report, and quarterly compliances as per the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Approval of Un-Audited Standalone Financial Results for Q3 &amp; Nine Months ended Dec 31, 2025</li><li>Review of financial results by R S Dani &amp; Co., Statutory Auditors</li><li>Consideration of quarterly integrated corporate governance report</li><li>Consideration of Investor Grievance Report</li><li>Consideration of quarterly compliances as per the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f8dd4480-79c5-427d-9743-a12b9c0cda04.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHRICON INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BTTL] Bhilwara Technical Textiles Ltd to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months of FY 2025-26 on Feb 13, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BHILWARA+TECHNICAL+TEXTILES+LTD.&title=Bhilwara+Technical+Textiles+Ltd+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+nine+months+of+FY+2025-26+on+Feb+13%2C+2026&newsId=a241e18c-6004-4d8a-8406-f66b7f566915&token=YTI0MWUxOGMtNjAw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a241e18c-6004-4d8a-8406-f66b7f566915</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:50:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bhilwara Technical Textiles Ltd has informed BSE that the company&apos;s Board of Directors will meet on February 13, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results (standalone and consolidated) for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The trading window for dealing in shares of the company will remain closed till February 15, 2026. The company&apos;s corporate office is located in Noida, India, and the registered office is in Banswara, Rajasthan, India.</p><ul><li>Bhilwara Technical Textiles Ltd to consider and approve unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months of FY 2025-26 on Feb 13, 2026</li><li>Trading window for dealing in shares of the company to remain closed till Feb 15, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/495e9499-860e-49cb-ac18-87c30a21daf1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BHILWARA TECHNICAL TEXTILES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EPACK] EPACK Durable Ltd Receives INR 7.36 Crore Incentive Under M-SIPS</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=EPACK+Durable+Ltd&title=EPACK+Durable+Ltd+Receives+INR+7.36+Crore+Incentive+Under+M-SIPS&newsId=003ebaea-3f7e-4b36-a19d-ed179469b8bc&token=MDAzZWJhZWEtM2Y3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">003ebaea-3f7e-4b36-a19d-ed179469b8bc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:49:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>EPACK Durable Ltd has announced that it has received an incentive of INR 7.36 Crore under The Modified Special Incentive Package Scheme (M-SIPS) of the Ministry of IT &amp; Electronics, Government of India. The scheme is designed to promote electronics manufacturing in the country and offers incentives in three phases for investments in capital expenditure for setting up electronic manufacturing units. The company had applied for the scheme to align with the Government of India’s vision of ‘Make in India &amp; Aatamnirbhar Bharat’.</p><ul><li>EPACK Durable Ltd has received an incentive of INR 7.36 Crore under M-SIPS</li><li>The scheme is designed to promote electronics manufacturing in the country</li><li>The incentive is part of the third phase of the M-SIPS scheme</li><li>The company had applied for the scheme to align with the Government of India’s vision of ‘Make in India &amp; Aatamnirbhar Bharat’</li><li>The incentive is a positive step towards promoting electronics manufacturing in the country</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f6b4a480-cf2c-4377-968e-398e4d9513aa.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: EPACK Durable Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SIDDHA] Siddha Ventures Ltd Appoints New Secretarial Auditor for FY 2025-2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SIDDHA+VENTURES+LTD.&title=Siddha+Ventures+Ltd+Appoints+New+Secretarial+Auditor+for+FY+2025-2026&newsId=d847a28e-cd68-4f2f-890d-900c6037f73c&token=ZDg0N2EyOGUtY2Q2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d847a28e-cd68-4f2f-890d-900c6037f73c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:49:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Siddha Ventures Ltd has appointed M/s Vidhya Baid &amp; Co as the new Secretarial Auditor for the Financial Year 2025-2026. The appointment was made to fill the casual vacancy that arose due to the resignation of the previous auditor, M/s Dash M &amp; Associates. M/s Vidhya Baid &amp; Co is a firm of Company Secretaries with over 15 years of professional experience, specializing in Secretarial Audit, Due Diligence, Corporate Compliance Management, and more. Ms. Vidhya Baid, the proprietor of the firm, is a Masters in Commerce (Hons), Fellow Member of Institute of Company Secretaries of India, and a registered Insolvency Professional.</p><ul><li>Siddha Ventures Ltd has appointed a new Secretarial Auditor, M/s Vidhya Baid &amp; Co.</li><li>The appointment is for the Financial Year 2025-2026.</li><li>The previous auditor, M/s Dash M &amp; Associates, resigned from the position.</li><li>M/s Vidhya Baid &amp; Co is a firm of Company Secretaries with over 15 years of experience.</li><li>Ms. Vidhya Baid, the proprietor of the firm, is a Masters in Commerce (Hons), Fellow Member of Institute of Company Secretaries of India, and a registered Insolvency Professional.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d78cab2c-6579-49f9-abbd-075e8ea0822f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SIDDHA VENTURES LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KALLAM] Kallam Textiles Ltd. to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025 in February Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kallam+Textiles+Ltd-%24&title=Kallam+Textiles+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025+in+February+Board+Meeting&newsId=906c4161-d5bf-43fa-868b-8948665cac1e&token=OTA2YzQxNjEtZDVi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">906c4161-d5bf-43fa-868b-8948665cac1e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:49:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kallam Textiles Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 14th February 2026 to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31.12.2025. The company will also discuss other business items during the meeting. The trading window for designated persons of the company will be closed 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results to the Stock Exchange.</p><ul><li>Kallam Textiles Ltd. to hold Board Meeting on 14th February 2026</li><li>Consideration and approval of unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31.12.2025</li><li>Trading window closure for designated persons till 48 hours after result declaration</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6c3cb577-c9dd-4f25-84f1-451df4569ad5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kallam Textiles Ltd-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GUJALKALI] Gujarat Alkalies and Chemicals Ltd. Announces Q3 Results with Profit of Rs. 1,262 Lakhs, Approves Installation of Bio Fuel Boilers and Food Grade Phosphoric Acid Plant</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GUJARAT+ALKALIES+%26+CHEMICALS+LTD.&title=Gujarat+Alkalies+and+Chemicals+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+Results+with+Profit+of+Rs.+1%2C262+Lakhs%2C+Approves+Installation+of+Bio+Fuel+Boilers+and+Food+Grade+Phosphoric+Acid+Plant&newsId=737b8551-cea9-4f32-99cb-28e0b6c75f63&token=NzM3Yjg1NTEtY2Vh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">737b8551-cea9-4f32-99cb-28e0b6c75f63</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:49:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Gujarat Alkalies and Chemicals Ltd. has announced its standalone and consolidated un-audited (provisional) financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended on 31st December 2025. The company reported a profit of Rs. 1,262 lakhs for the quarter. The board has approved the installation of two bio fuel/coal fired boilers each at Vadodara and Dahej Complex, and a 33870 TPA (85% H3PO4) Food Grade Phosphoric Acid Plant at Dahej, Gujarat. The board also approved the internal relocation of Electrolysers of Caustic Soda (NaOH) and Caustic Potash (KOH) at Vadodara Complex together with enhancement of capacity of KOH production from 120 TPD to 200 TPD. The company has also availed a Line of Credit facility from Gujarat State Financial Services Ltd (GSFS) for an amount of Rs. 250 Crore.</p><ul><li>Profit of Rs. 1,262 lakhs for Q3 2025</li><li>Approval for installation of bio fuel boilers</li><li>Approval for installation of Food Grade Phosphoric Acid Plant</li><li>Approval for capacity enhancement of KOH production</li><li>Availing of Line of Credit facility from GSFS for Rs. 250 Crore</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5a8f67b0-f8a2-464e-a689-f26d590291d0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GUJARAT ALKALIES & CHEMICALS LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INFORTEC] Informed Technologies India Ltd to Approve Q4 Results for 2025 in Board Meeting on Feb 13, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INFORMED+TECHNOLOGIES+INDIA+LTD.&title=Informed+Technologies+India+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+Results+for+2025+in+Board+Meeting+on+Feb+13%2C+2026&newsId=a6653240-2e48-44be-a527-76f36163a5fe&token=YTY2NTMyNDAtMmU0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a6653240-2e48-44be-a527-76f36163a5fe</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Informed Technologies India Ltd has informed the BSE that their Board of Directors will meet on February 13, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results (standalone and consolidated) for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for all directors, KMPs, designated employees, and their immediate relatives was closed on January 01, 2026, and will remain closed till 48 hours after the declaration of financial results for Q4 2025.</p><ul><li>Informed Technologies India Ltd to hold a Board Meeting on Feb 13, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve un-audited financial results for Q4 2025</li><li>Trading window for all directors, KMPs, designated employees, and their immediate relatives closed since Jan 1, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/26c70f38-587c-4ac8-a219-af16efaf249d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INFORMED TECHNOLOGIES INDIA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SREEL] Sreeleathers Ltd Declares Interim Dividend of Re.1/- per share for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SREELEATHERS+LTD.&title=Sreeleathers+Ltd+Declares+Interim+Dividend+of+Re.1%2F-+per+share+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=9dd0fce1-c8d5-421c-aff7-c9f69c7cf2ff&token=OWRkMGZjZTEtYzhk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9dd0fce1-c8d5-421c-aff7-c9f69c7cf2ff</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:48:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sreeleathers Ltd has declared an interim dividend of Re.1/- per share for the financial year 2025-26. The record date for determining the entitlement of members to this dividend has been fixed as Friday, 13th February, 2026. The dividend, subject to tax deduction at source (TDS), will be paid on Wednesday, 25.02.2026.</p><ul><li>Sreeleathers Ltd declares interim dividend of Re.1/- per share for FY 2025-26</li><li>Record date for dividend entitlement set as 13th February, 2026</li><li>Dividend payment to be made on 25th February, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/08206b55-e141-4b9b-9acb-591e452aca42.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SREELEATHERS LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ESARIND] Esaar India Ltd to Approve Un-audited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ESAAR+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Esaar+India+Ltd+to+Approve+Un-audited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=3ee32c4d-82ca-46aa-b093-2d505b266800&token=M2VlMzJjNGQtODJj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ee32c4d-82ca-46aa-b093-2d505b266800</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Esaar India Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 12, 2026, to consider and approve the Un-audited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will also approve the Limited Review Report. The trading window for dealing in shares of the company will remain closed till 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results.</p><ul><li>Esaar India Ltd to approve Un-audited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Trading window for dealing in shares of the company to remain closed till 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d4ae1f78-7cdd-4023-bfea-27a2d6c0d84b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ESAAR (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUNLOC] Sunil Healthcare Ltd Approves Un-Audited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months of FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sunil+Healthcare+Ltd&title=Sunil+Healthcare+Ltd+Approves+Un-Audited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+of+FY+2025-26&newsId=ce635747-90df-47ae-83aa-5c8a0808a8b5&token=Y2U2MzU3NDctOTBk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce635747-90df-47ae-83aa-5c8a0808a8b5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:47:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sunil Healthcare Ltd has approved the Un-Audited Financial Results for the 3rd quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The Board Meeting was held on February 06, 2026. The financial results are prepared in accordance with the Indian Accounting Standard 34 and other accounting principles generally accepted in India.</p><ul><li>Sunil Healthcare Ltd approves Un-Audited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months of FY 2025-26</li><li>The Board Meeting was held on February 06, 2026</li><li>Financial results are prepared in accordance with the Indian Accounting Standard 34 and other accounting principles generally accepted in India</li><li>Includes results of foreign subsidiaries Sunil Healthcare Mexico Sa De CV and Sunil Healthcare North America LLC</li><li>Two foreign subsidiaries&apos; interim financial results are not required to be audited/reviewed under the law of their respective countries</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/36cfb86a-c11f-48ad-8a00-4283fd04958e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sunil Healthcare Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>