<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:59:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[EIHAHOTELS] EIH Associated Hotels Ltd. Approves Q3 Results for FY2025-26, Announces Banquet Facility Opening in Agra</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=EIH+ASSOCIATED+HOTELS+LTD.-%24&title=EIH+Associated+Hotels+Ltd.+Approves+Q3+Results+for+FY2025-26%2C+Announces+Banquet+Facility+Opening+in+Agra&newsId=2e4b7639-a461-4eb6-b751-10c3aa69dc1e&token=MmU0Yjc2MzktYTQ2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e4b7639-a461-4eb6-b751-10c3aa69dc1e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:59:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>EIH Associated Hotels Ltd. has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at INR 12,946.65 million for the quarter and INR 27,066.86 million for the nine months period. The Board also approved the expected date of opening of the banquet facility at Trident Agra to April 2027. The company recognized an incremental obligation of INR 328.17 lakhs on account of increase in employee benefit liabilities arising from past service, presented under Exceptional Items.</p><ul><li>EIH Associated Hotels Ltd. reported a revenue from operations of INR 12,946.65 million for Q3 FY2025-26.</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue from operations for the nine months period ended 31st December 2025 stands at INR 27,066.86 million.</li><li>The Board approved the expected date of opening of the banquet facility at Trident Agra to April 2027.</li><li>The company recognized an exceptional item of INR 328.17 lakhs on account of increase in employee benefit liabilities.</li><li>The unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025 are not indicative of the full year&apos;s performance due to the seasonal nature of the Indian Hotel Industry.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/60b3274c-708e-4fd4-af5b-0ebdac41dcb3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: EIH ASSOCIATED HOTELS LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HAPPYFORGE] Happy Forgings Ltd: No Deviation from IPO Objects in Q3 FY2026, Proceeds Utilization in Line with Objectives</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Happy+Forgings+Ltd&title=Happy+Forgings+Ltd%3A+No+Deviation+from+IPO+Objects+in+Q3+FY2026%2C+Proceeds+Utilization+in+Line+with+Objectives&newsId=2109653e-a210-4cbc-927e-deaed342f46e&token=MjEwOTY1M2UtYTIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2109653e-a210-4cbc-927e-deaed342f46e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:59:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Happy Forgings Ltd, a Castings &amp; Forgings industry player, has not deviated from the objects of its Initial Public Offer (IPO) in the third quarter of the financial year 2026. The utilization of the issuance proceeds is in line with the original objects of the issue, according to the Monitoring Agency report by ICRA Limited. The report, which does not constitute a commentary on the quality of the issue or appropriateness of costs, confirmed that there were no material deviations from the expenditures disclosed in the Offer Document. The means of finance for the disclosed objects of the issue has not changed, and all Government/statutory approvals related to the object(s) have been obtained.</p><ul><li>Happy Forgings Ltd did not deviate from the objects of its IPO in Q3 FY2026.</li><li>The utilization of proceeds is in line with the original objects of the issue.</li><li>No material deviations from expenditures disclosed in the Offer Document.</li><li>All Government/statutory approvals related to the object(s) have been obtained.</li><li>No changes in the means of finance for the disclosed objects of the issue.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/414163c1-0101-4415-a933-d002c39f9f09.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Happy Forgings Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PVVINFRA] PVV Infra Ltd. Boosts Integrated Clean Energy Manufacturing Project to X1,250 Crore, Strengthens Andhra Pradesh MoU, and Appoints Additional Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PVV+Infra+Ltd&title=PVV+Infra+Ltd.+Boosts+Integrated+Clean+Energy+Manufacturing+Project+to+X1%2C250+Crore%2C+Strengthens+Andhra+Pradesh+MoU%2C+and+Appoints+Additional+Director&newsId=aa93c3ba-da93-4f1f-b4f1-e74805193f1e&token=YWE5M2MzYmEtZGE5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa93c3ba-da93-4f1f-b4f1-e74805193f1e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:59:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>PVV Infra Ltd. has announced enhancements to its Integrated Clean Energy Manufacturing Project, increasing the project value to approximately X1,250 Crore. The expansion includes a strategic technology collaboration with ITC Services Company Limited (Taiwan) for high-efficiency solar cell manufacturing, battery energy storage systems (BESS), micro-inverters, and smart power electronics. The company also strengthened its memorandum of understanding with the Andhra Pradesh government and appointed Mr. Tse Hsiung Norman Lao as an Additional Director (Non-Independent).</p><ul><li>Strategic technology collaboration with ITC Services Company Limited (Taiwan) for high-efficiency solar cell manufacturing, BESS, micro-inverters, and smart power electronics.</li><li>Enhancement of the project value to approximately X1,250 Crore for the Integrated Clean Energy Manufacturing Project.</li><li>Strengthening of the memorandum of understanding with the Andhra Pradesh government for renewable energy manufacturing infrastructure development.</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Tse Hsiung Norman Lao as an Additional Director (Non-Independent) to support commercialization and international market development initiatives.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/87bc6885-c4a4-4a43-8a1c-0c98c3e80599.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PVV Infra Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TRIDENT] Trident Ltd to Incorporate New Domestic Wholly Owned Subsidiary and Disinvest in MYTRIDENT.COM LIMITED</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TRIDENT+LTD.&title=Trident+Ltd+to+Incorporate+New+Domestic+Wholly+Owned+Subsidiary+and+Disinvest+in+MYTRIDENT.COM+LIMITED&newsId=f5221f97-0076-45f1-b7b1-d9e77d0f8970&token=ZjUyMjFmOTctMDA3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f5221f97-0076-45f1-b7b1-d9e77d0f8970</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Trident Ltd, in its board meeting held on February 09, 2026, approved the incorporation of a new Domestic Wholly Owned Subsidiary (DWOS) to enhance brand presence, brand-building initiatives, selling, and marketing for Trident products in overseas markets, with a special emphasis on the U.S. market. The company also approved the disinvestment of the entire stake in MYTRIDENT.COM LIMITED, a Domestic Wholly Owned Subsidiary (DWOS) of the Company.</p><ul><li>Incorporation of a new DWOS to boost brand presence and marketing in overseas markets, particularly the U.S.</li><li>Disinvestment of entire stake in MYTRIDENT.COM LIMITED, a DWOS of Trident Limited</li><li>Trident Global Corp Limited, an associate entity and part of the Promoter Group, bought MYTRIDENT.COM LIMITED for INR 1,00,000</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a84d6df3-fd35-4bac-8229-4622b6157bb6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TRIDENT LTD. | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SRMENERGY] SRM Energy Ltd Receives IDC Recommendations for Open Offer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SRM+ENERGY+LTD.&title=SRM+Energy+Ltd+Receives+IDC+Recommendations+for+Open+Offer&newsId=cba1b9af-1d02-4edf-8108-71eb502bf554&token=Y2JhMWI5YWYtMWQw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cba1b9af-1d02-4edf-8108-71eb502bf554</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:58:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>SRM Energy Ltd has received the Recommendations of the Committee of Independent Directors (&apos;IDC&apos;) regarding the Open Offer to the Shareholders. The IDC&apos;s recommendations were submitted to the Bombay Stock Exchange (BSE) by Sobhagya Capital Options Pvt Ltd, the Manager to the Offer. The IDC&apos;s recommendations are dated February 04, 2026.</p><ul><li>SRM Energy Ltd has received IDC recommendations for an Open Offer to shareholders.</li><li>The recommendations were submitted to the BSE by Sobhagya Capital Options Pvt Ltd.</li><li>The IDC&apos;s recommendations are dated February 04, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5C7DB00A-5CED-4D26-A8BB-9A3D2D373CF9-152300.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SRM ENERGY LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UGROCAP] Ugro Capital&apos;s Q3 FY2025-26 Standalone Profit Down by 3,693.54 Lakh, But Consolidated Profit Stands at 4,626.52 Lakh</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ugro+Capital+Ltd&title=Ugro+Capital%27s+Q3+FY2025-26+Standalone+Profit+Down+by+3%2C693.54+Lakh%2C+But+Consolidated+Profit+Stands+at+4%2C626.52+Lakh&newsId=ad2ae107-970a-4364-84bb-0052fddd4d49&token=YWQyYWUxMDctOTcw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad2ae107-970a-4364-84bb-0052fddd4d49</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:58:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ugro Capital Ltd. reported a decline in standalone Profit After Tax (PAT) for the quarter ended 31 December 2025, primarily due to lower gains from Direct Assignment transactions. The net gain on derecognition of financial instruments under amortised cost category reduced from 10,063.42 lakh in the previous quarter to 6,617.64 lakh in the current quarter. However, the consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) stood at 4,626.52 lakh, reflecting income from Direct Assignment transactions undertaken at Profectus, a subsidiary of the Company. The Company advises investors and analysts to review and evaluate UGRO’s performance using consolidated financial statements for comparative and analytical purposes.</p><ul><li>Standalone Profit After Tax (PAT) for the quarter ended 31 December 2025 was 637.58 lakh, down by 3,693.54 lakh from the previous quarter.</li><li>Consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) for the quarter ended 31 December 2025 was 4,626.52 lakh, which includes income from Direct Assignment transactions undertaken at Profectus.</li><li>The reduction in standalone PAT is primarily due to the execution of Direct Assignment transactions at the subsidiary level during the quarter.</li><li>The Company advises investors and analysts to consider consolidated financial statements for comparative and analytical purposes.</li><li>The comparison of standalone and consolidated numbers for the current quarter and previous quarters is provided in Annexure-1.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e20df63c-058c-401c-94cf-b5e89d98a688.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ugro Capital Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ATFL] Sundrop Brands Appoints Mr. Atin Gupta as Head of E-commerce and Business Analytics</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AGRO+TECH+FOODS+LTD.&title=Sundrop+Brands+Appoints+Mr.+Atin+Gupta+as+Head+of+E-commerce+and+Business+Analytics&newsId=b10d7f56-d1ab-497a-82c3-3e2427b4bfd8&token=YjEwZDdmNTYtZDFh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b10d7f56-d1ab-497a-82c3-3e2427b4bfd8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:58:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sundrop Brands Ltd has appointed Mr. Atin Gupta as the Head of E-commerce and Business Analytics for the company and its material subsidiary, Del Monte Foods Private Limited, effective from February 09, 2026. Mr. Gupta, with over 10 years of experience in e-commerce, data science, and advanced analytics, has previously worked with Piramal Consumer Healthcare, Indegene, Piramal Enterprises, and Mu Sigma Business Solutions. He holds an MA in Economics from Gokhale Institute of Politics and Economics, Pune and a BA(Hons) in Economics from Ramjas College, Delhi University.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Atin Gupta as Head of E-commerce and Business Analytics</li><li>Over 10 years of experience in e-commerce, data science, and advanced analytics</li><li>Previous experience with Piramal Consumer Healthcare, Indegene, Piramal Enterprises, and Mu Sigma Business Solutions</li><li>MA in Economics from Gokhale Institute of Politics and Economics, Pune</li><li>BA(Hons) in Economics from Ramjas College, Delhi University</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f1f4adb9-aac8-4213-88a8-fc44b6a198f8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AGRO TECH FOODS LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ECOBOAR] Ecoboard Industries Ltd to Consider and Approve Q3 Results on Feb 14, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ECOBOARD+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Ecoboard+Industries+Ltd+to+Consider+and+Approve+Q3+Results+on+Feb+14%2C+2026&newsId=f744038c-5b66-4817-90ac-d0e128768528&token=Zjc0NDAzOGMtNWI2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f744038c-5b66-4817-90ac-d0e128768528</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:58:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ecoboard Industries Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 14, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The meeting will be held through video conferencing/Other Audio - Visual means (OAVM) at the deemed Registered office of the Company. The Trading Window for dealing in the securities of the Company is closed from January 01, 2026, and will remain closed till 48 hours after the financial results and outcome of the aforesaid Board meeting are made public.</p><ul><li>Ecoboard Industries Ltd to consider and approve Q3 results on Feb 14, 2026</li><li>The meeting will be held through video conferencing/Other Audio - Visual means (OAVM)</li><li>The Trading Window for dealing in the securities of the Company is closed from January 01, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e30882a2-2d4a-4832-bd54-19bfc3c6c15b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ECOBOARD INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CPEDU] Career Point Edutech Ltd Announces Q3 &amp; 9M FY2026 Financial Results and Board Meeting Outcomes</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Career+Point+Edutech+Ltd&title=Career+Point+Edutech+Ltd+Announces+Q3+%26+9M+FY2026+Financial+Results+and+Board+Meeting+Outcomes&newsId=fb9a1ab8-e775-4b52-90e2-3aa9d000e8c4&token=ZmI5YTFhYjgtZTc3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fb9a1ab8-e775-4b52-90e2-3aa9d000e8c4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Career Point Edutech Ltd, a leading education company, announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s Board of Directors approved the un-audited financial results in a meeting held on February 09, 2026. The total revenues for the period from April 01, 2025 to December 31, 2025, were Rs 156.51 Lakhs. The company also addressed other routine business and compliances as per the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015. The &apos;Trading Window&apos; for all Directors, Promoters, Designated Persons and their immediate relatives of the Company, for trading in the shares of the Company, will be open after 48 hours of declaration of financial results.</p><ul><li>Career Point Edutech Ltd announced its Q3 &amp; 9M FY2026 financial results.</li><li>The company&apos;s total revenues for the period from April 01, 2025 to December 31, 2025, were Rs 156.51 Lakhs.</li><li>The Board of Directors approved the un-audited financial results in a meeting held on February 09, 2026.</li><li>The company addressed other routine business and compliances as per the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</li><li>The &apos;Trading Window&apos; for all Directors, Promoters, Designated Persons and their immediate relatives of the Company, for trading in the shares of the Company, will be open after 48 hours of declaration of financial results.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8a454926-1cd5-4259-ad31-475eca49357a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Career Point Edutech Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GTIL] Gabion Technologies India Ltd Receives Multiple Work Orders Worth INR 2,01,02,232 in February 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Gabion+Technologies+India+Ltd&title=Gabion+Technologies+India+Ltd+Receives+Multiple+Work+Orders+Worth+INR+2%2C01%2C02%2C232+in+February+2026&newsId=fa500925-8013-4fa2-8bb0-bcfdef712f6a&token=ZmE1MDA5MjUtODAx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa500925-8013-4fa2-8bb0-bcfdef712f6a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 09:57:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Gabion Technologies India Ltd, a company listed on the BSE SME Exchange, has received multiple routine work/supply orders during the week ended February 07, 2026. The total value of these orders, inclusive of applicable GST, is approximately INR 2,01,02,232. The orders are for the supply of gabion boxes and rockfall netting, received in the ordinary course of business as per respective contract/ Letter of Award (LOA) terms. These orders are routine in nature and do not result in any change in the business model, risk profile, or operational strategy of the Company.</p><ul><li>Gabion Technologies India Ltd received multiple work orders during the week ended February 07, 2026.</li><li>The total value of the orders is approximately INR 2,01,02,232, inclusive of applicable GST.</li><li>The orders are for the supply of gabion boxes and rockfall netting.</li><li>The orders have been received in the ordinary course of business as per respective contract/ Letter of Award (LOA) terms.</li><li>These orders do not result in any change in the business model, risk profile, or operational strategy of the Company.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f98e9762-c0ab-4126-bf8f-b20b8cebd828.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Gabion Technologies India Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>