<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 01:43:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[VIKRAN] Vikran Engineering Ltd Approves Rs. 300 Crores Term Loan, Reports Q3 Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vikran+Engineering+Ltd&title=Vikran+Engineering+Ltd+Approves+Rs.+300+Crores+Term+Loan%2C+Reports+Q3+Results&newsId=a2454a99-7a0b-4fe4-b977-85b54f9c4fb2&token=YTI0NTRhOTktN2Ew</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2454a99-7a0b-4fe4-b977-85b54f9c4fb2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:07:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vikran Engineering Ltd has approved the availing of a term loan or issuance of unlisted, secured, rated, redeemable non-convertible debentures for an aggregate amount of up to approximately Rs. 300 Crores. The company&apos;s Board has also delegated the powers to the Corporate Affairs Committee for finalization of terms &amp; conditions. The company reported its un-audited financial results for the quarter ended December 2025, with a profit before tax of INR 17,629 lakhs. The company also noted an ongoing litigation with a customer on recoverability of balance amounting to INR 2,929 lakhs.</p><ul><li>Approval of term loan or issuance of non-convertible debentures up to Rs. 300 Crores</li><li>Delegation of powers to Corporate Affairs Committee for finalization of terms &amp; conditions</li><li>Reported profit before tax of INR 17,629 lakhs for Q3 2025</li><li>Ongoing litigation with a customer on recoverability of balance amounting to INR 2,929 lakhs</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/30e4397a-4b82-4136-85b8-ca12ce4b90e3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vikran Engineering Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SICALLOG] Sical Logistics Approves Rights Issue of Equity Shares and Quarterly Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SICAL+LOGISTICS+LTD.&title=Sical+Logistics+Approves+Rights+Issue+of+Equity+Shares+and+Quarterly+Financial+Results&newsId=06692a4d-47b4-4d75-9c3b-466664dc7c64&token=MDY2OTJhNGQtNDdi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06692a4d-47b4-4d75-9c3b-466664dc7c64</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sical Logistics Limited has informed the exchange about the approval of the rights issue of equity shares and the quarterly financial results. The rights issue of equity shares will be offered to the public shareholders of the Company as on the record date, with a rights entitlement ratio of 11 (eleven) rights equity shares for every 5 (five) equity shares held. The quarterly financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, have been considered and approved by the Board.</p><ul><li>Sical Logistics approved a rights issue of equity shares for an aggregate amount not exceeding Rs. 93,02,90,560/-</li><li>The rights issue is offered to public shareholders as on the record date with a rights entitlement ratio of 11:5</li><li>The Board considered and approved the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4d700500-781b-4566-90b7-3181b8819a12.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SICAL LOGISTICS LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EMAINDIA] EMA India Ltd. Reports Q3 and Nine Months Results for FY 2025-26, Announces Director Appointments and Resignation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=EMA+INDIA+LTD.&title=EMA+India+Ltd.+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+FY+2025-26%2C+Announces+Director+Appointments+and+Resignation&newsId=a87c2553-75ad-40cf-bf66-d0956f517409&token=YTg3YzI1NTMtNzVh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a87c2553-75ad-40cf-bf66-d0956f517409</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>EMA India Ltd. announced the revised outcome of its board meeting held on February 13, 2026. The company reported the Un-audited Standalone Financial Results for the Quarter and nine months ended 31% December, 2025, along with the Limited Review Report of the Auditors on Standalone Financial Results. The board appointed Mr. Apurva Shivaji Adhalrao as an Additional Director (Executive, Non-Independent) and Mr. Rajendra Senapati as an Additional Director (Non-Executive, Independent). The board also accepted the resignation of Ms. Honey Bhatia as a Non-Executive Independent Director due to personal reasons. The Audit Committee and Nomination &amp; Remuneration Committee have been reconstituted following Ms. Bhatia&apos;s resignation.</p><ul><li>EMA India Ltd. reported Q3 and nine months results for FY 2025-26</li><li>Un-audited Standalone Financial Results and Limited Review Report of the Auditors on Standalone Financial Results were approved</li><li>Mr. Apurva Shivaji Adhalrao and Mr. Rajendra Senapati appointed as Additional Directors</li><li>Ms. Honey Bhatia resigned as a Non-Executive Independent Director</li><li>Audit Committee and Nomination &amp; Remuneration Committee reconstituted</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8162e292-a1d4-48aa-a1a4-b9f62e53f5cf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: EMA INDIA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SICALLOG] Sical Logistics Ltd. Approves Quarterly Financial Results and Rights Issue Terms</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SICAL+LOGISTICS+LTD.&title=Sical+Logistics+Ltd.+Approves+Quarterly+Financial+Results+and+Rights+Issue+Terms&newsId=fffa353a-7961-4e6a-9f30-6290e1aa8094&token=ZmZmYTM1M2EtNzk2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fffa353a-7961-4e6a-9f30-6290e1aa8094</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sical Logistics Limited has approved its quarterly financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s board of directors also approved certain clarificatory updates to the terms of the proposed rights issue of equity shares. The rights issue will offer 11 (eleven) rights equity shares for every 5 (five) equity shares held by public shareholders on the record date. The issue size is 1,45,35,790 (one crore forty-five lakh thirty-five thousand seven hundred ninety) fully paid-up equity shares, for an aggregate amount not exceeding Rs. 93,02,90,560/- (ninety-three crore two lakh ninety thousand five hundred sixty only). The rights issue price remains unchanged at Rs. 64 per rights equity share.</p><ul><li>Approval of Quarterly Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Clarificatory updates to the terms of the proposed rights issue of equity shares</li><li>Rights issue offers 11 (eleven) rights equity shares for every 5 (five) equity shares held by public shareholders</li><li>Issue size is 1,45,35,790 (one crore forty-five lakh thirty-five thousand seven hundred ninety) fully paid-up equity shares</li><li>Rights issue price remains unchanged at Rs. 64 per rights equity share</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d830f961-3875-4012-8023-04a14dbafeee.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SICAL LOGISTICS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VIKRAN] Vikran Engineering Ltd: Monitoring Agency Report for Q3 2025 confirms no deviation from IPO objects</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vikran+Engineering+Ltd&title=Vikran+Engineering+Ltd%3A+Monitoring+Agency+Report+for+Q3+2025+confirms+no+deviation+from+IPO+objects&newsId=fdb27b34-53d8-4880-8a3f-2f7fb4b03d47&token=ZmRiMjdiMzQtNTNk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fdb27b34-53d8-4880-8a3f-2f7fb4b03d47</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Care Ratings Limited, the Monitoring Agency appointed by Vikran Engineering Ltd, has released the Monitoring Agency Report for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The report confirms no deviation from the objects of the issue and provides an objective view of the utilization of the issue proceeds. The IPO proceeds of Rs.721 crore were raised in August 2025 and have been utilized as per the disclosures in the Offer Prospectus.</p><ul><li>Vikran Engineering Ltd&apos;s Monitoring Agency Report for Q3 2025 confirms no deviation from IPO objects</li><li>Care Ratings Limited, the Monitoring Agency, has released the report dated 13th February 2026</li><li>The IPO proceeds of Rs.721 crore were raised in August 2025 and have been utilized as per the disclosures in the Offer Prospectus</li><li>The report is based on the information provided by the Issuer and information obtained from sources believed by it to be accurate and reliable</li><li>The Monitoring Agency does not perform an audit and undertakes no independent verification of any information/ certifications/ statements it receives</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8543f9db-6bc9-4c3e-ab08-2ad8f52223df.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vikran Engineering Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VIKRAN] Vikran Engineering Ltd Announces Resignation of Internal Auditors Due to Health Issues</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vikran+Engineering+Ltd&title=Vikran+Engineering+Ltd+Announces+Resignation+of+Internal+Auditors+Due+to+Health+Issues&newsId=99157ba6-c3b9-4012-a13d-fd06cdf1af0d&token=OTkxNTdiYTYtYzNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">99157ba6-c3b9-4012-a13d-fd06cdf1af0d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vikran Engineering Ltd, formerly known as Vikran Engineering &amp; Exim Private Limited, has announced the resignation of its internal auditors, M/S. Shetty and Shetty, Chartered Accountants, with immediate effect from the close of business hours on 13th February 2026. The Senior auditor, who has been handling the company’s internal audit for the past four years, was diagnosed with dengue and other health-related issues, which impacted their ability to complete the audit work as per the original timelines. The company&apos;s registered office is at 401, Odyssey L.T. Park, Road No. 9, Wagle Indusirial Estate, Thane, Maharashtra - 400604. The CIN is L?3000MH2008PLC272209, and the company can be reached at info@vikrangroup.com or 022-6869 3200, with more information available at www.vikrangroup.com.</p><ul><li>Vikran Engineering Ltd announces the resignation of its internal auditors, M/S. Shetty and Shetty, Chartered Accountants.</li><li>The resignation is due to health issues, specifically dengue and other health-related problems affecting the Senior auditor&apos;s ability to complete audit work on time.</li><li>The resignation is effective immediately from the close of business hours on 13th February 2026.</li><li>Vikran Engineering Ltd&apos;s registered office is at 401, Odyssey L.T. Park, Road No. 9, Wagle Indusirial Estate, Thane, Maharashtra - 400604.</li><li>The CIN for Vikran Engineering Ltd is L?3000MH2008PLC272209, and they can be reached at info@vikrangroup.com or 022-6869 3200, with more information available at www.vikrangroup.com.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c8bfa257-e8e9-4c62-8431-67afac0e4e40.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vikran Engineering Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SICALLOG] Sical Logistics Ltd. approves Quarterly Financial Results and Rights Issue terms</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SICAL+LOGISTICS+LTD.&title=Sical+Logistics+Ltd.+approves+Quarterly+Financial+Results+and+Rights+Issue+terms&newsId=1bf84a5a-65ef-45f4-b610-aec8389e02d3&token=MWJmODRhNWEtNjVl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1bf84a5a-65ef-45f4-b610-aec8389e02d3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sical Logistics Limited has approved its Quarterly Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, and made certain clarificatory updates to the terms of the proposed Rights Issue. The Rights Issue, which was earlier approved on February 12, 2026, will offer 11 rights equity shares for every 5 equity shares held by public shareholders on the record date. The issue size is 1,45,35,790 fully paid-up equity shares of face value of Rs. 10 each, for an aggregate amount not exceeding Rs. 93,02,90,560. The Rights Issue price remains unchanged at Rs. 64 per rights equity share.</p><ul><li>Approval of Quarterly Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Clarificatory updates to the terms of the proposed Rights Issue</li><li>Rights Issue offers 11 rights equity shares for every 5 equity shares held by public shareholders</li><li>Issue size of 1,45,35,790 fully paid-up equity shares</li><li>Rights Issue price remains unchanged at Rs. 64 per rights equity share</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/11c0b8df-8fd2-4790-a828-3536dc511ebf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SICAL LOGISTICS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VIKRAN] Vikran Engineering Reports 9M FY26 Revenue Growth; Order Book Expands to ₹ 4,987 Crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vikran+Engineering+Ltd&title=Vikran+Engineering+Reports+9M+FY26+Revenue+Growth%3B+Order+Book+Expands+to+%E2%82%B9+4%2C987+Crore&newsId=e4d2e1ae-0c77-4245-b2fe-f1fe0ee60555&token=ZTRkMmUxYWUtMGM3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e4d2e1ae-0c77-4245-b2fe-f1fe0ee60555</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Vikran Engineering Limited, one of India’s fast-growing EPC companies, has announced its un-audited financial results for the third quarter and nine month ended December 315, 2025. The company has reported a robust increase in its consolidated order book, which stands at over ₹ 4,987 crore as of December 31st, 2025. This represents a 146% growth compared to ₹ 2,027 crore as on December 315t, 2024. The company has secured prestigious orders from Onix Renewables Limited and NTPC Renewable Energy, and won an order from M.P. Urja Vikas Nigam Limited. However, the company has cancelled an order from Carbonminus Maharashtra One Private Limited. The company&apos;s revenue visibility has been significantly enhanced with the consolidated order book now exceeding ₹ 4,700 crore as on 13th February 2026.</p><ul><li>Vikran Engineering reports 9M FY26 revenue growth</li><li>Order book expands to ₹ 4,987 crore, registering over 140% YoY and 120% QoQ growth</li><li>Secured a prestigious order from Onix Renewables Limited for supply of 600 MW AC solar plant</li><li>Won an EPC Contract from NTPC Renewable Energy for 400 MW AC Solar Project in Uttar Pradesh</li><li>Cancellation of order from Carbonminus Maharashtra One Private Limited worth ₹ 1,641.91 crores</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/be40d45e-7591-48ea-bebb-284dc802bef0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vikran Engineering Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BHARATAGRI] Bharat Agri Fert &amp; Realty Ltd Approves Q3 Results Amidst Management Absence</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BHARAT+AGRI+FERT+%26+REALTY+LTD.&title=Bharat+Agri+Fert+%26+Realty+Ltd+Approves+Q3+Results+Amidst+Management+Absence&newsId=099dfb7b-448b-4498-9c2e-92b05e2ad81b&token=MDk5ZGZiN2ItNDQ4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">099dfb7b-448b-4498-9c2e-92b05e2ad81b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 22:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bharat Agri Fert &amp; Realty Ltd has approved the Unaudited Financial Results for the Quarter and Nine Months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting was held by the independent directors due to the passing away of the Chairman and Managing Director, and the absence of other Executive Directors. The company has authorized Mr. Chunilal Gherwada, Independent Director, to sign the financial results on behalf of the Board. The Independent Auditor&apos;s Review Report has been submitted in accordance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Bharat Agri Fert &amp; Realty Ltd approves Q3 results in absence of Executive Directors</li><li>Meeting conducted by Independent Directors due to management absence</li><li>Mr. Chunilal Gherwada authorized to sign financial results on behalf of the Board</li><li>Independent Auditor&apos;s Review Report submitted in accordance with SEBI regulations</li><li>Company&apos;s Fertiliser Segment incurs significant loss with less than nil capacity utilization</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7d909848-b13e-4321-9ca2-80a2089be206.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BHARAT AGRI FERT & REALTY LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GKENERGY] GK Energy Corrects Typographical Error in Segment Assets of Consolidated Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GK+Energy+Ltd&title=GK+Energy+Corrects+Typographical+Error+in+Segment+Assets+of+Consolidated+Financial+Results&newsId=292f02ac-fc54-4c0f-bd39-b9467eb6394e&token=MjkyZjAyYWMtZmM1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">292f02ac-fc54-4c0f-bd39-b9467eb6394e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 22:32:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>GK Energy Limited has informed the Exchange about a Corrigendum related to a typographical error in the allocation of segment assets in the Consolidated Financial Results. The error was in the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The revised file, incorporating the bifurcation of allocable segment assets into EPC Business and Trading of Solar Cells (DCR), has been enclosed for reference. The correction does not affect any other information in the earlier intimation.</p><ul><li>GK Energy corrected a typographical error in the allocation of segment assets in the Consolidated Financial Results.</li><li>The error was in the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The revised file incorporates the bifurcation of allocable segment assets into EPC Business and Trading of Solar Cells (DCR).</li><li>The correction does not affect any other information in the earlier intimation.</li><li>The company is primarily into the business of design, manufacture, supply, transportation, installation, testing and commissioning of decentralized solar systems.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3e5fd79b-8aa3-42d6-b680-c4d12627beb8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GK Energy Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>