<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 06:31:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SATIN] Satin Creditcare Network Ltd. Approves Issuance of Non-Convertible Debentures Worth INR 175 Crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Satin+Creditcare+Network+Ltd&title=Satin+Creditcare+Network+Ltd.+Approves+Issuance+of+Non-Convertible+Debentures+Worth+INR+175+Crore&newsId=851268c1-f27e-4e51-b174-dc596febcce9&token=ODUxMjY4YzEtZjI3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">851268c1-f27e-4e51-b174-dc596febcce9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 06:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Satin Creditcare Network Ltd. announced the outcome of its Working Committee meeting held on January 20, 2026, which approved the issuance of non-convertible debentures (NCDs) on a private placement basis. The issuance includes 5,000 subordinated, unsecured, rated, listed, taxable, redeemable, transferable, non-convertible debentures (Subordinated Debentures) worth INR 50,00,00,000 and 1,25,000 senior, secured, rated, listed, taxable, redeemable, non-convertible debentures (Secured Debentures) worth INR 125,00,00,000. The Subordinated Debentures come with a 12% annual interest rate, while the Secured Debentures have a 10.50% annual interest rate, both payable monthly. The Subordinated Debentures have a tenure of 66 months, while the Secured Debentures have a tenure of 24 months.</p><ul><li>Satin Creditcare Network Ltd. approved the issuance of non-convertible debentures (NCDs) worth INR 175 crore.</li><li>The issuance includes 5,000 subordinated, unsecured, rated, listed, taxable, redeemable, transferable, non-convertible debentures (Subordinated Debentures) worth INR 50,00,00,000.</li><li>Additionally, 1,25,000 senior, secured, rated, listed, taxable, redeemable, non-convertible debentures (Secured Debentures) worth INR 125,00,00,000 will be issued.</li><li>The Subordinated Debentures have a 12% annual interest rate, while the Secured Debentures have a 10.50% annual interest rate.</li><li>The Subordinated Debentures have a tenure of 66 months, while the Secured Debentures have a tenure of 24 months.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ee61b5eb-2d5f-4d02-9c21-63cab056fa6f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Satin Creditcare Network Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CHANDRIMA] Chandrima Mercantiles Ltd. to Hold Extra-Ordinary General Meeting on 11% February, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Chandrima+Mercantiles+Ltd&title=Chandrima+Mercantiles+Ltd.+to+Hold+Extra-Ordinary+General+Meeting+on+11%25+February%2C+2026&newsId=53e2720a-63af-45c1-b20a-da4fcc2ddc84&token=NTNlMjcyMGEtNjNh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53e2720a-63af-45c1-b20a-da4fcc2ddc84</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 06:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Chandrima Mercantiles Ltd. has announced that it will hold an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) of the members on Wednesday, 11% February, 2026 at 11:30 A.M. The meeting will be conducted through Video Conferencing (VC) and Other Audio-Visual Means (OAVM) as per the Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Chandrima Mercantiles Ltd. to hold an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) on 11% February, 2026</li><li>The meeting will be conducted through Video Conferencing (VC) and Other Audio-Visual Means (OAVM)</li><li>The decision was made in the Board of Directors meeting held on 20 January, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8627fa1e-d929-47f3-bca2-03c09ba7442e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Chandrima Mercantiles Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASAHISONG] Asahi Songwon Colors Ltd set Board Meeting on January 29, 2026 to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ASAHI+SONGWON+COLORS+LTD.&title=Asahi+Songwon+Colors+Ltd+set+Board+Meeting+on+January+29%2C+2026+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results&newsId=702ebb1d-6714-4aba-820f-d3c4a042f3f0&token=NzAyZWJiMWQtNjcx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">702ebb1d-6714-4aba-820f-d3c4a042f3f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 06:24:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Asahi Songwon Colors Ltd has announced a Board of Directors meeting scheduled for January 29, 2026. The agenda includes the consideration and approval of the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting also aims to take on record other business items. In compliance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, the trading window for dealing in securities of the Company by its Designated Persons and their immediate relatives has been closed from January 01, 2026 and will be re-opened after 48 hours of submitting the financial results to the Stock Exchanges.</p><ul><li>Asahi Songwon Colors Ltd Board Meeting scheduled for January 29, 2026</li><li>Consideration and approval of unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities of the Company by its Designated Persons and their immediate relatives closed from January 01, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/00b45793-daed-437a-9955-31a5193b1526.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ASAHI SONGWON COLORS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BHARTIARTL] Bharti Airtel Ltd Fined Rs. 2,06,000 by DoT for Subscriber Verification Norms Violation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BHARTI+AIRTEL+LTD.&title=Bharti+Airtel+Ltd+Fined+Rs.+2%2C06%2C000+by+DoT+for+Subscriber+Verification+Norms+Violation&newsId=acde1959-6505-4dbb-9ce3-1674ff969b48&token=YWNkZTE5NTktNjUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">acde1959-6505-4dbb-9ce3-1674ff969b48</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 06:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bharti Airtel Ltd, a Bharti Enterprise, has been issued a notice by the Department of Telecommunications, Karnataka LSA (DoT), imposing a penalty of Rs. 2,06,000 for alleged violation of subscriber verification norms. The notice was received on January 19, 2026, at IST 1647 Hrs. The violation pertains to the period of November, 2025, and the Company has opted not to contest the penalty. The maximum financial impact of this violation is to the extent of the penalty levied.</p><ul><li>Bharti Airtel Ltd fined Rs. 2,06,000 by DoT for subscriber verification norms violation.</li><li>The violation pertains to the period of November, 2025.</li><li>The Company has opted not to contest the penalty.</li><li>The maximum financial impact of this violation is to the extent of the penalty levied.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/72d6a34a-196e-4ac2-bcdd-40d7840f224b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BHARTI AIRTEL LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NSDL] National Securities Depository Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=National+Securities+Depository+Ltd&title=National+Securities+Depository+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=87689201-0b80-4310-93f0-8a40f4c642b9&token=ODc2ODkyMDEtMGI4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">87689201-0b80-4310-93f0-8a40f4c642b9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 06:18:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>National Securities Depository Ltd has informed BSE that their Board of Directors will meet on 28th January, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting also aims to approve the Limited Review Report for the same period. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company by the Designated Persons/Connected Persons and their immediate relatives has been closed from January 01, 2026, and will reopen 48 hours after the announcement of the financial results.</p><ul><li>National Securities Depository Ltd to approve the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>The trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company by the Designated Persons/Connected Persons and their immediate relatives is closed from January 01, 2026</li><li>The trading window will reopen 48 hours after the announcement of the financial results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0d210fbf-b020-4bb4-9f00-0a75f4c1747c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: National Securities Depository Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CHANDRIMA] Chandrima Mercantiles Ltd. to Hold Extra-Ordinary General Meeting on 11% February, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Chandrima+Mercantiles+Ltd&title=Chandrima+Mercantiles+Ltd.+to+Hold+Extra-Ordinary+General+Meeting+on+11%25+February%2C+2026&newsId=00c48f5d-8506-4d0a-b9c3-a5b317cd48da&token=MDBjNDhmNWQtODUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00c48f5d-8506-4d0a-b9c3-a5b317cd48da</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 06:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Chandrima Mercantiles Ltd. has announced that it will hold an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) of the members of the Company on Wednesday, 11% February, 2026 at 11:30 A.M. The meeting will be conducted through Video Conferencing (VC) and Other Audio-Visual Means (OAVM). The decision was made during a Board of Directors meeting held on 20 January, 2026 at the Registered Office of the Company in Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India.</p><ul><li>Chandrima Mercantiles Ltd. to hold an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting on 11% February, 2026</li><li>The meeting will be conducted through Video Conferencing and Other Audio-Visual Means</li><li>The decision was made during a Board of Directors meeting held on 20 January, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8dcb21ae-2696-41d2-815b-332b7d5cf1ff.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Chandrima Mercantiles Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WESTLIFE] Westlife Foodworld Ltd to Approve Q4 Financials in February 2026 Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Westlife+Foodworld+Ltd&title=Westlife+Foodworld+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+Financials+in+February+2026+Board+Meeting&newsId=697cfbaa-86a3-4f9c-bbb2-ac90ad367f90&token=Njk3Y2ZiYWEtODZh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">697cfbaa-86a3-4f9c-bbb2-ac90ad367f90</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 06:14:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Westlife Foodworld Ltd has announced a Board of Directors meeting on 4th February 2026 to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The meeting is in compliance with Regulation 29 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Westlife Foodworld Ltd scheduled a Board of Directors meeting on 4th February 2026</li><li>The meeting aims to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for Q4 2025</li><li>The announcement is in compliance with Regulation 29 of SEBI&apos;s Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6020e36a-2c8c-4523-882f-e3d26fb79b9f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Westlife Foodworld Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASTEC] Astec Lifesciences Ltd to Consider and Approve Q3 and Nine Months’ Results on 30th January, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ASTEC+LIFESCIENCES+LIMITED&title=Astec+Lifesciences+Ltd+to+Consider+and+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months%E2%80%99+Results+on+30th+January%2C+2026&newsId=79fec1cd-edf6-47d1-80eb-9bc97ae24b1c&token=NzlmZWMxY2QtZWRm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79fec1cd-edf6-47d1-80eb-9bc97ae24b1c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 06:12:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Astec Lifesciences Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 30th January, 2026 to consider and approve the Standalone and Consolidated Unaudited Financial Results for the Quarter and Nine Months’ period ended 31st December, 2025. The meeting will be held after the results are reviewed by the Audit Committee. This announcement is in accordance with Regulations 29 and 50(1) of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Astec Lifesciences Ltd to consider and approve Q3 and Nine Months’ results on 30th January, 2026</li><li>The results will be reviewed by the Audit Committee before approval</li><li>The announcement is in compliance with Regulations 29 and 50(1) of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3cde6c05-b841-4eee-94f7-4cb6c526ef10.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ASTEC LIFESCIENCES LIMITED | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WINSOMBR] Winsome Breweries Ltd Announces Closure of Trading Window for Designated Persons</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=WINSOME+BREWERIES+LTD.&title=Winsome+Breweries+Ltd+Announces+Closure+of+Trading+Window+for+Designated+Persons&newsId=57cf2479-9338-42b8-982b-d0214c3d6739&token=NTdjZjI0NzktOTMz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57cf2479-9338-42b8-982b-d0214c3d6739</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 06:10:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Winsome Breweries Ltd has announced that the &apos;Trading Window&apos; will be closed for all &apos;Designated Persons&apos; with effect from Thursday, 01st January, 2026 till 48 hours after the announcement of the Financial Results for the quarter ended 31st December, 2025. The date of the Board Meeting for the declaration of financial results of the company for the quarter ended 31st December, 2025 will be intimated in due course.</p><ul><li>Winsome Breweries Ltd announces closure of trading window for designated persons</li><li>Trading window to be closed from 01st January, 2026 till 48 hours after the announcement of Q4 2025 financial results</li><li>The date of the Board Meeting for the declaration of financial results for Q4 2025 yet to be announced</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6684a1f4-7c4f-48d4-9017-0fac8a209559.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: WINSOME BREWERIES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PROSTARM] Prostarm Info Systems Ltd Wins 2MW Roof Top Solar Project from SAIL</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Prostarm+Info+Systems+Ltd&title=Prostarm+Info+Systems+Ltd+Wins+2MW+Roof+Top+Solar+Project+from+SAIL&newsId=c08f93c9-6246-4a7d-8439-f79780cc3d36&token=YzA4ZjkzYzktNjI0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c08f93c9-6246-4a7d-8439-f79780cc3d36</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 06:08:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Prostarm Info Systems Limited has been declared as the L-1 bidder by Steel Authority of India Ltd (SAIL) for the supply, installation, and commissioning of a 2MW (AC) Roof Top Solar PV System on Burnpur Plant, West Bengal. The project is priced at INR 6.71Cr.</p><ul><li>Prostarm Info Systems Ltd won the L-1 bidder status for a 2MW Roof Top Solar Project from SAIL.</li><li>The project involves the supply, installation, and commissioning of a 2MW (AC) Roof Top Solar PV System.</li><li>The project is to be executed in Burnpur Plant, West Bengal.</li><li>The project is priced at INR 6.71Cr.</li><li>The project is to be completed within 12 months.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/19b01b97-b73e-4bd6-8539-1cb907f4c813.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Prostarm Info Systems Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>