<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:21:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SALSTEEL] S.A.L. Steel Ltd: Babulal M Singhal Resigns as Whole Time Director, Continues as CFO</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=S.A.L.STEEL+LTD.&title=S.A.L.+Steel+Ltd%3A+Babulal+M+Singhal+Resigns+as+Whole+Time+Director%2C+Continues+as+CFO&newsId=34bea704-fc3d-4003-a111-7c8abb31318f&token=MzRiZWE3MDQtZmMz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">34bea704-fc3d-4003-a111-7c8abb31318f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>S.A.L. Steel Ltd announced the resignation of Babulal M Singhal as Whole Time Director due to personal and unavoidable circumstances, effective from the conclusion of the Board meeting held on February 14th, 2026. However, Singhal will continue to serve as the Chief Financial Officer of the company. The company has disclosed the necessary details as required under Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations &amp; Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Babulal M Singhal has resigned as Whole Time Director of S.A.L. Steel Ltd.</li><li>The resignation is due to personal and unavoidable circumstances.</li><li>Singhal will continue to serve as the Chief Financial Officer (CFO) of the company.</li><li>The resignation is effective from the conclusion of the Board meeting held on February 14th, 2026.</li><li>The company has disclosed the necessary details as required under Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations &amp; Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b80b4f68-ad92-4ffb-a378-11bdbb5367b2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: S.A.L.STEEL LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ORICON] Oricon Enterprises Ltd. Approves Sale of Shares in Tecnocap Oriental Private Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ORICON+ENTERPRISES+LTD.-%24&title=Oricon+Enterprises+Ltd.+Approves+Sale+of+Shares+in+Tecnocap+Oriental+Private+Limited&newsId=3b0b304a-706a-49fe-b311-ce52c2776bcf&token=M2IwYjMwNGEtNzA2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b0b304a-706a-49fe-b311-ce52c2776bcf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:14:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Oricon Enterprises Ltd. has announced the approval of the sale of 2,46,833 (Iwo Lakhs Forty-Six Thousand Eight Hundred Thirty-Three) equity shares, which is 25% of Tecnocap Oriental Private Limited, an Associate Company. The sale is in accordance with the Joint Venture Agreement dated February 28, 2020, between the COMPANY, TGP TECNOCAP GROUP PARTECIPAZOINI S.R.L and TECNOCAP ORIENTAL PRIVATE LIMITED. The details of the sale will be submitted on the execution of the agreement or the occurrence of the event, as per the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements), 2015.</p><ul><li>Oricon Enterprises Ltd. has approved the sale of shares in Tecnocap Oriental Private Limited.</li><li>The sale involves 2,46,833 equity shares, which is 25% of Tecnocap Oriental Private Limited.</li><li>The sale is in accordance with the Joint Venture Agreement dated February 28, 2020.</li><li>The details of the sale will be submitted as per the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements), 2015.</li><li>The sale is expected to occur after the execution of the agreement.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2f65e8c8-ad9d-4450-a9bc-ba6c819f965d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ORICON ENTERPRISES LTD.-$ | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PTC] PTC India Ltd Declares Interim Dividend of Rs. 3 per Share for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PTC+INDIA+LTD.&title=PTC+India+Ltd+Declares+Interim+Dividend+of+Rs.+3+per+Share+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=9cf4c729-4e5f-47a4-a3a2-e703311aeba0&token=OWNmNGM3MjktNGU1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9cf4c729-4e5f-47a4-a3a2-e703311aeba0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>PTC India Ltd held a Board meeting on 14th February 2026 and approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company declared an interim dividend of Rs. 3 per equity share of Rs. 10/- each for financial year 2025-26. The record date for the purpose of ascertaining the name of members entitled to receive the Interim Dividend is fixed as 20th February, 2026.</p><ul><li>PTC India Ltd announced an interim dividend of Rs. 3 per equity share for FY 2025-26.</li><li>The company&apos;s Board approved the unaudited financial results for quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The record date for the purpose of ascertaining the name of members entitled to receive the Interim Dividend is fixed as 20th February, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e2e9af32-6680-4025-a652-d7addee73d1c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PTC INDIA LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PARMAX] Parmax Pharma Reports Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Parmax+Pharma+Ltd&title=Parmax+Pharma+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=41dab187-61e3-4def-97f1-8b2d1ef18e15&token=NDFkYWIxODctNjFl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41dab187-61e3-4def-97f1-8b2d1ef18e15</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:12:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Parmax Pharma Ltd. announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations was ₹ 28,203.95 Lakhs for the quarter and ₹ 111,973.06 Lakhs for the nine months. The net loss for the quarter was ₹ 7,318.98 Lakhs and ₹ 20,940.10 Lakhs for the nine months. The company is operating in a single pharmaceutical segment and the results are for that segment only. The company has not charged depreciation on the clean room plant and effluent treatment plant for the nine months ended 31.12.2025. The company is awaiting the surveyor&apos;s report for a fire that occurred in December 2023 and has not yet submitted the claim of ₹ 35 Lakhs with the insurance company.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter is ₹ 28,203.95 Lakhs</li><li>Revenue from operations for the nine months is ₹ 111,973.06 Lakhs</li><li>Net loss for the quarter is ₹ 7,318.98 Lakhs</li><li>Net loss for the nine months is ₹ 20,940.10 Lakhs</li><li>Company is operating in a single pharmaceutical segment</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/10670d53-7ef5-479f-a5bc-5b97e951406c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Parmax Pharma Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RAINBOWF] Rainbow Foundations Ltd. Approves Q3 Results with Profit After Tax at ₹ 801.15 Lakhs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RAINBOW+FOUNDATIONS+LTD.&title=Rainbow+Foundations+Ltd.+Approves+Q3+Results+with+Profit+After+Tax+at+%E2%82%B9+801.15+Lakhs&newsId=876a8560-f1e7-41a0-bfec-f731555c5e5f&token=ODc2YTg1NjAtZjFl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">876a8560-f1e7-41a0-bfec-f731555c5e5f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:12:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rainbow Foundations Ltd. has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The total revenue stands at ₹ 3,434.45 Lakhs, with a profit before tax at ₹ 1,103.26 Lakhs. The profit after tax is ₹ 801.15 Lakhs. The Board has also approved providing a corporate guarantee in favor of the Debenture Trustee(s) for the issuance of unlisted, secured, redeemable, cumulative, non-convertible debentures by the wholly owned subsidiary, Rainbow Foundations and Real Estates Private Limited, up to ₹ 50.00 Crore.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for Q3 FY2025-26 is ₹ 3,417.74 Lakhs</li><li>Profit before tax for Q3 FY2025-26 is ₹ 1,103.26 Lakhs</li><li>Profit after tax for Q3 FY2025-26 is ₹ 801.15 Lakhs</li><li>The Board has approved providing a corporate guarantee in favor of the Debenture Trustee(s) for the issuance of unlisted, secured, redeemable, cumulative, non-convertible debentures by the wholly owned subsidiary, Rainbow Foundations and Real Estates Private Limited, up to ₹ 50.00 Crore</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3b5422fa-0356-498b-84ce-054a80a2e2a7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RAINBOW FOUNDATIONS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GKSL] Gujarat Kidney and Super Speciality Ltd. Approves Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended December 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Gujarat+Kidney+and+Super+Speciality+Ltd&title=Gujarat+Kidney+and+Super+Speciality+Ltd.+Approves+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+December+2025&newsId=810220a9-d6cb-497d-ad79-fa45de092e20&token=ODEwMjIwYTktZDZj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">810220a9-d6cb-497d-ad79-fa45de092e20</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:12:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gujarat Kidney and Super Speciality Ltd. held a Board meeting on 14th February 2026 and approved the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The results were reviewed by the statutory auditors and show a revenue from operations of INR 3,516.70 Lacs for the quarter and INR 10,252.44 Lacs for the nine-month period. The net profit for the quarter stands at INR 7.30 Lacs and INR 24.14 Lacs for the nine-month period. The EPS (Basic and Diluted) for the period is INR 0.23 and INR 0.78 respectively.</p><ul><li>Approval of Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended December 2025</li><li>Revenue from operations: INR 3,516.70 Lacs (Q3) and INR 10,252.44 Lacs (9M)</li><li>Net profit: INR 7.30 Lacs (Q3) and INR 24.14 Lacs (9M)</li><li>EPS (Basic and Diluted): INR 0.23 and INR 0.78 respectively</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1a115186-ab67-4e5e-8391-f36107b06fdc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Gujarat Kidney and Super Speciality Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDSOYA] Apollo Ingredients (Formerly Indsoya) Faces 75% Deviation from Objects in Rights Issue Proceeds Utilization</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDSOYA+LTD.&title=Apollo+Ingredients+%28Formerly+Indsoya%29+Faces+75%25+Deviation+from+Objects+in+Rights+Issue+Proceeds+Utilization&newsId=41f4c75c-8beb-418c-a667-0c3c13d51754&token=NDFmNGM3NWMtOGJl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41f4c75c-8beb-418c-a667-0c3c13d51754</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:12:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Apollo Ingredients Limited (formerly known as Indsoya Limited) has deviated from the objects of the issue by 75% in the utilization of proceeds raised through the Right Issue. The deviation was due to an advance lease payment of Rs. 3.00 crore made without shareholder approval through a special resolution. This deviation was reviewed by the Audit Committee and taken on record by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Apollo Ingredients (formerly Indsoya) has deviated from the objects of the issue by 75% in the utilization of proceeds raised through the Right Issue.</li><li>The deviation was due to an advance lease payment of Rs. 3.00 crore made without shareholder approval through a special resolution.</li><li>The deviation was reviewed by the Audit Committee and taken on record by the Board of Directors.</li><li>The Monitoring Agency Report was issued by Infomerics Valuation and Rating Limited.</li><li>The report was reviewed by the Audit Committee and taken on record by the Board of Directors at its meeting held on 14th February, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/eda6eb08-aa10-4f21-bfd4-aeb353a54e72.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDSOYA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GLOTTIS] Glottis Ltd Extends Timeline for Utilization of Unutilized IPO Proceeds by a Year</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Glottis+Ltd&title=Glottis+Ltd+Extends+Timeline+for+Utilization+of+Unutilized+IPO+Proceeds+by+a+Year&newsId=299fa55f-6f2b-4d55-b48c-9cb385bfb488&token=Mjk5ZmE1NWYtNmYy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">299fa55f-6f2b-4d55-b48c-9cb385bfb488</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Glottis Ltd announced the extension of the timeline for utilizing the unutilized IPO proceeds for a period of 1 year starting from April 01, 2026, to March 31, 2027. The company had proposed to utilize ¥1,599.99 Million from the IPO proceeds for various identified objects, out of which ¥354.36 Million has been utilized as of December 31, 2025. The unutilized amount stands at ¥1,245.63 Million, which is currently maintained in compliance with applicable provisions of the Companies Act, 2013, the SEBI (ICDR) Regulations, 2018, and other applicable laws and regulations. The extension of the timeline pertains solely to the deployment of the remaining funds and does not involve any change in the objects of the issue as stated in the Offer Document.</p><ul><li>Glottis Ltd extends timeline for utilization of unutilized IPO proceeds by a year</li><li>Unutilized IPO proceeds amounted to ¥1,245.63 Million as of December 31, 2025</li><li>Out of ¥1,599.99 Million proposed, ¥354.36 Million has been utilized</li><li>Unutilized proceeds maintained in compliance with applicable laws and regulations</li><li>Extension of timeline does not involve any change in the objects of the issue</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/029b594d-fea2-41ea-8f59-5011d5921943.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Glottis Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RAINBOWF] Rainbow Foundations Ltd Announces Q3 2025 Financial Results with a Profit After Tax of ₹ 801.15 Crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RAINBOW+FOUNDATIONS+LTD.&title=Rainbow+Foundations+Ltd+Announces+Q3+2025+Financial+Results+with+a+Profit+After+Tax+of+%E2%82%B9+801.15+Crore&newsId=6448ede4-85a1-4aae-8de5-2a41e97f868f&token=NjQ0OGVkZTQtODVh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6448ede4-85a1-4aae-8de5-2a41e97f868f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rainbow Foundations Ltd has announced its financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at ₹ 3,836.58 Crore. The profit before tax is ₹ 1,103.26 Crore, and the profit after tax is ₹ 801.15 Crore. The company operates in a single segment, and the statutory auditors have carried out a Limited Review of the financial results.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for Q3 2025 is ₹ 3,836.58 Crore</li><li>Profit before tax for Q3 2025 is ₹ 1,103.26 Crore</li><li>Profit after tax for Q3 2025 is ₹ 801.15 Crore</li><li>The company operates in a single segment</li><li>Statutory auditors have carried out a Limited Review of the financial results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2393088c-6230-4bc3-b48c-8cedd46b36db.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RAINBOW FOUNDATIONS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ORICON] Oricon Enterprises Ltd. Announces Q3 and Nine-Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ORICON+ENTERPRISES+LTD.-%24&title=Oricon+Enterprises+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+Nine-Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=a70a5acc-fe97-47cb-b858-aea81a63972c&token=YTcwYTVhY2MtZmU5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a70a5acc-fe97-47cb-b858-aea81a63972c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:07:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Oricon Enterprises Ltd. has announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue, expenses, and profits have been reported, along with details of discontinued operations and other comprehensive income.</p><ul><li>Revenue for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, is Rs. 6,916.93 lakhs.</li><li>Profit before tax for the quarter is Rs. 5,034.18 lakhs.</li><li>Profit after tax for the quarter is Rs. 4,561.17 lakhs.</li><li>Discontinued operations have resulted in a profit of Rs. 13.83 lakhs for the quarter.</li><li>Other comprehensive income for the period is Rs. 974.77 lakhs.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2df06357-8310-442f-995b-97a1dc56bb3f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ORICON ENTERPRISES LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>