<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:27:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[GROVY] Grovy India Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q4 Results and Evaluate Fund Raising Proposals</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Grovy+India+Ltd&title=Grovy+India+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q4+Results+and+Evaluate+Fund+Raising+Proposals&newsId=085fcffc-b153-4394-b53a-4ecc2e27bc13&token=MDg1ZmNmZmMtYjE1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">085fcffc-b153-4394-b53a-4ecc2e27bc13</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Grovy India Ltd has informed the BSE that its Board of Directors will meet on 28th January 2026 to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company will also evaluate proposals for fund raising, which may include the issuance of equity shares or equity-linked instruments. The trading window for dealing in the company&apos;s shares is closed as of 29th December 2025.</p><ul><li>Grovy India Ltd to consider and approve unaudited financial results for Q4 2025</li><li>Company to evaluate fund raising proposals through various modes</li><li>Trading window for dealing in company&apos;s shares is closed as of 29th December 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8b70c069-405f-4826-b0b8-8154b975ed37.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Grovy India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MCX] Multi Commodity Exchange of India Ltd Receives ESG Rating of &apos;78.8&apos; for FY 2025 by SES ESG Research</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MULTI+COMMODITY+EXCHANGE+OF+INDIA+LTD.&title=Multi+Commodity+Exchange+of+India+Ltd+Receives+ESG+Rating+of+%2778.8%27+for+FY+2025+by+SES+ESG+Research&newsId=f7caf6a6-98c1-4b98-8b40-63e5563f5b5b&token=ZjdjYWY2YTYtOThj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7caf6a6-98c1-4b98-8b40-63e5563f5b5b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Rating</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Multi Commodity Exchange of India Ltd has been assigned an ESG rating of &apos;78.8&apos; for the financial year 2025 by SES ESG Research Private Limited. This rating is based on the company&apos;s performance on Environmental, Social, and Governance parameters. The company clarifies that they have not engaged SES ESG for this rating, which is independently prepared by them based on information available in the public domain. This disclosure is being made in accordance with Regulation 30 of SEBI Listing Regulations and is also available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>SES ESG Research has assigned an ESG rating of &apos;78.8&apos; to Multi Commodity Exchange of India Ltd for FY 2025</li><li>The rating is based on the company&apos;s performance on Environmental, Social, and Governance parameters</li><li>The company did not engage SES ESG for this rating, which is independently prepared by them</li><li>The rating is based on information available in the public domain</li><li>The disclosure is being made in accordance with Regulation 30 of SEBI Listing Regulations and is also available on the company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/58303a81-0133-4ae4-94e9-37f8f101acce.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MULTI COMMODITY EXCHANGE OF INDIA LTD. | Category: Rating</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SERIND] SER Industries Ltd. Announces Changes in Corporate Office Address, MOA, and AOA</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SER+Industries+Ltd&title=SER+Industries+Ltd.+Announces+Changes+in+Corporate+Office+Address%2C+MOA%2C+and+AOA&newsId=7f67e27b-a172-4b59-b09b-6acb002d3a57&token=N2Y2N2UyN2ItYTE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7f67e27b-a172-4b59-b09b-6acb002d3a57</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:20:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SER Industries Ltd. has announced changes in its corporate office address, Memorandum of Association (MOA), and Articles of Association (AOA). The company&apos;s Board of Directors approved these changes at their meeting on January 22, 2026. The new corporate office will be located at Plot No 79, 501, 5th Floor Lalwani House, Sakore Nagar Viman Nagar, Pune, Maharashtra, India, 411014. The MOA will be amended as per the Companies Act, 2013, and the AOA will be replaced with a new set that aligns with the new Act. These changes are subject to the approval of the company&apos;s shareholders.</p><ul><li>Change in corporate office address to Pune, Maharashtra</li><li>Amendment of Memorandum of Association (MOA) as per Companies Act, 2013</li><li>Adoption of new Articles of Association (AOA) as per Companies Act, 2013</li><li>Changes subject to approval of the company&apos;s shareholders</li><li>Proposed increase in the Authorised Share Capital of the Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ccdd5d62-e0d6-4c3e-967f-fd3189b2cd47.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SER Industries Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RELIANCE] Reliance Industries Ltd Subsidiaries Amalgamate with Reliance New Energy Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RELIANCE+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Reliance+Industries+Ltd+Subsidiaries+Amalgamate+with+Reliance+New+Energy+Limited&newsId=1acdd5cb-bc0b-469a-9c61-9d3f2692efb1&token=MWFjZGQ1Y2ItYmMw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1acdd5cb-bc0b-469a-9c61-9d3f2692efb1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Reliance Industries Ltd has announced that 16 step-down wholly owned subsidiaries have amalgamated with Reliance New Energy Limited (&apos;RNEL&apos;) effective January 21, 2026. The amalgamation was pursuant to the order of the Regional Director, Western Region, Ministry of Corporate Affairs. The companies that have amalgamated include Reliance Power Electronics Limited, Reliance Electrolyser Manufacturing Limited, Reliance Green Hydrogen and Green Chemicals Limited, Reliance New Power Electronics Limited, Reliance New Energy Storage Limited, Reliance Carbon Fibre Cylinder Limited, Reliance New Energy Carbon Fibre Cylinder Limited, Reliance Hydrogen Electrolysis Limited, Reliance New Energy Hydrogen Electrolysis Limited, Reliance New Energy Power Electronics Limited, Reliance Hydrogen Fuel Cell Limited, Reliance New Energy Hydrogen Fuel Cell Limited, Kutch New Energy Projects Limited, Reliance Petro Materials Limited, Kalamboli East Infra Limited and Kalamboli North Third Infra Limited. The Company received intimation from RNEL on March 24, 2023 at 5:38 p.m. (IST).</p><ul><li>16 step-down wholly owned subsidiaries of Reliance Industries Ltd amalgamated with Reliance New Energy Limited</li><li>Amalgamation pursuant to the order of the Regional Director, Western Region, Ministry of Corporate Affairs</li><li>Companies involved in power electronics, electrolyser manufacturing, green hydrogen, energy storage, carbon fibre cylinder, hydrogen electrolysis, hydrogen fuel cell, and infra projects</li><li>Effective from January 21, 2026</li><li>Reliance Industries Ltd received intimation from RNEL on March 24, 2023</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fba55220-58be-4948-9d43-3a814fe58dd6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RELIANCE INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SURYODAY] Suryoday Small Finance Bank Reports Q3 &amp; 9M FY26 Results: Gross Advances at Rs. 11,885 Cr, Pre-provision Operating Profit at Rs. 277.1 Cr</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Suryoday+Small+Finance+Bank+Ltd&title=Suryoday+Small+Finance+Bank+Reports+Q3+%26+9M+FY26+Results%3A+Gross+Advances+at+Rs.+11%2C885+Cr%2C+Pre-provision+Operating+Profit+at+Rs.+277.1+Cr&newsId=e938433c-85d6-4f1f-8ca2-d5ebfb97f72f&token=ZTkzODQzM2MtODVk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e938433c-85d6-4f1f-8ca2-d5ebfb97f72f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Suryoday Small Finance Bank has reported its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The bank&apos;s gross advances stood at Rs. 11,885 Cr, up 24.3% YoY. The pre-provision operating profit was Rs. 277.1 Cr, down 19.1% YoY. The profit after tax was Rs. 102.2 Cr, down 31.3% YoY. The bank&apos;s GNPA stood at 6.6% and NNPA at 4.3%. The bank has a strong capital position with a CRAR at 21.9% and Tier I capital of 21.0%.</p><ul><li>Gross Advances at Rs. 11,885 Cr, up 24.3% YoY</li><li>Pre-provision Operating Profit at Rs. 277.1 Cr, down 19.1% YoY</li><li>Profit After Tax at Rs. 102.2 Cr, down 31.3% YoY</li><li>GNPA at 6.6% and NNPA at 4.3%</li><li>Strong capital position with a CRAR at 21.9% and Tier I capital of 21.0%</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f6b5c69d-eb53-4741-8955-b81f229800cc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Suryoday Small Finance Bank Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SERIND] SER Industries Ltd. Proposes Amendments to MOA &amp; Adoption of New AOA</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SER+Industries+Ltd&title=SER+Industries+Ltd.+Proposes+Amendments+to+MOA+%26+Adoption+of+New+AOA&newsId=be117acd-c524-469d-9bbb-758b1b61b3ca&token=YmUxMTdhY2QtYzUy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be117acd-c524-469d-9bbb-758b1b61b3ca</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:14:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SER Industries Ltd. has announced the intention to adopt amended Memorandum of Association (MOA) and new Articles of Association (AOA) in line with the Companies Act, 2013. The proposed amendments to the MOA include re-alignment of the Object Clause and Liability Clause, and a clearer description of the Company’s business activities. The new AOA will bring the existing AOA in line with the provisions of the new Act. The Company will also shift its Corporate Office to Pune, Maharashtra.</p><ul><li>SER Industries Ltd. proposes amendments to the Memorandum of Association (MOA) as per Companies Act, 2013.</li><li>The Company will adopt a new set of Articles of Association (AOA) in line with the Companies Act, 2013.</li><li>The Corporate Office of the Company will be shifted to Plot No 79, 501, 5th Floor Lalwani House, Sakore Nagar Viman Nagar, Pune, Maharashtra, India, 411014.</li><li>The proposed revisions in the MOA aim to provide a clearer and more comprehensive description of the Company’s business activities.</li><li>The new AOA will bring the existing AOA in line with the provisions of the Companies Act, 2013.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bd117f67-1a24-4ba7-aa41-e02682135183.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SER Industries Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NIITLTD] NIIT Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q3 and Q9 Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NIIT+LTD.&title=NIIT+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+and+Q9+Results+for+2025&newsId=5229ef22-affe-4515-8f64-f594195adc58&token=NTIyOWVmMjItYWZm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5229ef22-affe-4515-8f64-f594195adc58</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>NIIT Ltd, a leading IT services and training company, has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 30, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, for both Consolidated and Standalone operations. This meeting is in accordance with Regulation 29 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>NIIT Ltd scheduled a Board Meeting for January 30, 2026</li><li>The meeting aims to consider and approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Q9 of 2025</li><li>The approval will be for both Consolidated and Standalone operations</li><li>The announcement is in accordance with SEBI Regulations 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0e46f118-1ae3-4067-8252-599f7fab0a35.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NIIT LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FORTIS] Fortis Healthcare Wins Perjury Case Against Third Party, Ordered Inquiry for Filing False Affidavit</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=FORTIS+HEALTHCARE+LTD.&title=Fortis+Healthcare+Wins+Perjury+Case+Against+Third+Party%2C+Ordered+Inquiry+for+Filing+False+Affidavit&newsId=af23b0a0-fc0c-43d2-8671-e7a406d8961d&token=YWYyM2IwYTAtZmMw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">af23b0a0-fc0c-43d2-8671-e7a406d8961d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:11:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Fortis Healthcare Ltd has won a perjury case against a third party and its officers, as decided by the Hon’ble High Court of Delhi on January 21, 2026. The court ordered an inquiry against the officers of the third party for filing a false affidavit in court. The company had filed the application for perjury before the Hon’ble High Court of Delhi at New Delhi. There are no expected financial implications due to compensation or penalty.</p><ul><li>Fortis Healthcare wins perjury case against third party</li><li>Hon’ble High Court of Delhi orders inquiry for filing false affidavit</li><li>Third party officers to be investigated</li><li>No expected financial implications due to compensation or penalty</li><li>Case filed before the Hon’ble High Court of Delhi at New Delhi</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3239d400-7065-4f81-8665-9b98303737ce.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: FORTIS HEALTHCARE LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TATACOMM] Tata Communications Announces Composite Scheme of Arrangement for Wholly-Owned Subsidiaries</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TATA+COMMUNICATIONS+LTD.&title=Tata+Communications+Announces+Composite+Scheme+of+Arrangement+for+Wholly-Owned+Subsidiaries&newsId=459d4b88-eb62-434d-becb-3e473d72357e&token=NDU5ZDRiODgtZWI2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">459d4b88-eb62-434d-becb-3e473d72357e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tata Communications Ltd has informed about a composite scheme of arrangement for the demerger of Solutions Infini Technologies (India) Private Limited’s Non-licensed Business undertaking into Novamesh Limited and the subsequent amalgamation of the Transferor Company into Tata Communications Collaboration Services Private Limited. The scheme aims to provide operational synergies, centralisation, simplification, streamlining and facilitation of efficient administration, reduction of administrative costs, productivity gains, and enhanced potential for higher revenues and profits. It would also remove the multiplicity of legal and other regulatory compliances and reduce various running costs and overheads. The scheme is expected to be beneficial to the shareholders and creditors of the wholly-owned subsidiaries.</p><ul><li>Composite scheme of arrangement for wholly-owned subsidiaries of Tata Communications Ltd</li><li>Demerger of Solutions Infini Technologies (India) Private Limited’s Non-licensed Business undertaking into Novamesh Limited</li><li>Subsequent amalgamation of the Transferor Company into Tata Communications Collaboration Services Private Limited</li><li>Aims to provide operational synergies, centralisation, simplification, and reduction of administrative costs</li><li>Expected to enhance potential for higher revenues and profits</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/41140d6f-9ea9-46b8-8249-8b533e8257d1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TATA COMMUNICATIONS LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VISCO] Gamco Ltd Approves Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 &amp; Nine Months Ended 31st December, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Visco+Trade+Associates+Ltd&title=Gamco+Ltd+Approves+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Ended+31st+December%2C+2025&newsId=fddaf981-12c7-4b11-9f1d-50128ac6531a&token=ZmRkYWY5ODEtMTJj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fddaf981-12c7-4b11-9f1d-50128ac6531a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:01:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gamco Ltd, formerly known as Visco Trade Associates Limited, announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The results were approved at the board meeting held on 22nd January, 2026. The company&apos;s total revenue from operations stands at ₹ 8,795.81 lakhs for the quarter and ₹ 20,769.46 lakhs for the nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The company has also reported a net profit after tax of ₹ 2,332.19 lakhs for the period. The board also approved the acquisition of 96.27% shares of Uma Properties and Traders Limited, making it a subsidiary of the company. Furthermore, the company has entered into a scheme of amalgamation with Complify Trade Pvt Ltd, subject to approval from shareholders.</p><ul><li>Gamco Ltd approved unaudited financial results for Q3 &amp; nine months ended 31st December, 2025.</li><li>Total revenue from operations stands at ₹ 8,795.81 lakhs for the quarter and ₹ 20,769.46 lakhs for the nine months.</li><li>Net profit after tax reported is ₹ 2,332.19 lakhs.</li><li>Acquisition of 96.27% shares of Uma Properties and Traders Limited approved.</li><li>Company has entered into a scheme of amalgamation with Complify Trade Pvt Ltd.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8d01b175-16bf-483c-9628-fe8b6963bfeb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Visco Trade Associates Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>