<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:53:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[AIFL] Ashapura Intimates Fashion Ltd. Approves Q3 FY2025-26 Financial Results in Post-CIRP Scenario</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ashapura+Intimates+Fashion+Ltd&title=Ashapura+Intimates+Fashion+Ltd.+Approves+Q3+FY2025-26+Financial+Results+in+Post-CIRP+Scenario&newsId=923c667a-6aac-46fa-b53f-d35aaee7d5e6&token=OTIzYzY2N2EtNmFh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">923c667a-6aac-46fa-b53f-d35aaee7d5e6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:53:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ashapura Intimates Fashion Ltd. held a Board Meeting on 14th February 2026 to approve the unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The meeting was conducted in the context of the Regulation 30 and 33 of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015. The company has experienced multiple irregularities, suspected fraudulent transactions, and statutory dues during the financial years 2017-2026. However, subsequent to the NCLT order, all outstanding statutory dues and other related payables have been written off and charged to the Statement of Profit and Loss under &apos;Exceptional Items.&apos; The company has also been granted significant reliefs by the NCLT, including the conversion of its status from &apos;liquidation&apos; to &apos;active,&apos; removal of the existing Board of Directors, and appointment of new directors. The company is required to cancel the existing shareholding of both the promoters and the public shareholders and issue new shares to the applicant and its nominees. However, these actions have not yet been implemented as of the date of this report.</p><ul><li>Ashapura Intimates Fashion Ltd. approved the unaudited standalone financial results for Q3 FY2025-26.</li><li>The company has experienced multiple irregularities and suspected fraudulent transactions during the financial years 2017-2026.</li><li>Outstanding statutory dues and other related payables have been written off and charged to the Statement of Profit and Loss under &apos;Exceptional Items.&apos;</li><li>The NCLT granted significant reliefs to the company, including the conversion of its status from &apos;liquidation&apos; to &apos;active&apos; and removal of the existing Board of Directors.</li><li>The company is required to cancel the existing shareholding of both the promoters and the public shareholders and issue new shares to the applicant and its nominees.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/48646d6c-1b6b-4dfc-8b8f-e8508a144bce.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ashapura Intimates Fashion Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHRIRAMPPS] Deputy Chief Financial Officer of Shriram Properties Ltd, Mr. Rajesh Yashwant Shirwatkar, Resigns</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shriram+Properties+Ltd&title=Deputy+Chief+Financial+Officer+of+Shriram+Properties+Ltd%2C+Mr.+Rajesh+Yashwant+Shirwatkar%2C+Resigns&newsId=29720642-18cc-4b56-82c2-bb035803b2c6&token=Mjk3MjA2NDItMThj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29720642-18cc-4b56-82c2-bb035803b2c6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:52:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shriram Properties Ltd announces the resignation of Mr. Rajesh Yashwant Shirwatkar, Deputy Chief Financial Officer. He has tendered his resignation to pursue growth opportunities outside the organization and will cease to be a Senior Management Personnel effective from the close of business hours on February 16, 2026. Mr. Ravindra Kumar Pandey, Chief Financial Officer, will oversee the entire Finance and Accounts function of the Company.</p><ul><li>Mr. Rajesh Yashwant Shirwatkar has resigned as Deputy Chief Financial Officer of Shriram Properties Ltd.</li><li>He has tendered his resignation to pursue growth opportunities outside the organization.</li><li>His last day in the organization will be February 16, 2026.</li><li>Mr. Ravindra Kumar Pandey, Chief Financial Officer, will oversee the entire Finance and Accounts function of the Company.</li><li>The organization and the team are wished continued success in the future.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/282aa89e-702a-4d48-b683-af751d512f9a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shriram Properties Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SINNAR] Independent Director, Mr. Vijay Bankatlal Malpani, Resigns from Sinnar Bidi Udyog Ltd.</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SINNAR+BIDI+UDYOG+LTD.&title=Independent+Director%2C+Mr.+Vijay+Bankatlal+Malpani%2C+Resigns+from+Sinnar+Bidi+Udyog+Ltd.&newsId=10d0db9c-0c40-478f-9836-c48aa591b9e3&token=MTBkMGRiOWMtMGM0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">10d0db9c-0c40-478f-9836-c48aa591b9e3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:52:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mr. Vijay Bankatlal Malpani has resigned as an Independent Director from Sinnar Bidi Udyog Ltd. with effect from the close of business hours on 28th February 2026 due to pre-occupation. He has confirmed that there are no other reasons for his resignation. Mr. Malpani does not hold any other directorship in any other company except Sinnar Bidi Udyog Limited, where he serves as an Independent Director and is a member of the Audit Committee and Nomination and Remuneration Committee.</p><ul><li>Mr. Vijay Bankatlal Malpani resigns as Independent Director from Sinnar Bidi Udyog Ltd.</li><li>Resignation effective from the close of business hours on 28th February 2026.</li><li>Resignation due to pre-occupation.</li><li>No other reasons for resignation.</li><li>Does not hold any other directorship except in Sinnar Bidi Udyog Limited.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/679a8d39-6650-4805-ade3-a1c9ebbcaa8b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SINNAR BIDI UDYOG LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VIRTUALS] Virtual Software &amp; Training Pvt Ltd Disposes 14.96 Lakh Shares of Kati Patang Lifestyle Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VIRTUALSOFT+SYSTEMS+LTD.&title=Virtual+Software+%26+Training+Pvt+Ltd+Disposes+14.96+Lakh+Shares+of+Kati+Patang+Lifestyle+Ltd&newsId=3fea4448-90de-4d27-adc8-cf3ddb4893f8&token=M2ZlYTQ0NDgtOTBk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3fea4448-90de-4d27-adc8-cf3ddb4893f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Sale</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>According to a disclosure made under PIT Regulation 7(2), Virtual Software &amp; Training Pvt Ltd, a promoter group company of Kati Patang Lifestyle Ltd, has disposed of 14.96 lakh equity shares. This disposal represents 4.16% of the total shares of the company. The transaction took place on the open market. The company has also disclosed an arrangement of a loan taken of an amount 50 Lakh, where 20Lakh shares were transferred to a transferee as collateral against security.</p><ul><li>Virtual Software &amp; Training Pvt Ltd disposes 14.96 lakh shares of Kati Patang Lifestyle Ltd</li><li>The disposal represents 4.16% of the total shares of the company</li><li>The transaction took place on the open market</li><li>The company has also disclosed an arrangement of a loan taken of an amount 50 Lakh</li><li>20Lakh shares were transferred to a transferee as collateral against security</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e74241ca-b1ee-4dac-8981-0a128237ad32.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VIRTUALSOFT SYSTEMS LTD. | Category: Sale</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KRANTI] Kranti Industries Delivers Robust 9M FY26 Performance with Revenue 764.6 Cr, EBITDA 210.8 Cr, 16.7% Margin, =1.8 Cr PAT &amp; 5 New Defence Orders Win</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kranti+Industries+Ltd&title=Kranti+Industries+Delivers+Robust+9M+FY26+Performance+with+Revenue+764.6+Cr%2C+EBITDA+210.8+Cr%2C+16.7%25+Margin%2C+%3D1.8+Cr+PAT+%26+5+New+Defence+Orders+Win&newsId=5a796097-3065-447a-bffc-78214e323874&token=NWE3OTYwOTctMzA2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a796097-3065-447a-bffc-78214e323874</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:51:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Kranti Industries Limited (BSE: 542459), a leading precision engineering and machining solutions firm, has announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine-month ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a revenue of 764.6 Cr, EBITDA of 210.8 Cr, and a PAT of 1.8 Cr for the 9 months ended on December 31, 2025. The company has also secured 5 new defence orders worth approximately 173.25 lakh from Armoured Vehicles Nigam Limited (AVNL) - Machine Tool Prototype Factory (MTPF) and an additional order worth approximately 31.25 lakh from AVNL - Heavy Vehicles Factory (HVF) for defence applications. The company has also commissioned Plant 4, a 35,160 sq. ft. machining facility in Jaipur, equipped with advanced CNC machinery, utilities, and integrated infrastructure to support high-precision and scalable manufacturing requirements.</p><ul><li>Revenue of 764.6 Cr for 9M FY26</li><li>EBITDA of 210.8 Cr for 9M FY26</li><li>PAT of 1.8 Cr for 9M FY26</li><li>Secured 5 new defence orders worth approximately 204.5 lakh</li><li>Commissioned Plant 4 in Jaipur</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e8626093-91e8-475f-9719-319d4ce4ec5b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kranti Industries Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SWATIPRO] Swati Projects Ltd to Consider and Approve Resignation of Managing Director on Feb 24, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Swati+Projects+Ltd&title=Swati+Projects+Ltd+to+Consider+and+Approve+Resignation+of+Managing+Director+on+Feb+24%2C+2026&newsId=d1c5e1fd-f838-4d2e-ad57-0dcd815a9e75&token=ZDFjNWUxZmQtZjgz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d1c5e1fd-f838-4d2e-ad57-0dcd815a9e75</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Swati Projects Ltd has announced that a meeting of the Board of Directors will be held on February 24, 2026. The agenda includes the consideration and approval of the resignation of Mr. Shreegopal Daga as Managing Director, in accordance with the SEBI Listing Regulation.</p><ul><li>Swati Projects Ltd has scheduled a Board Meeting on February 24, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the resignation of Mr. Shreegopal Daga as Managing Director</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a61df26a-7e9c-474c-811b-cec54b489d6f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Swati Projects Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KWIL] Kwality Walls (India) Ltd Updates Materiality Policy and Authorized Persons List</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KWIL&title=Kwality+Walls+%28India%29+Ltd+Updates+Materiality+Policy+and+Authorized+Persons+List&newsId=560a5ff3-0ab2-4d09-ae27-18e6661ae029&token=NTYwYTVmZjMtMGFi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">560a5ff3-0ab2-4d09-ae27-18e6661ae029</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kwality Walls (India) Ltd has updated its Materiality Policy and provided a list of authorized persons for determining the materiality of an event or information and for making disclosures to the stock exchange(s). The list includes Mr. Chitrank Goel, Deputy Managing Director; Mr. Prashant Premrajka, Executive Director and Chief Financial Officer; Mr. Anand Upadhyay, Company Secretary and Compliance Officer; and Mr. Harshal Marathe, General Counsel. This update is in accordance with Regulation 30(5) of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015 and the Company&apos;s Policy on Determination of Materiality of Events.</p><ul><li>Kwality Walls (India) Ltd updates Materiality Policy</li><li>List of authorized persons for determining materiality of events provided</li><li>Includes Mr. Chitrank Goel, Deputy Managing Director</li><li>Mr. Prashant Premrajka, Executive Director and Chief Financial Officer</li><li>Mr. Anand Upadhyay, Company Secretary and Compliance Officer</li><li>Mr. Harshal Marathe, General Counsel</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f070013d-ef8c-41bb-8fb2-c0503749557a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KWIL | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VIRTUALS] Promoter Group&apos;s Virtual Software &amp; Training Pvt Ltd Discloses Share Disposal in Kati Patang Lifestyle Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VIRTUALSOFT+SYSTEMS+LTD.&title=Promoter+Group%27s+Virtual+Software+%26+Training+Pvt+Ltd+Discloses+Share+Disposal+in+Kati+Patang+Lifestyle+Ltd&newsId=1df48abe-cd63-482e-8a97-64b635f5b98f&token=MWRmNDhhYmUtY2Q2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1df48abe-cd63-482e-8a97-64b635f5b98f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:51:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Virtual Software &amp; Training Pvt Ltd, a promoter group company of Kati Patang Lifestyle Ltd, has disclosed the disposal of shares under SAST Disclosure Regulation 29(2). The disposal includes 20 Lakhs shares on February 13, 2026, and an earlier sale of 2.53 Lakhs shares. The disclosure also includes Gokul Naresh Tandan, Sagarika Tandan, Ritu Tandan, Prabhudev V Kulkarni, and Samrath Bedi, Kiran Nadar, Rajendra V Kulkarni, and M R Capital Pvt Ltd as persons acting in concert with the acquirer. The total shares acquired by the acquirer and persons acting in concert amount to 37,50,000.</p><ul><li>Virtual Software &amp; Training Pvt Ltd discloses share disposal in Kati Patang Lifestyle Ltd under SAST Disclosure Regulation 29(2)</li><li>Disposal includes 20 Lakhs shares on February 13, 2026, and an earlier sale of 2.53 Lakhs shares</li><li>Gokul Naresh Tandan, Sagarika Tandan, Ritu Tandan, Prabhudev V Kulkarni, and Samrath Bedi, Kiran Nadar, Rajendra V Kulkarni, and M R Capital Pvt Ltd identified as persons acting in concert with the acquirer</li><li>Total shares acquired by the acquirer and persons acting in concert amount to 37,50,000</li><li>Kati Patang Lifestyle Ltd shares listed on BSE Limited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/55ea3796-c55f-4b21-a930-bc66e0e8500c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VIRTUALSOFT SYSTEMS LTD. | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DELPHIFX] Delphi World Money Ltd Announces 2:1 Bonus Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Delphi+World+Money+Ltd&title=Delphi+World+Money+Ltd+Announces+2%3A1+Bonus+Issue&newsId=fc0388b0-b7d7-4167-8203-8cc9e1b6231a&token=ZmMwMzg4YjAtYjdk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc0388b0-b7d7-4167-8203-8cc9e1b6231a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:37:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Bonus</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Delphi World Money Ltd announced on February 16, 2026, that its Board of Directors has approved a bonus issue of 16,35,11,850 Equity Shares of Rs. 2/- each. The bonus issue will be given to members whose names appear in the Register of Members as on February 14, 2026, the Record Date. Each existing Equity Share of Rs. 2/- each will be allotted 2 new fully paid-up Equity Shares of Rs. 2/- each, resulting in a total increase in the issued, subscribed, and paid-up equity share capital of the Company from Rs. 16,35,11,850/- to Rs. 49,05,35,550/-. The new Bonus Equity Shares will rank pari-passu with the existing Equity Shares in the Company. The necessary compliances for crediting the Bonus Equity Shares in the demat accounts of the Shareholders will be completed in due course.</p><ul><li>Delphi World Money Ltd announces a 2:1 bonus issue</li><li>16,35,11,850 Equity Shares of Rs. 2/- each to be allotted</li><li>Allotment to members on the Register of Members as on February 14, 2026</li><li>Issued, subscribed, and paid-up equity share capital to increase from Rs. 16,35,11,850/- to Rs. 49,05,35,550/-</li><li>New Bonus Equity Shares to rank pari-passu with existing Equity Shares</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1e394fe3-2b99-4e37-b3f4-23c7b2c495f0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Delphi World Money Ltd | Category: Bonus</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDICAP] Resignation of Statutory Auditors of Inditrade Capital Ltd: Kirtane &amp; Pandit LLP</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Inditrade+Capital+Limited&title=Resignation+of+Statutory+Auditors+of+Inditrade+Capital+Ltd%3A+Kirtane+%26+Pandit+LLP&newsId=2138b42b-b7e2-4188-925c-c41882b959fa&token=MjEzOGI0MmItYjdl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2138b42b-b7e2-4188-925c-c41882b959fa</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 12:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Inditrade Capital Ltd announced the resignation of its Statutory Auditors, Kirtane &amp; Pandit LLP, due to the Management&apos;s failure to provide complete, accurate, and timely financial information necessary for the performance of their duties. The resignation will come into effect from closing of business hours of February 12, 2026.</p><ul><li>Inditrade Capital Ltd announced the resignation of its Statutory Auditors, Kirtane &amp; Pandit LLP.</li><li>The resignation is due to the Management&apos;s failure to provide necessary financial information for the performance of auditing duties.</li><li>The resignation will come into effect from closing of business hours of February 12, 2026.</li><li>The auditors were unable to issue limited review reports and audit reports due to insufficient time and lack of complete financial information.</li><li>The auditors have requested the Board of Directors to acknowledge their resignation and make necessary filings with the Registrar of Companies.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/64e7ffde-7ae7-4c9c-992e-999f6ecc5af9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Inditrade Capital Limited | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>