<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 18:28:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[KSE] KSE Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine-month Unaudited Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KSE+LTD.-%24&title=KSE+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine-month+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=5be3540b-80e3-415a-9c64-7202c8403cee&token=NWJlMzU0MGItODBl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5be3540b-80e3-415a-9c64-7202c8403cee</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 18:06:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>KSE Ltd has released its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The results were reviewed and recommended by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board. The company prepared the statement in accordance with the Indian Accounting Standard 34 and other accounting principles generally accepted in India. The review was conducted in accordance with the Standard on Review Engagements (SRE) 2410. The company made an ad hoc provision of Rs 5 crore towards the estimated liability on implementation of the ‘New Labour Codes’. The shareholders approved the sub-division of equity shares in accordance with Section 61(1)(d) of the Companies Act, 2013.</p><ul><li>Unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine-month ended 31st December 2025</li><li>Reviewed and recommended by the Audit Committee</li><li>Approved by the Board</li><li>Ad hoc provision of Rs 5 crore towards the estimated liability on implementation of the ‘New Labour Codes&apos;</li><li>Sub-division of equity shares in accordance with Section 61(1)(d) of the Companies Act, 2013</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/574c7d4b-9efe-4d31-af72-6c76f4b4b577.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KSE LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SKP] Shri Krishna Prasadam Ltd Appoints Krishnveer Chaudhary as Chairman and Additional Executive Director, Reports Q3 and Q4 Unaudited Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shri+Krishna+Prasadam+Ltd&title=Shri+Krishna+Prasadam+Ltd+Appoints+Krishnveer+Chaudhary+as+Chairman+and+Additional+Executive+Director%2C+Reports+Q3+and+Q4+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=ae5adba6-cbdc-4b82-a344-3c5810b7b4b1&token=YWU1YWRiYTYtY2Jk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae5adba6-cbdc-4b82-a344-3c5810b7b4b1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 17:49:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shri Krishna Prasadam Ltd has appointed Mr. Krishnveer Chaudhary as Chairman and Additional Executive Director, effective from 14th February 2026. The appointment was made based on the recommendation of the Nomination and Remuneration Committee. The company has also reported its unaudited financial results for the quarter and half-year ended September 30, 2025, and the third quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The financial results were reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Krishnveer Chaudhary as Chairman and Additional Executive Director</li><li>Unaudited financial results for Q2 and H1 2025</li><li>Unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months of 2025</li><li>Reviewed by the Audit Committee</li><li>Approved by the Board of Directors</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/97471739-7d2e-4976-b0e6-06b647414e10.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shri Krishna Prasadam Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASIL] Amit Spinning Industries Delays Q3 FY2025-26 Financial Results Submission</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Amit+Spinning+Industries+Ltd&title=Amit+Spinning+Industries+Delays+Q3+FY2025-26+Financial+Results+Submission&newsId=f4d4962c-8ca6-4698-8898-b80b28cd5887&token=ZjRkNDk2MmMtOGNh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4d4962c-8ca6-4698-8898-b80b28cd5887</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 17:44:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Amit Spinning Industries Ltd. has announced a delay in submitting its Standalone Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The delay is primarily due to additional time required by the Statutory Auditors to complete limited review procedures. The company has been cooperating with the auditors and expects to submit the results by February 16, 2026. The Board Meeting initially scheduled for this purpose has been adjourned to February 16, 2026, for the approval of the unaudited financial results.</p><ul><li>Amit Spinning Industries delays Q3 FY2025-26 financial results submission</li><li>Delay caused by additional time required by Statutory Auditors for limited review procedures</li><li>Company cooperating with auditors for expeditious completion of review process</li><li>Financial results expected to be submitted by February 16, 2026</li><li>Board Meeting adjourned to February 16, 2026, for approval of unaudited financial results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/676fda55-e681-4351-aa1d-0e02d355d063.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Amit Spinning Industries Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASIL] Amit Spinning Industries Delays Q3 FY2025-26 Financial Results Submission</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Amit+Spinning+Industries+Ltd&title=Amit+Spinning+Industries+Delays+Q3+FY2025-26+Financial+Results+Submission&newsId=8f55b5c9-09c6-4fd7-95f2-21a2ca86a907&token=OGY1NWI1YzktMDlj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f55b5c9-09c6-4fd7-95f2-21a2ca86a907</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 17:41:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Amit Spinning Industries Ltd has informed the BSE that the meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on 16/02/2026 to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company will not be able to submit the Standalone Unaudited Financial Results within the prescribed timeline due to additional time required by the Statutory Auditors to complete the limited review procedures. The company has been extending full cooperation and support to the Statutory Auditors for expeditious completion of the limited review process, which is presently in the final stage. The company expects to submit the Financial Results on or before February 16, 2026.</p><ul><li>Amit Spinning Industries Ltd delays Q3 FY2025-26 financial results submission</li><li>The delay is primarily due to additional time required by the Statutory Auditors for limited review procedures</li><li>The company is cooperating with the Statutory Auditors for the timely completion of the review process</li><li>The review process is in its final stage</li><li>The company expects to submit the financial results on or before February 16, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/be0e61cc-c41c-4b6e-b2b2-a7b016e3c899.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Amit Spinning Industries Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ROHLTD] Royal Orchid Hotels Ltd: Board Approves Change in Director&apos;s Designation, Appointment, and Remuneration Hike</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ROYAL+ORCHID+HOTELS+LTD.&title=Royal+Orchid+Hotels+Ltd%3A+Board+Approves+Change+in+Director%27s+Designation%2C+Appointment%2C+and+Remuneration+Hike&newsId=8ceb508a-2a5c-45e8-a329-345ad2b1b00d&token=OGNlYjUwOGEtMmE1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ceb508a-2a5c-45e8-a329-345ad2b1b00d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 17:36:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Royal Orchid Hotels Ltd announced that its Board of Directors, based on the recommendations of the Audit Committee and Nomination and Remuneration Committee, has approved the change in designation and appointment of Mr. Keshav Baljee from Non-Executive Director to Whole-Time Director designated as an Executive Director of the Company for a period of 5 years with a monthly remuneration of ₹10,00,000. The Board also approved an increase in the monthly remuneration of Mr. Arjun Baljee, President, from ₹5,00,000 to ₹7,50,000, making his total monthly remuneration from the Company and its subsidiary, Maruti Comforts &amp; Inn Private Limited, ₹10,00,000 per month. The changes are subject to approval of the shareholders of the Company.</p><ul><li>Royal Orchid Hotels Ltd Board approves change in director&apos;s designation and appointment</li><li>Mr. Keshav Baljee appointed as Whole-Time Director and Executive Director for 5 years</li><li>Monthly remuneration of ₹10,00,000 for Mr. Keshav Baljee</li><li>Remuneration of Mr. Arjun Baljee, President, increased to ₹7,50,000 per month</li><li>Changes subject to approval of the shareholders of the Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/37986cf4-d97f-46d8-a7bf-fe3041172677.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ROYAL ORCHID HOTELS LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ROHLTD] Royal Orchid Hotels Ltd: Board Approves Change in Designation, Appointment, and Increased Remuneration</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ROYAL+ORCHID+HOTELS+LTD.&title=Royal+Orchid+Hotels+Ltd%3A+Board+Approves+Change+in+Designation%2C+Appointment%2C+and+Increased+Remuneration&newsId=278520a7-5a7d-4936-b7e2-31041fc68780&token=Mjc4NTIwYTctNWE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">278520a7-5a7d-4936-b7e2-31041fc68780</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 17:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Royal Orchid Hotels Ltd has approved the change in designation and appointment of Mr. Keshav Baljee as Whole-time Director and Executive Director for a period of 5 years, with a monthly remuneration of ₹ 10,00,000. The Board has also approved an increase in the monthly remuneration of Mr. Arjun Baljee, President of the company, from ₹ 5,00,000 to ₹ 7,50,000. The decisions are subject to approval from the shareholders of the company.</p><ul><li>Board approves change in designation and appointment of Mr. Keshav Baljee as Whole-time Director and Executive Director</li><li>Mr. Keshav Baljee&apos;s appointment is for a period of 5 years with a monthly remuneration of ₹ 10,00,000</li><li>The Board approves an increase in the monthly remuneration of Mr. Arjun Baljee, President, from ₹ 5,00,000 to ₹ 7,50,000</li><li>The decisions are subject to approval from the shareholders of the company</li><li>The Board has considered and approved the unaudited Standalone &amp; Consolidated Financial Results for the Third Quarter and Nine Months ended December 31, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/805db05d-a287-4143-aa36-86dce7bf34d2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ROYAL ORCHID HOTELS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AQFINTECH] Algoquant Fintech Ltd. Approves Q3 and Nine Months Unaudited Standalone Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Algoquant+Fintech+Ltd&title=Algoquant+Fintech+Ltd.+Approves+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Unaudited+Standalone+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=65478c85-c207-4cf0-adf3-f1249b333fb2&token=NjU0NzhjODUtYzIw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65478c85-c207-4cf0-adf3-f1249b333fb2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 17:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Algoquant Fintech Ltd. has approved the unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations, other income, and total expenses for the period have been reported. The company&apos;s earnings per equity share (basic and diluted) have been adjusted due to a sub-division of shares, a split of shares, and the issuance of bonus shares.</p><ul><li>Algoquant Fintech Ltd. has approved the unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue from operations, other income, and total expenses for the period have been reported.</li><li>The company&apos;s earnings per equity share (basic and diluted) have been adjusted due to a sub-division of shares, a split of shares, and the issuance of bonus shares.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/36a7b69a-942e-40b2-be18-9dbd5b594305.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Algoquant Fintech Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RLFL] Ramchandra Leasing &amp; Finance Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ramchandra+Leasing+%26+Finance+Ltd&title=Ramchandra+Leasing+%26+Finance+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025&newsId=4d288709-984a-4a2e-8b97-34185bffb29a&token=NGQyODg3MDktOTg0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d288709-984a-4a2e-8b97-34185bffb29a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 17:25:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ramchandra Leasing &amp; Finance Ltd has reported its standalone unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The results were reviewed by Goyal Nagpal &amp; Co. Chartered Accountants and approved at the Board of Directors meeting held on February 14, 2026. The company&apos;s financial results are in compliance with the recognition and measurement principles laid down in Indian Accounting Standard 34 (Ind AS 34) and other accounting principles generally accepted in India.</p><ul><li>Ramchandra Leasing &amp; Finance Ltd reported its standalone unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025.</li><li>The results were reviewed by Goyal Nagpal &amp; Co. Chartered Accountants.</li><li>The company&apos;s financial results are in compliance with the recognition and measurement principles laid down in Indian Accounting Standard 34 (Ind AS 34) and other accounting principles generally accepted in India.</li><li>The results were approved at the Board of Directors meeting held on February 14, 2026.</li><li>The company&apos;s financial results are comparable with the previous year/period figures.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/964cc7a2-024b-4147-aad7-54dc99670512.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ramchandra Leasing & Finance Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SKP] Shri Krishna Prasadam Ltd Appoints Krishnveer Chaudhary as Chairman and Additional Executive Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shri+Krishna+Prasadam+Ltd&title=Shri+Krishna+Prasadam+Ltd+Appoints+Krishnveer+Chaudhary+as+Chairman+and+Additional+Executive+Director&newsId=c6b0556c-b87e-4405-b5e2-73b40ae9826a&token=YzZiMDU1NmMtYjg3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c6b0556c-b87e-4405-b5e2-73b40ae9826a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 17:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shri Krishna Prasadam Ltd, a renowned company based in New Delhi, has announced the appointment of Mr. Krishnveer Chaudhary as the Chairman and Additional Executive Director, effective from 14th February 2026. The appointment was made during a Board Meeting, upon the recommendation of the Nomination and Remuneration Committee. Mr. Chaudhary, a graduate with strong management and leadership skills, is not related to any director of the Company. The Company also approved the unaudited financial results for the quarters ended on September 30, 2025, and December 31, 2025.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Krishnveer Chaudhary as Chairman and Additional Executive Director</li><li>Mr. Chaudhary is a graduate with strong management and leadership skills</li><li>Unaudited financial results for the quarters ended on September 30, 2025, and December 31, 2025 approved</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0b599b3d-176a-4f23-9015-b78cb63f5a9c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shri Krishna Prasadam Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[3IINFOTECH] 3i Infotech Ltd: Monitoring Agency Report for Q4 2025 Shows No Deviation from Objectives</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=3I+INFOTECH+LTD.&title=3i+Infotech+Ltd%3A+Monitoring+Agency+Report+for+Q4+2025+Shows+No+Deviation+from+Objectives&newsId=46c2cd30-325a-43d0-96a1-13f08de52f7d&token=NDZjMmNkMzAtMzI1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">46c2cd30-325a-43d0-96a1-13f08de52f7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 17:22:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Monitoring Agency Report for 3i Infotech Limited for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, prepared by Infomerics Valuation and Rating Limited, indicates no deviation from the objects of the Rights Issue. The report has been reviewed by the Audit Committee of the Company and is now available on the Company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>The Monitoring Agency Report for Q4 2025 shows no deviation from the objectives of the Rights Issue.</li><li>The report has been reviewed by the Audit Committee of the Company.</li><li>The report is now available on the Company&apos;s website.</li><li>The Rights Issue amount was Rs. 64.10 crore.</li><li>The Monitoring Agency has a duty to report as per SEBI Regulations and the Monitoring Agency Agreement.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bc5f30ff-1c87-4909-b193-35e932c20ef1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: 3I INFOTECH LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>