<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 12:38:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[UTKARSHBNK] Utkarsh Small Finance Bank Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Business Updates for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Utkarsh+Small+Finance+Bank+Ltd&title=Utkarsh+Small+Finance+Bank+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Business+Updates+for+2025&newsId=f09920a8-6cda-4a75-8a42-cf1b609373e2&token=ZjA5OTIwYTgtNmNk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f09920a8-6cda-4a75-8a42-cf1b609373e2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 12:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Utkarsh Small Finance Bank Ltd has released its business updates for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The bank&apos;s gross loan portfolio stands at ₹ 18,306 crore, representing a quarter-over-quarter decrease of 1.9%. The JLG loan portfolio is ₹ 6,419 crore, down by 15.7% compared to the previous quarter. The non-JLG loan portfolio has increased by 27.5% to ₹ 11,888 crore. Total deposits amount to ₹ 21,087 crore, a 45% increase from September 30, 2025. The CASA deposits are ₹ 4,611 crore, up by 16.1% from the previous quarter. The bank&apos;s CASA ratio stands at 78.1%. The X Bucket Collection efficiency for the bank&apos;s Micro Banking loan portfolio is 99.1% for Q3, FY26. The Liquidity Coverage Ratio (LCR) is 200% as of December 31, 2025. Please note that the Q3 FY26 information is provisional and subject to review by the Joint Statutory Auditors of the Bank and approval of the Audit Committee and Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Gross loan portfolio decreased by 1.9% to ₹ 18,306 crore compared to the previous quarter</li><li>JLG loan portfolio decreased by 15.7% to ₹ 6,419 crore compared to the previous quarter</li><li>Non-JLG loan portfolio increased by 27.5% to ₹ 11,888 crore compared to the previous quarter</li><li>Total deposits increased by 45% to ₹ 21,087 crore compared to September 30, 2025</li><li>CASA deposits increased by 16.1% to ₹ 4,611 crore compared to the previous quarter</li><li>CASA ratio stands at 78.1%</li><li>X Bucket Collection efficiency for Micro Banking loan portfolio is 99.1% for Q3, FY26</li><li>Liquidity Coverage Ratio (LCR) is 200% as of December 31, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c0a18fdf-5b85-4481-bbd4-0f4a23fde0b8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Utkarsh Small Finance Bank Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AXITA] Axita Cotton Ltd Sets Record Date for 1:10 Bonus Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Axita+Cotton+Ltd&title=Axita+Cotton+Ltd+Sets+Record+Date+for+1%3A10+Bonus+Issue&newsId=f703e7f0-cce0-44b1-a2bf-5554be398a33&token=ZjcwM2U3ZjAtY2Nl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f703e7f0-cce0-44b1-a2bf-5554be398a33</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 12:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Bonus</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Axita Cotton Ltd has fixed the record date for the purpose of a bonus issue as 13-02-2026. The company will issue 1 bonus equity share for every 10 existing equity shares, subject to shareholder&apos;s approval. The bonus shares will be out of capitalization of free reserves available as on March 31, 2025. The record date for determining eligible shareholders is set for Friday, February 13, 2026. The actual number of bonus equity shares to be issued will be determined based on the paid-up share capital as on the record date.</p><ul><li>Bonus issue of 1:10 announced by Axita Cotton Ltd</li><li>Record date set for February 13, 2026</li><li>Bonus shares to be issued out of free reserves available as on March 31, 2025</li><li>Shareholder&apos;s approval is pending</li><li>The actual number of bonus equity shares to be issued will be determined based on the paid-up share capital as on the record date</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3d14b44d-49d0-4def-8296-66efcf58eba1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Axita Cotton Ltd | Category: Bonus</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SCL] Sunshine Capital Ltd Independent Director, Mr. Bhupendra Kaushik, Resigns Effective January 5, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sunshine+Capital+Ltd&title=Sunshine+Capital+Ltd+Independent+Director%2C+Mr.+Bhupendra+Kaushik%2C+Resigns+Effective+January+5%2C+2026&newsId=ee28262d-6bf2-47e9-8f02-b7f190ccdb9f&token=ZWUyODI2MmQtNmJm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee28262d-6bf2-47e9-8f02-b7f190ccdb9f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 12:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sunshine Capital Ltd announced the resignation of its Independent Director, Mr. Bhupendra Kaushik (DIN: 07016552), effective January 5, 2026. The resignation is due to personal reasons and unavoidable circumstances. The company confirmed that there are no other material reasons for his resignation. Mr. Kaushik served as a Non-Executive &amp; Independent Director and was a member of various board committees. The company has complied with all necessary disclosure requirements as per Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Mr. Bhupendra Kaushik resigns as Independent Director from Sunshine Capital Ltd.</li><li>Resignation takes effect from January 5, 2026.</li><li>Resignation is due to personal and unavoidable reasons.</li><li>Company has complied with all necessary disclosure requirements.</li><li>Mr. Kaushik was a Non-Executive &amp; Independent Director and a member of various board committees.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e6b1adfc-d43d-4ed4-a91e-00664cab6cfd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sunshine Capital Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DABUR] Dabur India Ltd Reports Mid-Single Digit Revenue Growth in Q3 FY26, Aided by GST Rate Revisions and Demand Recovery</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DABUR+INDIA+LTD.&title=Dabur+India+Ltd+Reports+Mid-Single+Digit+Revenue+Growth+in+Q3+FY26%2C+Aided+by+GST+Rate+Revisions+and+Demand+Recovery&newsId=edb7a00a-6021-4a98-83e0-f842ef951207&token=ZWRiN2EwMGEtNjAy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">edb7a00a-6021-4a98-83e0-f842ef951207</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 12:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Dabur India Ltd has reported an update on the performance and demand trends witnessed during the quarter ended December 31, 2025 (Q3 FY26). The company expects the Home &amp; Personal care business to grow in double digits, led by strong growth in Hair Oils and Oral care category. Healthcare is expected to witness a sequential improvement in the growth trajectory, supported by near 10% growth in Dabur Honey and 15%+ YoY growth in both Honitus and Health Juices. The F&amp;B business is expected to record double-digit growth in Culinary and mid-single digit growth in Hajmola franchise and Ethicals portfolio. The overall international business is expected to post near double digit growth in INR terms. The company expects consolidated revenue to grow in the mid-single digits with operating profit and Profit after Tax to grow ahead of revenue.</p><ul><li>Dabur India Ltd reports mid-single digit revenue growth in Q3 FY26, aided by GST rate revisions and demand recovery.</li><li>Home &amp; Personal care business expected to grow in double digits, led by strong growth in Hair Oils and Oral care category.</li><li>Healthcare expected to witness a sequential improvement in the growth trajectory, supported by near 10% growth in Dabur Honey and 15%+ YoY growth in both Honitus and Health Juices.</li><li>F&amp;B business expected to record double-digit growth in Culinary and mid-single digit growth in Hajmola franchise and Ethicals portfolio.</li><li>Overall international business expected to post near double digit growth in INR terms.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/101a3c20-d655-4d81-99cb-4f997e235a03.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DABUR INDIA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SATINDLTD] Aeroflex Enterprises to Disinvest Stake in M.R. Organisation Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SAT+INDUSTRIES+LTD.-%24&title=Aeroflex+Enterprises+to+Disinvest+Stake+in+M.R.+Organisation+Limited&newsId=8c9b1947-6cde-4184-9088-35d222916d92&token=OGM5YjE5NDctNmNk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c9b1947-6cde-4184-9088-35d222916d92</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 12:28:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Aeroflex Enterprises Ltd. has called for an Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EOGM) on January 27, 2026, to consider the disinvestment of its stake in M.R. Organisation Limited (MRO), a material subsidiary company. The disinvestment can be in one or more tranches, on terms and conditions beneficial to the company. The EOGM will be held through Video Conferencing (VC) / Other Audio Visual Means (OAVM) in accordance with the applicable circulars issued by the Ministry of Corporate Affairs and the Securities and Exchange Board of India. The remote e-voting will commence from January 23, 2026, and ends on January 26, 2026.</p><ul><li>Aeroflex Enterprises to disinvest its stake in M.R. Organisation Limited</li><li>Disinvestment can be in one or more tranches</li><li>The disinvestment is on terms and conditions beneficial to the company</li><li>The EOGM will be held through Video Conferencing (VC) / Other Audio Visual Means (OAVM)</li><li>Remote e-voting will commence from January 23, 2026, and ends on January 26, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f59f9486-50c5-4a4b-b5ad-b9ee368f280e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SAT INDUSTRIES LTD.-$ | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STHINPA] South India Paper Mills Ltd to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and 9 Months of FY2025-26 on 15th January, 2024</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SOUTH+INDIA+PAPER+MILLS+LTD.&title=South+India+Paper+Mills+Ltd+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+9+Months+of+FY2025-26+on+15th+January%2C+2024&newsId=fca58a0d-767d-46f6-b13a-53657885cf07&token=ZmNhNThhMGQtNzY3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fca58a0d-767d-46f6-b13a-53657885cf07</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 12:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>South India Paper Mills Ltd has announced a Board Meeting scheduled on 15th January, 2024. The meeting will consider and approve the unaudited financial results of the company for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. This is in accordance with Regulation 29 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>South India Paper Mills Ltd to hold a Board Meeting on 15th January, 2024</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the unaudited financial results for Q3 and 9 months of FY2025-26</li><li>The results are for the period ended 31st December, 2025</li><li>The announcement is in accordance with Regulation 29 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d25482b7-b26e-46e8-9083-bca6d0bda172.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SOUTH INDIA PAPER MILLS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SATIN] Satin Creditcare Network Ltd. Approves Issuance of INR 100,00,00,000 Non-Convertible Debentures</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Satin+Creditcare+Network+Ltd&title=Satin+Creditcare+Network+Ltd.+Approves+Issuance+of+INR+100%2C00%2C00%2C000+Non-Convertible+Debentures&newsId=506c587e-c264-486a-92f6-f9e332f00d5b&token=NTA2YzU4N2UtYzI2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">506c587e-c264-486a-92f6-f9e332f00d5b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 12:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Satin Creditcare Network Ltd. has approved the issuance of 1,00,000 (One Lakh) senior, secured, rated, listed, taxable, redeemable, transferable, non-convertible debentures (NCDs) denominated in INR, having a face value of INR 10,000 each and an aggregate nominal value of INR 100,00,00,000. This includes a green shoe option of 50,000 (Fifty Thousand) NCDs with an aggregate nominal value of INR 50,00,00,000. The NCDs will be issued on a private placement basis.</p><ul><li>Satin Creditcare Network Ltd. to issue 1,00,000 senior, secured, rated, listed, taxable, redeemable, transferable, non-convertible debentures</li><li>The face value of each debenture is INR 10,000 and the aggregate nominal value is INR 100,00,00,000</li><li>Includes a green shoe option of 50,000 debentures with an aggregate nominal value of INR 50,00,00,000</li><li>The debentures will be issued on a private placement basis</li><li>The debentures are proposed to be listed on BSE Limited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8f3d93cc-37b1-4b03-8690-37ab5bfe5098.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Satin Creditcare Network Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WANBURY] Wanbury Ltd Re-appoints Manojkumar Khubchand Gursahani as Non-Executive Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=WANBURY+LTD.&title=Wanbury+Ltd+Re-appoints+Manojkumar+Khubchand+Gursahani+as+Non-Executive+Independent+Director&newsId=e464df2e-2951-4a75-b329-93080df15f83&token=ZTQ2NGRmMmUtMjk1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e464df2e-2951-4a75-b329-93080df15f83</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 12:27:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Wanbury Ltd has announced the re-appointment of Mr. Manojkumar Khubchand Gursahani as the Non-Executive Independent Director for a term of one year, effective from January 08, 2026 to January 07, 2027. This decision was approved in the Extra-Ordinary General Meeting held on Monday, 05th January 2026. Mr. Gursahani holds a Graduate degree in commerce and is not related to any directors of the company. He is also not debarred from holding the office of director by virtue of any order of SEBI or any other authority.</p><ul><li>Re-appointment of Mr. Manojkumar Khubchand Gursahani as Non-Executive Independent Director</li><li>Term of appointment: One year (08th January 2026 - 07th January 2027)</li><li>Mr. Gursahani holds a Graduate degree in commerce</li><li>Not related to any directors of the company</li><li>Not debarred from holding the office of director by any order of SEBI or any other authority</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/990abca2-ac10-486e-8ba5-a9730d853c69.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: WANBURY LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HATSUN] Hatsun Agro Product Ltd Reports Unintentional Sharing of Draft Financial Statements</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HATSUN+AGRO+PRODUCT+LTD.&title=Hatsun+Agro+Product+Ltd+Reports+Unintentional+Sharing+of+Draft+Financial+Statements&newsId=12d0b6e6-89c6-4c39-91c8-814a74e7f1c6&token=MTJkMGI2ZTYtODlj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12d0b6e6-89c6-4c39-91c8-814a74e7f1c6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 12:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hatsun Agro Product Ltd has reported an incident where one of its Key Managerial Personnel (KMP) inadvertently uploaded draft financial statements for the quarter ended 31 December 2025 to his personal WhatsApp Status. The figures, which may constitute Unpublished Price Sensitive Information (UPSI), were seen by around 19 people, including some insiders of the company. The KMP deleted the status within an hour of posting. The company is reporting this incident to the Stock Exchanges, Audit Committee, and the Board of Directors. An internal inquiry has been initiated as per SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015 and the Company&apos;s Insider Trading Code. The persons who viewed the alleged UPSI are being included in the company&apos;s Structured Digital Database.</p><ul><li>Hatsun Agro Product Ltd reports unintentional sharing of draft financial statements by a Key Managerial Personnel.</li><li>The draft figures, which may constitute Unpublished Price Sensitive Information, were seen by around 19 people, including some insiders.</li><li>The KMP deleted the WhatsApp Status within an hour of posting.</li><li>The company is reporting the incident to the Stock Exchanges, Audit Committee, and the Board of Directors.</li><li>An internal inquiry has been initiated as per SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015 and the Company&apos;s Insider Trading Code.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e08cc12e-a8cb-477e-85f1-b4457ccd1fd2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HATSUN AGRO PRODUCT LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BENARAS] Benares Hotels Ltd. to Announce Q4 Results on Jan 15, 2026; Trading Window Closed</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BENARES+HOTELS+LTD.&title=Benares+Hotels+Ltd.+to+Announce+Q4+Results+on+Jan+15%2C+2026%3B+Trading+Window+Closed&newsId=daeaf702-9f24-4329-a935-d32b09d87f3c&token=ZGFlYWY3MDItOWYy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">daeaf702-9f24-4329-a935-d32b09d87f3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 12:21:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Benares Hotels Ltd. has announced that its Board Meeting will be held on January 15, 2026, to consider and take on record the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter/period ended December 31, 2025. In accordance with the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, the designated persons have been notified about the closure of the Trading Window from December 25, 2025, to January 17, 2026. The Trading Window will reopen 48 hours after the financial results are made public on January 18, 2026.</p><ul><li>Benares Hotels Ltd. to announce Q4 results on Jan 15, 2026</li><li>Trading Window closed from Dec 25, 2025, to Jan 17, 2026</li><li>Trading Window to reopen on Jan 18, 2026, 48 hours after results are made public</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/345a2538-2720-4a4e-a0ed-75aba6458e0d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BENARES HOTELS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>