<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:21:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[CARGOTRANS] Cargotrans Maritime Approves Preferential Allotment of Equity Shares and Convertible Warrants</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Cargotrans+Maritime+Ltd&title=Cargotrans+Maritime+Approves+Preferential+Allotment+of+Equity+Shares+and+Convertible+Warrants&newsId=06f4f23d-8433-4c17-9013-350341c983b2&token=MDZmNGYyM2QtODQz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06f4f23d-8433-4c17-9013-350341c983b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cargotrans Maritime Ltd. announced the approval of allotment of equity shares and convertible warrants on a preferential basis at their board meeting held on February 7, 2026. The company will allot 12,41,666 equity shares at a price of Rs. 120/- per share, amounting to Rs. 14,89,99,920/-. Additionally, 16,50,000 convertible warrants will be issued at an issue price of Rs. 120/- per warrant, convertible into one equity share within 18 months from the date of allotment. The allotment is in compliance with SEBI regulations and the approval of BSE Limited.</p><ul><li>Allotment of 12,41,666 equity shares on preferential basis</li><li>Allotment of 16,50,000 convertible warrants on preferential basis</li><li>Equity shares priced at Rs. 120/- per share</li><li>Convertible warrants priced at Rs. 120/- per warrant</li><li>Allotment in compliance with SEBI ICDR Regulations and BSE approval</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/033433f2-f943-4e12-8afa-bbf0f91a73a9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Cargotrans Maritime Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SPORTKING] Sportking India Ltd Reports Strong Profitability in Q3 FY26: Delivers Double Digit EBITDA and PAT Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sportking+India+Ltd&title=Sportking+India+Ltd+Reports+Strong+Profitability+in+Q3+FY26%3A+Delivers+Double+Digit+EBITDA+and+PAT+Growth&newsId=23a7f905-64b5-48d7-9fe3-7e228efc95a8&token=MjNhN2Y5MDUtNjRi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23a7f905-64b5-48d7-9fe3-7e228efc95a8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:12:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Sportking India Limited, one of India’s leading textile conglomerate, announced its financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The quarter reflected stable operating performance and continued improvement in profitability, supported by disciplined cost management and strong operational efficiency. Domestic demand remained a key growth driver during the quarter, growing by 29% year on year. The momentum in domestic sales more than offset softness in exports, supporting overall revenue growth and improving the business mix. Cotton prices have remained largely stable without major volatility. The recently concluded trade agreements with the United States and the European Union mark a turning point for India’s textile industry. The company is well positioned to capitalize on this renewed advantage. At the beginning of this financial year, the company announced a landmark greenfield capacity addition program with a planned investment of ~X1,000 crores to significantly expand its spindle capacity.</p><ul><li>Q3 FY26 Revenue from operations stood at Rs. 645.9 Crs.</li><li>Q3 FY26 Gross profit increased marginally by 0.6% YoY to Rs. 151.1 Crs.</li><li>Q3 FY26 EBITDA increased by 10.8% YoY to Rs. 65.6 Crs.</li><li>Q3 FY26 Profit After Tax stood at Rs. 24.6 Crs, registering a robust YoY growth of 33.0%.</li><li>Company announced a landmark greenfield capacity addition program with a planned investment of ~X1,000 crores.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/96577143-8457-4e6d-9170-f6f694e6c0a4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sportking India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VISESHINFO] Visesh Infotecnics Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025, Highlighting Key Financial Metrics</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VISESH+INFOTECNICS+LTD.&title=Visesh+Infotecnics+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Highlighting+Key+Financial+Metrics&newsId=1e374048-2265-479e-9b5a-aeb57bc2dfe0&token=MWUzNzQwNDgtMjI2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1e374048-2265-479e-9b5a-aeb57bc2dfe0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Visesh Infotecnics Ltd has reported its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at INR 27.32 crores and INR 36.05 crores for the quarter and nine months ended, respectively. The total expenses for the same periods are INR 108.83 crores and INR 342.23 crores, respectively. The company&apos;s profit before tax for the quarter and nine months ended is INR (1,010.56) crores and INR (268.86) crores, respectively. The company&apos;s profit (loss) for the period from continuing operations for the quarter and nine months ended is INR (87.22) crores and INR (88.09) crores, respectively.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter ended at INR 27.32 crores</li><li>Total expenses for the quarter ended at INR 108.83 crores</li><li>Profit before tax for the quarter ended at INR (1,010.56) crores</li><li>Profit (loss) for the period from continuing operations for the quarter ended at INR (87.22) crores</li><li>The company&apos;s financial results have been prepared in accordance with IND AS notified under the Companies (Indian Accounting Standards) Rules, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/68fef642-18c5-4ab1-b350-c87f19c8a83a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VISESH INFOTECNICS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VISESHINFO] Visesh Infotecnics Ltd. Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025, Revealing Increased Revenue and Expenses</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VISESH+INFOTECNICS+LTD.&title=Visesh+Infotecnics+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Revealing+Increased+Revenue+and+Expenses&newsId=6c53c5ec-5b6e-4175-8a42-1eb95f017966&token=NmM1M2M1ZWMtNWI2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c53c5ec-5b6e-4175-8a42-1eb95f017966</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:10:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Visesh Infotecnics Ltd. has announced its un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s total revenue stands at INR 44.10 crores, representing an increase from INR 36.05 crores in the same period last year. The expenses have also risen, with finance costs and depreciation and amortization expense being the major contributors. The company&apos;s profit before tax stands at INR (261.59) crores, a decrease from INR (196.19) crores in the same period last year. The company has operated in only one segment, IT enabled services, and has no operations in its subsidiaries. The statutory auditors have carried out a limited review of the result for the quarter ended December 31, 2025.</p><ul><li>Total revenue for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, stands at INR 44.10 crores.</li><li>Expenses have risen, with finance costs and depreciation and amortization expense being the major contributors.</li><li>Profit before tax for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, stands at INR (261.59) crores.</li><li>The company has no operations in its subsidiaries.</li><li>Statutory auditors have carried out a limited review of the result for the quarter ended December 31, 2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6aa9a4cf-2278-45f9-ac5b-6a01628c420d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VISESH INFOTECNICS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KSHINTL] KSH International Ltd CEO, Sandesh Bhagwat, Resigns Effective March 31, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KSH+International+Ltd&title=KSH+International+Ltd+CEO%2C+Sandesh+Bhagwat%2C+Resigns+Effective+March+31%2C+2026&newsId=98942412-9f7b-4894-afe6-f1080a2c9dc6&token=OTg5NDI0MTItOWY3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98942412-9f7b-4894-afe6-f1080a2c9dc6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>KSH International Limited has informed the Exchange about the resignation of Mr. Sandesh Bhagwat as Chief Executive Officer (CEO) of the Company, effective from March 31, 2026. Mr. Bhagwat has resigned to pursue a new career opportunity outside the organization. His resignation was accepted by the Board of Directors at their meeting held on February 07, 2026. He will be relieved from the services of the Company with effect from close of business hours on March 31, 2026.</p><ul><li>Sandesh Bhagwat has resigned as CEO of KSH International Ltd.</li><li>His resignation is effective from March 31, 2026.</li><li>He has resigned to pursue a new career opportunity outside the organization.</li><li>His resignation was accepted by the Board of Directors at their meeting held on February 07, 2026.</li><li>He will be relieved from the services of the Company with effect from close of business hours on March 31, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/927362ae-3b25-441e-a80d-44a871c25a44.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KSH International Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SNL] SNL Bearings Ltd. Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for FY2025-26, Approves Capacity Expansion and Policy Changes</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SNL+BEARINGS+LTD.&title=SNL+Bearings+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+FY2025-26%2C+Approves+Capacity+Expansion+and+Policy+Changes&newsId=08ac45a2-42b2-45f9-9e80-c6ff876320fb&token=MDhhYzQ1YTItNDJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08ac45a2-42b2-45f9-9e80-c6ff876320fb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>SNL Bearings Ltd. announced the outcomes of its Board Meeting held on February 07, 2026. The company approved the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. Ms. Pooja Ponda resigned as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer. The company approved capacity enhancement and changes in the Policy for materiality of Related Party Transactions. The proposed expansion is expected to lead to 20%-25% higher volumes for various product families. The company plans to invest approximately ₹8 Crores towards the purchase and installation of machines and related equipment. The company is a significant player in the supply of cages and needle rollers for various applications and has received orders beyond its current capacity.</p><ul><li>Approval of Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Resignation of Ms. Pooja Ponda as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer</li><li>Approval of capacity enhancement with an estimated 20%-25% higher volumes</li><li>Planned capital investment of approximately ₹8 Crores for the proposed expansion</li><li>Company is a key supplier of cages and needle rollers for various applications</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e3221f8e-16b8-457c-8877-aaece058940f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SNL BEARINGS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SNL] SNL Bearings Ltd. Approves Capacity Enhancement, Changes in Related Party Transactions Policy, and Announces Q3 Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SNL+BEARINGS+LTD.&title=SNL+Bearings+Ltd.+Approves+Capacity+Enhancement%2C+Changes+in+Related+Party+Transactions+Policy%2C+and+Announces+Q3+Results&newsId=825c259d-b3d6-451d-a911-5b48a0c711f9&token=ODI1YzI1OWQtYjNk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">825c259d-b3d6-451d-a911-5b48a0c711f9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SNL Bearings Ltd. announced the outcomes of its board meeting held on February 7, 2026. The company approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The board also approved the resignation of Ms. Pooja Ponda as the Company Secretary and Compliance Officer. Furthermore, the company approved capacity enhancement and changes in the Policy for materiality of Related Party Transactions and on dealing with Related party Transactions. The meeting commenced at 1:35 p.m. and concluded at 7:00 p.m.</p><ul><li>Approval of unaudited financial results for Q3 2025 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Resignation of Ms. Pooja Ponda as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer</li><li>Approval of capacity enhancement</li><li>Approval of changes in the Policy for materiality of Related Party Transactions and on dealing with Related party Transactions</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/124dc528-91cd-4079-99fb-a44263c76dbd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SNL BEARINGS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KDJHRL] KDJ Holidayscapes and Resorts Ltd Revises Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended December 31, 2024</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KDJ+Holidayscapes+and+Resorts+Ltd&title=KDJ+Holidayscapes+and+Resorts+Ltd+Revises+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+December+31%2C+2024&newsId=740bf4eb-5ce9-4b3a-b0d6-7517cfdf0057&token=NzQwYmY0ZWItNWNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">740bf4eb-5ce9-4b3a-b0d6-7517cfdf0057</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:52:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>KDJ Holidayscapes and Resorts Ltd has revised its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2024. The revision was due to a typographical error in the original report, where the period was wrongly mentioned as 30t September 2024 instead of 31 December 2024. The company is operating under the Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code, 2016, and the management has been transferred to a Resolution Applicant with effect from 04/03/2025. The audit is restricted to the period post implementation of the Resolution Plan, and the auditor has relied solely upon the information and explanations provided by the current management.</p><ul><li>KDJ Holidayscapes and Resorts Ltd revised its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2024.</li><li>The revision was due to a typographical error in the original report.</li><li>The company is operating under the Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code, 2016.</li><li>The management of the company has been transferred to a Resolution Applicant with effect from 04/03/2025.</li><li>The audit is restricted to the period post implementation of the Resolution Plan.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/df66a48d-7a41-437e-bbaf-e218a28b86de.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KDJ Holidayscapes and Resorts Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KSHINTL] CARE Ratings Limited Submits Monitoring Agency Report for KSH International Ltd&apos;s IPO Utilization</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KSH+International+Ltd&title=CARE+Ratings+Limited+Submits+Monitoring+Agency+Report+for+KSH+International+Ltd%27s+IPO+Utilization&newsId=9cf44e66-c798-4911-8aab-2efa8002ead8&token=OWNmNDRlNjYtYzc5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9cf44e66-c798-4911-8aab-2efa8002ead8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:51:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>CARE Ratings Limited, the Monitoring Agency for KSH International Limited&apos;s Initial Public Offer (IPO), has submitted a Monitoring Agency Report for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The report indicates that the utilization of proceeds is as per the disclosures in the offer document. The IPO was for Rs.626.35 crore, which was a combination of fresh issue and offer for sale. The report also mentions that there are no material deviations from the expenditures disclosed in the offer prospectus and management certificate.</p><ul><li>CARE Ratings Limited submits Monitoring Agency Report for KSH International Ltd&apos;s IPO utilization</li><li>Utilization of proceeds is as per the disclosures in the offer document</li><li>IPO was for Rs.626.35 crore</li><li>No material deviations from the expenditures disclosed in the offer prospectus and management certificate</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/26b6dcd1-34e3-4b9d-923f-a7fb5b856ea4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KSH International Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JOINDRE] Joindre Capital Services Ltd. to Consider and Approve Q4 Results for 2025 in Board Meeting on Feb 14, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JOINDRE+CAPITAL+SERVICES+LTD.&title=Joindre+Capital+Services+Ltd.+to+Consider+and+Approve+Q4+Results+for+2025+in+Board+Meeting+on+Feb+14%2C+2026&newsId=d0d4a3f0-9365-497b-bb54-853501f3b150&token=ZDBkNGEzZjAtOTM2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d0d4a3f0-9365-497b-bb54-853501f3b150</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Joindre Capital Services Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 14, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025. The meeting will also consider any other matter with the permission of the Chair.</p><ul><li>Joindre Capital Services Ltd. to consider and approve Q4 results for 2025</li><li>Board meeting scheduled on February 14, 2026</li><li>Meeting to be held at the registered office of the company</li><li>Un-audited financial results for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025, to be considered</li><li>Other matters may be considered with the permission of the Chair</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f091affe-3ac7-4341-9d55-d23393c90573.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JOINDRE CAPITAL SERVICES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>