<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 01:21:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[VAIBHAVGBL] Vaibhav Global Ltd Declares 3% Interim Dividend, Grants ESOPs and RSUs, and Reports Q3 and YTD Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vaibhav+Global+Ltd&title=Vaibhav+Global+Ltd+Declares+3%25+Interim+Dividend%2C+Grants+ESOPs+and+RSUs%2C+and+Reports+Q3+and+YTD+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=3cdb195e-fd29-4046-b783-32e977bd859f&token=M2NkYjE5NWUtZmQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3cdb195e-fd29-4046-b783-32e977bd859f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vaibhav Global Ltd has declared a 3% interim dividend of Rs. 1.50 per equity share for the financial year 2025-26. The company has also granted 63,789 stock options (ESOPs) and 5,862 restricted stock units (RSUs) to eligible employees. The Board approved the unaudited financial results for Q3 and YTD ended 31st December 2025. The company reported a revenue of Rs. 1,06,602.51 lakhs for Q3 and Rs. 2,75,707.83 lakhs for YTD 2025.</p><ul><li>Declared 3% interim dividend of Rs. 1.50 per equity share</li><li>Granted 63,789 stock options (ESOPs) and 5,862 restricted stock units (RSUs) to eligible employees</li><li>Approved unaudited financial results for Q3 and YTD ended 31st December 2025</li><li>Revenue of Rs. 1,06,602.51 lakhs for Q3 and Rs. 2,75,707.83 lakhs for YTD 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1127f9ba-eb40-44fd-8231-f3d5e9370f7e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vaibhav Global Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VAIBHAVGBL] Vaibhav Global Ltd. Declares Interim Dividend, Approves Grant of ESOPs and RSUs, and Reports Q3 Results for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vaibhav+Global+Ltd&title=Vaibhav+Global+Ltd.+Declares+Interim+Dividend%2C+Approves+Grant+of+ESOPs+and+RSUs%2C+and+Reports+Q3+Results+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=ae9021e8-5699-40d9-abc2-ffa4f919831a&token=YWU5MDIxZTgtNTY5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae9021e8-5699-40d9-abc2-ffa4f919831a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In a recent board meeting, Vaibhav Global Ltd. approved the unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31 December 2025. The company declared an interim dividend of Rs. 1.50 per equity share for FY 2025-26, with a record date set for 03 February 2026. Additionally, the board granted 63,789 stock options and 5,862 restricted stock units under the VGL ESOP Plan — 2021 and VGL RSU Plan — 2019, respectively. The company also provided updates on various legal proceedings and assessed the incremental impact of the new Labour Codes.</p><ul><li>Declared interim dividend of Rs. 1.50 per equity share for FY 2025-26</li><li>Granted 63,789 stock options and 5,862 restricted stock units</li><li>Approved unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31 December 2025</li><li>Provided updates on various legal proceedings</li><li>Assessed the incremental impact of new Labour Codes</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8244db23-70b3-406d-aa67-25e8fb142b97.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vaibhav Global Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ALLSEC] Alldigi Tech Q3 FY26 Revenue up by 10%; EBITDA up by 42%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ALLSEC+TECHNOLOGIES+LTD.&title=Alldigi+Tech+Q3+FY26+Revenue+up+by+10%25%3B+EBITDA+up+by+42%25&newsId=1194e81e-190b-4c3b-b350-215e7c63fad6&token=MTE5NGU4MWUtMTkw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1194e81e-190b-4c3b-b350-215e7c63fad6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Alldigi Tech Limited, a global leader in Tech &amp; Digital (T&amp;D) &amp; BPM solutions, announced its financial results for Q3 FY26. The company&apos;s Q3 FY 26 YoY revenue from Operations is up by 9.5% and EBIDTA up by 41.7%. The Board has declared an interim dividend of Rs.30/- per equity share. The BPM vertical&apos;s revenue is up by 7.4% YoY and 3.2% QoQ, with international revenue up by 13.8% YoY and 7.9% QoQ. The Tech &amp; Digital vertical&apos;s revenue is up by 16.2% YoY and 4.9% QoQ.</p><ul><li>Q3 FY26 YoY revenue up by 9.5% and EBIDTA up by 41.7%</li><li>International revenue in BPM up by 13.8% YoY and 7.9% QoQ</li><li>Tech &amp; Digital revenue up by 16.2% YoY and 4.9% QoQ</li><li>Interim dividend of Rs.30/- per equity share declared</li><li>48.5 lacs employee records processed in Tech &amp; Digital, up by 10.0% YoY</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a5cc78f8-f236-4068-85ee-3abc812675ea.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ALLSEC TECHNOLOGIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VAIBHAVGBL] Vaibhav Global Q3 FY26: Revenue Over ₹ 31,000 Cr, Profit Up 41%, Declares Dividend</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vaibhav+Global+Ltd&title=Vaibhav+Global+Q3+FY26%3A+Revenue+Over+%E2%82%B9+31%2C000+Cr%2C+Profit+Up+41%25%2C+Declares+Dividend&newsId=d34d2669-dc20-405d-b5e4-43889663b51c&token=ZDM0ZDI2NjktZGMy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d34d2669-dc20-405d-b5e4-43889663b51c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Vaibhav Global Limited (VGL) announced its Q3 FY26 financial results, revealing a revenue of ₹ 3,106.6 crores, a 9.1% YoY growth. The gross margin stood at 63%, with EBITDA increasing 26% YoY. The net cash position was ₹ 213 crores, with ROCE at 21% and ROE at 15%. The company declared a third interim dividend of Rs. 1.50/ equity share, which is a 28% payout. The company&apos;s digital revenue mix was 42% of B2C revenue, with in-house brands contributing 48% of gross B2C revenue.</p><ul><li>Revenue over ₹ 31,000 Cr in Q3 FY26</li><li>Profit After Tax (PAT) up 41% YoY</li><li>EBITDA increased 26% YoY with margin expansion</li><li>Strong balance sheet with net cash position of ₹ 213 crores</li><li>In-house brands contributed 48% of gross B2C revenue</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a2ad3b21-6404-4a29-b0df-9fed73c787cb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vaibhav Global Ltd | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZAPPFRESH] Promoter Deepanshu Manchanda Acquires 0.05% Stake in DSM Fresh Foods Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DSM+Fresh+Foods+Ltd&title=Promoter+Deepanshu+Manchanda+Acquires+0.05%25+Stake+in+DSM+Fresh+Foods+Ltd&newsId=cf2cc3b7-c036-4ce8-a6a1-ae1d4073eecc&token=Y2YyY2MzYjctYzAz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cf2cc3b7-c036-4ce8-a6a1-ae1d4073eecc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:01:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pursuant to the purchase of 10,800 equity shares by Mr. Deepanshu Manchanda, Promoter in DSM Fresh Foods Limited, the following information is disclosed under Regulation 29(2) of the SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeover) Regulations, 2011. The acquisition took place between 20th to 23rd January 2026, through the open market. The total equity shares of DSM Fresh Foods Limited stand at 2,22,87,138 Equity Shares, both before and after the acquisition.</p><ul><li>Promoter Deepanshu Manchanda acquired 0.05% stake in DSM Fresh Foods Ltd</li><li>The acquisition was carried out through the open market</li><li>The total equity shares of DSM Fresh Foods Limited remain unchanged at 2,22,87,138 Equity Shares</li><li>The acquisition happened between 20th to 23rd January 2026</li><li>DSM Fresh Foods Limited shares are listed on BSE Limited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/031c8658-e516-45de-b59c-a9b68eaa6eda.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DSM Fresh Foods Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RELINFRA] Reliance Infrastructure Ltd Announces Resignation of Secretarial Auditor Ajay Kumar &amp; Co.</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RELIANCE+INFRASTRUCTURE+LTD.&title=Reliance+Infrastructure+Ltd+Announces+Resignation+of+Secretarial+Auditor+Ajay+Kumar+%26+Co.&newsId=ce358768-9f86-4f30-89ef-28c5f579c639&token=Y2UzNTg3NjgtOWY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce358768-9f86-4f30-89ef-28c5f579c639</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Reliance Infrastructure Ltd has announced the resignation of its Secretarial Auditor, Ajay Kumar &amp; Co., due to certain urgent personal problems. The company confirmed that there are no other reasons for the resignation. The Secretarial Auditor was appointed on January 27, 2026, and has confirmed that the resignation is not due to any other reasons.</p><ul><li>Reliance Infrastructure Ltd announces resignation of Secretarial Auditor Ajay Kumar &amp; Co.</li><li>Ajay Kumar &amp; Co. resigned due to certain urgent personal problems.</li><li>No other reasons for resignation confirmed by the Secretarial Auditor.</li><li>Ajay Kumar &amp; Co. was appointed on January 27, 2026.</li><li>Resignation not due to any other reasons, as confirmed by the Secretarial Auditor.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fda43c7f-f8ea-43f5-a358-ebcf5e0d78ba.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RELIANCE INFRASTRUCTURE LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VAIBHAVGBL] Vaibhav Global Ltd Announces Record Date for Interim Dividend Payment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vaibhav+Global+Ltd&title=Vaibhav+Global+Ltd+Announces+Record+Date+for+Interim+Dividend+Payment&newsId=1a8bfa14-1b0a-409f-9044-6bc3b05eba7b&token=MWE4YmZhMTQtMWIw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a8bfa14-1b0a-409f-9044-6bc3b05eba7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vaibhav Global Ltd has fixed Tuesday, 03rd February, 2026 as the &apos;Record Date&apos; for the purpose of ascertaining the eligibility of the shareholders for payment of 3rd Interim dividend for the financial year 2025-26. This decision was made in accordance with Regulation 42 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Vaibhav Global Ltd has announced the Record Date for the payment of 3rd Interim dividend for the financial year 2025-26.</li><li>The Record Date is set for Tuesday, 03rd February, 2026.</li><li>This decision is in accordance with Regulation 42 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li><li>The Record Date is used to ascertain the eligibility of shareholders for dividend payment.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c67cb283-1701-4c44-a531-9a3658d855a9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vaibhav Global Ltd | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JONJUA] Jonjua Overseas Ltd Announces Closure of Trading Window for Quarterly Financial Statement Filing</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jonjua+Overseas+Ltd&title=Jonjua+Overseas+Ltd+Announces+Closure+of+Trading+Window+for+Quarterly+Financial+Statement+Filing&newsId=2833e480-196a-437c-99e7-645870d519bd&token=MjgzM2U0ODAtMTk2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2833e480-196a-437c-99e7-645870d519bd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jonjua Overseas Ltd, in compliance with SEBI guidelines, will now be filing quarterly financial statements. The trading window for all insiders, directors, promoters, and designated employees will be closed from January 27, 2026, until the declaration of financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The date of the board meeting will be intimated in due course.</p><ul><li>Jonjua Overseas Ltd to file quarterly financial statements</li><li>Trading window closure for all insiders, directors, promoters, and designated employees from January 27, 2026, to the declaration of financial results</li><li>Closure in compliance with SEBI guidelines</li><li>Financial results are for the quarter ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Board meeting date to be intimated later</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d04ea5a0-bcbd-4ae0-8db5-0afa18b41b66.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jonjua Overseas Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JONJUA] Jonjua Overseas Ltd Sells Intangible Asset for Rs. 15.11 Crores in a Material Related Party Transaction</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jonjua+Overseas+Ltd&title=Jonjua+Overseas+Ltd+Sells+Intangible+Asset+for+Rs.+15.11+Crores+in+a+Material+Related+Party+Transaction&newsId=ab742842-5fc1-4257-b3c4-18b9ec7bf19e&token=YWI3NDI4NDItNWZj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab742842-5fc1-4257-b3c4-18b9ec7bf19e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Sale of Intangible Asset</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Jonjua Overseas Limited has sold an intangible asset - &apos;SPENT COFFEE GROUNDS AND SPENT COFFEE GROUNDS ASH BRICK PROCESS AND TECHNOLOGY (TRADE SECRET)&apos; on a &apos;Going Concern&apos; basis at arm&apos;s length to HSJONJUA INNOVATEAGRO PRIVATE LIMITED. The sale price is determined in accordance with the valuation report and amounts to Rs. 15.11 crores. This transaction represents 317% of the company&apos;s annual consolidated turnover for the immediately preceding financial year.</p><ul><li>The sale involves an intangible asset - &apos;SPENT COFFEE GROUNDS AND SPENT COFFEE GROUNDS ASH BRICK PROCESS AND TECHNOLOGY (TRADE SECRET)&apos;, which is a part of the company&apos;s Global Inhouse Centre (GIC) business.</li><li>The sale price is Rs. 15.11 crores, which is determined in accordance with the valuation report.</li><li>The transaction represents 317% of the company&apos;s annual consolidated turnover for the immediately preceding financial year.</li><li>The transaction is a Material Related Party Transaction.</li><li>The sale is beneficial to the company as per the justification provided in the text.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e1d2b4ec-0215-4e3c-9e79-ec9e2529f77d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jonjua Overseas Ltd | Category: Sale of Intangible Asset</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NRBBEARING] NRB Bearings Ltd Subsidiary to Acquire Aerospace Component Manufacturer for INR 27.5 Crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NRB+BEARINGS+LTD.&title=NRB+Bearings+Ltd+Subsidiary+to+Acquire+Aerospace+Component+Manufacturer+for+INR+27.5+Crore&newsId=0c37e83d-d243-4824-96ac-821a3a1307c4&token=MGMzN2U4M2QtZDI0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c37e83d-d243-4824-96ac-821a3a1307c4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>NRB Bearings Ltd announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, Mahant Tool Room Private Limited (MTRPL), has agreed to acquire the business of M/s. Mahant Tool Room (MTR), a sole proprietorship concern based out of Bangalore, engaged in the manufacturing of precision machined components for engine and fuel systems for the aerospace industry. The acquisition is subject to completion of certain conditions precedent with a cash consideration of INR 27,50,00,000. This acquisition will mark NRB Bearings Ltd&apos;s entry in the aerospace industry.</p><ul><li>NRB Bearings Ltd&apos;s subsidiary, MTRPL, to acquire MTR for INR 27.5 crore</li><li>MTR is engaged in the manufacturing of precision machined components for the aerospace industry</li><li>The acquisition is subject to completion of certain conditions precedent</li><li>MTR has an annual turnover of INR 1,88,30,000 and a confirmed order book of over INR 25 crore</li><li>This acquisition will mark NRB Bearings Ltd&apos;s entry in the aerospace industry</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e778c9db-9175-4c99-a659-53481c9a118f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NRB BEARINGS LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>