<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:55:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ZAGGLE] Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd Incorporates Wholly Owned Subsidiary - Zaggle Payments IFSC Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Zaggle+Prepaid+Ocean+Services+Ltd&title=Zaggle+Prepaid+Ocean+Services+Ltd+Incorporates+Wholly+Owned+Subsidiary+-+Zaggle+Payments+IFSC+Limited&newsId=573f021d-5b13-4b6d-b908-bca583798b15&token=NTczZjAyMWQtNWIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">573f021d-5b13-4b6d-b908-bca583798b15</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:53:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd has incorporated a new wholly owned subsidiary, Zaggle Payments IFSC Limited, in GIFT City, Gujarat. The Certificate of Incorporation was received from the Ministry of Corporate Affairs on February 25, 2026. This development is in line with the company&apos;s strategic growth plans and expansion in the financial services sector.</p><ul><li>Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd has incorporated a new wholly owned subsidiary.</li><li>The new subsidiary, Zaggle Payments IFSC Limited, is incorporated in GIFT City, Gujarat.</li><li>The Certificate of Incorporation was received on February 25, 2026.</li><li>This move is a part of the company&apos;s strategic growth plans.</li><li>It signifies the company&apos;s expansion in the financial services sector.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/55066059-3475-4ef1-ba84-01976d2cf5f2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[COSMOFIRST] Cosmo First Ltd Clarifies Volume Movement Due to Market Conditions</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Cosmo+First+Ltd&title=Cosmo+First+Ltd+Clarifies+Volume+Movement+Due+to+Market+Conditions&newsId=d94d88b7-953f-4a26-8489-9ef5adbc4108&token=ZDk0ZDg4YjctOTUz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d94d88b7-953f-4a26-8489-9ef5adbc4108</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:52:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cosmo First Ltd has clarified a recent increase in trading volume of its shares, stating that it is due to market conditions and is market-driven. The company has been informing the Stock Exchanges about all events and information that have a bearing on its operation or performance. There is no undisclosed price sensitive information that needs to be informed to the exchanges at this point in time. Cosmo First Ltd assures that it will continue to promptly inform the exchanges of all material events/information/actions as required under SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Cosmo First Ltd clarifies increase in trading volume due to market conditions</li><li>Company has been informing Stock Exchanges about events and information affecting operation or performance</li><li>No undisclosed price sensitive information</li><li>Cosmo First Ltd committed to informing exchanges of material events as per SEBI regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0ab39508-774a-473d-b9ad-08b2e87e1818.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Cosmo First Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[YESBANK] Yes Bank&apos;s Forex Cards Hit by Unauthorized Transactions; No Material Impact</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=YES+BANK+LTD.&title=Yes+Bank%27s+Forex+Cards+Hit+by+Unauthorized+Transactions%3B+No+Material+Impact&newsId=32e84159-6e19-4b90-b8ce-f0ede1c30b6a&token=MzJlODQxNTktNmUx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32e84159-6e19-4b90-b8ce-f0ede1c30b6a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:49:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Yes Bank&apos;s Multi-Currency Prepaid Forex Card, issued in partnership with BookMyForex, observed an unusual increase in transaction decline by the bank’s fraud monitoring system. These unauthorized transactions were attempted on specific BIN numbers only, carried out on 15 merchants based in a Latin American Country. The Bank has restricted e-commerce transactions from this country and is working with Card Network to raise chargeback to ensure that the impacted customers do not face any financial loss. The internal investigation revealed that approximately USD 0.28 MN (Approx. INR 2.5 Cr) have been approved on behalf of 5000 customers. However, due to the Bank’s monitoring and control mechanisms, 688 unauthorized transaction attempts were declined, which led to safeguarding of approximately equivalent to USD 0.1 MN. Yes Bank remains committed to the highest standards of data security and customer protection.</p><ul><li>Yes Bank&apos;s Multi-Currency Prepaid Forex Card observed an unusual increase in transaction decline by the bank’s fraud monitoring system.</li><li>Unauthorized transactions were attempted on specific BIN numbers only, carried out on 15 merchants based in a Latin American Country.</li><li>The Bank has restricted e-commerce transactions from this country and is working with Card Network to raise chargeback.</li><li>Internal investigation revealed that approximately USD 0.28 MN (Approx. INR 2.5 Cr) have been approved on behalf of 5000 customers.</li><li>Yes Bank remains committed to the highest standards of data security and customer protection.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d7ba5cad-aa53-4d5a-9149-72a561bc5674.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: YES BANK LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[USHAMART] Usha Martin Ltd Clarifies on Significant Increase in Security Volume</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=USHA+MARTIN+LTD.&title=Usha+Martin+Ltd+Clarifies+on+Significant+Increase+in+Security+Volume&newsId=134f9478-7dd8-4e51-a100-2a8115681660&token=MTM0Zjk0NzgtN2Rk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">134f9478-7dd8-4e51-a100-2a8115681660</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:49:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Usha Martin Ltd has clarified regarding a significant increase in the volume of the company&apos;s security. The company has been disclosing all necessary information to the Exchange as per Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. There are no pending announcements or information that may affect the price or volume behavior of the scrip. The company reaffirms its adherence to the disclosure requirements and will inform the Stock Exchanges of any material information or events as required under the regulations.</p><ul><li>Usha Martin Ltd has clarified a significant increase in the volume of its security.</li><li>The company has been disclosing all necessary information to the Exchange as per SEBI regulations.</li><li>There are no pending announcements or information that may affect the price or volume behavior of the scrip.</li><li>The company reaffirms its adherence to the disclosure requirements.</li><li>Usha Martin Ltd will inform the Stock Exchanges of any material information or events as required under the regulations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/484f02bd-4006-476d-8be2-c99adc624026.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: USHA MARTIN LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VIRINCHI] Vivo Bio Tech Ltd Acquires 1.22% Stake in Virinchi Ltd Through Warrant Conversion</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Virinchi+Ltd&title=Vivo+Bio+Tech+Ltd+Acquires+1.22%25+Stake+in+Virinchi+Ltd+Through+Warrant+Conversion&newsId=10f1120d-08ab-4609-b99b-b4871a7d0c9e&token=MTBmMTEyMGQtMDhh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">10f1120d-08ab-4609-b99b-b4871a7d0c9e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vivo Bio Tech Ltd, a Promoter Group of Virinchi Limited, has acquired 1,22,15,715 equity shares, which is 1.22% of the total share and voting capital, of Virinchi Limited. This acquisition was made through the conversion of warrants issued on a preferential basis on February 24, 2026. The total equity share capital of Virinchi Limited stands at Rs. 108,79,68,960 before and after the acquisition. The total diluted share capital of the company after the acquisition is Rs. 126,04,68,960.</p><ul><li>Vivo Bio Tech Ltd, a Promoter Group of Virinchi Limited, has acquired 1.22% stake in Virinchi Limited</li><li>The acquisition was made through the conversion of warrants issued on a preferential basis on February 24, 2026</li><li>The total equity share capital of Virinchi Limited stands at Rs. 108,79,68,960 before and after the acquisition</li><li>The total diluted share capital of the company after the acquisition is Rs. 126,04,68,960</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9B3746B2_6DC6_43BB_98D0_7DFB676BABBB_121628.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Virinchi Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HNDFDS] Hindustan Foods Ltd. Receives NCLT Approval for Scheme of Arrangement with Avalon Cosmetics and Vanity Case India</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HINDUSTAN+FOODS+LTD.&title=Hindustan+Foods+Ltd.+Receives+NCLT+Approval+for+Scheme+of+Arrangement+with+Avalon+Cosmetics+and+Vanity+Case+India&newsId=0bf05758-6bee-4e44-8ee4-aa4035b27a9d&token=MGJmMDU3NTgtNmJl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0bf05758-6bee-4e44-8ee4-aa4035b27a9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:48:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Hindustan Foods Ltd. (HFL) has received approval from the National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT) for a Scheme of Arrangement between HFL, Avalon Cosmetics Private Limited (ACPL), and Vanity Case India Private Limited (VCIPL). The Scheme involves the demerger of ACPL&apos;s Contract Manufacturing (Nashik) Business into HFL and the amalgamation of VCIPL with HFL. The NCLT sanctioned the Scheme on February 25, 2026. The Scheme is expected to provide several benefits, including concentrated management focus, better utilization of industrial land, operational rationalization, and expansion and diversification of business. The equity shares of the Resulting Company/Transferee Company are listed on the Bombay Stock Exchange Limited (BSE) and National Stock Exchange of India Limited (NSE).</p><ul><li>HFL receives NCLT approval for Scheme of Arrangement with ACPL and VCIPL</li><li>Scheme involves demerger of ACPL&apos;s Contract Manufacturing (Nashik) Business into HFL and amalgamation of VCIPL with HFL</li><li>Expected to provide benefits such as concentrated management focus, better utilization of industrial land, operational rationalization, and expansion and diversification of business</li><li>Equity shares of the Resulting Company/Transferee Company listed on BSE and NSE</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6b74c80b-5aa6-49ae-a592-4f4a37d396a9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HINDUSTAN FOODS LTD. | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EIKO] Promoter Group Entity, Lenus Finvest Pvt Ltd Acquires 1.22% Stake in Eiko Lifesciences Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Eiko+Lifesciences+Ltd&title=Promoter+Group+Entity%2C+Lenus+Finvest+Pvt+Ltd+Acquires+1.22%25+Stake+in+Eiko+Lifesciences+Ltd&newsId=f40befde-67b6-42a1-aa82-c39434fe7c2f&token=ZjQwYmVmZGUtNjdi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f40befde-67b6-42a1-aa82-c39434fe7c2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:47:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>On 24th February 2026, Eiko Lifesciences Ltd&apos;s Board of Directors allotted 1,75,000 equity shares and 1,50,000 warrants on a preferential basis to Lenus Finvest Private Limited, a Promoter Group Entity. This acquisition resulted in Lenus Finvest Private Limited holding 1.22% (non-diluted) and 1.09% (diluted) of the issued and subscribed equity shares of Eiko Lifesciences Limited. Post conversion of all warrants, Lenus Finvest Private Limited would hold 15.56% of the company.</p><ul><li>Lenus Finvest Pvt Ltd, a Promoter Group Entity, acquired 1,75,000 equity shares of Eiko Lifesciences Ltd</li><li>This acquisition represents 1.22% (non-diluted) and 1.09% (diluted) of the issued and subscribed equity shares</li><li>Additionally, 1,50,000 warrants were allotted, which upon conversion would result in a 15.56% stake</li><li>The transaction was completed on a preferential basis</li><li>The acquisition was disclosed under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/389BFEEC_144E_48FF_8B7D_49900072E0E6_121525.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Eiko Lifesciences Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUNCLAY] Sundaram-Clayton Ltd: Mr Vivek S Joshi Resigns as Director &amp; CEO, Mr R Venkatesh Appointed as Successor</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sundaram-Clayton+Ltd&title=Sundaram-Clayton+Ltd%3A+Mr+Vivek+S+Joshi+Resigns+as+Director+%26+CEO%2C+Mr+R+Venkatesh+Appointed+as+Successor&newsId=c4df5cf0-62e6-46f6-bfb3-0e4d8da1036d&token=YzRkZjVjZjAtNjJl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4df5cf0-62e6-46f6-bfb3-0e4d8da1036d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sundaram-Clayton Ltd announced the resignation of Mr Vivek S Joshi as Director &amp; CEO and Key Managerial Personnel, effective 31st March 2026 due to personal reasons. The company also announced the appointment of Mr R Venkatesh as an Additional Director designated as Director &amp; CEO and Key Managerial Personnel, effective 1st April 2026. Mr Venkatesh has 26+ years of rich experience in the auto component industry and has worked in multiple group companies of TVS - Sundaram Clayton group.</p><ul><li>Mr Vivek S Joshi resigns as Director &amp; CEO of Sundaram-Clayton Ltd.</li><li>Mr R Venkatesh appointed as Additional Director designated as Director &amp; CEO and Key Managerial Personnel.</li><li>Mr Venkatesh has 26+ years of experience in the auto component industry.</li><li>He has worked in multiple group companies of TVS - Sundaram Clayton group.</li><li>His areas of expertise include total quality management, strategic planning, operations management, and more.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/89c81c0e-2e12-4856-9139-2d67b449143f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sundaram-Clayton Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BANDHANBNK] RBI Approves SBI Mutual Fund&apos;s 9.99% Stake Acquisition in Bandhan Bank</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Bandhan+Bank+Ltd&title=RBI+Approves+SBI+Mutual+Fund%27s+9.99%25+Stake+Acquisition+in+Bandhan+Bank&newsId=7c431086-b663-4666-9ba4-9502fa359deb&token=N2M0MzEwODYtYjY2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c431086-b663-4666-9ba4-9502fa359deb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:37:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has granted approval to SBI Mutual Fund to acquire an &apos;aggregate holding&apos; of up to 9.99% of the paid-up share capital or voting rights in Bandhan Bank. The approval is subject to compliance with various statutes, regulations, and guidelines, including the Banking Regulation Act, 1949, and the Reserve Bank of India (Commercial Banks - Acquisition and Holding of Shares or Voting Rights) Directions, 2025. The RBI has also stated that if the applicant fails to acquire the major shareholding within a year, the approval will be cancelled. Furthermore, the applicant has been advised to ensure that their &apos;aggregate holding&apos; does not exceed 9.99% at any time.</p><ul><li>RBI approves SBI Mutual Fund&apos;s 9.99% stake acquisition in Bandhan Bank</li><li>Approval subject to compliance with various statutes and regulations</li><li>Applicant must acquire the stake within a year, else approval will be cancelled</li><li>Applicant advised to ensure &apos;aggregate holding&apos; does not exceed 9.99% at any time</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d1682c33-2638-4785-a049-3c534ee779e8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Bandhan Bank Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AUROPHARMA] Aurobindo Pharma&apos;s Subsidiary, Eugia Pharma, Receives USFDA Approval for Everolimus Tablets</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AUROBINDO+PHARMA+LTD.&title=Aurobindo+Pharma%27s+Subsidiary%2C+Eugia+Pharma%2C+Receives+USFDA+Approval+for+Everolimus+Tablets&newsId=a562df79-e258-42f7-a0d8-bd777b79398d&token=YTU2MmRmNzktZTI1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a562df79-e258-42f7-a0d8-bd777b79398d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 06:35:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>USFDA</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Aurobindo Pharma Limited announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, Eugia Pharma Specialities Limited, has received final approval from the US Food &amp; Drug Administration (USFDA) to manufacture and market Everolimus Tablets, 0.25 mg, 0.5 mg, 0.75 mg, 1 mg. This approval has been received from Eugia Unit-1 and is expected to be launched in Q1FY27. The approved product has an estimated market size of USS 78 million for the twelve months ending December 2025, according to IQVIA MAT. This is the 184th ANDA approval (including 10 tentative approvals received) out of Eugia Pharma Specialities Group (EPSG) facilities, manufacturing both oncology oral and sterile specialty products.</p><ul><li>Eugia Pharma Specialities Limited, a subsidiary of Aurobindo Pharma, received USFDA approval for Everolimus Tablets</li><li>The approval is for 0.25 mg, 0.5 mg, 0.75 mg, and 1 mg strengths</li><li>The approval is expected to be launched in Q1FY27</li><li>The estimated market size of the approved product is USS 78 million for the twelve months ending December 2025</li><li>This is the 184th ANDA approval (including 10 tentative approvals received) out of Eugia Pharma Specialities Group (EPSG) facilities</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/727fa546-25f2-4459-a804-c4bf4cf09601.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AUROBINDO PHARMA LTD. | Category: USFDA</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>