<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:41:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[CELEBRITY] Celebrity Fashions Ltd. Clarifies Figures in Preferential Issue of Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CELEBRITY+FASHIONS+LTD.&title=Celebrity+Fashions+Ltd.+Clarifies+Figures+in+Preferential+Issue+of+Equity+Shares&newsId=f25a3d6d-3c46-458d-af46-84bb86ea055a&token=ZjI1YTNkNmQtM2M0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f25a3d6d-3c46-458d-af46-84bb86ea055a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:37:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Celebrity Fashions Ltd. has issued a clarification regarding the approval of issuance of Equity Shares by way of preferential issue on a private placement basis. The numbers disclosed in the earlier outcome were in rounded-off figures, and have now been revised to reflect the exact figures including decimal points. The issue size, pricing, and other terms of the preferential issue remain unchanged. The approval is for the issuance of 48,69,933 fully paid up equity shares to Promoters, Director, and Body Corporate. The Board Meeting commenced at 14:30 PM and concluded at 15:20 PM on 19th January 2026.</p><ul><li>Celebrity Fashions Ltd. clarifies figures in preferential issue of equity shares.</li><li>The numbers disclosed in the earlier outcome were in rounded-off figures and have now been revised.</li><li>The issue size, pricing, and other terms of the preferential issue remain unchanged.</li><li>Approval for the issuance of 48,69,933 fully paid up equity shares to Promoters, Director, and Body Corporate.</li><li>The Board Meeting commenced at 14:30 PM and concluded at 15:20 PM on 19th January 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6f64d208-56fa-4cf0-a83e-039978785940.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CELEBRITY FASHIONS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FMEC] F Mec International Financial Services Ltd Increases Authorized Share Capital to Rs. 15 Crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=F+Mec+International+Financial+Services+Ltd&title=F+Mec+International+Financial+Services+Ltd+Increases+Authorized+Share+Capital+to+Rs.+15+Crore&newsId=fede4f93-b93b-4296-aef4-e764b7c9c078&token=ZmVkZTRmOTMtYjkz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fede4f93-b93b-4296-aef4-e764b7c9c078</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:34:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>F Mec International Financial Services Ltd has announced an increase in its authorized share capital from Rs. 10 crore to Rs. 15 crore. This decision was approved by the shareholders in the 2nd Extra-ordinary General Meeting held on December 18, 2025, through Video Conference. The company has filed E form SH-7 for the increase in authorized share capital on January 19, 2026. The amendment to the Memorandum of Association (MOA) has been made to modify the capital clause, increasing the number of equity shares from 1 crore to 1.5 crore.</p><ul><li>F Mec International Financial Services Ltd has increased its authorized share capital from Rs. 10 crore to Rs. 15 crore.</li><li>The decision was approved by the shareholders in the 2nd Extra-ordinary General Meeting held on December 18, 2025.</li><li>The company has filed E form SH-7 for the increase in authorized share capital on January 19, 2026.</li><li>The amendment to the Memorandum of Association (MOA) has been made to modify the capital clause.</li><li>The number of equity shares has been increased from 1 crore to 1.5 crore.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f50eff37-5099-42d5-8b41-f2e0db500b37.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: F Mec International Financial Services Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SEL] Sanathnagar Enterprises Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Unaudited Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sanathnagar+Enterprises+Limited&title=Sanathnagar+Enterprises+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=32bcbef4-7431-4a21-8e1a-fcb0dc9d9939&token=MzJiY2JlZjQtNzQz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32bcbef4-7431-4a21-8e1a-fcb0dc9d9939</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:32:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sanathnagar Enterprises Ltd, a real estate development company, has reported its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations for the quarter is INR 379.75 lakhs, with a profit before tax of INR 7.54 lakhs. The company&apos;s earnings per share (EPS) for the quarter is INR 0.24. The company operates in a single reportable segment and does not have any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or associate companies.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter is INR 379.75 lakhs</li><li>Profit before tax for the quarter is INR 7.54 lakhs</li><li>Earnings per share (EPS) for the quarter is INR 0.24</li><li>The company operates in a single reportable segment</li><li>The company does not have any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or associate companies</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/be334cd8-c4ff-4c7f-9baf-a2447a301cc3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sanathnagar Enterprises Limited | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LEMONTREE] Lemon Tree Hotels Signs New Property in Uttarakhand&apos;s Serene Khurpatal</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Lemon+Tree+Hotels+Ltd&title=Lemon+Tree+Hotels+Signs+New+Property+in+Uttarakhand%27s+Serene+Khurpatal&newsId=32f0ce85-feb4-4dbe-bac7-89e37fdd7271&token=MzJmMGNlODUtZmVi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32f0ce85-feb4-4dbe-bac7-89e37fdd7271</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Lemon Tree Hotels Limited, India’s fastest-growing mid-scale and premium hotel chain, has announced the signing of its latest property - Keys Select by Lemon Tree Hotels, Khurpatal, Uttarakhand. The property, managed by Carnation Hotels Private Limited, a wholly-owned subsidiary of Lemon Tree Hotels Limited, will feature 120 well-appointed rooms, a restaurant, a banquet hall, a meeting room, and recreational facilities including a swimming pool, spa, and a fitness centre. The hotel is located on a serene hill hamlet near Nainital, Uttarakhand, known for its striking blue-green lake and dense pine, oak, and deodar forests, making it ideal for slow travel, meditation, and nature lovers.</p><ul><li>The hotel is located in Khurpatal, Uttarakhand, known for its serene blue-green lake and dense forests.</li><li>It will feature 120 well-appointed rooms, a restaurant, a banquet hall, a meeting room, and recreational facilities.</li><li>The property is managed by Carnation Hotels Private Limited, a wholly-owned subsidiary of Lemon Tree Hotels Limited.</li><li>The hotel is well-connected by both public and private transport, with the Pantnagar Airport approximately 70 kms away and the Kathgodam Railway Station about 36 kms away.</li><li>This signing will further strengthen Lemon Tree Hotels’ presence in Uttarakhand, catering to both religious and leisure travellers.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9bda900b-fa4d-4e34-aad9-b9cf0cba77d7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Lemon Tree Hotels Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SEL] Sanathnagar Enterprises Ltd Appoints Sandeep Lakhotia as CFO, Vikash Mundhra Resigns</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sanathnagar+Enterprises+Limited&title=Sanathnagar+Enterprises+Ltd+Appoints+Sandeep+Lakhotia+as+CFO%2C+Vikash+Mundhra+Resigns&newsId=f4e31a9b-c322-4334-bb88-3430ae6f174a&token=ZjRlMzFhOWItYzMy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4e31a9b-c322-4334-bb88-3430ae6f174a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sanathnagar Enterprises Ltd has appointed Mr. Sandeep Lakhotia as the new Chief Financial Officer and Key Managerial Personnel, effective from January 20, 2026. Mr. Lakhotia is a qualified Chartered Accountant with over 15 years of experience in various fields of finance, strategy, governance, and commercial operations. He joined the Lodha group in August 2024. The appointment comes after the resignation of Mr. Vikash Mundhra, who served as the CFO and Key Managerial Personnel until the closure of business hours on January 19, 2026 due to pre-occupations and other personal reasons.</p><ul><li>Sanathnagar Enterprises Ltd appoints Sandeep Lakhotia as Chief Financial Officer</li><li>Mr. Lakhotia has over 15 years of experience in various fields of finance and strategy</li><li>Vikash Mundhra resigns from the post of Chief Financial Officer due to pre-occupations and personal reasons</li><li>Mr. Mundhra&apos;s resignation is effective from the closure of business hours on January 19, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/de21d7cb-f28a-415a-87f3-871da89114f7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sanathnagar Enterprises Limited | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BIRLACABLE] Birla Cable Ltd: CEO and Manager, R. Sridharan, Resigns After Two Decades</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Birla+Cable+Ltd&title=Birla+Cable+Ltd%3A+CEO+and+Manager%2C+R.+Sridharan%2C+Resigns+After+Two+Decades&newsId=1d1892bf-a2ea-436f-8e9a-f703caf42d81&token=MWQxODkyYmYtYTJl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d1892bf-a2ea-436f-8e9a-f703caf42d81</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Auditor</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Birla Cable Ltd announced the resignation of its Chief Executive Officer (CEO) and Manager, R. Sridharan, due to personal reasons. Sridharan has been associated with the company for over two decades and has contributed significantly to its growth. His resignation will be effective from the close of business hours on 19th January, 2026. Sridharan also ceases to be a Key Managerial Personnel (KMP) in terms of Section 203 of the Companies Act, 2013 and Regulation 30(5) of the Listing Regulations. The company has expressed its appreciation for Sridharan&apos;s contributions during his tenure.</p><ul><li>R. Sridharan resigns from the post of CEO and Manager due to personal reasons.</li><li>Sridharan has been associated with the company for over two decades.</li><li>His resignation will be effective from the close of business hours on 19th January, 2026.</li><li>Sridharan ceases to be a Key Managerial Personnel (KMP) in terms of Section 203 of the Companies Act, 2013 and Regulation 30(5) of the Listing Regulations.</li><li>The company has expressed its appreciation for Sridharan&apos;s contributions.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e69ef00b-b5b9-4447-ae70-8439aeaa157e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Birla Cable Ltd | Category: Auditor</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SEL] Sanathnagar Enterprises Ltd: New CFO Appointed, Old CFO Resigns</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sanathnagar+Enterprises+Limited&title=Sanathnagar+Enterprises+Ltd%3A+New+CFO+Appointed%2C+Old+CFO+Resigns&newsId=c2aa172a-ff08-48f9-ad9e-d523713a1f2e&token=YzJhYTE3MmEtZmYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c2aa172a-ff08-48f9-ad9e-d523713a1f2e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sanathnagar Enterprises Ltd has announced the appointment of Mr. Sandeep Lakhotia as the new Chief Financial Officer and Key Managerial Personnel, effective from January 20, 2026. Mr. Lakhotia, a qualified Chartered Accountant with over 15 years of experience, joined the Lodha group in August 2024. On the other hand, Mr. Vikash Mundhra has resigned from his position as the Chief Financial Officer and Key Managerial Personnel due to pre-occupations and other personal reasons, with effect from the closure of business hours on January 19, 2026.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Sandeep Lakhotia as the new CFO and Key Managerial Personnel</li><li>Mr. Lakhotia has over 15 years of experience in finance, strategy, governance, capital markets, treasury, and more</li><li>Resignation of Mr. Vikash Mundhra due to pre-occupations and personal reasons</li><li>Mr. Mundhra&apos;s resignation is effective from the closure of business hours on January 19, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7e13183a-0fd2-45f5-bd75-55614f087687.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sanathnagar Enterprises Limited | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NAVNETEDUL] Navneet Education Ltd Incorporates Wholly Owned Subsidiary &apos;Navneet Global FZE&apos; in UAE</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Navneet+Education+Limited&title=Navneet+Education+Ltd+Incorporates+Wholly+Owned+Subsidiary+%27Navneet+Global+FZE%27+in+UAE&newsId=626dc64f-a749-4423-ad2e-6eadcab1de50&token=NjI2ZGM2NGYtYTc0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">626dc64f-a749-4423-ad2e-6eadcab1de50</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Navneet Education Ltd has incorporated a wholly owned subsidiary named &apos;Navneet Global FZE&apos; in UAE, following the approval from the Government of Fujairah, Fujairah Free Zone Authority. The Certificate of Incorporation has been issued by the UAE authorities. The necessary details have already been submitted to the stock exchanges on 16th December, 2025, as required under various regulations and circulars.</p><ul><li>Navneet Education Ltd incorporates a wholly owned subsidiary, Navneet Global FZE, in UAE</li><li>Incorporation approved by Government of Fujairah, Fujairah Free Zone Authority</li><li>Certificate of Incorporation issued by UAE authorities</li><li>Details submitted to stock exchanges as per regulations</li><li>Navneet Global FZE incorporated on 19th January, 2026 with License No 4582 and Registration No 26-FZE-2289</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d1bba31a-d438-45bd-96ba-82cca0d6be6e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Navneet Education Limited | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NATIONALUM] National Aluminium Company Ltd Board Meeting on January 30, 2026, to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NATIONAL+ALUMINIUM+CO.LTD.&title=National+Aluminium+Company+Ltd+Board+Meeting+on+January+30%2C+2026%2C+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results&newsId=3abe62ae-4492-4ef2-815d-4c3453ec4400&token=M2FiZTYyYWUtNDQ5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3abe62ae-4492-4ef2-815d-4c3453ec4400</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:31:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>National Aluminium Company Ltd has announced a Board Meeting scheduled for January 30, 2026. The meeting will consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The trading window will be closed from January 15, 2026, to February 1, 2026. This information is for record purposes.</p><ul><li>Board Meeting scheduled for January 30, 2026</li><li>Consideration and approval of Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December 2025</li><li>Trading window closure from January 15, 2026, to February 1, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d8118fe2-6555-4f52-b10e-13d5754a52f4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NATIONAL ALUMINIUM CO.LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PIIND] PI Industries Ltd Adopts New Corporate Logo</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PI+Industries+Ltd&title=PI+Industries+Ltd+Adopts+New+Corporate+Logo&newsId=73ddf3b5-8b06-4605-85f4-b3ff987bfe31&token=NzNkZGYzYjUtOGIw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73ddf3b5-8b06-4605-85f4-b3ff987bfe31</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Branding &amp; Identity</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>PI Industries Ltd has adopted a new corporate logo as part of a refresh of its brand identity. The new logo does not entail any change to the Company&apos;s name, legal status, or nature of business operations. The Company will adopt the new logo in a phased manner across various platforms and materials. During the transition period, both the existing and the new logo will be used concurrently. This intimation is being made for information and record purposes and is also available on the Company’s website.</p><ul><li>PI Industries Ltd has adopted a new corporate logo</li><li>The new logo does not entail any change to the Company&apos;s name, legal status, or nature of business operations</li><li>The Company will adopt the new logo in a phased manner across various platforms and materials</li><li>Both the existing and the new logo will be used concurrently during the transition period</li><li>The intimation is being made for information and record purposes and is also available on the Company’s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/56456728-5ec3-496b-9beb-17098a644917.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PI Industries Ltd | Category: Branding & Identity</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>