<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:25:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[JBCHEPHARM] Tau Investment Releases Encumbrance on JB Chemicals &amp; Pharmaceuticals Shares After Selling to Torrent Pharmaceuticals</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=J.B.CHEMICALS+%26+PHARMACEUTICALS+LTD.&title=Tau+Investment+Releases+Encumbrance+on+JB+Chemicals+%26+Pharmaceuticals+Shares+After+Selling+to+Torrent+Pharmaceuticals&newsId=664e9754-85ab-4f79-ab66-0b81de09b54c&token=NjY0ZTk3NTQtODVh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">664e9754-85ab-4f79-ab66-0b81de09b54c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tau Investment Holdings Pte. Ltd., a promoter of JB Chemicals &amp; Pharmaceuticals Ltd., has released an encumbrance on its shares in the company. This move follows the sale of 7,44,81,519 equity shares to Torrent Pharmaceuticals Limited, as per a share purchase agreement dated 29 June 2025. The sale was executed on 21 January 2026, leading to Tau Investment&apos;s reclassification from the &apos;promoter&apos; category to the &apos;public&apos; category. The release of encumbrance is due to the covenants in the finance agreement no longer being applicable.</p><ul><li>Tau Investment Holdings Pte. Ltd. sells shares of JB Chemicals &amp; Pharmaceuticals Ltd. to Torrent Pharmaceuticals Limited.</li><li>The sale results in Tau Investment&apos;s reclassification from &apos;promoter&apos; to &apos;public&apos; category.</li><li>The release of encumbrance is due to the covenants in the finance agreement no longer being applicable.</li><li>The transaction contributes to changes in shareholding and control of JB Chemicals &amp; Pharmaceuticals Ltd.</li><li>The sale marks a significant shift in the pharmaceuticals industry with Torrent Pharmaceuticals expanding its portfolio.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/51B86AAD_ABCA_4DA2_9308_360A992F2F84_114028.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: J.B.CHEMICALS & PHARMACEUTICALS LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[REPCOHOME] Repco Home Finance Ltd. to Consider and Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results for FY 2025-26, and Declare Second Interim Dividend</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=REPCO+HOME+FINANCE+LTD.&title=Repco+Home+Finance+Ltd.+to+Consider+and+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+FY+2025-26%2C+and+Declare+Second+Interim+Dividend&newsId=a4dc2a27-158a-43c2-8a39-8b565d197c59&token=YTRkYzJhMjctMTU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a4dc2a27-158a-43c2-8a39-8b565d197c59</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:21:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Repco Home Finance Ltd. has informed the BSE that a Board of Directors meeting is scheduled on 5th February 2026. The agenda includes the consideration and approval of un-audited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025, and the declaration of a second interim dividend for the financial year 2025-26. The record date for the dividend is 6th February 2026, and the trading window for dealing in the company&apos;s securities will remain closed for designated persons and their immediate relatives until 48 hours after the announcement of the results. This intimation is given in accordance with Regulations 29, 33, and 42 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Repco Home Finance Ltd. to consider and approve Q3 and nine months results for FY 2025-26</li><li>The company to declare a second interim dividend for the financial year 2025-26</li><li>The record date for the dividend is 6th February 2026</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the company&apos;s securities to remain closed for designated persons and their immediate relatives</li><li>Intimation given in accordance with Regulations 29, 33, and 42 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2abe5d1d-13c8-4c4e-aeb3-a4ed16ef053b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: REPCO HOME FINANCE LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[REPCOHOME] Repco Home Finance Ltd. to Consider and Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025, Declare Second Interim Dividend</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=REPCO+HOME+FINANCE+LTD.&title=Repco+Home+Finance+Ltd.+to+Consider+and+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025%2C+Declare+Second+Interim+Dividend&newsId=c0900fd1-c9fe-44b2-8f4f-5e641beca0e8&token=YzA5MDBmZDEtYzlm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c0900fd1-c9fe-44b2-8f4f-5e641beca0e8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:21:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Repco Home Finance Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 5th February, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results of the Company for the third quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The Company also plans to declare a second interim dividend for the financial year 2025-26. The record date for the dividend is 6th February, 2026. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company, which was closed from 1st January, 2026, will remain closed till 48 hours after the announcement of the un-audited financial results.</p><ul><li>Board meeting scheduled for 5th February, 2026, to consider and approve Q3 and nine months financial results for 2025</li><li>Company to declare second interim dividend for the financial year 2025-26</li><li>Record date for dividend payment set as 6th February, 2026</li><li>Trading window for securities dealing to remain closed till 48 hours after financial results announcement</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dcbd91a0-b001-465e-85ea-a3feba5c198b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: REPCO HOME FINANCE LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ALSL] Alacrity Securities Ltd to Approve Un-audited Financial Results for Q4 2025 in Board Meeting on Jan 29, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Alacrity+Securities+Ltd&title=Alacrity+Securities+Ltd+to+Approve+Un-audited+Financial+Results+for+Q4+2025+in+Board+Meeting+on+Jan+29%2C+2026&newsId=9d8abaa9-d4cf-4f90-b422-bb011f4489f1&token=OWQ4YWJhYTktZDRj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d8abaa9-d4cf-4f90-b422-bb011f4489f1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:21:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Alacrity Securities Ltd has informed BSE that a Board Meeting is scheduled on 29/01/2026 to consider and approve the Un-audited Financial Results (Standalone) for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee. The trading window for Directors, Designated Persons and their immediate relatives is closed from January 1, 2026.</p><ul><li>Alacrity Securities Ltd to approve Un-audited Financial Results for Q4 2025 in Board Meeting on Jan 29, 2026</li><li>Results reviewed by the Audit Committee</li><li>Trading window closed for Directors, Designated Persons and their immediate relatives from January 1, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b985f4c2-2570-4af9-a9ac-acbd52180f9b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Alacrity Securities Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SVGLOBAL] S V Global Mill Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=S+V+GLOBAL+MILL+LTD.&title=S+V+Global+Mill+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025&newsId=5122f880-174d-4cea-8d50-9de3efaa0550&token=NTEyMmY4ODAtMTc0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5122f880-174d-4cea-8d50-9de3efaa0550</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:21:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>S V Global Mill Ltd has informed the BSE that its Board of Directors will meet on 5th February 2026 to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The meeting will also discuss any other business with the permission of the Chair. The company&apos;s trading window will remain closed from 1st January 2026 and will open after 48 hours of the declaration of Un-Audited financial results on 5th February 2026.</p><ul><li>S V Global Mill Ltd to consider and approve un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025</li><li>The meeting will also discuss any other business with the permission of the Chair</li><li>The company&apos;s trading window will remain closed from 1st January 2026 and will open after 48 hours of the declaration of Un-Audited financial results on 5th February 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1dbe9965-f55e-4f39-bfbd-3f6472a8bf0a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: S V GLOBAL MILL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NRBBEARING] NRB Bearings Ltd: Harshbeena Sahney Zaveri Creates Pledge of 80,00,000 Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NRB+BEARINGS+LTD.&title=NRB+Bearings+Ltd%3A+Harshbeena+Sahney+Zaveri+Creates+Pledge+of+80%2C00%2C000+Equity+Shares&newsId=0afc103f-2a6e-4648-9880-20e7b32eae05&token=MGFmYzEwM2YtMmE2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0afc103f-2a6e-4648-9880-20e7b32eae05</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:04:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Pledge</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Exchange has received a disclosure under Regulation 31(1) and 31(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011 on January 23, 2026. Harshbeena Sahney Zaveri has created a pledge of 80,00,000 Equity Shares of NRB Bearings Limited on January 21, 2026. This move is seen as a prudent measure to maintain a buffer with the lender amid recent volatility in the stock market.</p><ul><li>Harshbeena Sahney Zaveri creates pledge of 80,00,000 Equity Shares</li><li>Pledge created on January 21, 2026</li><li>Move seen as prudent amid recent volatility in the stock market</li><li>Tata Capital is the lender</li><li>Promoters maintain much more than the required buffer with the lender</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/A4B6BD48_0EB5_4B98_816C_0EF1D4981E07_112635.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NRB BEARINGS LTD. | Category: Pledge</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHIVAMILLS] Shiva Mills Ltd to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 &amp; Quarter Ended 31.12.2025 on 05/02/2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shiva+Mills+Ltd&title=Shiva+Mills+Ltd+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+%26+Quarter+Ended+31.12.2025+on+05%2F02%2F2026&newsId=3b6fadf8-c9ed-4b25-a731-88ceeb238427&token=M2I2ZmFkZjgtYzll</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b6fadf8-c9ed-4b25-a731-88ceeb238427</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shiva Mills Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 05 February 2026 to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31 December 2025. The meeting is scheduled in accordance with Regulation 29 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The company had previously communicated that the trading window will remain closed from 1 January 2026 to 7 February 2026 (both days inclusive) after the declaration of the Unaudited Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Shiva Mills Ltd to approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 &amp; quarter ended 31.12.2025 on 05/02/2026</li><li>Meeting of the Board of Directors scheduled on 05 February 2026</li><li>Trading window to remain closed from 1 January 2026 to 7 February 2026</li><li>Financial Results relate to the quarter and nine months ended 31 December 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/30b34712-0abc-4479-b16f-4a68427ecf58.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shiva Mills Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RUSTOMJEE] Keystone Realtors Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Month Results for 2025 in February 2026 Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Keystone+Realtors+Ltd&title=Keystone+Realtors+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Month+Results+for+2025+in+February+2026+Board+Meeting&newsId=18757415-cb3d-4ffb-9d88-7afd6f768719&token=MTg3NTc0MTUtY2Iz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18757415-cb3d-4ffb-9d88-7afd6f768719</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 05:51:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Keystone Realtors Ltd, a company listed on the BSE, has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 4, 2026. The agenda of the meeting includes the consideration and approval of the unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Statements / Results of the Company for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. This meeting is in compliance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The announcement also states that the meeting&apos;s details will be uploaded on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Keystone Realtors Ltd to hold a Board Meeting on February 4, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Statements / Results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>The meeting is in compliance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>The meeting&apos;s details will be uploaded on the company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/adf363e0-4123-4ed3-8102-0f96dd0f45c5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Keystone Realtors Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INCON] Incon Engineers Ltd to Approve Q4 Financial Results on Feb 14, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INCON+ENGINEERS+LTD.&title=Incon+Engineers+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+Financial+Results+on+Feb+14%2C+2026&newsId=cbf27131-f7c7-45f4-b45d-3789de2951e6&token=Y2JmMjcxMzEtZjdj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cbf27131-f7c7-45f4-b45d-3789de2951e6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 05:40:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Incon Engineers Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 14, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter ended 31st December, 2025. The company has also informed that in accordance with the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, the trading window will remain closed and will re-open after 48 hours of the declaration of the Unaudited Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Incon Engineers Ltd to consider and approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q4 2025</li><li>Trading window to remain closed until 48 hours after results declaration</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cfbf5b25-6fc0-487c-a503-cd3a90a8109e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INCON ENGINEERS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BKMINDST] BKM Industries Ltd.: Monitoring Committee Meeting Outcome and NCLT Order Rectification</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BKM+Industries+Ltd&title=BKM+Industries+Ltd.%3A+Monitoring+Committee+Meeting+Outcome+and+NCLT+Order+Rectification&newsId=6743ea3c-31f4-4d06-b848-93a5c8ac9bc1&token=Njc0M2VhM2MtMzFm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6743ea3c-31f4-4d06-b848-93a5c8ac9bc1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 05:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>BKM Industries Ltd. has announced the outcome of a Monitoring Committee meeting held on 20th January 2026, in accordance with the order passed by the Hon&apos;ble NCLT on 14th November 2025. The company has also rectified a previous order dated 27th March 2025. The meeting, which commenced at 4:00 PM and concluded at 4:30 PM, resulted in the enclosure of the NCLT order dated 14th November 2025 and the final corrective order dated 4th December 2025 for reference. The company has requested that the intimation be taken on record and acknowledged.</p><ul><li>Outcome of Monitoring Committee meeting held on 20th January 2026</li><li>Rectification of NCLT order dated 27th March 2025</li><li>Enclosure of NCLT order dated 14th November 2025 and final corrective order dated 4th December 2025</li><li>Request to record and acknowledge the intimation</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b0a56d28-8b3c-4fdd-bbaa-87718e079f42.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BKM Industries Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>