<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:44:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[CAMLINFINE] Camlin Fine Sciences Ltd: Release of Pledge of 30,00,000 Equity Shares by Ashish Subhash Dandekar</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CAMLIN+FINE+SCIENCES+LTD.&title=Camlin+Fine+Sciences+Ltd%3A+Release+of+Pledge+of+30%2C00%2C000+Equity+Shares+by+Ashish+Subhash+Dandekar&newsId=d9c850d6-334c-4e31-984f-12f84e73fa94&token=ZDljODUwZDYtMzM0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d9c850d6-334c-4e31-984f-12f84e73fa94</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:44:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Pledge</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Exchange has received a disclosure under Regulation 31(1) and 31(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011 from Ashish Subhash Dandekar. The disclosure is in compliance with the SEBI SAST Regulations as amended, relating to the release of pledge of 30,00,000 Equity Shares of Camlin Fine Sciences Ltd. The release of pledge was due to the pledge margin exceeding the required security cover at Aditya Birla Finance Ltd.</p><ul><li>Ashish Subhash Dandekar releases pledge of 30,00,000 Equity Shares of Camlin Fine Sciences Ltd.</li><li>The release of pledge was due to the pledge margin exceeding the required security cover at Aditya Birla Finance Ltd.</li><li>The disclosure is in compliance with the SEBI SAST Regulations as amended.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/78DA09E0_5F25_4CF3_9976_32BC090C6D6B_101239.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CAMLIN FINE SCIENCES LTD. | Category: Pledge</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUZLON] Suzlon Energy Faces Rs.9.60 Crores Penalty from Principal Commissioner of Customs, Chennai</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SUZLON+ENERGY+LTD.&title=Suzlon+Energy+Faces+Rs.9.60+Crores+Penalty+from+Principal+Commissioner+of+Customs%2C+Chennai&newsId=60b30627-02f3-4de1-920f-b70381fd8e73&token=NjBiMzA2MjctMDJm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60b30627-02f3-4de1-920f-b70381fd8e73</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Suzlon Energy Ltd. has received an order from the Principal Commissioner of Customs, Chennai, imposing a penalty of Rs.9.60 Crores on Suzlon Global Services Limited, which has since been merged with Suzlon Energy Limited. The penalty is due to an alleged short payment of IGST. The company plans to appeal the decision. This update is in accordance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Suzlon Energy Ltd. has been levied a penalty of Rs.9.60 Crores by the Principal Commissioner of Customs, Chennai.</li><li>The penalty is a result of an alleged short payment of IGST by Suzlon Global Services Limited.</li><li>Suzlon Global Services Limited has since been merged with Suzlon Energy Limited.</li><li>The company plans to appeal the decision.</li><li>This update is in accordance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b0b10e59-d63e-43f3-b7d7-79207c5462f8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SUZLON ENERGY LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KPIGREEN] KPI Green Energy Completes 92.4 MW Wind Power Project for Ayana Renewable Power Four</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KPI+Green+Energy+Ltd&title=KPI+Green+Energy+Completes+92.4+MW+Wind+Power+Project+for+Ayana+Renewable+Power+Four&newsId=69f6e0c3-9ee6-42d9-9d1b-6a3e70628f23&token=NjlmNmUwYzMtOWVl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69f6e0c3-9ee6-42d9-9d1b-6a3e70628f23</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:23:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>KPI Green Energy Limited has successfully completed a 92.4 MW wind power project for Ayana Renewable Power Four at Nakhatrana, Bhuj, Gujarat. The project includes 28 wind turbine generators (WTGs), and KPI Green Energy Limited has completed all works under its scope, including Balance of Plant (BOP), Power Substation (PSS), EHV transmission line, and erection and installation of the WTGs. The project has received the requisite CEA approval, reflecting the company&apos;s execution capabilities in delivering large-scale and complex renewable energy infrastructure projects. This completion contributes to India’s clean energy transition and strengthens the country’s renewable power capacity.</p><ul><li>KPI Green Energy Limited completes 92.4 MW wind power project for Ayana Renewable Power Four</li><li>Project located at Nakhatrana, Bhuj, Gujarat</li><li>Includes 28 wind turbine generators (WTGs)</li><li>Completed all works under its scope, including Balance of Plant (BOP), Power Substation (PSS), EHV transmission line, and erection and installation of the WTGs</li><li>Project received requisite CEA approval, reflecting company’s execution capabilities in delivering large-scale and complex renewable energy infrastructure projects</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a0505133-da92-4842-a4b2-912f972e9cfc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KPI Green Energy Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BLBLIMITED] BLB Ltd Assures Compliance with SEBI Regulations, No Price Sensitive Information Disclosed</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BLB+LTD.&title=BLB+Ltd+Assures+Compliance+with+SEBI+Regulations%2C+No+Price+Sensitive+Information+Disclosed&newsId=d67de731-b2d3-42ca-ab1d-373a3fde7a37&token=ZDY3ZGU3MzEtYjJk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d67de731-b2d3-42ca-ab1d-373a3fde7a37</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:10:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>BLB Ltd, in response to an email regarding price movement clarification, stated that they are in compliance with SEBI (LODR) Regulations. The company has been promptly informing the Stock Exchanges on all material events and information. There is no undisclosed/price sensitive information or any impending announcement/corporate action pending. The company will continue to promptly inform the Exchanges of all material events/information/actions as required under SEBI (LODR) Regulations 2015.</p><ul><li>BLB Ltd confirms compliance with SEBI (LODR) Regulations</li><li>No undisclosed/price sensitive information or impending announcements</li><li>Company will continue to promptly inform Exchanges of material events/information/actions</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/10d24899-91dd-4fc7-9c3d-c6acc3504c52.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BLB LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AURIONPRO] Aurionpro Solutions and CBC Sri Lanka go-live with modern cash management platform for corporate banking growth</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AURIONPRO+SOLUTIONS+LTD.&title=Aurionpro+Solutions+and+CBC+Sri+Lanka+go-live+with+modern+cash+management+platform+for+corporate+banking+growth&newsId=93576bbe-bb16-4bfe-b662-54235f2b3863&token=OTM1NzZiYmUtYmIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93576bbe-bb16-4bfe-b662-54235f2b3863</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:09:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Aurionpro Solutions Limited, a global leader in banking technology, has successfully implemented its next-generation cash management platform, iCashpro, at Commercial Bank of Ceylon (CBC), Sri Lanka. This go-live marks a significant milestone in CBC’s digital transformation journey, strengthening its corporate and institutional banking capabilities. The partnership has seen the implementation of Aurionpro’s payments and portals stack within the iCashpro platform, setting the foundation for a comprehensive modernization of the bank’s cash management stack.</p><ul><li>Aurionpro Solutions implements its next-generation cash management platform, iCashpro, at Commercial Bank of Ceylon (CBC), Sri Lanka.</li><li>The go-live marks a significant milestone in CBC’s digital transformation journey, strengthening its corporate and institutional banking capabilities.</li><li>The partnership has seen the implementation of Aurionpro’s payments and portals stack within the iCashpro platform.</li><li>Future phases will extend to liquidity management, post-dated cheque (PDC) reporting, and virtual account management.</li><li>The deployment reinforces CBC’s commitment to innovation and customer-centricity as it continues to lead Sri Lanka’s banking sector in digital capability and excellence.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4c9ea06a-57e2-47fd-b35f-3f46d1d806d3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AURIONPRO SOLUTIONS LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HCLTECH] HCLTech Unveils VisionX 2.0, a Next-Gen Multi-Modal AI Edge Platform with NVIDIA</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HCL+TECHNOLOGIES+LTD.&title=HCLTech+Unveils+VisionX+2.0%2C+a+Next-Gen+Multi-Modal+AI+Edge+Platform+with+NVIDIA&newsId=ad6837e9-3011-472b-9495-5427091e58a9&token=YWQ2ODM3ZTktMzAx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad6837e9-3011-472b-9495-5427091e58a9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>HCL Technologies Ltd, a leading global technology company, has unveiled VisionX 2.0, an upgraded version of its multi-modal AI edge platform. This platform delivers real-time intelligence, enhanced safety, and operational efficiency at scale for mission-critical industrial environments. It harnesses the NVIDIA physical AI computing stack, including NVIDIA Blueprint for video search and summarization (VSS), NVIDIA DeepStream, NVIDIA Cosmos Reason VLM, and NVIDIA TAO for post-training vision models for unparalleled performance. VisionX 2.0 is purpose-built for demanding industrial use cases and introduces several innovations such as on-prem edge AI performance, multi-modal AloT engine, VSS event reviewer, zero-trust edge security, and seamless integration.</p><ul><li>HCLTech unveils VisionX 2.0, a next-gen multi-modal AI edge platform</li><li>Platform delivers real-time intelligence, enhanced safety, and operational efficiency</li><li>Harnesses NVIDIA physical AI computing stack for unparalleled performance</li><li>Introduces several innovations for demanding industrial use cases</li><li>Purpose-built for zero-trust edge security and seamless integration</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8bfbdff0-1579-4fd2-bb78-05caa0ed1b39.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HCL TECHNOLOGIES LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NOVARTIND] Acquirers Announce Open Offer for 26% Stake in Novartis India Ltd at INR 860.64 Per Share</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NOVARTIS+INDIA+LTD.&title=Acquirers+Announce+Open+Offer+for+26%25+Stake+in+Novartis+India+Ltd+at+INR+860.64+Per+Share&newsId=5b04622c-670a-41bc-8d84-9b6011561966&token=NWIwNDYyMmMtNjcw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b04622c-670a-41bc-8d84-9b6011561966</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Axis Capital Limited has submitted a public announcement for an open offer to acquire up to 64,19,608 fully paid-up equity shares of Novartis India Ltd, representing 26% of the voting share capital, at a price of INR 860.64 per share. The acquirers are WaveRise Investments Limited, ChrysCapital Fund X, and Two Infinity Partners. The offer is being made in compliance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. The offer price is determined in accordance with Regulations 8(1) and 8(2) of the SEBI (SAST) Regulations and may be revised. The offer is a triggered offer and not subject to any minimum level of acceptance or a competing offer.</p><ul><li>Acquirers announce open offer for 26% stake in Novartis India Ltd</li><li>Offer price set at INR 860.64 per share</li><li>Offer made in compliance with SEBI (SAST) Regulations, 2011</li><li>Not subject to minimum level of acceptance or competing offer</li><li>Determined in accordance with Regulations 8(1) and 8(2) of the SEBI (SAST) Regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/D9D631A2-1D59-47FA-94FD-3D99E54F2948-075935.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NOVARTIS INDIA LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NOVARTIND] Novartis India Ltd Receives Open Offer from Axis Capital Limited for 26% Stake</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NOVARTIS+INDIA+LTD.&title=Novartis+India+Ltd+Receives+Open+Offer+from+Axis+Capital+Limited+for+26%25+Stake&newsId=2fb64d5c-cc20-4416-94b3-9b754b46aa37&token=MmZiNjRkNWMtY2My</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2fb64d5c-cc20-4416-94b3-9b754b46aa37</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Novartis India Limited has received a public announcement from Axis Capital Limited, acting on behalf of WaveRise Investments Limited, ChrysCapital Fund X, Two Infinity Partners, ChrysCapital X, LLC, and OceanEdge Investments Limited. These entities, collectively referred to as the Acquirers, are planning to acquire up to 64,19,608 fully paid-up equity shares, representing 26% of the Voting Share Capital, from the Public Shareholders of Novartis India Limited. The offer is priced at INR 860.64 per Equity Share, amounting to a total consideration of INR 552,49,71,429.12. The offer is being made in compliance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</p><ul><li>Novartis India Limited has received a public announcement from Axis Capital Limited for an open offer.</li><li>The open offer is from WaveRise Investments Limited, ChrysCapital Fund X, Two Infinity Partners, ChrysCapital X, LLC, and OceanEdge Investments Limited.</li><li>The Acquirers aim to acquire up to 26% of the Voting Share Capital of Novartis India Limited.</li><li>The offer price is INR 860.64 per Equity Share, amounting to a total consideration of INR 552,49,71,429.12.</li><li>The offer is being made in compliance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/825bf5b9-b420-48a5-bb18-96245bde7684.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NOVARTIS INDIA LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NOVARTIND] Novartis AG to Sell 70.68% Stake in Novartis India Ltd to WaveRise Investments, ChrysCapital and Two Infinity Partners</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NOVARTIS+INDIA+LTD.&title=Novartis+AG+to+Sell+70.68%25+Stake+in+Novartis+India+Ltd+to+WaveRise+Investments%2C+ChrysCapital+and+Two+Infinity+Partners&newsId=8e134a61-b9fa-4074-bc2d-b5302d78dbb4&token=OGUxMzRhNjEtYjlm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8e134a61-b9fa-4074-bc2d-b5302d78dbb4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Novartis AG, the promoter of Novartis India Ltd, has entered into an agreement to sell 1,74,50,680 fully paid-up equity shares, representing 70.68% of the paid-up equity share capital, to WaveRise Investments Limited, ChrysCapital Fund X and Two Infinity Partners. The transaction is expected to be completed by February 19, 2026. Post-completion, Novartis AG will cease to be a &apos;Promoter&apos; of the company, and the acquirers will acquire control and be classified as the &apos;Promoter&apos;. The company has agreed to comply with certain customary interim obligations and post-closing obligations.</p><ul><li>Novartis AG to sell 70.68% stake in Novartis India Ltd to WaveRise Investments, ChrysCapital and Two Infinity Partners</li><li>Transaction value not disclosed</li><li>Transaction expected to be completed by February 19, 2026</li><li>Novartis AG to cease to be a &apos;Promoter&apos; post-completion</li><li>Acquirers to acquire control and be classified as &apos;Promoter&apos; post-completion</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/587cf80a-af2c-4245-9ed3-17ac84c70970.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NOVARTIS INDIA LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NTPCGREEN] NTPC Green Energy Declares Commercial Operation of 165 MW from Khavda-II Solar PV Project</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NTPC+Green+Energy+Ltd&title=NTPC+Green+Energy+Declares+Commercial+Operation+of+165+MW+from+Khavda-II+Solar+PV+Project&newsId=ad79c253-c11a-43a9-9602-11ecadbf876a&token=YWQ3OWMyNTMtYzEx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad79c253-c11a-43a9-9602-11ecadbf876a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:01:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>NTPC Green Energy Limited, a subsidiary of NTPC Limited, has declared the commercial operation of the second part capacity of 165 MW out of 1200 MW Khavda-II Solar PV Project of NTPC Renewable Energy Limited. This project is located in Gujarat. The commercial capacity of NTPC Green Energy Limited Group now stands at 8827.68 MW, with the addition of this capacity, the total installed capacity of the NTPC Green Energy Limited Group has increased to 8992.68 MW.</p><ul><li>NTPC Green Energy Limited has declared the commercial operation of 165 MW from the Khavda-II Solar PV Project.</li><li>The Khavda-II Solar PV Project is a 1200 MW project located in Gujarat.</li><li>NTPC Renewable Energy Limited, a wholly owned subsidiary of NTPC Green Energy Limited, is the parent company of the project.</li><li>The commercial capacity of NTPC Green Energy Limited Group is now 8827.68 MW.</li><li>The total installed capacity of the NTPC Green Energy Limited Group has increased to 8992.68 MW with the addition of this capacity.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7166306e-7855-4d34-b0c9-d6c0b5317fd3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NTPC Green Energy Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>