<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 09:16:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[RBGUPTA] Aarcon Facilities Ltd to Consider Approving Q4 Results, Opening New Bank Account, and Appointing Project Manager</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=R.B.GUPTA+FINANCIALS+LTD.&title=Aarcon+Facilities+Ltd+to+Consider+Approving+Q4+Results%2C+Opening+New+Bank+Account%2C+and+Appointing+Project+Manager&newsId=217aa963-5a19-48d5-bd2f-5c83a4158747&token=MjE3YWE5NjMtNWEx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">217aa963-5a19-48d5-bd2f-5c83a4158747</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 07:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Aarcon Facilities Ltd has announced a board meeting on 20th January 2026, to consider and approve various business transactions. The agenda includes the adoption of un-audited financial results for the quarter ended 31/12/2025, opening a new bank account, approval of the Aarcon Abhayanand Residential Project at RS No. 95/pond 96/p at Karelibaug, Vadodara, and appointment of a Project Manager for necessary government work related to the project. Any other matter with the permission of the chair will also be discussed.</p><ul><li>Aarcon Facilities Ltd to consider approving Q4 results for 2025</li><li>New bank account opening by Aarcon Facilities Ltd</li><li>Approval of Aarcon Abhayanand Residential Project at Karelibaug, Vadodara</li><li>Appointment of Project Manager for Aarcon Abhayanand Residential Project</li><li>Discussion of any other matter with the permission of the chair</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/932ce343-ba7b-4214-97fc-050925f8cbe2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: R.B.GUPTA FINANCIALS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WAAREERTL] Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on Jan 14, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Waaree+Renewable+Technologies+Ltd&title=Waaree+Renewable+Technologies+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+Jan+14%2C+2026&newsId=24b5efb4-9d56-4443-bca3-53802fdc6c7e&token=MjRiNWVmYjQtOWQ1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24b5efb4-9d56-4443-bca3-53802fdc6c7e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 07:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd has announced a Board of Directors meeting on January 14, 2026. The agenda includes approval and recording of the un-audited standalone financial results under Indian Accounting Standards (Ind AS) for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. Additionally, the Board will approve and record the un-audited consolidated financial results of the Company under Ind AS for the same period.</p><ul><li>Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd has scheduled a Board of Directors meeting on January 14, 2026</li><li>The meeting will approve and record the un-audited standalone financial results under Ind AS for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>The meeting will also approve and record the un-audited consolidated financial results of the Company under Ind AS for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dbade2bb-1141-4043-9825-711fba0ea6a2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RELTD] Ravindra Energy Ltd to Approve Q3 Financial Results on January 15, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ravindra+Energy+Ltd&title=Ravindra+Energy+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+Financial+Results+on+January+15%2C+2026&newsId=4db3544b-5b4b-4375-b52a-2fb7b40cb49a&token=NGRiMzU0NGItNWI0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4db3544b-5b4b-4375-b52a-2fb7b40cb49a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:54:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ravindra Energy Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 15, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the third quarter ended on December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the company will remain closed for designated persons, designated employees, and all other applicable persons covered under the code from the end of the third quarter till 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results to the stock exchanges.</p><ul><li>Ravindra Energy Ltd to consider and approve Q3 financial results on January 15, 2026</li><li>Trading window to remain closed for designated persons, designated employees, and all other applicable persons from the end of the Q3 till 48 hours after the declaration of financial results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2d3a0f67-e5e1-4d31-a483-dfc519c268a7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ravindra Energy Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[QUANTDIA] Quantum Digital Vision India Ltd. to Convene Extra-Ordinary General Meeting on 5th February, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=QUANTUM+DIGITAL+VISION+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Quantum+Digital+Vision+India+Ltd.+to+Convene+Extra-Ordinary+General+Meeting+on+5th+February%2C+2026&newsId=deda21bf-0d49-4503-9056-21bd09d89e6a&token=ZGVkYTIxYmYtMGQ0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">deda21bf-0d49-4503-9056-21bd09d89e6a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:47:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Quantum Digital Vision India Ltd. has considered the convening of an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) on 5th February, 2026. The meeting was held on 10th January, 2026 and commenced at 11:00 a.m., concluding at 11:55 a.m. Mrs. Siddhi Singhania (Nee Dhandharia) has been appointed as the Scrutinizer for scrutinising the voting process at the EGM.</p><ul><li>Quantum Digital Vision India Ltd. to convene an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting on 5th February, 2026</li><li>The meeting was held on 10th January, 2026</li><li>Mrs. Siddhi Singhania (Nee Dhandharia) appointed as the Scrutinizer for the voting process</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6958c88a-05b3-453b-af6a-14218d67525e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: QUANTUM DIGITAL VISION (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JSWENERGY] JSW Energy Ltd Faces Material Litigation from Maharashtra Electricity Regulatory Commission Order</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JSW+Energy+Ltd&title=JSW+Energy+Ltd+Faces+Material+Litigation+from+Maharashtra+Electricity+Regulatory+Commission+Order&newsId=352e0d2d-5ff0-416b-817a-7a1512bb7cca&token=MzUyZTBkMmQtNWZm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">352e0d2d-5ff0-416b-817a-7a1512bb7cca</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:36:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>JSW Energy Ltd has been served with a copy of the appeal filed by Maharashtra State Electricity Distribution Company Limited (MSEDCL) against the Final Combined Order passed by the Maharashtra Electricity Regulatory Commission (MERC) on 24th December 2025. The MERC Order had rejected MSEDCL&apos;s petition seeking to quash the invoices raised by JSW Energy and allowed the Company’s petition. This update comes after the Company&apos;s earlier disclosure on 25th December 2025, informing about the MERC Order.</p><ul><li>JSW Energy Ltd served with an appeal by MSEDCL against MERC Order</li><li>MERC Order rejected MSEDCL&apos;s petition and allowed JSW Energy&apos;s petition</li><li>Appeal filed on 9th January 2026</li><li>Maharashtra Electricity Regulatory Commission Order dated 24th December 2025</li><li>JSW Energy&apos;s invoices raised controversy</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/21b49ca2-bd9d-4537-92da-8b2e227e4018.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JSW Energy Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[POOJA] Poojawestern Metaliks Subsidiary Receives $103,603.57 Overseas Purchase Order</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Poojawestern+Metaliks+Ltd&title=Poojawestern+Metaliks+Subsidiary+Receives+%24103%2C603.57+Overseas+Purchase+Order&newsId=719bb25e-1c3c-4548-bf20-47d618291377&token=NzE5YmIyNWUtMWMz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">719bb25e-1c3c-4548-bf20-47d618291377</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Poojawestern Metaliks Limited has announced that its Wholly Owned Subsidiary Company, Sierra Metal Industries Private Limited, has received a purchase order worth USD 1,03,603.57 (approximately INR Rs 9.37 million) from B&amp;K LLC (Mueller Comercial De Mexico) for the supply of Brass Sanitary Parts. This order is expected to strengthen the company&apos;s customer base and contribute positively to its profitability. The payment will be executed within 75 days from the issuance of bill of lading, and the order shall be shipped latest by April 23, 2026.</p><ul><li>Poojawestern Metaliks&apos; subsidiary received a purchase order worth USD 1,03,603.57 from B&amp;K LLC (Mueller Comercial De Mexico)</li><li>The order is for the supply of Brass Sanitary Parts</li><li>The payment will be executed within 75 days from the issuance of bill of lading</li><li>The order is expected to strengthen the company&apos;s customer base and contribute positively to its profitability</li><li>The order shall be shipped latest by April 23, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b622a6c1-2463-4e66-b54a-297422e44c7a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Poojawestern Metaliks Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VPRPL] Promoters of Vishnu Prakash R Punglia Ltd Infuse ₹200 Crore Received from Equity Divestment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vishnu+Prakash+R+Punglia+Ltd&title=Promoters+of+Vishnu+Prakash+R+Punglia+Ltd+Infuse+%E2%82%B9200+Crore+Received+from+Equity+Divestment&newsId=5ca54b7b-2d6a-4c5f-afb9-46547cdc23d8&token=NWNhNTRiN2ItMmQ2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ca54b7b-2d6a-4c5f-afb9-46547cdc23d8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vishnu Prakash R Punglia Ltd, a leading EPC company, announced that its promoters have infused ₹200 crore received from a 19.18% equity divestment as an interest-free loan. This step reflects the promoters’ continued confidence in the company’s fundamentals, long-term prospects, and growth strategy. The divestment and subsequent capital infusion are part of a prudent capital management initiative aimed at enhancing liquidity, strengthening the company’s financial position, and supporting long-term strategic and growth objectives. The promoters remain fully aligned with the company’s long-term vision, governance framework, and growth plans, and continue to be actively involved in supporting the company’s operations and future expansion. Vishnu Prakash R Punglia Limited maintains a healthy and robust order book and is focused on timely execution, operational efficiency, financial discipline, and sustainable value creation.</p><ul><li>Promoters of Vishnu Prakash R Punglia Ltd have divested approximately 19.18% of the company’s equity, raising ₹200 crore.</li><li>The entire proceeds from the divestment have been infused into the company by the promoters in the form of an interest-free loan.</li><li>This move reflects the promoters’ confidence in the company’s fundamentals, long-term prospects, and growth strategy.</li><li>The divestment and capital infusion are part of a prudent capital management initiative to enhance liquidity and support long-term growth.</li><li>Promoters remain fully committed to the company’s vision, governance framework, and growth plans.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dacdfbda-2c76-4a94-aa60-c45dcb07308f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vishnu Prakash R Punglia Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JRELTD] Eraaya Lifespaces Secures Judicial Protection against False Claims by Mr. Robin Raina</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Justride+Enterprises+Ltd&title=Eraaya+Lifespaces+Secures+Judicial+Protection+against+False+Claims+by+Mr.+Robin+Raina&newsId=74ccfe05-7a45-4d6e-ad1e-b2f6b3ed644c&token=NzRjY2ZlMDUtN2E0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74ccfe05-7a45-4d6e-ad1e-b2f6b3ed644c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:21:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Eraaya Lifespaces Limited has secured comprehensive judicial protection against false claims and frivolous pleas filed by Mr. Robin Raina based on a forged document. The Hon’ble District Judge (Commercial Court), Delhi, has passed an order rejecting the Arbitration Plea filed by Mr. Raina and granting several interim reliefs in favor of the Company and its global subsidiaries operating under Ebix Inc. The litigation between the Company and Mr. Raina emanates from a disputed document, which the Company has consistently maintained to be forged and fabricated. The Hon’ble Court has restrained and injuncted Mr. Raina from seeking or pursuing any reliefs, remedies, or proceedings of any nature founded upon or arising out of the disputed document.</p><ul><li>Eraaya Lifespaces Limited secures comprehensive judicial protection against false claims and frivolous pleas filed by Mr. Robin Raina based on a forged document.</li><li>The Hon’ble District Judge (Commercial Court), Delhi, has passed an order rejecting the Arbitration Plea filed by Mr. Raina and granting several interim reliefs in favor of the Company and its global subsidiaries operating under Ebix Inc.</li><li>The disputed document, which the Company has consistently maintained to be forged and fabricated, is the basis of the litigation between the Company and Mr. Raina.</li><li>The Hon’ble Court has restrained and injuncted Mr. Raina from seeking or pursuing any reliefs, remedies, or proceedings of any nature founded upon or arising out of the disputed document.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b6c73f96-026e-48c8-88ca-ddda04e959c1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Justride Enterprises Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SANPA] Sangal Papers Ltd Confirms Status of Re-lodgement Requests for Physical Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SANGAL+PAPERS+LTD.&title=Sangal+Papers+Ltd+Confirms+Status+of+Re-lodgement+Requests+for+Physical+Shares&newsId=5e9ab1e2-6999-4824-84db-815a8e997345&token=NWU5YWIxZTItNjk5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5e9ab1e2-6999-4824-84db-815a8e997345</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:11:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sangal Papers Ltd has confirmed the status of re-lodgement requests for physical shares. The company received a report from their Registrar and Transfer Agent, MAS Services Limited, on re-lodgement of transfer requests of physical shares, dated 07/01/2026, which was received on 09/01/2026. The confirmation is for the period from December 1, 2025, to December 31, 2025. The company has processed a certain number of requests during this period.</p><ul><li>Sangal Papers Ltd confirms the status of re-lodgement requests for physical shares.</li><li>Report received from Registrar and Transfer Agent MAS Services Limited on re-lodgement of transfer requests.</li><li>Period for re-lodgement requests confirmation: December 1, 2025, to December 31, 2025.</li><li>Number of requests received and processed during the mentioned period.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4769f41e-331d-4912-953d-29c9420f65ee.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SANGAL PAPERS LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZYDUSWELL] Zydus Wellness Ltd. Granted Ad-Interim Relief in GST Demand Case by Gujarat High Court</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ZYDUS+WELLNESS+LTD.-%24&title=Zydus+Wellness+Ltd.+Granted+Ad-Interim+Relief+in+GST+Demand+Case+by+Gujarat+High+Court&newsId=c456537b-7847-40e8-9ec8-ada1f417086a&token=YzQ1NjUzN2ItNzg0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c456537b-7847-40e8-9ec8-ada1f417086a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Zydus Wellness Ltd. has received an ad-interim relief from the Gujarat High Court in a writ petition filed by its subsidiary, Zydus Wellness Products Limited (ZWPL), against a GST demand of ₹ 56.33 crores. The demand was raised by The Directorate General of Goods and Services Tax Intelligence, Surat Zonal Unit (DGGI) under section 74(5) of the Central Goods and Services Tax Act, 2017. The period covered by the order relates to a pre-acquisition period prior to January 30, 2019, and hence the liability stands fully indemnified by Heinz Italia S.P.A. The matter was listed for hearing on January 9, 2026, and the court has granted ad-interim relief to ZWPL, restraining further proceedings in relation to the said order.</p><ul><li>Zydus Wellness Ltd. subsidiary, Zydus Wellness Products Limited (ZWPL), received an ad-interim relief from the Gujarat High Court in a writ petition.</li><li>The petition was filed against a GST demand of ₹ 56.33 crores raised by The Directorate General of Goods and Services Tax Intelligence, Surat Zonal Unit (DGGI).</li><li>The demand was raised under section 74(5) of the Central Goods and Services Tax Act, 2017 for the pre-acquisition period prior to January 30, 2019.</li><li>The liability stands fully indemnified by Heinz Italia S.P.A.</li><li>The Gujarat High Court restrained further proceedings in relation to the said order.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/055a1755-3d53-4901-bc21-0a488aa9708d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ZYDUS WELLNESS LTD.-$ | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>