<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 18:51:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[OLAELEC] Bombay High Court Stays Warrant Issued by District Consumer Commission Against Ola Electric Mobility</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ola+Electric+Mobility+Ltd&title=Bombay+High+Court+Stays+Warrant+Issued+by+District+Consumer+Commission+Against+Ola+Electric+Mobility&newsId=ef90a759-fac3-4df8-9371-76cc8e082290&token=ZWY5MGE3NTktZmFj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef90a759-fac3-4df8-9371-76cc8e082290</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:34:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ola Electric Mobility Limited has informed the exchange about a clarification on a news item appearing in the media. The Hon’ble High Court of Bombay at Goa has stayed the warrant issued by the District Consumer Commission, South Goa. The Court observed that the Commission exceeded its jurisdiction under the Consumer Protection Act in issuing the warrant. The Company has requested that due note be taken of the aforesaid factual legal position.</p><ul><li>Bombay High Court stays warrant issued by District Consumer Commission against Ola Electric Mobility</li><li>The warrant was issued by the District Consumer Commission, South Goa</li><li>The High Court observed that the Commission exceeded its jurisdiction under the Consumer Protection Act in issuing the warrant</li><li>Ola Electric Mobility has requested that due note be taken of the aforesaid factual legal position</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a775580c-7902-4c03-a247-5600171ebfde.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ola Electric Mobility Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ARYAVAN] Aryavan Enterprise Ltd to Consider Equity Shares Issuance in Board Meeting on 20/02/2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Aryavan+Enterprise+Ltd&title=Aryavan+Enterprise+Ltd+to+Consider+Equity+Shares+Issuance+in+Board+Meeting+on+20%2F02%2F2026&newsId=a6ed09a2-ea50-4d75-83c9-892b18fe0536&token=YTZlZDA5YTItZWE1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a6ed09a2-ea50-4d75-83c9-892b18fe0536</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Aryavan Enterprise Ltd has announced that a Board Meeting is scheduled on 20th February 2026 to consider a proposal for issuance of Equity Shares and Equity Warrants by way of a preferential allotment. This decision is in accordance with the SEBI (Issue of Capital and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2018 and the Companies Act, 2013. The trading window for dealing in the securities will be closed from 18th February 2026 till the end of 48 hours from the conclusion of the meeting for all connected persons and directors of the Company.</p><ul><li>Aryavan Enterprise Ltd to consider Equity Shares issuance in the Board Meeting on 20th February 2026.</li><li>The issuance is in accordance with the SEBI (Issue of Capital and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2018 and the Companies Act, 2013.</li><li>The trading window for dealing in the securities will be closed from 18th February 2026 till the end of 48 hours from the conclusion of the meeting.</li><li>The closure applies to all connected persons and directors of the Company.</li><li>The trading window is set to reopen on 23rd February 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/95cf536e-47ec-4ecf-aaed-dabd12c2d8bb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Aryavan Enterprise Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HCG] HealthCare Global Enterprises Ltd. to Hold Board Meeting on February 24, 2026, for Rights Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HealthCare+Global+Enterprises+Ltd&title=HealthCare+Global+Enterprises+Ltd.+to+Hold+Board+Meeting+on+February+24%2C+2026%2C+for+Rights+Issue&newsId=01537b8f-6abe-41b1-9ad7-80644d5f4a6f&token=MDE1MzdiOGYtNmFi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01537b8f-6abe-41b1-9ad7-80644d5f4a6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>HealthCare Global Enterprises Ltd. has informed the BSE that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on February 24, 2026. The meeting will consider and approve various matters, including the specific terms of a rights issue. The rights issue, decided by the Board on February 17, 2026, is for an amount not exceeding X 42,500 Lakhs (Rupees Forty Two Thousand and Five Hundred Lakhs). The Board will discuss and decide on the rights issue price, payment mechanism, rights entitlement ratio, record date, and timing, subject to the receipt of in-principle approval from the stock exchanges or other regulatory authorities.</p><ul><li>HealthCare Global Enterprises Ltd. to hold a Board meeting on February 24, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve various matters related to a rights issue</li><li>The rights issue is for an amount not exceeding X 42,500 Lakhs</li><li>The Board will discuss and decide on the rights issue price, payment mechanism, rights entitlement ratio, record date, and timing</li><li>The decision is subject to the receipt of in-principle approval from the stock exchanges or other regulatory authorities</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6f1ca910-b0b2-45e7-936c-ae80e9172a0d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HealthCare Global Enterprises Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ARTSONEN] Artson Ltd Receives Amendment of Purchase Order from Tata Projects Limited Worth Rs. 11.09 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ARTSON+ENGINEERING+LTD.&title=Artson+Ltd+Receives+Amendment+of+Purchase+Order+from+Tata+Projects+Limited+Worth+Rs.+11.09+Crores&newsId=f02b0cd0-a984-4064-8781-27f0d0754f3d&token=ZjAyYjBjZDAtYTk4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f02b0cd0-a984-4064-8781-27f0d0754f3d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Artson Ltd has received an amendment of purchase order from Tata Projects Limited (TPL) for a total amount of Rs. 11.09 Crores including taxes. This amount includes an enhanced value of Rs. 4.62 Crs. The original purchase order was for Rs. 6.47 Crs., which has now been increased. The order is for the supply of finished structures, and it is a domestic order awarded by a domestic entity. The order is to be executed within four months from 24th November 2025. TPL is the Promoter/Holding Company of Artson Ltd, making this a related party transaction in the ordinary course of business and at arm&apos;s length.</p><ul><li>Artson Ltd receives amendment of purchase order from Tata Projects Limited.</li><li>The amended order is worth Rs. 11.09 Crores including taxes.</li><li>The original purchase order was for Rs. 6.47 Crs., which has been enhanced by Rs. 4.62 Crs.</li><li>The order is for the supply of finished structures.</li><li>The transaction is a related party transaction.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1860f0d1-d1da-4e21-bd24-b4055a607b5e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ARTSON ENGINEERING LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JONJUA] Jonjua Overseas Ltd. Board Meeting on 20/02/2026 to Consider Rights Issue and Review Company Affairs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jonjua+Overseas+Ltd&title=Jonjua+Overseas+Ltd.+Board+Meeting+on+20%2F02%2F2026+to+Consider+Rights+Issue+and+Review+Company+Affairs&newsId=9fa53adf-19c5-43f7-9736-928736dc38ea&token=OWZhNTNhZGYtMTlj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9fa53adf-19c5-43f7-9736-928736dc38ea</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:01:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jonjua Overseas Ltd. has announced a Board Meeting scheduled on 20th February 2026, 04:30 PM. The agenda includes the consideration of subscribing to the Rights Issue of HSJONJUA INNOVATEAGRO PRIVATE LIMITED and reviewing the day-to-day affairs of the company. The meeting is in compliance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements), Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Jonjua Overseas Ltd. Board Meeting on 20th February 2026</li><li>Consideration of subscribing to the Rights Issue of HSJONJUA INNOVATEAGRO PRIVATE LIMITED</li><li>Review of day-to-day affairs of the company</li><li>Meeting in compliance with Securities and Exchange Board of India regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/05476120-4e6e-4f7d-a1df-95478a630c69.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jonjua Overseas Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CAPFIN] Capfin India Ltd. to Consider Equity Shares Issuance on Feb 20, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Capfin+India+Ltd&title=Capfin+India+Ltd.+to+Consider+Equity+Shares+Issuance+on+Feb+20%2C+2026&newsId=34ecb814-2586-4737-8572-aceb6f2eaef5&token=MzRlY2I4MTQtMjU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">34ecb814-2586-4737-8572-aceb6f2eaef5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Capfin India Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 20, 2026, to consider and evaluate a proposal for issuance of equity shares or any eligible securities through a preferential issue on a private placement basis or through any other permissible mode. The issuance is subject to regulatory/statutory approvals, including the approval of the members of the Company. The Company will also consider and approve the issuance of a Postal Ballot Notice for seeking shareholders’ approval on the aforesaid agenda item. The Trading Window for dealing in the securities of the Company for all Designated Persons and their immediate relatives will remain closed from February 17, 2026, and will re-open on expiry of forty-eight hours after the outcome of the Board meeting is published.</p><ul><li>Capfin India Ltd. to consider issuance of equity shares on February 20, 2026</li><li>Issuance to be on a private placement basis or through any other permissible mode</li><li>Subject to regulatory/statutory approvals, including members&apos; approval</li><li>Company to consider and approve the issuance of a Postal Ballot Notice</li><li>Trading Window for dealing in securities to remain closed from Feb 17, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/28f9ae87-4e60-44b9-bf4c-9d95798eeca4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Capfin India Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WMINIMT] Western Ministil Ltd Allots Convertible Warrants on Preferential Basis</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=WESTERN+MINISTIL+LTD.&title=Western+Ministil+Ltd+Allots+Convertible+Warrants+on+Preferential+Basis&newsId=8c273991-7b9c-4889-844a-824dde2772ee&token=OGMyNzM5OTEtN2I5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c273991-7b9c-4889-844a-824dde2772ee</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Western Ministil Limited, in a meeting held on February 17, 2026, approved the allotment of 4,68,562 Convertible Warrants on a preferential basis. The warrants were issued at a price of =10/- (Rupees Ten Only) per warrant, in line with the Special Resolution passed by the Members at the Extra-Ordinary General Meeting held on December 24, 2025, and the In-Principle Approval received from BSE Limited on February 02, 2026. The allottees include Himanshu Shah and Sheetal Jethaji Solanki, each receiving 2,34,281 warrants.</p><ul><li>Western Ministil Ltd approved the allotment of 4,68,562 Convertible Warrants on a preferential basis.</li><li>The warrants were issued at a price of =10/- (Rupees Ten Only) per warrant.</li><li>The allotment is in line with the Special Resolution passed by the Members at the Extra-Ordinary General Meeting held on December 24, 2025.</li><li>In-Principle Approval was received from BSE Limited on February 02, 2026.</li><li>Himanshu Shah and Sheetal Jethaji Solanki are the allottees, each receiving 2,34,281 warrants.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5fd83a65-7f94-4445-962d-285bdc759c73.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: WESTERN MINISTIL LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WMINIMT] Western Ministil Ltd Allots Convertible Warrants on Preferential Basis</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=WESTERN+MINISTIL+LTD.&title=Western+Ministil+Ltd+Allots+Convertible+Warrants+on+Preferential+Basis&newsId=c4684dc1-c9cb-4da4-b012-3e4aaa0f7592&token=YzQ2ODRkYzEtYzlj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4684dc1-c9cb-4da4-b012-3e4aaa0f7592</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Western Ministil Limited, in a meeting held on February 17, 2026, approved the allotment of 4,68,562 Convertible Warrants on a preferential basis. The warrants were issued at an issue price of =10/- (Rupees Ten Only) per warrant, in line with the Special Resolution passed by the Members at the Extra-Ordinary General Meeting held on December 24, 2025, and the In-Principle Approval received from BSE Limited on February 02, 2026. The allotment was made to two allottees: Himanshu Shah received 2,34,281 warrants and Sheetal Jethaji Solanki received the same number. This decision is now being reported to the stock exchange for record.</p><ul><li>Western Ministil Ltd approved the allotment of 4,68,562 Convertible Warrants on a preferential basis.</li><li>The warrants were issued at an issue price of =10/- (Rupees Ten Only) per warrant.</li><li>The allotment was made in accordance with the Special Resolution passed by the Members at the Extra-Ordinary General Meeting held on December 24, 2025.</li><li>BSE Limited had given In-Principle Approval on February 02, 2026.</li><li>The allotment was made to two allottees: Himanshu Shah and Sheetal Jethaji Solanki.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/59260fb4-b9e3-47a3-8a59-404042c38b58.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: WESTERN MINISTIL LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HIL] Birlanu Ltd Announces Resignation of Chief Procurement Officer, Mr. Sunit Kumar Dey</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HIL+LTD.&title=Birlanu+Ltd+Announces+Resignation+of+Chief+Procurement+Officer%2C+Mr.+Sunit+Kumar+Dey&newsId=a24983e8-5fe4-415b-a294-0c0e91ee8e01&token=YTI0OTgzZTgtNWZl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a24983e8-5fe4-415b-a294-0c0e91ee8e01</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 17:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Birlanu Ltd, formerly known as HIL Limited, has announced the resignation of its Chief Procurement Officer, Mr. Sunit Kumar Dey, due to personal reasons. Mr. Dey&apos;s last working day will be February 27, 2026, subject to the company&apos;s service rules. The relevant details of the resignation are available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Birlanu Ltd announces the resignation of its Chief Procurement Officer, Mr. Sunit Kumar Dey.</li><li>Mr. Dey&apos;s last working day will be February 27, 2026, subject to the company&apos;s service rules.</li><li>The resignation is due to personal reasons.</li><li>The relevant details of the resignation are available on the company&apos;s website.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5d481e2e-a52d-458a-911c-d96b08af2ca1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HIL LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AKZOINDIA] Akzo Nobel India Ltd Announces Resignation of HR Director, Ms. Neelima Kataria</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Akzo+Nobel+India+Limited&title=Akzo+Nobel+India+Ltd+Announces+Resignation+of+HR+Director%2C+Ms.+Neelima+Kataria&newsId=6ddabdf2-08bf-4b80-a2b9-7f6d3ea9be79&token=NmRkYWJkZjItMDhi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ddabdf2-08bf-4b80-a2b9-7f6d3ea9be79</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 16:27:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Akzo Nobel India Ltd has announced the resignation of its HR Director, Ms. Neelima Kataria, who has served the company for four years. She has tendered her resignation to pursue new professional opportunities. The management has accepted her resignation, and she will serve her notice period until May 6, 2026, ensuring a smooth transition.</p><ul><li>Ms. Neelima Kataria has resigned from her position as HR Director of Akzo Nobel India Ltd.</li><li>She has served the company for four years and will pursue new professional opportunities.</li><li>The management has accepted her resignation and she will serve her notice period until May 6, 2026.</li><li>She will ensure a smooth and responsible transition during her notice period.</li><li>Akzo Nobel India Ltd appreciates her contributions during her tenure.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e4ee7e71-9276-4bd8-b6d2-64451228906c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Akzo Nobel India Limited | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>