<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:27:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[KIRLPNU] Kirloskar Pneumatic Declares Interim Dividend of Rs. 3.50, Appoints New Managing Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KIRLOSKAR+PNEUMATIC+CO.LTD.&title=Kirloskar+Pneumatic+Declares+Interim+Dividend+of+Rs.+3.50%2C+Appoints+New+Managing+Director&newsId=d3529c7c-2c27-4ce6-8b61-c2ef5d636c93&token=ZDM1MjljN2MtMmMy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3529c7c-2c27-4ce6-8b61-c2ef5d636c93</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:27:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kirloskar Pneumatic Company Ltd has declared an interim dividend of Rs. 3.50 per equity share for the Financial Year 2025-26. The company has also appointed Mr. Aman Rahul Kirloskar as a Director and Managing Director, effective from April 1, 2026. Mr. Kirloskar is a part of the promoter group and has been instrumental in developing business and formulating strategies at Kirloskar Pneumatic. He has been elevated to various positions within the company and has led the ACR SBU to achieve its highest ever sales since inception.</p><ul><li>Kirloskar Pneumatic declares an interim dividend of Rs. 3.50 per equity share for the Financial Year 2025-26.</li><li>Mr. Aman Rahul Kirloskar appointed as a Director and Managing Director, effective from April 1, 2026.</li><li>Mr. Kirloskar is a part of the promoter group and has a significant role in the company&apos;s business development and strategy formulation.</li><li>He has been elevated to various positions within the company and has led the ACR SBU to achieve its highest ever sales since inception.</li><li>The company has assessed and estimated the incremental impact of new Labour Codes, presented as ‘Statutory impact of new Labour Codes’ under ‘Exceptional Items’ in the statement of profit and loss.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/67baddda-2cba-4aba-9be1-c8bd4acc8d5f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KIRLOSKAR PNEUMATIC CO.LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VINDHYATEL] Vindhya Telelinks Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on Feb 6, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VINDHYA+TELELINKS+LTD.&title=Vindhya+Telelinks+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+Feb+6%2C+2026&newsId=b4026bf4-203d-473f-97e3-57635a7dd8cd&token=YjQwMjZiZjQtMjAz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4026bf4-203d-473f-97e3-57635a7dd8cd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vindhya Telelinks Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 6, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The results will be submitted for a &apos;Limited Review&apos; by the Statutory Auditors. The trading window for dealing in securities/equity shares of the company will remain closed until 8th February 2026, 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results.</p><ul><li>Vindhya Telelinks Ltd to consider and approve Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended on 31st December, 2025</li><li>Financial Results to be submitted for a &apos;Limited Review&apos; by the Statutory Auditors</li><li>Trading Window for dealing in securities/equity shares of the company to remain closed until 8th February, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a5e96e32-1ce0-4266-aa46-039302f6baa3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VINDHYA TELELINKS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GARWAMAR] Garware Marine Industries Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results on Feb 3, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GARWARE+MARINE+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Garware+Marine+Industries+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+on+Feb+3%2C+2026&newsId=2fd03d05-ef23-4943-88b8-524b72dbd0bc&token=MmZkMDNkMDUtZWYy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2fd03d05-ef23-4943-88b8-524b72dbd0bc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Garware Marine Industries Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 3, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2026. The meeting will be held via Video Conferencing at 03</p><ul><li>Garware Marine Industries Ltd to hold Board Meeting on Feb 3, 2026</li><li>Unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ending 31st December, 2026 to be considered</li><li>Meeting to be held via Video Conferencing</li><li>Meeting venue presumed to be at 03&quot; Floor, Prospect Chambers, D. N. Road, Fort, Mumbai 40001</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/39323241-748f-4fcc-bfd0-87b6c4280b2f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GARWARE MARINE INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CSL] Promoter Hemant Gupta Disposes of 2,00,000 Shares in Continental Securities Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Continental+Securities+Ltd&title=Promoter+Hemant+Gupta+Disposes+of+2%2C00%2C000+Shares+in+Continental+Securities+Ltd&newsId=0a0f7842-4682-4f8e-a26f-53321f84ace9&token=MGEwZjc4NDItNDY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a0f7842-4682-4f8e-a26f-53321f84ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Continental Securities Ltd has received disclosures from Hemant Gupta, a Promoter Group member, under Regulation 29 (2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. Gupta has sold 2,00,000 equity shares dated 22-01-2026. The necessary disclosures as required under Regulation 29(2) of the SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011 have been enclosed. The sale resulted in a decrease in Gupta&apos;s holding from 0.72% to 0.04% of the total share capital and total diluted capital of the company.</p><ul><li>Hemant Gupta, a Promoter Group member, sold 2,00,000 equity shares in Continental Securities Ltd.</li><li>The sale resulted in a decrease in Gupta&apos;s holding from 0.72% to 0.04% of the total share capital and total diluted capital of the company.</li><li>The sale was made through the open market.</li><li>The sale was made on 22nd January 2026.</li><li>The total share capital and total diluted capital of the company remain unchanged at 5,85,06,000 and 2,92,53,000 respectively.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/F4D4A3AA_DC5F_487E_A563_F6F208DE1E45_145435.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Continental Securities Ltd | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RAMAPETRO] Rama Petrochemicals Ltd Approves Conversion of Warrants into Equity Shares for ₹ 1,19,73,375</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RAMA+PETROCHEMICALS+LTD.&title=Rama+Petrochemicals+Ltd+Approves+Conversion+of+Warrants+into+Equity+Shares+for+%E2%82%B9+1%2C19%2C73%2C375&newsId=6d4844da-a317-48fc-961d-4a466555bfcf&token=NmQ0ODQ0ZGEtYTMx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d4844da-a317-48fc-961d-4a466555bfcf</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:24:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rama Petrochemicals Ltd has approved the conversion of 15,96,450 warrants into 15,96,450 Equity Shares of face value of ₹ 10 each. The conversion has been made for cash, upon the receipt of the exercise price of ₹ 7.5 per Share Warrant, aggregating to ₹ 1,19,73,375. The allotted equity shares shall rank pari-passu with the existing equity shares of the Company. The paid-up equity share capital of the Company has increased from ₹ 11,72,41,500 to ₹ 13,32,06,000 post the allotment.</p><ul><li>Rama Petrochemicals Ltd has approved the conversion of warrants into equity shares for ₹ 1,19,73,375.</li><li>15,96,450 warrants have been converted into 15,96,450 Equity Shares of face value of ₹ 10 each.</li><li>The conversion has been made for cash, upon the receipt of the exercise price of ₹ 7.5 per Share Warrant.</li><li>The allotted equity shares shall rank pari-passu with the existing equity shares of the Company.</li><li>The paid-up equity share capital of the Company has increased from ₹ 11,72,41,500 to ₹ 13,32,06,000 post the allotment.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b845d6a5-7d2e-4c95-869b-8548ee72c1e4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RAMA PETROCHEMICALS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LAURUSLABS] Laurus Labs Approves Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 2025, Announces New Corporate Office Address</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Laurus+Labs+Ltd&title=Laurus+Labs+Approves+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+2025%2C+Announces+New+Corporate+Office+Address&newsId=f509f460-87d0-4676-96bb-a6e69177cf99&token=ZjUwOWY0NjAtODdk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f509f460-87d0-4676-96bb-a6e69177cf99</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:24:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Laurus Labs Ltd approved the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine-months ended December 31, 2025. The company has also announced a change in the address of its corporate office. The new address is Plot No. 103, Road No.1, Jubilee Hills, Hyderabad — 500033, Telangana, India.</p><ul><li>Approval of unaudited financial results for Q3 2025</li><li>Change in address of corporate office</li><li>Available on the company&apos;s website and stock exchanges&apos; websites</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b5d1dd19-9af2-49e8-9ca2-d4336b6f50d6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Laurus Labs Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HGINFRA] Four H.G. Infra Engineering Officials Arrested by CBI; Company Examining Matter</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=H.G.+Infra+Engineering+Ltd&title=Four+H.G.+Infra+Engineering+Officials+Arrested+by+CBI%3B+Company+Examining+Matter&newsId=4507ad09-648f-4db9-814d-5c865fe08ef6&token=NDUwN2FkMDktNjQ4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4507ad09-648f-4db9-814d-5c865fe08ef6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>H.G. Infra Engineering Ltd. has announced that four of its officials, including Mr. Anoop Singh, Mr. Gaurav Kushwaha, Mr. Akash Patra, and Mr. Dhiraj Virmani, have been taken into custody by the Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI). The company, however, has not received any further details or the First Information Report (FIR) from the CBI. The company is currently evaluating the situation and considering appropriate legal steps. Despite the ongoing investigation, the company assures that it is conducting business as usual and remains dedicated to maintaining high standards of corporate governance and transparency, with a focus on protecting the interests of all stakeholders.</p><ul><li>Four officials of H.G. Infra Engineering Ltd. have been arrested by the Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI).</li><li>The company is yet to receive the FIR and other necessary details from the CBI.</li><li>H.G. Infra Engineering is evaluating appropriate legal steps and will inform the stock exchanges.</li><li>The company&apos;s operations continue as normal.</li><li>H.G. Infra Engineering is committed to high standards of corporate governance, transparency, and protecting stakeholder interests.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0676f299-1585-4026-99a8-9385ceb11c48.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: H.G. Infra Engineering Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MMRUBBR-B] MM Rubber Company Ltd to Approve Q4 Financial Results on Feb 5, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MM+RUBBER+COMPANY+LTD.&title=MM+Rubber+Company+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+Financial+Results+on+Feb+5%2C+2026&newsId=3a8823ce-85f3-4893-bd56-008b51a56fde&token=M2E4ODIzY2UtODVm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a8823ce-85f3-4893-bd56-008b51a56fde</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:22:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>MM Rubber Company Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 5, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The meeting is scheduled in accordance with Regulation 29 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The company has also closed its trading window from January 15, 2026, till the 48 hours after the declaration of financial results.</p><ul><li>MM Rubber Company Ltd to consider and approve Q4 financial results on Feb 5, 2026</li><li>The meeting is in accordance with Regulation 29 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Company&apos;s trading window closed from January 15, 2026, till the 48 hours after the declaration of financial results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/78ca4910-7a95-4fbc-9082-c5da93abad84.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MM RUBBER COMPANY LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EPSOMPRO] Epsom Properties Ltd to Consider and Approve Unaudited Financials for Q3 and Q9 Ended on Dec 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=EPSOM+PROPERTIES+LTD.&title=Epsom+Properties+Ltd+to+Consider+and+Approve+Unaudited+Financials+for+Q3+and+Q9+Ended+on+Dec+31%2C+2025&newsId=ff073577-d00b-4f0f-bc42-7458348ce9d4&token=ZmYwNzM1NzctZDAw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff073577-d00b-4f0f-bc42-7458348ce9d4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:22:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Epsom Properties Ltd has informed BSE that the meeting of the Board of Directors of the Company is scheduled on 29/01/2026. The meeting will inter alia consider and approve the unaudited Financials for the third quarter and nine months ended on 31st December, 2025. This is in compliance with the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015, SEBI Guidelines and Corporate Laws.</p><ul><li>Epsom Properties Ltd scheduled a Board Meeting on 29th January, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the unaudited Financials for the third quarter and nine months ended on 31st December, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2d29b4f8-2405-45a9-9881-5dc037608f77.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: EPSOM PROPERTIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AJWAFUN] Ajwa Fun World &amp; Resort Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on Feb 13, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AJWA+FUN+WORLD+%26+RESORT+LTD.&title=Ajwa+Fun+World+%26+Resort+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+Feb+13%2C+2026&newsId=2956ef25-2874-4e0a-9a78-0cdaadfbc622&token=Mjk1NmVmMjUtMjg3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2956ef25-2874-4e0a-9a78-0cdaadfbc622</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 09:21:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ajwa Fun World &amp; Resort Ltd has scheduled a Board of Directors meeting on February 13, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The meeting will be held at the registered office of the company in Vadodara, Gujarat.</p><ul><li>Ajwa Fun World &amp; Resort Ltd is scheduled to hold a Board of Directors meeting on February 13, 2026.</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025.</li><li>The meeting will take place at the registered office of the company in Vadodara, Gujarat.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c15a3f8b-1dd7-4087-adec-bda0e8b5cc2e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AJWA FUN WORLD & RESORT LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>