<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 01:20:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[NDTV] New Delhi Television Ltd Receives Show Cause Notice for Alleged Tax Violations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NEW+DELHI+TELEVISION+LTD.&title=New+Delhi+Television+Ltd+Receives+Show+Cause+Notice+for+Alleged+Tax+Violations&newsId=101c86d4-eabb-4f51-9e77-17f8b80128b8&token=MTAxYzg2ZDQtZWFi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">101c86d4-eabb-4f51-9e77-17f8b80128b8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:34:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>New Delhi Television Limited has received scrutiny notices in Form GST ASMT-10 dated January 7, 2026, issued by the Assistant Commissioner / GSTO, Ward 300 (E-Commerce), Zone 10, Delhi. The notices pertain to the financial years 2022-23 and 2023-24 and allege wrongful availment and utilisation of excess Input Tax Credit (ITC) and short payment of tax. The proposed liability includes tax, interest, and penalty, amounting to approximately INR 13.69 crore for FY 2022-23 and INR 20.25 crore for FY 2023-24. The Company is examining the allegations and will take appropriate legal and procedural steps. There is no immediate impact on the Company&apos;s financial position, operations, or other activities.</p><ul><li>New Delhi Television Ltd has received scrutiny notices for the financial years 2022-23 and 2023-24.</li><li>The notices allege wrongful availment and utilisation of excess Input Tax Credit (ITC) and short payment of tax.</li><li>The proposed liability includes tax, interest, and penalty, amounting to approximately INR 13.69 crore for FY 2022-23 and INR 20.25 crore for FY 2023-24.</li><li>The Company is examining the allegations and will take appropriate legal and procedural steps.</li><li>There is no immediate impact on the Company&apos;s financial position, operations, or other activities.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/016a1eec-38b8-4db0-a4ee-a75d34ea5cb5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NEW DELHI TELEVISION LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[POWERMECH] Power Mech Projects Secures 1 GWh BESS Order from West Bengal State Electricity Distribution Company</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Power+Mech+Projects+Ltd&title=Power+Mech+Projects+Secures+1+GWh+BESS+Order+from+West+Bengal+State+Electricity+Distribution+Company&newsId=3b2a1d3c-962c-453c-a5a2-26f0f342e280&token=M2IyYTFkM2MtOTYy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b2a1d3c-962c-453c-a5a2-26f0f342e280</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Power Mech Projects Limited (PMPL), a leading industrial engineering, construction and services company, has announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, PM Green Private Limited, has secured a contract for 1 GWh Battery Energy Storage System (BESS) from West Bengal State Electricity Distribution Company Limited (WBSEDCL). The project, valued at Rs. 1,563 Cr (Rs. 3,126 Cr including Greenshoe option), is structured as a Build, Own, Operate (BOO) model with a 100% off-take guarantee from WBSEDCL. The scope of work includes design, finance, engineering, procurement, construction, operation, and maintenance of the BESS facility at the Goaltore Substation. There is an additional greenshoe option for a further 1 GWh to be established at Durgapur Project Limited Campus, Durgapur.</p><ul><li>Power Mech Projects Limited&apos;s wholly owned subsidiary, PM Green Private Limited, has secured a contract for 1 GWh Battery Energy Storage System (BESS) from West Bengal State Electricity Distribution Company Limited (WBSEDCL).</li><li>The project is structured as a Build, Own, Operate (BOO) model with a 100% off-take guarantee from WBSEDCL.</li><li>The scope of work includes design, finance, engineering, procurement, construction, operation, and maintenance of the BESS facility at the Goaltore Substation.</li><li>The project is valued at Rs. 1,563 Cr (Rs. 3,126 Cr including Greenshoe option).</li><li>There is an additional greenshoe option for a further 1 GWh to be established at Durgapur Project Limited Campus, Durgapur.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/11b398ed-88d7-4f49-a166-98ad5a18e239.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Power Mech Projects Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ELPROINTL] Elpro International Ltd Acquires Sundrop Brands Limited for INR 39.18 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ELPRO+INTERNATIONAL+LTD.&title=Elpro+International+Ltd+Acquires+Sundrop+Brands+Limited+for+INR+39.18+Crores&newsId=0c4f396b-70d8-4b34-85b9-6ef6b22b1e0e&token=MGM0ZjM5NmItNzBk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c4f396b-70d8-4b34-85b9-6ef6b22b1e0e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Elpro International Ltd has acquired 5,47,946 equity shares of Sundrop Brands Limited (Formely known as Agro Tech Foods Limited), a public limited company involved in manufacturing, marketing, and selling a wide range of Food Products and Edible Oils. The acquisition was made for a cash consideration of INR 39.18 Crores, increasing Elpro&apos;s total holding to 5,56,946 equity shares. Sundrop Brands, established in 1986, has a consolidated turnover of INR 898.87 Crores, INR 759.67 Crores, and INR 849.71 Crores in the last three financial years, respectively. The company is listed on the National Stock Exchange (NSE) and Bombay Stock Exchange (BSE) and has a presence in India and one plant and office outside India.</p><ul><li>Elpro International Ltd acquires 5,47,946 equity shares of Sundrop Brands Limited</li><li>Acquisition for a cash consideration of INR 39.18 Crores</li><li>Sundrop Brands Limited involved in manufacturing, marketing, and selling Food Products and Edible Oils</li><li>Consolidated turnover of INR 898.87 Crores, INR 759.67 Crores, and INR 849.71 Crores in the last three financial years</li><li>Sundrop Brands listed on National Stock Exchange (NSE) and Bombay Stock Exchange (BSE)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0282e696-ee30-4af7-9fae-85a27ede3b97.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ELPRO INTERNATIONAL LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[POWERMECH] Power Mech Projects Ltd Subsidiary Receives Large-Scale Order for 250 MW BESS from WBSEDCL</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Power+Mech+Projects+Ltd&title=Power+Mech+Projects+Ltd+Subsidiary+Receives+Large-Scale+Order+for+250+MW+BESS+from+WBSEDCL&newsId=333192fb-c2eb-4518-9789-068116d88831&token=MzMzMTkyZmItYzJl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">333192fb-c2eb-4518-9789-068116d88831</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Power Mech Projects Ltd&apos;s subsidiary, PM Green Private Limited, has received a large-scale order from West Bengal State Electricity Distribution Company Limited (WBSEDCL) for the setting up of a 250 MW / 1,000 MWh Standalone Battery Energy Storage System (BESS) at Goaltore, Paschim Medinipur, West Bengal. The order is under the Build-Own-Operate (BOO) model, with an additional Greenshoe option of 250 MW / 1,000 MWh at the Durgapur Project Limited (DPL) campus, Durgapur, West Bengal. The scope of work includes design, finance, engineering, procurement, construction, operation, and maintenance of the BESS facility. The scheduled commissioning date is 18 months from the date of signing of the Battery Energy Storage Purchase Agreement (BESPA), with an operation and maintenance period of 180 months from the SCD. The total consideration is 3,126 Crores (Excluding GST) (Including Greenshoe option).</p><ul><li>Power Mech Projects Ltd&apos;s subsidiary, PM Green Private Limited, receives a large-scale order from WBSEDCL for a 250 MW / 1,000 MWh Standalone Battery Energy Storage System (BESS).</li><li>The order is under the Build-Own-Operate (BOO) model with an additional Greenshoe option of 250 MW / 1,000 MWh.</li><li>The scope of work includes design, finance, engineering, procurement, construction, operation, and maintenance of the BESS facility.</li><li>The scheduled commissioning date is 18 months from the date of signing of the Battery Energy Storage Purchase Agreement (BESPA).</li><li>The total consideration is 3,126 Crores (Excluding GST) (Including Greenshoe option).</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/37ab7dab-e2b3-4820-946e-6925709d67ed.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Power Mech Projects Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GENESIS] Genesis Ibrc India Ltd Promoters Reclassified to Public Category After Share Transfer to Acquirers</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Genesis+Ibrc+India+Ltd&title=Genesis+Ibrc+India+Ltd+Promoters+Reclassified+to+Public+Category+After+Share+Transfer+to+Acquirers&newsId=0405719b-3686-4171-9a75-1e199069d86b&token=MDQwNTcxOWItMzY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0405719b-3686-4171-9a75-1e199069d86b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:54:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Genesis Ibrc India Ltd announced the reclassification of its promoters, Mr. Mastan Rao Pesala, Ms. Pesala Venkata Subbamma, Mr. Arun Kumar Pesala and Mr. Srikanth Pesala from the Promoter Category to the Public Category. This reclassification follows the execution of a Share Purchase Agreement with Mr. Padmanabhan Krishnamoorthy and Ms. Venkatraman Varalakshmi on 06th March 2025. The promoters transferred their entire shareholding, amounting to 14,73,000 shares, to the acquirers on 08th January 2026. This transfer was completed in compliance with SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015 and SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares Transfer) Regulations, 2011.</p><ul><li>Genesis Ibrc India Ltd promoters reclassified to Public Category.</li><li>Share Purchase Agreement executed with acquirers on 06th March 2025.</li><li>Promoters transferred entire shareholding of 14,73,000 shares to acquirers on 08th January 2026.</li><li>Transfer completed in compliance with SEBI regulations.</li><li>Reclassification follows open offer requirements regulations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4db28d23-25e7-4fde-b425-bd0452ee8668.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Genesis Ibrc India Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TOYAMSL] Toyam Sports Ltd Reschedules Board Meeting to Approve Q3 Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Toyam+Sports+Ltd&title=Toyam+Sports+Ltd+Reschedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+Financial+Results&newsId=4719b372-ba7a-4000-998b-9c55985a4450&token=NDcxOWIzNzItYmE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4719b372-ba7a-4000-998b-9c55985a4450</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:47:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Toyam Sports Limited has rescheduled its Board of Directors meeting to Friday, 9th January, 2026. The meeting was previously scheduled for Thursday, 8th January, 2026. The primary objective of the meeting is to consider and approve the Standalone and Consolidated Un-Audited Financial Results for the quarter ended September 30, 2025, along with the Limited Review Report on the results. The trading window for dealing in securities/shares of the company will open 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results.</p><ul><li>Toyam Sports Ltd reschedules Board Meeting to 9th January, 2026</li><li>Board meeting to consider and approve Q3 financial results for the period ended 30th September, 2025</li><li>Trading window to open 48 hours after the declaration of financial results</li><li>Meeting to be held at the Registered office in Mumbai</li><li>Limited Review Report on the results of the company for Q3 2025 will also be considered</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6a555814-139e-4d53-9e8c-c3096613bd90.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Toyam Sports Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHRIPISTON] Shriram Pistons &amp; Rings Ltd Completes Acquisition of Grupo Antolin-lrausa SA and Grupo Antolin Ingenieria SA Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shriram+Pistons+%26+Rings+Ltd&title=Shriram+Pistons+%26+Rings+Ltd+Completes+Acquisition+of+Grupo+Antolin-lrausa+SA+and+Grupo+Antolin+Ingenieria+SA+Shares&newsId=034cde9c-fbd9-41c0-9237-73a8721031a8&token=MDM0Y2RlOWMtZmJk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">034cde9c-fbd9-41c0-9237-73a8721031a8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:41:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shriram Pistons &amp; Rings Ltd has completed the acquisition of the entire outstanding capital of Antolin Lighting India Private Limited (T1) and Grupo Antolin India Private Limited (T2), and consequently, indirectly acquired ~99.99% of the outstanding capital of Grupo Antolin Chakan Private Limited (T3). T1 has become the wholly-owned subsidiary of the Company, T2 has become the wholly-owned subsidiary and an unlisted material subsidiary of the Company, and T3 has become the step-down subsidiary of the Company. This acquisition was executed in accordance with the terms and conditions of a Share Purchase Agreement (SPA) with Grupo Antolin-lrausa SA and Grupo Antolin Ingenieria SA.</p><ul><li>Shriram Pistons &amp; Rings Ltd has completed the acquisition of 100% of the outstanding capital of Antolin Lighting India Private Limited (T1) and Grupo Antolin India Private Limited (T2).</li><li>The Company has indirectly acquired ~99.99% of the outstanding capital of Grupo Antolin Chakan Private Limited (T3).</li><li>T1 has become the wholly-owned subsidiary of the Company, T2 has become the wholly-owned subsidiary and an unlisted material subsidiary of the Company, and T3 has become the step-down subsidiary of the Company.</li><li>The acquisition was executed in accordance with the terms and conditions of a Share Purchase Agreement (SPA) with Grupo Antolin-lrausa SA and Grupo Antolin Ingenieria SA.</li><li>This intimation is also being uploaded on the Company’s website at https://shrirampistons.com/investors-quide-2/</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a8708237-bf2a-4836-97a7-13d6ecf40c3d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shriram Pistons & Rings Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TOYAMSL] Toyam Sports Ltd Reschedules Board Meeting to Approve Q3 Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Toyam+Sports+Ltd&title=Toyam+Sports+Ltd+Reschedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+Results&newsId=e20ef4d8-a89c-4c00-a2ad-7058893cfc14&token=ZTIwZWY0ZDgtYTg5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e20ef4d8-a89c-4c00-a2ad-7058893cfc14</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Toyam Sports Ltd has rescheduled its Board of Directors meeting to Friday, 9th January, 2026. The meeting was originally scheduled for Thursday, 8th January, 2026. The primary objective of the meeting is to consider and approve the Standalone and Consolidated Un-Audited Financial Results for the Quarter ended September 30, 2025, along with the Limited Review Report on the Results of the Company for the same quarter.</p><ul><li>Toyam Sports Ltd reschedules Board Meeting to 9th January, 2026</li><li>The meeting aims to consider and approve Q3 FY2025-26 financial results</li><li>The company will also approve the Limited Review Report for Q3 FY2025-26</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3ec9abce-4568-470b-9f20-1653825e9c63.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Toyam Sports Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GMDCLTD] Gujarat Mineral Development Corporation Ltd Receives Provisional ESG Rating of 77.7 from CareEdge ESG Ratings Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GUJARAT+MINERAL+DEVELOPMENT+CORPORATION+LTD.&title=Gujarat+Mineral+Development+Corporation+Ltd+Receives+Provisional+ESG+Rating+of+77.7+from+CareEdge+ESG+Ratings+Ltd&newsId=d558fdf8-40d6-4982-a205-2c7cd8a65444&token=ZDU1OGZkZjgtNDBk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d558fdf8-40d6-4982-a205-2c7cd8a65444</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Rating</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gujarat Mineral Development Corporation Ltd (GMDC) has been assigned an ESG rating of 77.7 (CareEdge-ESG 1) by CareEdge ESG Ratings Ltd. The rating, which places GMDC in the ‘Leadership’ category for ESG risk management, was assigned following an independent assessment that included on-ground assessment, management engagement, and field visits to GMDC’s operational assets. The rating reflects GMDC’s commitment to responsible growth, strong governance, environmental stewardship, and social responsibility.</p><ul><li>Gujarat Mineral Development Corporation Ltd (GMDC) receives an ESG rating of 77.7 (CareEdge-ESG 1) from CareEdge ESG Ratings Ltd.</li><li>The rating places GMDC in the ‘Leadership’ category for ESG risk management.</li><li>The rating is based on an independent assessment that included on-ground assessment, management engagement, and field visits to GMDC’s operational assets.</li><li>The rating reflects GMDC’s commitment to responsible growth, strong governance, environmental stewardship, and social responsibility.</li><li>GMDC is one of the leading mining players in India and is a State Public Undertaking of the Government of Gujarat.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/61deba17-c833-4ee5-98ec-fb171056ac97.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GUJARAT MINERAL DEVELOPMENT CORPORATION LTD. | Category: Rating</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IOB] Indian Overseas Bank to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months of FY2025-26 on January 14, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDIAN+OVERSEAS+BANK&title=Indian+Overseas+Bank+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+of+FY2025-26+on+January+14%2C+2026&newsId=84edb50d-63ec-420c-989a-513d70e18dc7&token=ODRlZGI1MGQtNjNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">84edb50d-63ec-420c-989a-513d70e18dc7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indian Overseas Bank has announced a Board Meeting on January 14, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited (Reviewed) Financial Results (Standalone and Consolidated) for the Quarter and Nine Months ended 31st December, 2025. The Bank also announced the closure of the Trading Window for Designated Persons and their immediate relatives from January 1, 2026, to January 16, 2026, in accordance with the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015 and the IOB Code of Conduct for Prohibition of Insider Trading.</p><ul><li>Indian Overseas Bank to approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months of FY2025-26 on January 14, 2026</li><li>Trading Window for Designated Persons and their immediate relatives to be closed from January 1, 2026, to January 16, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bee2415d-50f8-4d13-ac2d-6c85443cb5d7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDIAN OVERSEAS BANK | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>