<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 01:19:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[JONJUA] Jonjua Air Limited Disposes Portion of Holding in Jonjua Overseas Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jonjua+Overseas+Ltd&title=Jonjua+Air+Limited+Disposes+Portion+of+Holding+in+Jonjua+Overseas+Limited&newsId=a1787f3a-4bd1-40d3-9fe8-15db0236fb32&token=YTE3ODdmM2EtNGJk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a1787f3a-4bd1-40d3-9fe8-15db0236fb32</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:04:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Sale of Property</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jonjua Air Limited, a Promoter Group of Jonjua Overseas Limited, has sold a portion of its holding in Jonjua Overseas Limited on 05/01/2026. The disclosure for the same has been attached and submitted in compliance with Regulation 29 (2) of SEBI (SAST) Regulations, 2011 and other applicable rules and regulations. The sale details include 40,63,222 shares, reducing their holding from 63.222% to 12.16% of the total share/voting capital.</p><ul><li>Jonjua Air Limited, a Promoter Group of Jonjua Overseas Limited, has sold a portion of its holding in Jonjua Overseas Limited.</li><li>The sale includes 40,63,222 shares, reducing their holding from 63.222% to 12.16% of the total share/voting capital.</li><li>The disclosure has been submitted in compliance with Regulation 29 (2) of SEBI (SAST) Regulations, 2011 and other applicable rules and regulations.</li><li>The sale occurred on 05/01/2026.</li><li>Jonjua Air Limited remains a Promoter Group of Jonjua Overseas Limited post-sale.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/38906ac1-1245-4f60-8e19-354657d20a1d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jonjua Overseas Ltd | Category: Sale of Property</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LICI] Life Insurance Corporation of India Launches New Savings Plan &apos;Jeevan Utsav&apos;</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Life+Insurance+Corporation+of+India&title=Life+Insurance+Corporation+of+India+Launches+New+Savings+Plan+%27Jeevan+Utsav%27&newsId=339a0bbe-cf32-4210-a030-a1c74c1e073e&token=MzM5YTBiYmUtY2Yz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">339a0bbe-cf32-4210-a030-a1c74c1e073e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>The Life Insurance Corporation of India has announced the launch of a new product, &apos;Jeevan Utsav&apos;. This Non-Par, Non-Linked, Individual, Single Premium Savings, Whole Life Insurance Plan will be available for sale in the domestic market from January 12, 2026. The announcement was made in accordance with the Listing Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Life Insurance Corporation of India launches a new product called &apos;Jeevan Utsav&apos;</li><li>The product is a Non-Par, Non-Linked, Individual, Single Premium Savings, Whole Life Insurance Plan</li><li>The product is intended for the domestic market</li><li>The product will be available for sale from January 12, 2026</li><li>The announcement is made in accordance with the Listing Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/520bc52b-2ddb-4dc8-a3c8-54ab11c8e536.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Life Insurance Corporation of India | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SANCF] Sanchay Finvest Ltd. Proposes Preferential Issue of 48,50,000 Equity Shares at Rs. 10/- Each</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SANCHAY+FINVEST+LTD.&title=Sanchay+Finvest+Ltd.+Proposes+Preferential+Issue+of+48%2C50%2C000+Equity+Shares+at+Rs.+10%2F-+Each&newsId=0d92661c-f7bf-45da-b8eb-4c02cefa111a&token=MGQ5MjY2MWMtZjdi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d92661c-f7bf-45da-b8eb-4c02cefa111a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sanchay Finvest Ltd. held a Board Meeting on Monday, 5% January, 2026, where they approved several matters. The key highlights are: 1. The company proposed to increase its authorized capital from Rs. 8,00,00,000 to Rs. 12,00,00,000/- to accommodate the fresh issue of proposed preferential allotment. 2. The company plans to issue up to 48,50,000 Equity Shares at a price of Rs. 10/- per equity share to proposed allottees on a preferential basis. 3. The company has taken a Valuation Report from CA. Jay Ashok Shah, IBBI Registered Valuer and Regulation 163(2) certificate from Mr. Ramesh Chandra Mishra, Practicing Company Secretary. 4. The company has fixed 6\</p><ul><li>Proposed increase in authorized capital from Rs. 8,00,00,000 to Rs. 12,00,00,000/-</li><li>Issuance of up to 48,50,000 Equity Shares at a price of Rs. 10/- per equity share</li><li>Valuation Report from CA. Jay Ashok Shah, IBBI Registered Valuer</li><li>Relevant Date for the Preferential Issue set to 6&quot; January, 2026</li><li>Provision of e-voting facility for the ensuing Extraordinary General Meeting</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a1181185-eb8a-4eb6-bc39-55831637716e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SANCHAY FINVEST LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SANCF] Sanchay Finvest Ltd. Proposes Capital Increase and Preferential Allotment of Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SANCHAY+FINVEST+LTD.&title=Sanchay+Finvest+Ltd.+Proposes+Capital+Increase+and+Preferential+Allotment+of+Equity+Shares&newsId=90bec894-41e5-490c-9a2c-0e4d4e5597e7&token=OTBiZWM4OTQtNDFl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90bec894-41e5-490c-9a2c-0e4d4e5597e7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:42:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sanchay Finvest Ltd. announced that its Board of Directors held a meeting on January 5, 2026, and approved several key matters. The Board proposed to increase the authorized capital of the company from Rs. 8,00,00,000 to Rs. 12,00,00,000, subject to necessary approvals in the ensuing EGM. Additionally, the Board approved the issuance of up to 48,50,000 equity shares at a price of Rs. 10/- per equity share on a preferential basis to selected allottees. The company has taken valuation and regulatory compliance measures to ensure a smooth process. The preferential issue is subject to the approval of the members of the company and relevant regulatory/statutory authorities.</p><ul><li>Proposed increase in authorized capital from Rs. 8,00,00,000 to Rs. 12,00,00,000</li><li>Issuance of up to 48,50,000 equity shares at a price of Rs. 10/- per equity share on a preferential basis</li><li>Valuation Report from CA. Jay Ashok Shah, IBBI Registered &apos; Valuer&apos; and Regulation 163(2) certificate from Mr. Ramesh Chandra Mishra</li><li>Change of registered office from State of Madhya Pradesh to State of Maharashtra</li><li>Extraordinary General Meeting scheduled for 5% February, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bd7e0e78-e3ed-4311-a07c-e31072f37f98.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SANCHAY FINVEST LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SANCF] Sanchay Finvest Ltd. Proposes Capital Increase and Preferential Allotment of Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SANCHAY+FINVEST+LTD.&title=Sanchay+Finvest+Ltd.+Proposes+Capital+Increase+and+Preferential+Allotment+of+Equity+Shares&newsId=a8fddeed-c47d-486b-8bc9-d5a041067de3&token=YThmZGRlZWQtYzQ3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8fddeed-c47d-486b-8bc9-d5a041067de3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sanchay Finvest Ltd. held a Board Meeting on 5th January, 2026, where they proposed to increase the authorized capital of the company from Rs. 8,00,00,000 to Rs. 12,00,00,000/- after seeking necessary approvals in an ensuing EGM. The company also proposed to accommodate the fresh issue of proposed preferential allotment of 48,50,000 equity shares. The proposed allottees include SATRA Promoter, Non-SATRA Promoter, and Non-Promoter. The issue price per share is decided at Rs. 10/- per share. The company has fixed 6th January, 2026 as the Relevant Date for the Preferential Issue and decided to provide e-voting facility to the shareholders of the Company for the ensuing Extraordinary General Meeting through CSDL platform.</p><ul><li>Proposed increase in authorized capital from Rs. 8,00,00,000 to Rs. 12,00,00,000/-</li><li>Preferential allotment of 48,50,000 equity shares</li><li>Issue price per share is Rs. 10/-</li><li>Fixed Relevant Date for the Preferential Issue as 6th January, 2026</li><li>Decision to provide e-voting facility for the ensuing Extraordinary General Meeting</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ff914982-fc4a-4c0a-b911-7abdf66d61ac.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SANCHAY FINVEST LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HAPPSTMNDS] Happiest Minds Technologies Clarifies Clerical Error in Gavs Technologies Acquisition</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Happiest+Minds+Technologies+Ltd&title=Happiest+Minds+Technologies+Clarifies+Clerical+Error+in+Gavs+Technologies+Acquisition&newsId=64788bd3-50d6-4403-96bb-a05ac0372396&token=NjQ3ODhiZDMtNTBk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">64788bd3-50d6-4403-96bb-a05ac0372396</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Happiest Minds Technologies Ltd. has issued a corrigendum to clarify an inadvertent error in their earlier intimation regarding the acquisition of Gavs Technologies Limited. The company confirmed that it has not acquired Gavs Technologies Limited. Instead, it executed a Share Purchase Agreement with Gavs Technologies Limited to acquire 100% business interest of their Middle East business, including InnovazIT Technologies LLC, Dubai; Gavs Technologies LLC, Oman; and Gavs Technologies Saudi Arabia for Telecommunications and Information Technology, Saudi Arabia. The integration process of these acquired companies has been completed as of January 05, 2026. The company clarified that this error was unintentional and not deliberate, requesting stakeholders to accept the corrigendum and update their records accordingly.</p><ul><li>Happiest Minds Technologies clarified a clerical error in their earlier intimation about acquiring Gavs Technologies Limited.</li><li>The company has not acquired Gavs Technologies Limited but executed a Share Purchase Agreement to acquire 100% business interest of their Middle East business.</li><li>The acquired Middle East businesses include InnovazIT Technologies LLC, Dubai; Gavs Technologies LLC, Oman; and Gavs Technologies Saudi Arabia for Telecommunications and Information Technology, Saudi Arabia.</li><li>The integration process of the acquired companies has been completed as of January 05, 2026.</li><li>The company ensured stakeholders that the error was unintentional and not deliberate.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a22bd87a-6efd-4e2b-97fd-fa6e345ae028.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Happiest Minds Technologies Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SANCF] Sanchay Finvest Ltd. Proposes Capital Increase for Preferential Allotment of Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SANCHAY+FINVEST+LTD.&title=Sanchay+Finvest+Ltd.+Proposes+Capital+Increase+for+Preferential+Allotment+of+Equity+Shares&newsId=ae597316-233c-4691-8344-3c17b7cf022c&token=YWU1OTczMTYtMjMz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae597316-233c-4691-8344-3c17b7cf022c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:41:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sanchay Finvest Ltd. announced a Board Meeting on Monday, 5% January, 2026, where they proposed to increase the authorized capital of the company from Rs. 8,00,00,000 to Rs. 12,00,00,000/- after seeking necessary approvals in an ensuing EGM. The company plans to accommodate a fresh issue of proposed preferential allotment of 48,50,000 equity shares. The proposed allottees include SATRA Promoter, VRUTIKA PRAFUL, ANIL BABUBHAI, and SAUMYA SINGH. The issue price per share is decided at Rs. 10/- each, with a total amount of up to Rs. 4,85,00,000. The company has also appointed Mr. Ramesh Chandra Mishra as a Scrutinizer for the ensuing EGM.</p><ul><li>Proposed increase in authorized capital from Rs. 8,00,00,000 to Rs. 12,00,00,000/-</li><li>Preferential allotment of 48,50,000 equity shares</li><li>Issue price per share set at Rs. 10/-</li><li>Total amount for the preferential issue is up to Rs. 4,85,00,000</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Ramesh Chandra Mishra as a Scrutinizer for the ensuing EGM</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ef9860b4-c994-42f2-b97e-54c8a75648e9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SANCHAY FINVEST LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SANCF] Sanchay Finvest Ltd. Proposes Capital Increase and Preferential Allotment of Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SANCHAY+FINVEST+LTD.&title=Sanchay+Finvest+Ltd.+Proposes+Capital+Increase+and+Preferential+Allotment+of+Equity+Shares&newsId=a18889f0-8675-427d-a31b-941cbb0c0eef&token=YTE4ODg5ZjAtODY3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a18889f0-8675-427d-a31b-941cbb0c0eef</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:34:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sanchay Finvest Ltd. held a Board Meeting on Monday, 5% January, 2026, where they proposed to increase the authorized capital of the company from Rs. 8,00,00,000 to Rs. 12,00,00,000/-. They also approved the issuance of up to 48,50,000 Equity Shares at a price of Rs. 10/- each to proposed allottees on a preferential basis. The proposed allottees include SATRA Promoter, VRUTIKA PRAFUL, BABUBHAI MEHTA, SHANKAR DAYAL, and SAUMYA SINGH. The company has taken Valuation Report from CA. Jay Ashok Shah, IBBI Registered Valuer and Regulation 163(2) certificate from Mr. Ramesh Chandra Mishra, Practicing Company Secretary. The company has also decided to provide e-voting facility to the shareholders for the ensuing Extraordinary General Meeting.</p><ul><li>Proposal to increase the authorized capital from Rs. 8,00,00,000 to Rs. 12,00,00,000/-</li><li>Issuance of up to 48,50,000 Equity Shares at a price of Rs. 10/- each to proposed allottees</li><li>Valuation Report from CA. Jay Ashok Shah, IBBI Registered Valuer and Regulation 163(2) certificate from Mr. Ramesh Chandra Mishra</li><li>Decision to provide e-voting facility to the shareholders for the ensuing Extraordinary General Meeting</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/13cc4754-b446-490f-afe4-69e25b911744.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SANCHAY FINVEST LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BIOCON] Biocon Ltd Completes Acquisition of Biocon Biologics Limited Shares for USD 200 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BIOCON+LTD.&title=Biocon+Ltd+Completes+Acquisition+of+Biocon+Biologics+Limited+Shares+for+USD+200+Million&newsId=7846d37a-6d9c-43cd-9ad9-6dd16fd662ac&token=Nzg0NmQzN2EtNmQ5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7846d37a-6d9c-43cd-9ad9-6dd16fd662ac</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Biocon Ltd has completed the acquisition of 7,18,34,691 equity shares of Biocon Biologics Limited from Mylan Inc. for a cash consideration of USD 200 million. This acquisition is part of the total acquisition of 14,36,69,382 equity shares of Biocon Biologics Limited from Mylan Inc. for a cash consideration of USD 400 million, which was approved by the Board on December 06, 2025. Post this acquisition, Biocon Ltd holds approximately 94% of the paid-up equity share capital of Biocon Biologics Limited on a fully diluted basis.</p><ul><li>Biocon Ltd completes acquisition of 7,18,34,691 equity shares of Biocon Biologics Limited from Mylan Inc. for USD 200 million.</li><li>This acquisition is part of the total acquisition of 14,36,69,382 equity shares of Biocon Biologics Limited from Mylan Inc. for USD 400 million.</li><li>Post acquisition, Biocon Ltd holds approximately 94% of the paid-up equity share capital of Biocon Biologics Limited on a fully diluted basis.</li><li>The acquisition was completed on January 05, 2026.</li><li>Biocon Ltd has issued and allotted 17,12,79,553 equity shares of the Company as consideration for the acquisition.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/48be3f21-059d-4e34-a270-fcb7caecacb0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BIOCON LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[M&amp;M] Mahindra Premieres XUV 7XO with 5 Pioneering Tech Disruptions Starting at 13.66 Lakh</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MAHINDRA+%26+MAHINDRA+LTD.&title=Mahindra+Premieres+XUV+7XO+with+5+Pioneering+Tech+Disruptions+Starting+at+13.66+Lakh&newsId=63269cb7-d3ff-4da8-9f3b-399bc35d49b8&token=NjMyNjljYjctZDNm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63269cb7-d3ff-4da8-9f3b-399bc35d49b8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:22:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Ltd., India’s leading SUV manufacturer, launched the new XUV 7XO, an advanced SUV with five pioneering tech disruptions. The XUV 7XO, starting at 13.66 lakh (ex-showroom), offers advanced features like Coast-to-Coast 31.24 cm Triple HD screens, Intelligent ADRENOX, Wireless Android Auto &amp; Apple CarPlay, Alexa Built-in with ChatGPT, Cruise Control, Push Button Start/Stop, and 75 safety features—all as standard. The XUV 7XO is designed to elevate sophistication and technology in the SUV segment.</p><ul><li>World’s first DAVINCI suspension system</li><li>India’s first ICE SUV with coast-to-coast triple screen across all variants</li><li>India’s first ICE Software Defined Vehicle (SDV)</li><li>India’s first Integrated Dolby Atmos and Dolby Vision Experience</li><li>India’s first ADAS Level 2 with Dynamic Visualisation</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/82b25991-56ee-483d-9830-a1c2b74ede4f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MAHINDRA & MAHINDRA LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>