<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:21:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[KRSNAA] Krsnaa Diagnostics Ltd CFO Pawan Daga Resigns</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Krsnaa+Diagnostics+Ltd&title=Krsnaa+Diagnostics+Ltd+CFO+Pawan+Daga+Resigns&newsId=afdc1a3e-f50b-4d2f-91fe-03a1938d27e3&token=YWZkYzFhM2UtZjUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">afdc1a3e-f50b-4d2f-91fe-03a1938d27e3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Auditor</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Krsnaa Diagnostics Ltd announced the resignation of its Chief Financial Officer, Mr. Pawan Daga. His last working day with the Company will be till the close of business hours on January 19, 2026. The Company expressed gratitude for his services and contributions during his five-year tenure.</p><ul><li>Mr. Pawan Daga resigns from the position of Chief Financial Officer of Krsnaa Diagnostics Ltd.</li><li>His last working day will be on January 19, 2026.</li><li>The Company expressed appreciation for his services and contributions during his tenure.</li><li>The resignation is due to personal and professional priorities.</li><li>The finance function is said to be well-positioned for continued success.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ccdd0072-35ff-48dd-9406-ad529a2e323e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Krsnaa Diagnostics Ltd | Category: Auditor</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LUMAXTECH] Lumax Auto Technologies Ltd: National Company Law Tribunal Sanctions Scheme of Arrangement for Amalgamation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LUMAX+AUTO+TECHNOLOGIES+LTD.&title=Lumax+Auto+Technologies+Ltd%3A+National+Company+Law+Tribunal+Sanctions+Scheme+of+Arrangement+for+Amalgamation&newsId=2e29ac04-f3d0-4e48-9a53-3778008307f4&token=MmUyOWFjMDQtZjNk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e29ac04-f3d0-4e48-9a53-3778008307f4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:11:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Lumax Auto Technologies Ltd has announced that the Hon&apos;ble National Company Law Tribunal, Chandigarh Bench has pronounced an order sanctioning the Scheme of Arrangement for Amalgamation between Greenfuel Energy Solutions Private Limited and Lumax Resources Private Limited, both subsidiaries of the company. The order, however, contains certain factual errors which the company is taking necessary steps to rectify. Upon receipt of the rectified order, the company will intimate and file the requisite disclosure with the Stock Exchanges.</p><ul><li>National Company Law Tribunal sanctions Scheme of Arrangement for Amalgamation between Lumax Auto Technologies subsidiaries</li><li>Scheme involves Greenfuel Energy Solutions Private Limited and Lumax Resources Private Limited</li><li>Company to rectify certain factual errors in the order</li><li>Rectified order to be intimated and filed with Stock Exchanges upon receipt</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/10945b06-2555-415b-a25d-c671362b11a6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LUMAX AUTO TECHNOLOGIES LTD. | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RBA] Restaurant Brands Asia Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Discuss Fund Raising</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Restaurant+Brands+Asia+Ltd&title=Restaurant+Brands+Asia+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Discuss+Fund+Raising&newsId=88e7b900-cbaf-45f9-b102-60c0f53e19fc&token=ODhlN2I5MDAtY2Jh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88e7b900-cbaf-45f9-b102-60c0f53e19fc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:11:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Restaurant Brands Asia Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 20, 2026, to consider and approve a proposal for fund raising. The company may consider various methods for fund raising, including a preferential issue on a private placement basis, rights issue, qualified institutional placement, or any other methods as appropriate. The company will also consider convening an extraordinary general meeting to seek approval from members for the fund raising proposal. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the company by designated persons and their immediate relatives will remain closed from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the conclusion of the Board Meeting.</p><ul><li>Restaurant Brands Asia Ltd to consider fund raising proposal on January 20, 2026</li><li>Company may consider various methods for fund raising</li><li>Extraordinary general meeting to be considered for member approval</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities to remain closed</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/911dfc62-cfbe-41a1-ba54-c4b2dc049712.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Restaurant Brands Asia Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HSCL] Himadri Speciality Chemical Ltd. Reports on Re-lodgement of Transfer Requests of Physical Shares for December 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Himadri+Speciality+Chemical+Ltd&title=Himadri+Speciality+Chemical+Ltd.+Reports+on+Re-lodgement+of+Transfer+Requests+of+Physical+Shares+for+December+2025&newsId=5f80f623-6f02-466d-8846-1388c8527f75&token=NWY4MGY2MjMtNmYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f80f623-6f02-466d-8846-1388c8527f75</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:47:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Himadri Speciality Chemical Ltd. has released a report on the re-lodgement of transfer requests of physical shares for the month of December 2025. The report, provided by the Registrar and Share Transfer Agent (RTA) M/s. S. K. Infosolutions Private Limited, confirms the status of requests received from shareholders for the re-lodgment of transfer requests for physical shares under the special window provided by the SEBI Circular dated 2nd July 2025. The report includes the number of requests received, processed, approved, and rejected during the month, with an average processing time.</p><ul><li>Himadri Speciality Chemical Ltd. releases report on re-lodgement of transfer requests of physical shares for December 2025.</li><li>Report provided by Registrar and Share Transfer Agent (RTA) M/s. S. K. Infosolutions Private Limited.</li><li>Includes number of requests received, processed, approved, and rejected during the month.</li><li>Includes average processing time for requests.</li><li>Confirms compliance with SEBI circular no. SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97dated 2nd July, 2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ecaf4917-e66c-49a3-bcb8-a7eabc3408e3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Himadri Speciality Chemical Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HSCL] Himadri Speciality Chemical Ltd Secures EcoVadis Platinum for Second Consecutive Year</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Himadri+Speciality+Chemical+Ltd&title=Himadri+Speciality+Chemical+Ltd+Secures+EcoVadis+Platinum+for+Second+Consecutive+Year&newsId=3f0dc45c-a4d4-464d-ae43-c8b6b12f7495&token=M2YwZGM0NWMtYTRk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3f0dc45c-a4d4-464d-ae43-c8b6b12f7495</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:41:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Award</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Himadri Speciality Chemical Ltd has been awarded the EcoVadis Platinum Medal for the second consecutive year, placing the company in the top 1% of more than 150,000+ companies globally assessed by EcoVadis. This recognition is a strong validation of the company&apos;s sustainability approach and its commitment to responsible business practices and sustainable value creation.</p><ul><li>Himadri Speciality Chemical Ltd secures EcoVadis Platinum for the second consecutive year</li><li>Company is among the top 1% of more than 150,000+ companies assessed by EcoVadis worldwide</li><li>Achievement reflects Himadri’s consistent leadership in responsible business practices and sustainable value creation</li><li>EcoVadis evaluation assesses performance across 21 criteria under four core pillars—Environment, Labour &amp; Human Rights, Ethics, and Sustainable Procurement</li><li>Sustainability has been a core pillar of Himadri’s growth strategy, reflected in focused investments across energy efficiency, emission reduction, circularity, employee well-being, and transparent disclosures aligned with global ESG standards</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/247e65e4-468f-45b5-a771-eb08577a4d64.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Himadri Speciality Chemical Ltd | Category: Award</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GRANDFONRY] Grand Foundry Ltd: Board Meeting Approves Changes in Auditors, Company Secretary, and Object Clause</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GRAND+FOUNDRY+LTD.&title=Grand+Foundry+Ltd%3A+Board+Meeting+Approves+Changes+in+Auditors%2C+Company+Secretary%2C+and+Object+Clause&newsId=a845753e-ad4b-4cc2-a119-aa69fafb95b5&token=YTg0NTc1M2UtYWQ0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a845753e-ad4b-4cc2-a119-aa69fafb95b5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In a recent board meeting, Grand Foundry Ltd announced the resignation of their statutory auditor, internal auditor, and company secretary. The board has recommended the appointment of new auditors and internal auditors, subject to shareholder approval. Additionally, the board has approved the addition of new objects to the main objects clauses in the Memorandum of Association, focusing on telecom and communication services, broadband and high-speed internet access, and dedicated leased line and bandwidth services. The company has also fixed a cut-off date for determining the eligibility of members entitled to vote and appointed a scrutinizer for the upcoming Extra-Ordinary General Meeting.</p><ul><li>Resignation of statutory auditor, internal auditor, and company secretary</li><li>Recommendation of new auditors and internal auditors</li><li>Addition of new objects to the main objects clauses in the Memorandum of Association</li><li>Fixing of cut-off date for determining the eligibility of members entitled to vote</li><li>Appointment of scrutinizer for the upcoming Extra-Ordinary General Meeting</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/60f2ec0a-90a4-4e32-9a7c-c3ee30ebc140.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GRAND FOUNDRY LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JSWENERGY] JSW Energy Secures Supply of Turbine Generators for 1,600 MW Salboni Plant</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JSW+Energy+Ltd&title=JSW+Energy+Secures+Supply+of+Turbine+Generators+for+1%2C600+MW+Salboni+Plant&newsId=f3fd7190-a173-4698-9723-dfbb797bf957&token=ZjNmZDcxOTAtYTE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3fd7190-a173-4698-9723-dfbb797bf957</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:34:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>JSW Energy Ltd, through its subsidiary JSW Thermal Energy Limited, has entered into a contract with its associate company, Toshiba JSW Power Systems Private Limited, for the procurement of two steam turbine generators of 800 MW each for its thermal project at Salboni, West Bengal. This strategic move aims to enhance supply-chain certainty, improve coordination during execution, and reduce risks arising from industry-wide equipment shortages. The company currently owns and operates 5,658 MW of thermal generation capacity and is expecting to increase its total thermal capacity to 9,058 MW with the Salboni and KSK Mahanadi projects. JSW Energy is committed to supporting India’s energy security by adding reliable baseload capacity that complements the country’s expanding renewable footprint.</p><ul><li>JSW Energy secures supply of turbine generators for 1,600 MW Salboni plant</li><li>Contract with associate company Toshiba JSW Power Systems Private Limited</li><li>Enhance supply-chain certainty, improve coordination and reduce risks</li><li>Company&apos;s total thermal capacity expected to increase to 9,058 MW</li><li>Supporting India’s energy security by adding reliable baseload capacity</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/acd77abf-b33a-404e-afe3-f55fd9f55e7b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JSW Energy Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SMARTWORKS] Smartworks Enters Compounding Phase in Q3 FY26 with Record EBITDA and Strong Cash Conversion</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Smartworks+Coworking+Spaces+Ltd&title=Smartworks+Enters+Compounding+Phase+in+Q3+FY26+with+Record+EBITDA+and+Strong+Cash+Conversion&newsId=c285773a-e68a-4878-8ded-1e7d9a0478da&token=YzI4NTc3M2EtZTY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c285773a-e68a-4878-8ded-1e7d9a0478da</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Smartworks Coworking Spaces Limited, India’s largest managed office platform, reported its strongest quarterly performance in Q3 FY26, marking a structural inflection in the Company’s growth trajectory. The quarter reflects rising portfolio maturity, a higher share of large-format enterprise contracts, and operating leverage inherent in Smartworks’ managed campus model. Record normalised EBITDA during the quarter was supported by an expanding base of mature centres, while operating cash flow exceeded EBITDA, reinforcing the Company’s cash-compounding and self-funded growth model.</p><ul><li>Revenue of ~%472 crore, up 34% YoY and 11% QoQ</li><li>Normalised EBITDA at an all-time high of ~%85 crore; margin expanded to ~18%</li><li>Normalised operating cash flow of ~=101 crore; OCF-to-EBITDA at ~1.2</li><li>Annualised ROCE improved to ~21%, continuing its upward trajectory</li><li>Net-debt negative balance sheet sustained at ~%42 crore</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d4b873ca-ea31-4326-8fe7-4afc8ece7665.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Smartworks Coworking Spaces Ltd | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HATHWAY] Hathway Cable &amp; Datacom Ltd. Announces Q3 and 9M Unaudited Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Hathway+Cable+%26+Datacom+Ltd&title=Hathway+Cable+%26+Datacom+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+9M+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=e5e1b231-724b-4472-9451-48be6bb3a8b1&token=ZTVlMWIyMzEtNzI0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5e1b231-724b-4472-9451-48be6bb3a8b1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hathway Cable &amp; Datacom Ltd. has announced its unaudited consolidated and standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The results were reviewed and approved by the Audit Committee and the Board of Directors in their respective meetings. The company&apos;s total income, expenses, and net profit for the period are disclosed in the statement, along with the share of profit/loss of associates and joint ventures. The statement also includes the Group&apos;s share of net profit/loss after tax and total comprehensive income/loss for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, in respect of three joint ventures and one associate, whose unaudited standalone/consolidated interim financial information has not been reviewed by the company&apos;s auditor. The auditor has not identified any material misstatements in the statement.</p><ul><li>Unaudited consolidated and standalone financial results for Q3 and 9M 2025 announced</li><li>Reviewed and approved by the Audit Committee and the Board of Directors</li><li>Total income, expenses, and net profit disclosed in the statement</li><li>Group&apos;s share of net profit/loss after tax and total comprehensive income/loss for the quarter and nine months included</li><li>Auditor&apos;s review did not identify any material misstatements</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a52f740c-696c-4595-989d-0e800aa5549c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Hathway Cable & Datacom Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HATHWAY] Hathway Cable &amp; Datacom Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Hathway+Cable+%26+Datacom+Ltd&title=Hathway+Cable+%26+Datacom+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=29ea3b17-6e79-4973-90b5-e0d76f73d0f1&token=MjllYTNiMTctNmU3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29ea3b17-6e79-4973-90b5-e0d76f73d0f1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:22:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hathway Cable &amp; Datacom Ltd has released its unaudited consolidated and standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The results were reviewed and approved by the Audit Committee and the Board of Directors. The company&apos;s total income and expenses are detailed in the statement, along with exceptional items and tax expenses. The statement also includes the group&apos;s share of net profit/loss after tax and total comprehensive income/loss of its joint ventures and associates.</p><ul><li>Hathway Cable &amp; Datacom Ltd reports Q3 and nine months financial results for 2025.</li><li>Results reviewed and approved by the Audit Committee and the Board of Directors.</li><li>Detailed total income, expenses, exceptional items, and tax expenses provided.</li><li>Includes the group&apos;s share of net profit/loss after tax and total comprehensive income/loss of its joint ventures and associates.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0a1d71d5-451b-4618-bf3f-f175491d4621.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Hathway Cable & Datacom Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>