<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:17:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[STUDDS] Studds Accessories Ltd. to Approve Q3 and 9M Financial Results on January 31, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Studds+Accessories+Ltd&title=Studds+Accessories+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q3+and+9M+Financial+Results+on+January+31%2C+2026&newsId=7d49b0fa-d6a5-4fdc-97c1-75823ae8ab94&token=N2Q0OWIwZmEtZDZh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7d49b0fa-d6a5-4fdc-97c1-75823ae8ab94</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 14:57:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Studds Accessories Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 31, 2026, to consider and approve the Standalone and Consolidated Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for all Designated Persons and their immediate relatives will remain closed 48 hours after the declaration of the results. This information is pursuant to Regulation 29 and other applicable provisions of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Studds Accessories Ltd. to approve Q3 and 9M financial results on January 31, 2026</li><li>Trading window to remain closed for 48 hours after the declaration of results for all Designated Persons and their immediate relatives</li><li>Information submitted in accordance with Regulation 29 and other applicable provisions of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/31f3bf7e-5130-4f05-89df-7fb633bda79a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Studds Accessories Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VELHO] Velan Hotels Ltd to Approve Q4 Results for 2025 in Board Meeting on Feb 4, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VELAN+HOTELS+LTD.&title=Velan+Hotels+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+Results+for+2025+in+Board+Meeting+on+Feb+4%2C+2026&newsId=76c85f31-a23d-4c0d-97e8-e3e9638c3f59&token=NzZjODVmMzEtYTIz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76c85f31-a23d-4c0d-97e8-e3e9638c3f59</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 14:51:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Velan Hotels Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 4, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The meeting is in accordance with Regulation 29(1)(a) of SEBI (LODR) Regulation, 2015. The company has also disclosed the closure of the Trading Window as per its Code of Conduct to regulate, monitor and report trading by insiders, adopted by the Board pursuant to SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulation, 2015.</p><ul><li>Velan Hotels Ltd to approve Q4 results for 2025 in Board Meeting on Feb 4, 2026</li><li>Meeting scheduled in accordance with Regulation 29(1)(a) of SEBI (LODR) Regulation, 2015</li><li>Company has disclosed closure of the Trading Window as per its Code of Conduct</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4b8eea11-2888-44a4-a221-06e2bdbf98e0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VELAN HOTELS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DJML] DJ Mediaprint &amp; Logistics Ltd to Approve Q3 Results and Material Related Party Transactions on Jan 31, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DJ+Mediaprint+%26+Logistics+Ltd&title=DJ+Mediaprint+%26+Logistics+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+Results+and+Material+Related+Party+Transactions+on+Jan+31%2C+2026&newsId=f60a4e08-f370-4147-aa3f-79ab1af7eb13&token=ZjYwYTRlMDgtZjM3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f60a4e08-f370-4147-aa3f-79ab1af7eb13</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 14:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>DJ Mediaprint &amp; Logistics Ltd has announced a Board Meeting on January 31, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The meeting will also approve Material Related Party Transactions. The trading window for dealing in securities of the company is closed from January 1, 2026, and will reopen 48 hours after the announcement of the aforesaid un-audited financial results.</p><ul><li>DJ Mediaprint &amp; Logistics Ltd to approve Q3 results on Jan 31, 2026</li><li>The company will also approve Material Related Party Transactions</li><li>Trading window for securities dealing is closed from Jan 1, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f5bedd71-dc15-4d47-9376-0141f47272c7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DJ Mediaprint & Logistics Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GANDHAR] Gandhar Oil Refinery Declares Interim Dividend of Rs. 0.75 per Equity Share for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Gandhar+Oil+Refinery+%28India%29+Ltd&title=Gandhar+Oil+Refinery+Declares+Interim+Dividend+of+Rs.+0.75+per+Equity+Share+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=61a0ac5d-ea77-4db7-9edc-720192be02f4&token=NjFhMGFjNWQtZWE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61a0ac5d-ea77-4db7-9edc-720192be02f4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 14:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gandhar Oil Refinery (India) Ltd has declared an interim dividend of Rs. 0.75 per equity share for the financial year 2025-26. The dividend will be payable to those members whose names appear in the Register of Members/ list of Beneficial Owners as provided by the Depositories i.e. National Securities Depository Limited (NSDL) and Central Depository Services (India) Ltd (CDSL) as on Friday, January 30, 2026 (Record date fixed for Interim dividend payment). The company will deduct tax at source (TDS) at the time of making the payment of the said Interim Dividend. The TDS rate may vary depending on the residential status of the shareholder and the documents submitted to the Company in accordance with the provisions of the Income Tax Act, 1961.</p><ul><li>Gandhar Oil Refinery declares an interim dividend of Rs. 0.75 per equity share for FY 2025-26.</li><li>The dividend will be payable to those members whose names appear in the Register of Members/ list of Beneficial Owners as provided by the Depositories i.e. National Securities Depository Limited (NSDL) and Central Depository Services (India) Ltd (CDSL) as on Friday, January 30, 2026.</li><li>The company will deduct tax at source (TDS) at the time of making the payment of the said Interim Dividend.</li><li>The TDS rate may vary depending on the residential status of the shareholder and the documents submitted to the Company in accordance with the provisions of the Income Tax Act, 1961.</li><li>The record date for the dividend payment is fixed for January 30, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0bde831a-927b-44f9-a416-3d7a6551da92.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Gandhar Oil Refinery (India) Ltd | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SARVESHWAR] Sarveshwar Foods Allots 37,50,000 Equity Shares Upon Conversion of Warrants</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sarveshwar+Foods+Ltd&title=Sarveshwar+Foods+Allots+37%2C50%2C000+Equity+Shares+Upon+Conversion+of+Warrants&newsId=3a15e56f-b4b6-4955-8cdb-26971cc64a7b&token=M2ExNWU1NmYtYjRi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a15e56f-b4b6-4955-8cdb-26971cc64a7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 14:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sarveshwar Foods Ltd. has allotted 37,50,000 equity shares upon conversion of warrants on a preferential basis. This allotment is in furtherance to the company&apos;s earlier intimation dated July 25, 2024, regarding the allotment of 10,20,00,000 warrants. The warrants were convertible into equity shares of the company within a period of 18 months from the date of allotment. The Board of Directors has approved the allotment of equity shares at an issue price of Rs. 9.70 per share, consequent upon the conversion of 37,50,000 warrants. The paid-up equity share capital of the company stands increased to Rs. 123,26,76,469 consisting of 123,26,76,469 equity shares of face value of Re. 1 each.</p><ul><li>Sarveshwar Foods allots 37,50,000 equity shares upon conversion of warrants.</li><li>The allotment is on a preferential basis and is in furtherance to the company&apos;s earlier intimation dated July 25, 2024.</li><li>The warrants were convertible into equity shares of the company within a period of 18 months from the date of allotment.</li><li>The Board of Directors has approved the allotment of equity shares at an issue price of Rs. 9.70 per share.</li><li>The paid-up equity share capital of the company stands increased to Rs. 123,26,76,469 consisting of 123,26,76,469 equity shares of face value of Re. 1 each.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2c25a311-970c-48b6-bca5-a35d58d1ae39.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sarveshwar Foods Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RPOWER] Reliance Power Ltd Schedules Board Meeting on Jan 30, 2026 to Approve Q3 and 9M 2025 Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RELIANCE+POWER+LTD.&title=Reliance+Power+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+on+Jan+30%2C+2026+to+Approve+Q3+and+9M+2025+Financial+Results&newsId=2c31e65b-7ad2-4e93-8319-971aee3be6d3&token=MmMzMWU2NWItN2Fk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2c31e65b-7ad2-4e93-8319-971aee3be6d3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 14:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Reliance Power Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 30, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting is in accordance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The trading window for designated persons is closed from Thursday, January 01, 2026, till the end of 48 hours after the outcome of the Board Meeting is made public.</p><ul><li>Reliance Power Ltd Board Meeting scheduled on January 30, 2026</li><li>To consider and approve the unaudited financial results for Q3 and 9M 2025</li><li>Meeting in accordance with Securities and Exchange Board of India regulations</li><li>Trading window for designated persons closed from January 01, 2026</li><li>Window to remain closed till the end of 48 hours after the outcome of the Board Meeting is made public</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/89e15fba-78e4-4b73-8365-4471441e9b1a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RELIANCE POWER LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZPPOLYSA] Statutory Auditor of Cropster Agro Ltd Resigns</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PLANTER+POLYSACKS+LTD.&title=Statutory+Auditor+of+Cropster+Agro+Ltd+Resigns&newsId=5aa37a8d-6ce5-4338-bc09-5a3df6993099&token=NWFhMzdhOGQtNmNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5aa37a8d-6ce5-4338-bc09-5a3df6993099</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 14:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Auditor</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cropster Agro Ltd has received the resignation of its Statutory Auditor, M/s. J Singh &amp; Associates, Chartered Accountants, Mumbai (FRN: 110266W), with effect from 24th January, 2026. The resignation was reviewed by the Audit Committee and there were no concerns raised by the resigning auditor with respect to the management of the Company. The auditor cited a significant reduction in their overall audit leadership capacity due to the resignation of a key partner and acute staff constraints as the reasons for their resignation.</p><ul><li>M/s. J Singh &amp; Associates, Chartered Accountants, Mumbai (FRN: 110266W) has resigned as Statutory Auditor of Cropster Agro Ltd</li><li>The resignation is effective from 24th January, 2026</li><li>The resignation has been reviewed by the Audit Committee</li><li>The auditor cited a significant reduction in their overall audit leadership capacity and acute staff constraints as the reasons for their resignation</li><li>There were no concerns raised by the resigning auditor with respect to the management of the Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0e0e91f0-ef42-4761-8f84-6ff01b7b17b8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PLANTER POLYSACKS LTD. | Category: Auditor</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STARLENT] Starlineps Enterprises Ltd Announces E-voting Facility for Upcoming EGM</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Starlineps+Enterprises+Ltd&title=Starlineps+Enterprises+Ltd+Announces+E-voting+Facility+for+Upcoming+EGM&newsId=38bec258-96b9-4bce-bd31-46288e134bd3&token=MzhiZWMyNTgtOTZi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">38bec258-96b9-4bce-bd31-46288e134bd3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 14:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Starlineps Enterprises Ltd has announced that it will provide a remote e-voting facility to its members for the Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) scheduled on Tuesday, 24th February, 2026 at 01:00 p.m. (IST) through Video Conference (‘VC’)/ Other Audio Visual Means ((OAVM’). The e-voting will commence on 21st February, 2026 at 09.00 a.m. and end on 23rd February, 2026 at 5.00 p.m. Only members whose names are recorded in the register of members or depositories as on the cut-off date (19th February, 2026) are entitled to avail the facility of remote E-voting as well as voting in the EGM. For any queries or issues regarding E-voting, members can write an email to evoting@nsdl.com.</p><ul><li>Starlineps Enterprises Ltd announces e-voting facility for EGM</li><li>EGM scheduled on 24th February, 2026 at 01:00 p.m. (IST) through VC/OAVM</li><li>E-voting to commence on 21st February, 2026 at 09.00 a.m. and end on 23rd February, 2026 at 5.00 p.m.</li><li>Only members recorded in the register of members or depositories as on the cut-off date are eligible for e-voting</li><li>For queries or issues regarding E-voting, members can write an email to evoting@nsdl.com</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/25956517-d34b-4eaf-af8e-24f70a3d7825.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Starlineps Enterprises Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SWADHATURE] Swadha Nature Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Swadha+Nature+Ltd&title=Swadha+Nature+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=c34d7247-e7c4-4fb2-9fe2-b8a81632b503&token=YzM0ZDcyNDctZTdj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c34d7247-e7c4-4fb2-9fe2-b8a81632b503</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 14:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Swadha Nature Ltd (Formerly Known as MS Securities Limited) has reported its unaudited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended on 31st December 2025. The review was conducted by the Audit Committee and the Statutory Auditors of the Company. The company operates in a single reportable business segment and has prepared the financial results in accordance with the Indian Accounting Standards (Ind AS) notified under Section 133 of the Companies Act, 2013.</p><ul><li>Unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended on 31st December 2025 have been reported.</li><li>The results were reviewed by the Audit Committee and the Statutory Auditors of the Company.</li><li>Swadha Nature Ltd operates in a single reportable business segment.</li><li>The financial results have been prepared in accordance with the Indian Accounting Standards (Ind AS) notified under Section 133 of the Companies Act, 2013.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5e5d6e4c-9dca-4f09-b4ef-ee1e89b34d0e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Swadha Nature Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CHENNPETRO] Chennai Petroleum Corporation Ltd Reports Audited Financial Results for Q3 &amp; Nine Months Ended 31.12.2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CHENNAI+PETROLEUM+CORPORATION+LTD.&title=Chennai+Petroleum+Corporation+Ltd+Reports+Audited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Ended+31.12.2025&newsId=9a6fbd2d-aac8-4de4-ab75-b1ed66068d60&token=OWE2ZmJkMmQtYWFj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a6fbd2d-aac8-4de4-ab75-b1ed66068d60</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 14:02:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Chennai Petroleum Corporation Ltd, a Government of India Enterprise and Group Company of IOCL, has reported the Audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the Quarter and Nine Months ended 31.12.2025. The results were recommended by the Audit Committee on 24.01.2026 and approved by the Board of Directors at their meeting held on the same date. The Statutory Auditor of the Company has issued Audit Reports with Unmodified Opinion on the Audited Standalone &amp; Consolidated Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the Quarter and Nine Months ended 31.12.2025</li><li>Recommended by the Audit Committee on 24.01.2026</li><li>Approved by the Board of Directors at their meeting held on 24.01.2026</li><li>Unmodified Opinion by the Statutory Auditor</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a9291ea0-32a4-4acb-a6c1-2e11483ff577.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CHENNAI PETROLEUM CORPORATION LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>