<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:53:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[INTELLECT] Intellect Design Arena &amp; Adrenalin Jointly Launch HR TeamSpace for Measurable Business Impact from HR AI</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Intellect+Design+Arena+Ltd&title=Intellect+Design+Arena+%26+Adrenalin+Jointly+Launch+HR+TeamSpace+for+Measurable+Business+Impact+from+HR+AI&newsId=b3075a51-d948-43cb-83d4-9404e7b9cf87&token=YjMwNzVhNTEtZDk0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3075a51-d948-43cb-83d4-9404e7b9cf87</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:53:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>In a significant development for the HR landscape, Intellect Design Arena Ltd. and Adrenalin eSystems have launched HR TeamSpace, a secure, collaborative AI environment for HR teams. Built on Intellect’s Purple Fabric Open Business Impact AI platform, HR TeamSpace aims to accelerate AI adoption across HR, enabling HR teams to deploy pre-built AI agents with speed and measurable outcomes. Priced at $99,500 per month for up to 50 users, HR TeamSpace addresses the gap between labour-intensive, manual operations and fragmented, one-off experiments with standalone AI tools. It provides a shared environment where teams can deploy AI with confidence, collaborate on use cases, and scale adoption. HR TeamSpace is designed to operationalise AI across critical HR functions and drive measurable business impact.</p><ul><li>Joint launch of HR TeamSpace by Intellect Design Arena and Adrenalin eSystems.</li><li>Built on Intellect’s Purple Fabric Open Business Impact AI platform.</li><li>Priced at $99,500 per month for up to 50 users, bringing enterprise-grade AI capabilities within reach of functional teams.</li><li>Enables HR teams to deploy pre-built AI agents with speed and measurable outcomes.</li><li>Addresses the gap between manual operations and fragmented AI experiments.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8c287d0f-e3ef-4416-8d1f-442804a81984.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Intellect Design Arena Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUPREMEIND] Supreme Industries Elects M.P. Taparia as Chairman of the Board and Company</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SUPREME+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Supreme+Industries+Elects+M.P.+Taparia+as+Chairman+of+the+Board+and+Company&newsId=0c22c3e6-124f-42ff-bc45-8771f997b5ae&token=MGMyMmMzZTYtMTI0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c22c3e6-124f-42ff-bc45-8771f997b5ae</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Supreme Industries Ltd has elected Shri M.P. Taparia, Managing Director, as the Chairman of the Board and Company with effect from 17th February, 2026. This decision was made at a Board of Directors meeting held on the same day. Taparia is now both the Chairman and Managing Director of the Company.</p><ul><li>Shri M.P. Taparia elected as Chairman of the Board and Company</li><li>Taparia is now both Chairman and Managing Director</li><li>Election took place at a Board of Directors meeting on 17th February, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f6c70bfe-f7d7-4ea2-a5b2-48d494990d31.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SUPREME INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PGINVIT] SEBI Grants Relaxation to POWERGRID Infrastructure Investment Trust Until March 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=POWERGRID+Infrastructure+Investment+Trust&title=SEBI+Grants+Relaxation+to+POWERGRID+Infrastructure+Investment+Trust+Until+March+2026&newsId=cd20c0e3-de9e-4f7d-90a2-ad43f3f375f6&token=Y2QyMGMwZTMtZGU5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd20c0e3-de9e-4f7d-90a2-ad43f3f375f6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:43:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>POWERGRID Infrastructure Investment Trust has received a relaxation from the Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) until March 31, 2026, from the applicability of certain provisions of the SEBI Circular no. SEBI/HO/DDHS-PoD-2/P/CIR/2023/153 dated September 11, 2023. The relaxation pertains to board nomination rights to unitholders of Infrastructure Investment Trusts (InvITs). However, SEBI did not grant relaxation from strict compliance with certain corporate governance norms related to the requisite number of independent directors on the Board of POWERGRID Unchahar Transmission Limited (PUTL). PUTL, being a subsidiary of Power Grid Corporation of India Limited, a government company, has the power to appoint Independent Directors on its Board, which vests with the Ministry of Power, Government of India. Any developments in this regard will be promptly communicated by PUTL.</p><ul><li>SEBI grants relaxation to POWERGRID Infrastructure Investment Trust until March 2026</li><li>Relaxation does not include certain corporate governance norms related to independent directors</li><li>POWERGRID Unchahar Transmission Limited, a subsidiary of Power Grid Corporation of India Limited, has the power to appoint Independent Directors on its Board</li><li>Any developments regarding Independent Directors will be communicated promptly</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/eb64accc-c810-4507-a500-4fecd3a0f1c6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: POWERGRID Infrastructure Investment Trust | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KRBL] KRBL Ltd&apos;s CFO Discusses Business Updates on ET NOW</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KRBL+LTD.&title=KRBL+Ltd%27s+CFO+Discusses+Business+Updates+on+ET+NOW&newsId=e5b22ab6-6ca7-4710-973a-821d82b7744f&token=ZTViMjJhYjYtNmNh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5b22ab6-6ca7-4710-973a-821d82b7744f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>KRBL Limited, through its Chief Financial Officer, Mr. Ashish Jain, has interacted with ET NOW, discussing business updates. The media interaction, held on February 17, 2026, can be viewed on the provided link.</p><ul><li>KRBL Ltd&apos;s CFO, Mr. Ashish Jain, had a media interaction with ET NOW</li><li>The interaction focused on business updates of KRBL Ltd</li><li>The discussion was held on February 17, 2026</li><li>The interaction can be viewed on a provided link</li><li>The interaction is in compliance with Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cb4da4a5-10c1-4bfe-9f11-064b4d2b10ad.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KRBL LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DODLA] Dodla Dairy Ltd Receives Platinum Award and Global Recognition at LACP Vision Awards 2024-25</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Dodla+Dairy+Ltd&title=Dodla+Dairy+Ltd+Receives+Platinum+Award+and+Global+Recognition+at+LACP+Vision+Awards+2024-25&newsId=6d06a25f-ffaa-4bed-8b2a-0e03bcd17f4f&token=NmQwNmEyNWYtZmZh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d06a25f-ffaa-4bed-8b2a-0e03bcd17f4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Award</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dodla Dairy Limited has been honored with a Platinum Award for excellence within its industry for the development of its Annual Report for FY 2024-25 at the League of American Communications Professionals (LACP) Vision Awards. The company also secured a spot among the Top 100 Reports Worldwide, ranking #41 globally, and received a Technical Achievement Award for overall communications. These recognitions highlight Dodla Dairy&apos;s commitment to transparency, quality disclosures, and excellence in corporate reporting.</p><ul><li>Received Platinum Award for excellence within the industry for the Annual Report FY 2024-25</li><li>Ranked #41 among the Top 100 Reports Worldwide</li><li>Awarded Technical Achievement Award for overall communications</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/96dc7bc9-df8b-4bd8-838f-bf848b0f8493.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Dodla Dairy Ltd | Category: Award</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RSYSTEMINT] R Systems International Ltd Allots 17,984 Equity Shares Upon Exercise of RSUs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=R+Systems+International+Limited&title=R+Systems+International+Ltd+Allots+17%2C984+Equity+Shares+Upon+Exercise+of+RSUs&newsId=a2a5f861-ddb8-4953-9404-4bbeb574ccc9&token=YTJhNWY4NjEtZGRi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2a5f861-ddb8-4953-9404-4bbeb574ccc9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:39:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>R Systems International Ltd has allotted 17,984 equity shares upon exercise of 17,984 Restricted Stock Units (RSUs) under the company&apos;s Management Incentive Plan 2023 (MIP). This allotment was approved by the Nomination, Remuneration and Compensation Committee of the Board of Directors on February 17, 2026. The issued, subscribed, and paid-up share capital of the company has subsequently increased to INR 11,84,82,061/-, divided into 11,84,82,061 equity shares of INR 1/- each. This information is shared in accordance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulation, 2015.</p><ul><li>R Systems International Ltd has allotted 17,984 equity shares upon exercise of RSUs.</li><li>The allotment was approved by the Nomination, Remuneration and Compensation Committee of the Board of Directors.</li><li>The issued, subscribed, and paid-up share capital of the company has increased to INR 11,84,82,061/-.</li><li>The allotment was made under the company&apos;s Management Incentive Plan 2023 (MIP).</li><li>The information is shared in accordance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulation, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/566eb9a4-ab74-4a6d-b6d3-1a6fe1236453.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: R Systems International Limited | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NRAGRINDQ] NR Agarwal Industries Ltd: Promoter Shares Encumbered Under SEBI Regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=N.R.AGARWAL+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=NR+Agarwal+Industries+Ltd%3A+Promoter+Shares+Encumbered+Under+SEBI+Regulations&newsId=71603325-e5d3-4c6b-9a03-424ebc01e202&token=NzE2MDMzMjUtZTVk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71603325-e5d3-4c6b-9a03-424ebc01e202</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:37:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Exchange has received disclosures of reasons for encumbrance by promoters of NR Agarwal Industries Ltd. The encumbered shares, amounting to 73.55% of the total share capital, are held by promoters Reena Agarwal and Raunak Agarwal. The encumbrances include pledges, non-release of pledges, and non-disposal undertakings in favor of entities such as SBICAP Trustee Company Limited and Axis Bank Limited. The purpose of the encumbrance is to secure debt instruments for the benefit of the listed company. The total amount involved is approximately INR 4,26,80,00,000, with the shares valued at INR 2,65,36,03,576, INR 6,18,84,03,811, INR 8,12,06,63,565, and INR 5,65,76,83,096 at the time of the events or agreements. The end use of the money is for business purposes, specifically for repayment of term loans.</p><ul><li>Promoter shares of NR Agarwal Industries Ltd encumbered under SEBI regulations</li><li>73.55% of total share capital encumbered</li><li>Encumbrances include pledges, non-release of pledges, and non-disposal undertakings</li><li>Amount involved: INR 4,26,80,00,000</li><li>End use of money: Repayment of term loans for the benefit of the listed company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/36ABE285_77E8_4FFC_AE30_CBE02E3C5579_120505.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: N.R.AGARWAL INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NRAGRINDQ] NR Agarwal Industries Ltd: Promoters Disclose Share Encumbrance under SEBI Regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=N.R.AGARWAL+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=NR+Agarwal+Industries+Ltd%3A+Promoters+Disclose+Share+Encumbrance+under+SEBI+Regulations&newsId=844040b3-c199-435b-9755-51e16872db65&token=ODQ0MDQwYjMtYzE5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">844040b3-c199-435b-9755-51e16872db65</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:35:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>NR Agarwal Industries Ltd. announced that promoters R N Agarwal and Reena Agarwal have disclosed encumbrance of shares under Regulation 31(1) and 31(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. The shares were encumbered on 16th February 2026 with Raunak Agarwal as the trustee. The encumbrance was made for non-disposal undertaking loans from State Bank of India and Punjab National Bank.</p><ul><li>NR Agarwal Industries Ltd. promoters R N Agarwal and Reena Agarwal disclose share encumbrance under SEBI regulations.</li><li>Encumbrance made on 16th February 2026 for non-disposal undertaking loans from State Bank of India and Punjab National Bank.</li><li>Raunak Agarwal appointed as the trustee for the encumbered shares.</li><li>7978105 shares encumbered, representing 46.88% of the total shares of NR Agarwal Industries Ltd.</li><li>4538861 shares encumbered, representing 26.67% of the total shares of NR Agarwal Industries Ltd.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5113C886_7186_4EB6_BDD7_5CE3F950323F_120329.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: N.R.AGARWAL INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SENORES] Espee Therapeutics LLP Creates Pledge of 4 Lakhs Equity Shares in Senores Pharmaceuticals Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Senores+Pharmaceuticals+Ltd&title=Espee+Therapeutics+LLP+Creates+Pledge+of+4+Lakhs+Equity+Shares+in+Senores+Pharmaceuticals+Ltd&newsId=d2446dd0-c1ca-4baa-b791-2469f2e8724c&token=ZDI0NDZkZDAtYzFj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2446dd0-c1ca-4baa-b791-2469f2e8724c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Pledge</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Espee Therapeutics LLP has created a pledge of 4,00,000 (Four Lakhs) Equity Shares in Senores Pharmaceuticals Limited. This disclosure was made in accordance with Regulation 31(1) and 31(2) of Securities and Exchange Board of India (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. The shares encumbered by Espee Therapeutics LLP and other promoters are detailed in the disclosure.</p><ul><li>Espee Therapeutics LLP creates pledge of 4 Lakhs Equity Shares in Senores Pharmaceuticals Ltd</li><li>Disclosure made under Regulation 31(1) and 31(2) of Securities and Exchange Board of India (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011</li><li>Espee Therapeutics LLP holds 7.4801% of the total shares of Senores Pharmaceuticals Ltd</li><li>Other promoters also hold encumbered shares in Senores Pharmaceuticals Ltd</li><li>The purpose of the pledge is not explicitly stated in the document</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/12B5F729_EBDF_433B_870A_0A8E76E9928A_115810.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Senores Pharmaceuticals Ltd | Category: Pledge</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUPREMEIND] Supreme Industries&apos; MD, M.P. Taparia, Elected as Chairman</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SUPREME+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Supreme+Industries%27+MD%2C+M.P.+Taparia%2C+Elected+as+Chairman&newsId=b252c9c8-4668-4626-b556-1c9e5df62a1a&token=YjI1MmM5YzgtNDY2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b252c9c8-4668-4626-b556-1c9e5df62a1a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Supreme Industries Ltd. announced the election of its Managing Director, M.P. Taparia, as the Chairman of the Board and Company. The election took place during the Board of Directors&apos; meeting on February 17, 2026. Taparia now holds the positions of Chairman and Managing Director.</p><ul><li>M.P. Taparia elected as Chairman of Supreme Industries Ltd.</li><li>Taparia continues to serve as Managing Director.</li><li>Election took place during a Board of Directors&apos; meeting on February 17, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/134ff644-590e-4022-b97f-9e90db6c44dd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SUPREME INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>