<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 02:00:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ADANIPORTS] Adani Ports Announces Cash Tender Offers for up to US$345,137,000 4.0% Senior Notes due 2027 and US$150,000,000 3.10% Senior Notes due 2031</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADANI+PORTS+AND+SPECIAL+ECONOMIC+ZONE+LTD.&title=Adani+Ports+Announces+Cash+Tender+Offers+for+up+to+US%24345%2C137%2C000+4.0%25+Senior+Notes+due+2027+and+US%24150%2C000%2C000+3.10%25+Senior+Notes+due+2031&newsId=2e260f8e-bb08-440a-8dcb-6b44f7189812&token=MmUyNjBmOGUtYmIw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e260f8e-bb08-440a-8dcb-6b44f7189812</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 00:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone Limited has commenced tender offers to purchase for cash up to US$345,137,000 in aggregate principal amount of its outstanding 4.0% Senior Notes due 2027 and up to US$150,000,000 in aggregate principal amount of its outstanding 3.10% Senior Notes due 2031. The Tender Offers are being made as part of the Company’s continuing capital management programme and to further proactively optimize its liability structure.</p><ul><li>Adani Ports has commenced tender offers for up to US$345,137,000 in aggregate principal amount of its outstanding 4.0% Senior Notes due 2027 and up to US$150,000,000 in aggregate principal amount of its outstanding 3.10% Senior Notes due 2031.</li><li>The Tender Offers are being made as part of the Company’s continuing capital management programme and to further proactively optimize its liability structure.</li><li>The Tender Offers will expire at 5:00 p.m., New York time, on March 11, 2026.</li><li>Holders who validly tender and do not validly withdraw their Notes on or prior to the Withdrawal Deadline, and whose Notes are accepted for payment by the Company, will receive the Tender Offer Consideration and the Early Tender Premium.</li><li>The Company intends to fund the Notes accepted for purchase in the Tender Offers from a mix of borrowed debt and its cash reserves.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7e43adf1-e935-4284-b2d6-812c82bcb49a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADANI PORTS AND SPECIAL ECONOMIC ZONE LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AMBER] Amber Enterprises India Ltd Approves Q3 and Nine Months Ended Dec 2025 Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Amber+Enterprises+India+Ltd&title=Amber+Enterprises+India+Ltd+Approves+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+Dec+2025+Financial+Results&newsId=8acc31c4-61c5-44b6-9697-b5e99c4d8b12&token=OGFjYzMxYzQtNjFj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8acc31c4-61c5-44b6-9697-b5e99c4d8b12</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 00:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Amber Enterprises India Ltd has approved the unaudited financial results (standalone and consolidated) for the quarter and nine months ended 31 December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue, net profit, and total comprehensive income for the quarter and nine months ended 31 December 2025 have been disclosed in the financial results. The results have been reviewed by the independent auditor S.R. Batliboi &amp; Co LLP.</p><ul><li>Amber Enterprises India Ltd has approved the unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended Dec 2025</li><li>The results have been reviewed by the independent auditor S.R. Batliboi &amp; Co LLP</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue, net profit, and total comprehensive income for the quarter and nine months ended 31 December 2025 have been disclosed</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ec571ce4-967c-4c9e-9e4f-c20247cfbea1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Amber Enterprises India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AMBER] Amber Enterprises India Ltd. Announces Q3 and 9M FY2025 Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Amber+Enterprises+India+Ltd&title=Amber+Enterprises+India+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+9M+FY2025+Financial+Results&newsId=6ec49691-2d97-4a82-ae20-b415ab594814&token=NmVjNDk2OTEtMmQ5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ec49691-2d97-4a82-ae20-b415ab594814</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 00:06:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Amber Enterprises India Ltd. announced the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025 at a Board Meeting held on 9th February 2026. The company&apos;s revenue and net profit for the quarter showed an increase compared to the same period last year. The Board also approved the unaudited consolidated financial results and the limited review report issued by the statutory auditor.</p><ul><li>Unaudited financial results for Q3 and 9M FY2025 approved</li><li>Increase in revenue and net profit compared to Q3 and 9M FY2024</li><li>Limited review report submitted by the statutory auditor</li><li>Board Meeting commenced at 12:00 Noon IST and concluded at 10:30 P.M. IST</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4883cf28-d9f2-48e9-87ae-45d5c5663c11.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Amber Enterprises India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AMBER] Amber Enterprises India Ltd Reports on QIP Proceeds Utilization for Q4 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Amber+Enterprises+India+Ltd&title=Amber+Enterprises+India+Ltd+Reports+on+QIP+Proceeds+Utilization+for+Q4+2025&newsId=00592fff-5a72-444d-aed6-cbabc154509c&token=MDA1OTJmZmYtNWE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00592fff-5a72-444d-aed6-cbabc154509c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 00:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Amber Enterprises India Ltd has released the Monitoring Agency Report for the quarter ended 31st December 2025, highlighting the utilization of proceeds raised through the Qualified Institutions Placement (QIP). The report was reviewed by the Audit Committee and taken on record by the Board of Directors. The company raised Rs. 1,000.00 crore through the QIP, and the Monitoring Agency, CARE Ratings Limited, confirmed that the utilization is as per the disclosures in the Offer Document.</p><ul><li>Amber Enterprises India Ltd released the Monitoring Agency Report for Q4 2025</li><li>The company raised Rs. 1,000.00 crore through the QIP</li><li>The utilization of proceeds is as per the disclosures in the Offer Document</li><li>The report was reviewed by the Audit Committee</li><li>The Board of Directors took the report on record</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9e932a53-6600-440b-babe-ff729d8f4b59.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Amber Enterprises India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AMBER] Amber Enterprises Reports Q3 &amp; 9MFY26 Financials with 38% Revenue Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Amber+Enterprises+India+Ltd&title=Amber+Enterprises+Reports+Q3+%26+9MFY26+Financials+with+38%25+Revenue+Growth&newsId=192b2290-93a4-4084-8a58-9eb067c9b457&token=MTkyYjIyOTAtOTNh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">192b2290-93a4-4084-8a58-9eb067c9b457</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 00:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Amber Enterprises India Ltd. has declared its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company reported a consolidated revenue of 38,039 Cr for 9MFY26 and 32,943 Cr for Q3FY26, representing a growth of 29% and 38% respectively. The operating EBITDA for Q3FY26 was 3,247 Cr, up by 53% YoY.</p><ul><li>Revenue for 9MFY26 stood at 38,039 Cr, with a growth of 29% YoY.</li><li>Revenue for Q3FY26 was 32,943 Cr, reflecting a growth of 38% YoY.</li><li>Operating EBITDA for Q3FY26 was 3,247 Cr, up by 53% YoY.</li><li>Profit After Tax (PAT) for Q3FY26 was 384 Cr, a growth of 128% YoY.</li><li>Amber Enterprises secured land allotment at YEIDA, Uttar Pradesh, for new manufacturing facilities.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/16fe6e4a-4d6e-4954-b0bb-d5fc5e140d46.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Amber Enterprises India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MPSLTD] MPS Ltd Completes Acquisition of Unbound Medicine, Inc., USA</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MPS+LTD.&title=MPS+Ltd+Completes+Acquisition+of+Unbound+Medicine%2C+Inc.%2C+USA&newsId=6f792917-ff85-4b96-8a82-b954c2565132&token=NmY3OTI5MTctZmY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f792917-ff85-4b96-8a82-b954c2565132</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 00:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>MPS Ltd has successfully completed the acquisition of 100% stake in Unbound Medicine, Inc., USA, through its wholly-owned subsidiary MPS North America LLC. The total consideration for the acquisition is USD 16.50 million, payable in accordance with the terms and conditions set out in the Stock Purchase Agreement and other definitive transaction documents. Unbound Medicine, Inc., USA has become a wholly-owned step-down subsidiary of MPS Limited with effect from the date of completion.</p><ul><li>MPS North America LLC, a wholly-owned subsidiary of MPS Limited, has completed the acquisition of 100% stake in Unbound Medicine, Inc., USA</li><li>The total consideration for the acquisition is USD 16.50 million</li><li>The acquisition is subject to customary adjustments and was completed upon satisfaction of customary closing conditions</li><li>Unbound Medicine, Inc., USA has become a wholly-owned step-down subsidiary of MPS Limited with effect from the date of completion</li><li>The acquisition details have been disclosed as required under SEBI Listing Regulations and SEBI Master Circular No. HO/49/14/14(7)2025-CFD-POD2/1/3762/2026 dated 30 January 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b6f922cb-a72e-4106-a9ee-db9a27fde430.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MPS LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADANIPORTS] Adani Ports Approves Tender Offer for Up to US$495,137,000 of Its Outstanding Senior Notes</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADANI+PORTS+AND+SPECIAL+ECONOMIC+ZONE+LTD.&title=Adani+Ports+Approves+Tender+Offer+for+Up+to+US%24495%2C137%2C000+of+Its+Outstanding+Senior+Notes&newsId=a143f6f0-074f-42fc-b938-eee995aa875e&token=YTE0M2Y2ZjAtMDc0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a143f6f0-074f-42fc-b938-eee995aa875e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 00:04:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone Limited&apos;s Finance Committee has approved a tender offer to purchase up to US$345,137,000 in principal amount of its outstanding USS$345,137,000 4.0% Senior Notes due 2027 and up to US$150,000,000 in principal amount of its outstanding USS$500,000,000 3.10% Senior Notes due 2031. The Committee also approved the Tender Offer Memorandum, Dealer Manager Agreement, and other necessary documents for the tender offer.</p><ul><li>Adani Ports has approved a tender offer for up to US$345,137,000 in principal amount of its 4.0% Senior Notes due 2027 and up to US$150,000,000 in principal amount of its 3.10% Senior Notes due 2031.</li><li>The Finance Committee approved the Tender Offer Memorandum, Dealer Manager Agreement, and other necessary documents for the tender offer.</li><li>The tender offer is not a related party transaction.</li><li>The tender offer is not being registered in India and does not constitute an offer, invitation, or solicitation in India.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9c3ae264-1cad-4f66-9fc3-a6fd7f204f55.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADANI PORTS AND SPECIAL ECONOMIC ZONE LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KBSINDIA] KBS India Ltd Reports Q3 Results for FY2025-26, Profit Before Tax Increases</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KBS+INDIA+LIMITED&title=KBS+India+Ltd+Reports+Q3+Results+for+FY2025-26%2C+Profit+Before+Tax+Increases&newsId=2707a9ad-536f-4a57-a80f-cf3f89b18339&token=MjcwN2E5YWQtNTM2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2707a9ad-536f-4a57-a80f-cf3f89b18339</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 20:34:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>KBS India Ltd, a shares and stock broking company, has reported its unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s profit before tax has increased compared to the previous year. However, there are certain matters that require attention, such as the non-provision of gratuity liability for employees and outstanding loans to a former subsidiary, KBS Capital Management Singapore Pte Ltd, which has been struck off.</p><ul><li>Profit before tax has increased compared to the previous year.</li><li>Gratuity liability for employees is not provided for as required by Ind AS 19 on &apos;Employee Benefits&apos;.</li><li>Long-term loan and current account balance amounting to Rs. 16,65,40,533/- and Rs. 8,02,444/- respectively are outstanding and receivable from KBS Capital Management Singapore Pte Ltd.</li><li>The company&apos;s operations are focused on shares and stock broking.</li><li>The unaudited financial results have been reviewed by the Audit committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b9f87321-a014-4707-aaf8-8e93a6078abe.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KBS INDIA LIMITED | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STDSHOE] Standard Shoe Sole And Mould (India) Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results on Feb 13, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=STANDARD+SHOE+SOLE+AND+MOULD+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Standard+Shoe+Sole+And+Mould+%28India%29+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+on+Feb+13%2C+2026&newsId=8ebb76a8-0167-4e38-86b7-9cbd57421de9&token=OGViYjc2YTgtMDE2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ebb76a8-0167-4e38-86b7-9cbd57421de9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:51:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Standard Shoe Sole And Mould (India) Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 13, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting is scheduled in accordance with Regulation 33 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The company has also announced that the trading window for dealing with shares/securities of the company has been closed for designated persons as per the company&apos;s insider trading code and will reopen after 48 hours from the announcement of the financial results.</p><ul><li>Standard Shoe Sole And Mould (India) Ltd to consider and approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended 31 December 2025.</li><li>Trading window closed for designated persons as per the company&apos;s insider trading code.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b1058bc4-1981-4ac7-92e3-70bac9c25a24.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: STANDARD SHOE SOLE AND MOULD (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AKASHDEEP] Kalyan Capitals Ltd to Approve Un-audited Financial Results on Feb 12, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Akashdeep+Metal+Industries+Ltd&title=Kalyan+Capitals+Ltd+to+Approve+Un-audited+Financial+Results+on+Feb+12%2C+2026&newsId=d11dacb2-7cc3-4768-8172-07c94b5d97e9&token=ZDExZGFjYjItN2Nj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d11dacb2-7cc3-4768-8172-07c94b5d97e9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 17:51:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kalyan Capitals Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 12, 2026, to consider and approve the Un-audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for designated persons, their immediate relatives, and other connected persons will be closed till the conclusion of 48 hours after the declaration of the Un-audited Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Kalyan Capitals Ltd to consider and approve Un-audited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>Trading window to be closed for all designated persons, their immediate relatives, and other connected persons till the conclusion of 48 hours after the declaration of Un-audited Financial Results.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0cf6d1df-5cd5-4fba-ba6d-217ba6157900.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Akashdeep Metal Industries Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>