<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:28:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[BONDADA] Bondada Engineering Ltd Approves Q3 Results for Dec 2025 with Profit Before Tax at 8,191.66 Lakhs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Bondada+Engineering+Ltd&title=Bondada+Engineering+Ltd+Approves+Q3+Results+for+Dec+2025+with+Profit+Before+Tax+at+8%2C191.66+Lakhs&newsId=c00117c3-1397-488d-a036-778506701f1f&token=YzAwMTE3YzMtMTM5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c00117c3-1397-488d-a036-778506701f1f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bondada Engineering Ltd, at its board meeting on 27th January 2026, approved the un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company reported a profit before tax of 8,191.66 Lakhs for the quarter. The review report by Sreedar Mohan &amp; Associates, the independent auditor, concluded that the financial statements were free of material misstatements.</p><ul><li>Bondada Engineering Ltd approved the un-audited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December 2025.</li><li>The company reported a profit before tax of 8,191.66 Lakhs for the quarter.</li><li>The independent auditor, Sreedar Mohan &amp; Associates, concluded that the financial statements were free of material misstatements.</li><li>The financial results include the results of six subsidiaries.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/52a164d9-b7b8-412f-aaee-d7d7cc6033f2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Bondada Engineering Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GALAGEX] Galaxy Agrico Exports Ltd Executive Director, Mr. Abhay Vasantrao Galgate, Resigns Due to Health Reasons</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GALAXY+AGRICO+EXPORTS+LTD.&title=Galaxy+Agrico+Exports+Ltd+Executive+Director%2C+Mr.+Abhay+Vasantrao+Galgate%2C+Resigns+Due+to+Health+Reasons&newsId=042c7f1d-dd80-4293-8972-c6f89321d1a1&token=MDQyYzdmMWQtZGQ4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">042c7f1d-dd80-4293-8972-c6f89321d1a1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:21:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Galaxy Agrico Exports Ltd announced the resignation of its Executive Director, Mr. Abhay Vasantrao Galgate, due to health reasons. Mr. Galgate suffered a hand injury and is currently unable to perform his duties effectively. His resignation will take effect from 27th January, 2026. Mr. Galgate has confirmed that there are no other material reasons for his resignation. The company&apos;s Board of Directors will take note of the resignation at the upcoming Board Meeting and file it with the Stock Exchange accordingly. Mr. Galgate has also requested the company to remove his appointment as Executive Director, delete his name from all records as an authorized signatory, and not to assign any management position to him in the future.</p><ul><li>Mr. Abhay Vasantrao Galgate, Executive Director of Galaxy Agrico Exports Ltd, has resigned due to health reasons.</li><li>His resignation will take effect from 27th January, 2026.</li><li>Mr. Galgate has confirmed that there are no other material reasons for his resignation.</li><li>The company&apos;s Board of Directors will take note of the resignation at the upcoming Board Meeting.</li><li>Mr. Galgate has requested the company to remove his appointment as Executive Director and not to assign any management position to him in the future.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8cb7bc8a-1219-4a9e-a39d-aa2d88645a27.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GALAXY AGRICO EXPORTS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SIYSIL] Siyaram Silk Mills Declares 2nd Interim Dividend of Rs. 3/- for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SIYARAM+SILK+MILLS+LTD.-%24&title=Siyaram+Silk+Mills+Declares+2nd+Interim+Dividend+of+Rs.+3%2F-+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=a6d42b5c-6782-4450-88fc-523a9e112dcd&token=YTZkNDJiNWMtNjc4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a6d42b5c-6782-4450-88fc-523a9e112dcd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:21:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Siyaram Silk Mills Ltd. has declared a 2nd interim dividend of Rs. 3/- (150%) per equity share for the financial year 2025-26. The record date for determining the entitlement of shareholders for this dividend is 02nd February, 2026. The company&apos;s equity shares of Rs. 2/- each fully paid up will be used for this dividend payment.</p><ul><li>Siyaram Silk Mills declares 2nd interim dividend of Rs. 3/- per equity share for FY 2025-26</li><li>Record date for dividend entitlement set as 02nd February, 2026</li><li>Dividend payment to be made on equity shares of Rs. 2/- each fully paid up</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1c80860e-36ba-430f-9679-0578bb17f694.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SIYARAM SILK MILLS LTD.-$ | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CENTENKA] Century Enka Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on Feb 6, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CENTURY+ENKA+LTD.&title=Century+Enka+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+Feb+6%2C+2026&newsId=20815e0d-bf77-4d7c-972b-fe787cc6e3cf&token=MjA4MTVlMGQtYmY3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">20815e0d-bf77-4d7c-972b-fe787cc6e3cf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Century Enka Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 6, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company has been closed for all Connected/Designated persons from January 15, 2026, and will remain closed until 48 hours after the announcement of the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated financial results.</p><ul><li>Century Enka Ltd to approve Q3 and nine months financial results on Feb 6, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company is closed for all Connected/Designated persons from January 15, 2026</li><li>Trading window to remain closed until 48 hours after the announcement of the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated financial results</li><li>Announcement made in compliance with Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements), Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5bef2101-8315-4d58-aa01-ac354ce68737.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CENTURY ENKA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAGL] Spice Lounge Food Works Ltd to Host Landmark Music Event Celebrating 50 Years of Maestro Ilaiyaraaja</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shalimar+Agencies+Ltd&title=Spice+Lounge+Food+Works+Ltd+to+Host+Landmark+Music+Event+Celebrating+50+Years+of+Maestro+Ilaiyaraaja&newsId=da2ce9f4-0a95-434c-8b61-5cb227636855&token=ZGEyY2U5ZjQtMGE5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">da2ce9f4-0a95-434c-8b61-5cb227636855</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Spice Lounge Food Works Ltd, through its cultural and experiential events platform XORA World, will host a large-scale music event celebrating 50 years of Maestro Ilaiyaraaja, one of India’s most iconic and influential composers. The event will be held on 28 March 2026 at Gachibowli Stadium, Hyderabad. This event marks a significant milestone for XORA World and reflects the Company’s strategic expansion into experience-led consumer platforms alongside its core food and beverage businesses.</p><ul><li>Spice Lounge Food Works Ltd to host a large-scale music event celebrating 50 years of Maestro Ilaiyaraaja</li><li>Event to be held on 28 March 2026 at Gachibowli Stadium, Hyderabad</li><li>XORA World, a proprietary platform of Rightfest, a wholly owned subsidiary / group entity of Spice Lounge Food Works Limited, will host the event</li><li>Event reflects the Company’s strategic expansion into experience-led consumer platforms alongside its core food and beverage businesses</li><li>Maestro Ilaiyaraaja has composed over 7,000 songs across a remarkable five-decade career, creating music for thousands of films in multiple languages</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0c6a1348-facf-43d3-a5d7-c44090e3f2b0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shalimar Agencies Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SIYSIL] Siyaram Silk Mills Ltd. Declares 2nd Interim Dividend of Rs. 3/- for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SIYARAM+SILK+MILLS+LTD.-%24&title=Siyaram+Silk+Mills+Ltd.+Declares+2nd+Interim+Dividend+of+Rs.+3%2F-+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=2ce8227f-82da-4032-9fb4-9aae3d75b2d5&token=MmNlODIyN2YtODJk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ce8227f-82da-4032-9fb4-9aae3d75b2d5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:21:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Siyaram Silk Mills Ltd. has declared a 2nd interim dividend of Rs. 3/- (150%) per equity share for the financial year 2025-26. The record date for determining the entitlement of shareholders for this dividend is fixed as Monday, 0274 February, 2026. The Board of Directors made this decision at their meeting on Tuesday, 27th January, 2026.</p><ul><li>Siyaram Silk Mills Ltd. declares 2nd interim dividend of Rs. 3/- per equity share for FY 2025-26</li><li>Record date for dividend entitlement set as Monday, 0274 February, 2026</li><li>Decision made at the Board of Directors meeting on Tuesday, 27th January, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8a114aca-7782-4043-a822-146fbd0709e7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SIYARAM SILK MILLS LTD.-$ | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SIYSIL] Siyaram Silk Mills Ltd: Board Approves Unaudited Financial Results, Declares 2nd Interim Dividend, and Appoints New Vice President</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SIYARAM+SILK+MILLS+LTD.-%24&title=Siyaram+Silk+Mills+Ltd%3A+Board+Approves+Unaudited+Financial+Results%2C+Declares+2nd+Interim+Dividend%2C+and+Appoints+New+Vice+President&newsId=d376b53c-053b-4918-bc3d-8a3f73ae8e31&token=ZDM3NmI1M2MtMDUz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d376b53c-053b-4918-bc3d-8a3f73ae8e31</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:02:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Siyaram Silk Mills Ltd held a Board Meeting on 27th January, 2026. The Board approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025, declared a 2nd interim dividend of Rs. 3/- per equity share, and appointed Shri. Dinesh Kumar Jaithliya as Vice President — Finance. The meeting was commenced at 4.30 p.m. and concluded at 8.05 p.m.</p><ul><li>Approval of unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025</li><li>Declaration of 2nd interim dividend of Rs. 3/- per equity share for the Financial Year 2025-26</li><li>Appointment of Shri. Dinesh Kumar Jaithliya as Vice President — Finance as a Senior Managerial Personnel of the Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dd8f6069-5d36-4d0d-8652-a4933151bf43.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SIYARAM SILK MILLS LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IDEA] Vodafone Idea Ltd Utilizes FPO Proceeds as Per Disclosures</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vodafone+Idea+Ltd&title=Vodafone+Idea+Ltd+Utilizes+FPO+Proceeds+as+Per+Disclosures&newsId=4ac6db5c-05b6-482a-981e-fa01a8982886&token=NGFjNmRiNWMtMDVi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4ac6db5c-05b6-482a-981e-fa01a8982886</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vodafone Idea Ltd has utilized the proceeds from its Further Public Offer (FPO) as per the disclosures in the Offer Document, as confirmed by the Monitoring Agency Report for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. The report, issued by CARE Ratings Limited, has been reviewed by the Audit Committee and taken on record by the Board.</p><ul><li>Vodafone Idea Ltd has utilized the FPO proceeds as per the disclosures in the Offer Document.</li><li>The utilization of funds has been confirmed by the Monitoring Agency Report for the quarter ended 31 December 2025.</li><li>The report has been reviewed by the Audit Committee and taken on record by the Board.</li><li>The Monitoring Agency Report is in line with the format prescribed by SEBI.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/59080495-4720-41d0-8c09-36489a227845.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vodafone Idea Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUNTECK] Sunteck Realty&apos;s Q4 2025 Monitoring Agency Report: No Deviation from Objects, Proceeds Utilized as Per SEBI Regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SUNTECK+REALTY+LTD.&title=Sunteck+Realty%27s+Q4+2025+Monitoring+Agency+Report%3A+No+Deviation+from+Objects%2C+Proceeds+Utilized+as+Per+SEBI+Regulations&newsId=87642717-53e7-4c0c-9c47-f83c7448281c&token=ODc2NDI3MTctNTNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">87642717-53e7-4c0c-9c47-f83c7448281c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:02:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sunteck Realty Ltd, a prominent player in the real estate sector, has released the Monitoring Agency Report for the quarter ended 31st December, 2025. The report, issued by India Ratings &amp; Research Private Limited, indicates no deviation from the objects of the preferential issue of warrants convertible into equity shares. The company has utilized the proceeds as per the Schedule XI of the SEBI ICDR Regulations. The monitoring agency, India Ratings &amp; Research Private Limited, has not observed any deviation from the object and has declared that the report provides an objective view of the utilization of the issue proceeds.</p><ul><li>No deviation from the objects of the preferential issue of warrants convertible into equity shares</li><li>Proceeds utilized as per the Schedule XI of the SEBI ICDR Regulations</li><li>Monitoring agency, India Ratings &amp; Research Private Limited, has not observed any deviation from the object</li><li>The report provides an objective view of the utilization of the issue proceeds</li><li>The company is in the real estate sector</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1e21c1f5-ad41-4ab8-a894-7d9f19b16813.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SUNTECK REALTY LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PENINLAND] Peninsula Land Ltd Subsidiary Invests in Zenithvista Real Estate LLP for Mumbai Real Estate Project</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PENINSULA+LAND+LTD.&title=Peninsula+Land+Ltd+Subsidiary+Invests+in+Zenithvista+Real+Estate+LLP+for+Mumbai+Real+Estate+Project&newsId=3d93d8e5-e94c-4ebe-a31c-01b41a721621&token=M2Q5M2Q4ZTUtZTk0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3d93d8e5-e94c-4ebe-a31c-01b41a721621</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Peninsula Land Ltd&apos;s wholly owned subsidiary, Peninsula Holdings and Investments Private Limited (PHIPL), has invested in M/s. Zenithvista Real Estate LLP (the LLP) for a residential redevelopment project in Mumbai. The LLP is a Real Estate Platform entity formed under a Joint Venture Agreement (JVA) between the Company, the Real Estate 2.0 Residential Opportunities Fund (a scheme of Alpha Alternatives Special Situations Fund), and Delta Corp Limited. PHIPL has committed an initial investment of INR 29,420 for a 29.42% stake in the LLP&apos;s fixed capital and has made further fund commitments as required for the project.</p><ul><li>Peninsula Land Ltd&apos;s subsidiary PHIPL invests in M/s. Zenithvista Real Estate LLP for a Mumbai real estate project</li><li>The LLP is a Real Estate Platform entity formed under a Joint Venture Agreement between Peninsula Land Ltd, Alpha Alternatives Special Situations Fund, and Delta Corp Limited</li><li>PHIPL has committed an initial investment of INR 29,420 for a 29.42% stake in the LLP&apos;s fixed capital</li><li>The LLP is expected to undertake a residential redevelopment project in Mumbai</li><li>PHIPL has also made further fund commitments as required for the project</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d0248d77-26b0-49ae-8625-df8c1bbab052.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PENINSULA LAND LTD. | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>