<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 18:43:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[VASWANI] Vaswani Industries Ltd Closes Trading Window Ahead of Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VASWANI+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Vaswani+Industries+Ltd+Closes+Trading+Window+Ahead+of+Board+Meeting&newsId=d0e2ceb8-e0ed-4d8d-b3a3-2503966d0fd8&token=ZDBlMmNlYjgtZTBl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d0e2ceb8-e0ed-4d8d-b3a3-2503966d0fd8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:44:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vaswani Industries Ltd has announced the closure of its trading window from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The decision comes in anticipation of the Board of Directors&apos; meeting scheduled on February 13, 2026, to consider these financial results. The trading window for dealing in the company&apos;s securities will remain closed for Directors, KMPs, designated employees, and other covered persons under the Insider Trading Code till 48 hours after the conclusion of the Board Meeting, i.e., up to February 15, 2026.</p><ul><li>Vaswani Industries Ltd closes trading window from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of Q4 2025 financial results</li><li>Board of Directors meeting scheduled on February 13, 2026, to consider these financial results</li><li>Trading window to remain closed for Directors, KMPs, designated employees, and other covered persons under the Insider Trading Code till 48 hours after the Board Meeting</li><li>Trading window to reopen on February 15, 2026</li><li>Announcement made to keep stakeholders informed</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e0f12d33-b330-499d-9ef3-b5c2f84d6732.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VASWANI INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VASWANI] Vaswani Industries Ltd to Approve Q4 Results on Feb 13, 2026; Trading Window Closed</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VASWANI+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Vaswani+Industries+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+Results+on+Feb+13%2C+2026%3B+Trading+Window+Closed&newsId=142c0f8d-5a6c-4dac-af8b-969ce9b82995&token=MTQyYzBmOGQtNWE2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">142c0f8d-5a6c-4dac-af8b-969ce9b82995</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vaswani Industries Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 13, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited standalone financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. In accordance with the Company’s Code of Conduct for Prevention of Insider Trading, the trading window for trading in the Company’s equity shares has been closed from January 01, 2026, till the expiry of 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results.</p><ul><li>Vaswani Industries Ltd to consider and approve Q4 results on Feb 13, 2026</li><li>Trading Window closed from Jan 01, 2026, till 48 hours after result declaration</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/eb9b906d-1564-466b-ab4b-278840564bdc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VASWANI INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TELGE] Telge Projects Ltd to Consider Unaudited Financial Results and ESOP Scheme on Feb 09, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Telge+Projects+Ltd&title=Telge+Projects+Ltd+to+Consider+Unaudited+Financial+Results+and+ESOP+Scheme+on+Feb+09%2C+2026&newsId=44c5e42e-ef23-421b-b4e1-d6a9c1354ba9&token=NDRjNWU0MmUtZWYy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">44c5e42e-ef23-421b-b4e1-d6a9c1354ba9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:34:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Telge Projects Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 09, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results (Standalone &amp; Consolidated) for the Third Quarter ended on December 31, 2025. The Board will also consider approving the Employee Stock Option (ESOP) Scheme of the Company, subject to applicable laws and approvals. Any other matter with the permission of the board may also be discussed.</p><ul><li>Telge Projects Ltd to consider and approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 2025</li><li>The company may approve Employee Stock Option (ESOP) Scheme, subject to applicable laws and approvals</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/aa1368d1-3b84-4a66-9d52-68341ac25128.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Telge Projects Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ANANTAM] Anantam Highways Trust to Approve Q3 Results and Declare Distribution on Feb 11, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Anantam+Highways+Trust&title=Anantam+Highways+Trust+to+Approve+Q3+Results+and+Declare+Distribution+on+Feb+11%2C+2026&newsId=9b977fa6-ab80-4fef-be12-6877d0e89680&token=OWI5NzdmYTYtYWI4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b977fa6-ab80-4fef-be12-6877d0e89680</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Anantam Highways Trust is set to hold a Board of Directors meeting on February 11, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The Trust will also declare any distribution to Unitholders for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, with the record date set for February 16, 2026. The trading window for Designated Persons and their immediate relatives remains closed until 48 hours after the public announcement of the meeting&apos;s outcome.</p><ul><li>Anantam Highways Trust to approve Q3 results on Feb 11, 2026</li><li>Distribution to Unitholders for Q4 2025 to be declared</li><li>Record date for distribution set as Feb 16, 2026</li><li>Trading window for Designated Persons and relatives closed until 48 hours after the announcement</li><li>Unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results to be approved</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/13438171-ba15-4944-ad9d-b0655d8ddbad.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Anantam Highways Trust | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ONMOBILE] OnMobile Global Ltd Appoints Manoranjan Mohapatra as Additional Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=OnMobile+Global+Ltd.&title=OnMobile+Global+Ltd+Appoints+Manoranjan+Mohapatra+as+Additional+Independent+Director&newsId=f24d4f84-9117-4ca1-b9ed-130cd5cfee59&token=ZjI0ZDRmODQtOTEx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f24d4f84-9117-4ca1-b9ed-130cd5cfee59</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:21:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>OnMobile Global Ltd has informed the stock exchange about the appointment of Manoranjan Mohapatra as an Additional Director in the category of Independent Director. Mohapatra has over four decades of experience in the telecom and fintech industries and has served as CEO of Comviva Technologies from 2007 to 2024. He has been appointed for a term of 5 years, subject to the approval of shareholders.</p><ul><li>OnMobile Global Ltd has appointed Manoranjan Mohapatra as an Additional Director in the category of Independent Director.</li><li>Mohapatra has over four decades of experience in the telecom and fintech industries.</li><li>He served as the Chief Executive Officer of Comviva Technologies from 2007 to 2024.</li><li>Mohapatra has been appointed for a term of 5 years, subject to the approval of shareholders.</li><li>He is widely recognized for his leadership in technology, innovation, shareholder value creation, and governance.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/852558cf-58e0-4458-8d7e-ba64302f9663.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: OnMobile Global Ltd. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SEQUENT] Viyash Scientific Ltd Announces Q3 Results, Changes in Senior Management, and New ESOP Scheme</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SEQUENT+SCIENTIFIC+LTD.&title=Viyash+Scientific+Ltd+Announces+Q3+Results%2C+Changes+in+Senior+Management%2C+and+New+ESOP+Scheme&newsId=d24f305c-c445-4f64-aadc-37bb5e6cad04&token=ZDI0ZjMwNWMtYzQ0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d24f305c-c445-4f64-aadc-37bb5e6cad04</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:21:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Viyash Scientific Ltd has announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company has also approved changes in the senior management personnel and the introduction and adoption of a new employee stock option scheme, subject to necessary approvals. The changes in the senior management are aimed at aligning with the post-merger strategic objectives and operational requirements.</p><ul><li>Viyash Scientific Ltd announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The company approved changes in senior management personnel to align with post-merger strategic objectives and operational requirements.</li><li>Viyash Scientific Ltd introduced and adopted a new employee stock option scheme, &apos;Viyash Scientific Limited Employee Stock Option Scheme 2026&apos;, subject to necessary approvals.</li><li>The changes in senior management and the new ESOP scheme are aimed at strengthening the company&apos;s leadership and motivating its employees.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a2484fd3-8912-4a83-b5cf-0bd0c03da7f1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SEQUENT SCIENTIFIC LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NXST] Nexus Select Trust Approves Allotment of INR 150 Crores Commercial Papers to Select Mall Management</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Nexus+Select+Trust&title=Nexus+Select+Trust+Approves+Allotment+of+INR+150+Crores+Commercial+Papers+to+Select+Mall+Management&newsId=584992bb-7841-4618-beed-d67c4e2fbda2&token=NTg0OTkyYmItNzg0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">584992bb-7841-4618-beed-d67c4e2fbda2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:07:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Nexus Select Trust has informed the Exchange about the approval of allotment of 3000 units of listed, rated, redeemable, rupee denominated commercial papers with a face value of INR 5,00,000/- each, for an aggregate principal amount of INR 150,00,00,000/- by the Borrowings Committee of Nexus Select Mall Management Private Limited, Manager to Nexus Select Trust. The commercial papers have a term of 46 days from the date of allotment i.e. February 05, 2026, at a discount of 6.86% and will be listed on the wholesale debt market segment of BSE Limited. The maturity date for these commercial papers is March 23, 2026.</p><ul><li>Nexus Select Trust approves allotment of INR 150 Crores commercial papers to Select Mall Management</li><li>The commercial papers have a term of 46 days from the date of allotment i.e. February 05, 2026</li><li>The commercial papers will be listed on the wholesale debt market segment of BSE Limited</li><li>The commercial papers have a maturity date of March 23, 2026</li><li>The commercial papers are issued at a discount of 6.86%</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7f41893b-a78a-47b3-86ac-b8cbc9292a9c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Nexus Select Trust | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ONMOBILE] OnMobile Global Ltd Approves Q3 Results, Appoints New Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=OnMobile+Global+Ltd.&title=OnMobile+Global+Ltd+Approves+Q3+Results%2C+Appoints+New+Independent+Director&newsId=5d605b17-88bc-406e-b442-f8643287361e&token=NWQ2MDViMTctODhi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d605b17-88bc-406e-b442-f8643287361e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:03:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>OnMobile Global Limited announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, at its board meeting held on February 5, 2026. The company reported a profit before tax of ₹ 214.19 Crores. The board also approved the appointment of Manoranjan Mohapatra as an Additional Director in the category of Independent Director.</p><ul><li>OnMobile Global Limited reported a profit before tax of ₹ 214.19 Crores for Q3 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue from operations for the quarter stood at ₹ 2,393.13 Crores.</li><li>Manoranjan Mohapatra has been appointed as an Additional Director in the category of Independent Director.</li><li>Mohapatra is not debarred from holding the office of director by virtue of any SEBI order or any other such authority.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0c411958-7312-4782-84fc-67553b7a1cce.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: OnMobile Global Ltd. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHIKHAR] Shikhar Consultants Ltd to Approve Q4 2025 Financial Results on February 11, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHIKHAR+CONSULTANTS+LTD.&title=Shikhar+Consultants+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+2025+Financial+Results+on+February+11%2C+2026&newsId=f6cc0a45-5242-4540-9a0e-d41f23c70f0a&token=ZjZjYzBhNDUtNTI0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6cc0a45-5242-4540-9a0e-d41f23c70f0a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shikhar Consultants Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 11, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The meeting is scheduled in accordance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The trading window for dealing in shares of the company has been closed for all Directors/ KMPs/ Designated Employees/ Connected Person of the Company from January 01, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration/ announcement of the un-audited Financial Results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, as per the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulation, 2015.</p><ul><li>Shikhar Consultants Ltd to approve Q4 2025 financial results on February 11, 2026</li><li>Meeting scheduled in accordance with SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Trading window for dealing in shares of the company closed from January 01, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration/ announcement of un-audited Financial Results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d695b0ad-3903-4dc9-980c-75ace8f50bf6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHIKHAR CONSULTANTS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TNTELE] Tamilnadu Telecommunications Ltd to Approve Q4 Results on Feb 12, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TAMILNADU+TELECOMMUNICATIONS+LTD.&title=Tamilnadu+Telecommunications+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+Results+on+Feb+12%2C+2026&newsId=00927023-f071-462e-a594-dbfa11260989&token=MDA5MjcwMjMtZjA3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00927023-f071-462e-a594-dbfa11260989</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 17:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tamilnadu Telecommunications Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 12, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025. The meeting will be held through video conferencing / Audio Visual Means at M/s. Telecommunications Consultants India Limited, TCIL Bhawan, Greater Kailash — I, New Delhi — 110048. The Audit Committee has already reviewed the results.</p><ul><li>Tamilnadu Telecommunications Ltd to consider and approve Q4 results for 2025</li><li>Meeting to be held on February 12, 2026</li><li>Meeting to be conducted through video conferencing / Audio Visual Means</li><li>Audit Committee has already reviewed the results</li><li>Meeting to be held at M/s. Telecommunications Consultants India Limited, TCIL Bhawan, Greater Kailash — I, New Delhi — 110048</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e13879d9-85a9-40b7-827b-56dbfa69478b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TAMILNADU TELECOMMUNICATIONS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>