<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 01:51:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[EVERESTO] Everest Organics Ltd Submits Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 &amp; Nine Months Ended Dec 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=EVEREST+ORGANICS+LTD.&title=Everest+Organics+Ltd+Submits+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Ended+Dec+31%2C+2025&newsId=3623f418-5764-444b-a864-621bdc6777e1&token=MzYyM2Y0MTgtNTc2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3623f418-5764-444b-a864-621bdc6777e1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:07:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Everest Organics Limited has submitted its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a sales turnover of Rs 5026.85 Lakhs for the quarter, with domestic sales at Rs. 3970.75 Lakhs and export sales at Rs. 1056.10 Lakhs. The company operates in one reportable business segment: Active Pharmaceutical Ingredients (APIs) and Intermediates. There were 2,63,157 Equity Share Warrants outstanding on 31.12.2025. The financial results were reviewed and recommended by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Sales turnover of Rs 5026.85 Lakhs for the quarter</li><li>Domestic sales of Rs. 3970.75 Lakhs and export sales of Rs. 1056.10 Lakhs</li><li>Operates in the Active Pharmaceutical Ingredients (APIs) and Intermediates segment</li><li>2,63,157 Equity Share Warrants outstanding on 31.12.2025</li><li>Financial results reviewed and approved by the Audit Committee and Board of Directors</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ad154429-25ae-4fcd-8e5b-34284c38769b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: EVEREST ORGANICS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GKSL] Gujarat Kidney and Super Speciality Ltd Confirms No Deviations in Fund Utilization as of December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Gujarat+Kidney+and+Super+Speciality+Ltd&title=Gujarat+Kidney+and+Super+Speciality+Ltd+Confirms+No+Deviations+in+Fund+Utilization+as+of+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=65bd83b8-ba8d-422e-aec8-dee45dbca5db&token=NjViZDgzYjgtYmE4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65bd83b8-ba8d-422e-aec8-dee45dbca5db</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:03:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gujarat Kidney and Super Speciality Ltd, previously known as Gujarat Kidney and Super Speciality Private Limited, has released a statement of deviation and variation for the third quarter ended on December 31, 2025. The statement confirms that there were no deviations or variations in the use of proceeds of the public issue. The company has utilized funds for various purposes including proposed acquisitions, part payment of purchase consideration for acquired hospitals, acquisitions of additional shareholding in subsidiaries, funding capital expenditure, buying robotics equipment, and funding inorganic growth. The company has also made partial repayment and prepayment of certain outstanding secured borrowings.</p><ul><li>Gujarat Kidney and Super Speciality Ltd confirms no deviations in fund utilization</li><li>Funds utilized for proposed acquisitions, part payment of purchase consideration, and acquisitions of additional shareholding</li><li>Funding provided for capital expenditure, buying robotics equipment, and inorganic growth</li><li>Partial repayment and prepayment of certain outstanding secured borrowings</li><li>Statement released as per Regulation 32 of SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirements) Regulation 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/723e78e5-419d-42df-9c9d-60e85533b325.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Gujarat Kidney and Super Speciality Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KMFBLDR] KMF Builders &amp; Developers Ltd. Announces Q3 and Nine Months Unaudited Financial Results for the Period Ending 31st December, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KMF+BUILDERS+%26+DEVELOPERS+LTD.&title=KMF+Builders+%26+Developers+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+the+Period+Ending+31st+December%2C+2025&newsId=dffb94e3-b3c5-41dc-b91a-86269ee91d4a&token=ZGZmYjk0ZTMtYjNj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dffb94e3-b3c5-41dc-b91a-86269ee91d4a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:03:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>KMF Builders &amp; Developers Ltd. has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations and other income have been reported. The financial results have been prepared in accordance with Indian Accounting Standards (Ind AS) and other applicable accounting principles. The company&apos;s management acknowledges the lack of ongoing projects, resulting in a loss with no revenue except interest income.</p><ul><li>Unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025</li><li>Revenue from operations and other income reported</li><li>Financial results prepared in accordance with Ind AS and other accounting principles</li><li>Company acknowledges loss with no revenue except interest income</li><li>Reviewed by the audit committee and approved by the board of Directors</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8bcf68bc-8df3-446b-83b9-fd852a967ac4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KMF BUILDERS & DEVELOPERS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VISVEN] Vishvprabha Ventures Ltd. Announces Q3 Results with Net Profit of ₹ 58.83 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vishvprabha+Ventures+Ltd&title=Vishvprabha+Ventures+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+Results+with+Net+Profit+of+%E2%82%B9+58.83+Crores&newsId=f37792bd-dcb3-4878-895f-38e288ff74e8&token=ZjM3NzkyYmQtZGNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f37792bd-dcb3-4878-895f-38e288ff74e8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:02:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vishvprabha Ventures Ltd. has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s total income from operations stands at ₹ 762.17 Crores, with a net profit of ₹ 58.83 Crores. The results were reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Total income from operations: ₹ 762.17 Crores</li><li>Net profit: ₹ 58.83 Crores</li><li>Reviewed by the Audit Committee</li><li>Approved by the Board of Directors</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/de3f6ab0-faff-41c3-9d6c-58b8672264dd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vishvprabha Ventures Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EVERESTO] Everest Organics Q3 &amp; YTD 2025 Financial Results Submitted, With Unaudited Financial Results &amp; Limited Review Report</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=EVEREST+ORGANICS+LTD.&title=Everest+Organics+Q3+%26+YTD+2025+Financial+Results+Submitted%2C+With+Unaudited+Financial+Results+%26+Limited+Review+Report&newsId=9a9b45ae-f4bc-484e-b9a4-a2bc43533473&token=OWE5YjQ1YWUtZjRi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a9b45ae-f4bc-484e-b9a4-a2bc43533473</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Everest Organics Limited has submitted its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue for Q3 2025 was Rs. 5026.85 Lakhs, with domestic sales of Rs. 3970.75 Lakhs and export sales of Rs. 1056.10 Lakhs. The company operates in the Active Pharmaceutical Ingredients (API) business segment. There are 2,63,157 Equity Share Warrantis outstanding, and 1,60,322 equity shares are still in the Unclaimed Suspense Account as of December 31, 2025. The company is undergoing a review by the Audit Committee and the Board of Directors. The company&apos;s financial results were prepared in accordance with Ind AS and other accounting principles generally accepted in India.</p><ul><li>Everest Organics Limited submitted unaudited financial results for Q3 and YTD 2025.</li><li>Revenue for Q3 2025 was Rs. 5026.85 Lakhs with domestic and export sales.</li><li>The company operates in the Active Pharmaceutical Ingredients (API) business segment.</li><li>There are 2,63,157 Equity Share Warrantis outstanding and 1,60,322 equity shares in the Unclaimed Suspense Account.</li><li>The company&apos;s financial results were prepared in accordance with Ind AS and other accounting principles generally accepted in India.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6eb0b160-91b7-4276-a260-6aa17c487009.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: EVEREST ORGANICS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ANURAS] Anupam Rasayan India Ltd Executes Agreements and Corporate Guarantee for Overseas Investments and Credit Facilities</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Anupam+Rasayan+India+Ltd&title=Anupam+Rasayan+India+Ltd+Executes+Agreements+and+Corporate+Guarantee+for+Overseas+Investments+and+Credit+Facilities&newsId=c0608b86-e14d-4186-a805-e2ed52ca9c3d&token=YzA2MDhiODYtZTE0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c0608b86-e14d-4186-a805-e2ed52ca9c3d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Anupam Rasayan India Limited has informed about the execution of agreements and corporate guarantee in accordance with the Listing Regulations, 2015. The company acquired 100% equity stake in Doriath S.a r.1. and 15% equity stake in Batam S.a r.l. through overseas investments. A credit facility of USD 20,000,000 has been availed by Doriath, and a credit facility of USD 30,000,000 has been availed by the company as External Commercial Borrowing. Additionally, various agreements such as note subscription agreements, facility agreements, security agent agreements, security trustee agreements, corporate guarantee deeds, deeds of hypothecation, mortgage documents, pledge agreements, non-disposal undertaking, loan agreement, and share subscription agreement have been executed.</p><ul><li>Execution of agreements and corporate guarantee for overseas investments and credit facilities.</li><li>Acquisition of 100% equity stake in Doriath S.a r.1. and 15% equity stake in Batam S.a r.l.</li><li>Availing of credit facilities worth USD 20,000,000 by Doriath and USD 30,000,000 by the company as External Commercial Borrowing.</li><li>Execution of various agreements such as note subscription agreements, facility agreements, security agent agreements, security trustee agreements, corporate guarantee deeds, deeds of hypothecation, mortgage documents, pledge agreements, non-disposal undertaking, loan agreement, and share subscription agreement.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/17627797-0e47-418b-b729-d133133a49de.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Anupam Rasayan India Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SSMD] SSMD Agrotech India Ltd. Appoints Ms. Nancy Jain as Internal Auditor, Authorizes MD for MOU and OD Facility</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SSMD+Agrotech+India+Ltd&title=SSMD+Agrotech+India+Ltd.+Appoints+Ms.+Nancy+Jain+as+Internal+Auditor%2C+Authorizes+MD+for+MOU+and+OD+Facility&newsId=8b6132a1-67b6-4053-aa64-322ea70ac86b&token=OGI2MTMyYTEtNjdi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b6132a1-67b6-4053-aa64-322ea70ac86b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SSMD Agrotech India Ltd. has made several significant decisions during its Board meeting on 14th February 2026. The company accepted the resignation of Mr. Rajmani Thakur as Internal Auditor and appointed Ms. Nancy Jain as the new Internal Auditor for the Financial Year 2025-26. The Board also authorized Mr. Ishu Munjal, Managing Director, to negotiate, finalize, sign, and execute the Memorandum of Understanding (MOU) with DEMETER COMMODITIES SL for expansion of business in the Oil Sector. Furthermore, the Board approved the proposal for availing an Overdraft (OD) Facility up to ¥5 Crore from a Bank and/or Financial Institution for the same purpose. The Board also adopted the Monitoring Agency Report for the quarter ended 31st December 2025.</p><ul><li>Resignation of Mr. Rajmani Thakur as Internal Auditor</li><li>Appointment of Ms. Nancy Jain as the new Internal Auditor</li><li>Authorization of Managing Director for MOU execution with DEMETER COMMODITIES SL</li><li>Approval for Overdraft (OD) Facility up to ¥5 Crore</li><li>Adoption of Monitoring Agency Report for Q4 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b68942a7-cd3a-4342-8fd9-c7c0e2855e94.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SSMD Agrotech India Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EVERESTO] Everest Organics Approves Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025, Despite Production Capacity Concerns and Pending Liabilities</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=EVEREST+ORGANICS+LTD.&title=Everest+Organics+Approves+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Despite+Production+Capacity+Concerns+and+Pending+Liabilities&newsId=06e23d08-db10-4973-9b6d-20773a049983&token=MDZlMjNkMDgtZGIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06e23d08-db10-4973-9b6d-20773a049983</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Everest Organics Limited has approved its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a sales turnover of Rs 5026.85 Lakhs, with domestic sales at Rs.3970.75 Lakhs and export sales at Rs. 1056.10 Lakhs. However, the company is operating at a higher production capacity without necessary approvals from the Telangana State Pollution Control Board (TSPCB), which could impact its going concern status. Additionally, the company has not recognized Rs.143 lakhs in interest expenses towards delayed payments to suppliers, nor has it determined the additional employee benefit obligation from the implementation of the New Labour Codes. The company&apos;s stock secretary and compliance officer, Shweta Singh, announced the results.</p><ul><li>Everest Organics reported a sales turnover of Rs 5026.85 Lakhs for Q3 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s domestic sales stood at Rs.3970.75 Lakhs, while export sales were at Rs. 1056.10 Lakhs.</li><li>The company is operating at a higher production capacity without necessary approvals from the TSPCB, which could impact its going concern status.</li><li>Everest Organics has not recognized Rs.143 lakhs in interest expenses towards delayed payments to suppliers.</li><li>The company has not determined the additional employee benefit obligation from the implementation of the New Labour Codes.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/18a54a84-e2f8-419a-8b5f-e2cd25c93732.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: EVEREST ORGANICS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FILTRON] Filtron Engineers Ltd. Approves Q3 Results, Regularises Director Appointments, and Proposes Office Relocation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=FILTRON+ENGINEERS+LTD.&title=Filtron+Engineers+Ltd.+Approves+Q3+Results%2C+Regularises+Director+Appointments%2C+and+Proposes+Office+Relocation&newsId=80fa6497-b23f-40ca-89b1-5dff5dabde43&token=ODBmYTY0OTctYjIz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80fa6497-b23f-40ca-89b1-5dff5dabde43</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 22:20:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Filtron Engineers Ltd. has approved the standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company has also regularised the appointments of three directors and proposed to change its registered office. The proposed changes are subject to approval from shareholders and relevant authorities.</p><ul><li>Filtron Engineers Ltd. approved the standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 2025.</li><li>The company regularised the appointments of three directors: Mr. Jayesh Sheshmal Rawal, Mr. Tarak Bipinchandra Gor, and Mr. Ankit Jayesh Rawal.</li><li>Filtron proposed to change its registered office from Pune to Mumbai, subject to approval from shareholders and relevant authorities.</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue from operations for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, was 1,09,495.27 Rs. Thousand.</li><li>The net loss for the quarter was 10,913.44 Rs. Thousand.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/162cd078-d661-4528-8377-e245d2d460e8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: FILTRON ENGINEERS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WARDWIZFBL] Wardwizard Foods and Beverages Ltd: Unaudited Financial Result for Q3 and Nine Months Ended on 31st December, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Wardwizard+Foods+and+Beverages+Ltd&title=Wardwizard+Foods+and+Beverages+Ltd%3A+Unaudited+Financial+Result+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+on+31st+December%2C+2025&newsId=e45155c8-84c9-4c36-ae60-f2d1b3b8a738&token=ZTQ1MTU1YzgtODRj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e45155c8-84c9-4c36-ae60-f2d1b3b8a738</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 22:19:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Wardwizard Foods and Beverages Ltd has announced its unaudited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended on 31st December, 2025. The meeting was held on Saturday, 14th February, 2026 and the results were approved by the Board of Directors. The company&apos;s revenue for the quarter is INR 6743.50 lakhs, with a profit before tax of INR 135.0 lakhs. The company operates in three segments: Sale of RTE, Frozen, Sauces &amp; Mayo, Food Commodities, and C Services. The financial results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and are available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Revenue for the quarter is INR 6743.50 lakhs</li><li>Profit before tax for the quarter is INR 135.0 lakhs</li><li>The company operates in three segments: Sale of RTE, Frozen, Sauces &amp; Mayo, Food Commodities, and C Services</li><li>The financial results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee</li><li>The results are available on the company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/985e0503-5c42-4456-92b7-60fd5bb5cb3e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Wardwizard Foods and Beverages Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>