<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:44:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[RBLBANK] Emirates NBD Bank to Acquire 26% Stake in RBL Bank for INR 116 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RBL+Bank+Ltd&title=Emirates+NBD+Bank+to+Acquire+26%25+Stake+in+RBL+Bank+for+INR+116+Billion&newsId=bff4d831-a634-4801-affb-27202515e65e&token=YmZmNGQ4MzEtYTYz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bff4d831-a634-4801-affb-27202515e65e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Emirates NBD Bank (P.J.S.C.) has announced an open offer to acquire up to 415,586,443 fully-paid-up equity shares of RBL Bank Ltd, representing 26% of the Expanded Voting Share Capital of the Target Company, at a price of INR 280.00 per Equity Share. The total consideration of the offer is INR 116,364,204,040, payable in cash. The public announcement was made on October 18, 2025, and the detailed public statement was made on October 27, 2025. A corrigendum was made on November 3, 2025, and the draft letter of offer was issued on November 4, 2025.</p><ul><li>Emirates NBD Bank to acquire 26% stake in RBL Bank Ltd</li><li>Total consideration of INR 116,364,204,040</li><li>Offer price of INR 280.00 per Equity Share</li><li>Public announcement made on October 18, 2025</li><li>Draft letter of offer issued on November 4, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/FB76F3F1-E889-4311-82B7-3874125143E6-121002.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RBL Bank Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KSOILS] K S Oils Ltd to Approve Q3 Financial Results on Feb 12, 2026; Trading Window Closed</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=K+S+Oils+Ltd-%24&title=K+S+Oils+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+Financial+Results+on+Feb+12%2C+2026%3B+Trading+Window+Closed&newsId=0cd222c7-ba0f-4024-b8ad-0afc1627f56c&token=MGNkMjIyYzctYmEw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0cd222c7-ba0f-4024-b8ad-0afc1627f56c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:42:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>K S Oils Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 12, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone Financial Results for the 3rd quarter of the Financial Year 2025-26. In compliance with the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, and the Company’s ‘Code of Internal Procedures and Conduct for Regulating, Monitoring and Reporting of Trading in Securities by Insiders&apos;, the Trading Window for dealing in the securities of the Company for all the Designated Persons including Insiders, has been closed since January 1, 2026, and will remain closed until 48 hours after the financial results are declared to the stock exchange.</p><ul><li>K S Oils Ltd to consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone Financial Results for Q3 FY 2025-26 on Feb 12, 2026</li><li>Trading Window closed for all Designated Persons and Insiders since Jan 1, 2026, and will remain closed until 48 hours after the financial results are declared</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/beb75fac-9e4b-46fd-948b-7fca5e7f6eb3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: K S Oils Ltd-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PREMIERPOL] Promoter Group Company, D L Millar &amp; Co Ltd, Acquires 0.03% Stake in Premier Polyfilm Ltd via Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PREMIER+POLYFILM+LTD.&title=Promoter+Group+Company%2C+D+L+Millar+%26+Co+Ltd%2C+Acquires+0.03%25+Stake+in+Premier+Polyfilm+Ltd+via+Open+Market&newsId=1eedb3ee-d065-41c6-a16e-74364435787a&token=MWVlZGIzZWUtZDA2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1eedb3ee-d065-41c6-a16e-74364435787a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In a recent disclosure under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011, D L Millar &amp; Co Ltd, a promoter group company of Premier Polyfilm Limited, has acquired equity shares of Premier Polyfilm Limited through open market transactions. The acquisition took place on 02-02-2026, with the purchase of 28,106 shares, which amounts to 0.03% of the total shareholding of the target company.</p><ul><li>D L Millar &amp; Co Ltd, a promoter group company of Premier Polyfilm Limited, has acquired shares of Premier Polyfilm Limited.</li><li>The acquisition was made through open market transactions on 02-02-2026.</li><li>28,106 shares, or 0.03% of the total shareholding, were acquired.</li><li>The acquisition is disclosed under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/FED2ABD1_EE03_4B66_9F87_0D91E5F44071_115016.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PREMIER POLYFILM LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AHLUCONT] Ahluwalia Contracts to Consider Un-Audited Financial Results and Scheme of Amalgamation of Subsidiaries</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AHLUWALIA+CONTRACTS+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Ahluwalia+Contracts+to+Consider+Un-Audited+Financial+Results+and+Scheme+of+Amalgamation+of+Subsidiaries&newsId=b7313008-e28b-4252-8e63-a06b5c5a5d84&token=YjczMTMwMDgtZTI4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7313008-e28b-4252-8e63-a06b5c5a5d84</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ahluwalia Contracts (India) Ltd will consider the Un-Audited Financial Results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company will also consider and approve the Scheme of Amalgamation of five Wholly Owned Subsidiary Companies with and into Ahluwalia Contracts (India) Limited. The information is available on the company’s website and the website of the Stock Exchange.</p><ul><li>Ahluwalia Contracts to consider Un-Audited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>The company will consider the Scheme of Amalgamation of five Wholly Owned Subsidiary Companies with and into Ahluwalia Contracts (India) Limited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/27246d05-1985-430f-b27c-9256aadccaef.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AHLUWALIA CONTRACTS (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VBL] Varun Beverages Ltd: Board Meeting Approves Audited Financial Results, Dividend Recommendation, and Director Continuation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Varun+Beverages+Ltd&title=Varun+Beverages+Ltd%3A+Board+Meeting+Approves+Audited+Financial+Results%2C+Dividend+Recommendation%2C+and+Director+Continuation&newsId=3e0b7fee-feb3-478a-b1bf-671a71f97d4a&token=M2UwYjdmZWUtZmVi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e0b7fee-feb3-478a-b1bf-671a71f97d4a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:39:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Varun Beverages Ltd held a meeting on [start date] and concluded at [end time]. The Board approved the Audited Financial Results for the Quarter and Financial Year ended December 31, 2025. A final dividend of 70.50 (Fifty Paisa only) per Equity Share was recommended, subject to shareholder approval. The Board also approved the continuation of Mr. Abhiram Seth as a Non-Executive Independent Director, subject to shareholder approval at the upcoming AGM. The 31st AGM of the Company will be held on April 1, 2026, through Video Conferencing / Other Audio Video Means. The Board also approved investing up to 30% of Equity Share Capital in FPEL HR2 Energy Private Limited for captive solar power consumption.</p><ul><li>Audited Financial Results for Q4 and FY ended December 31, 2025 approved</li><li>Recommendation of final dividend of 70.50 per share</li><li>Continuation of Mr. Abhiram Seth as Non-Executive Independent Director</li><li>31st AGM to be held on April 1, 2026 through VC/OAVM</li><li>Investment in FPEL HR2 Energy Private Limited for captive solar power consumption</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/93f90fcc-4290-42d1-8a11-b56c689ab4a7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Varun Beverages Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GOLDIAM] Goldiam International Ltd Opens 14th ORIGEM Retail Store at South City Mall, Kolkata</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GOLDIAM+INTERNATIONAL+LTD.&title=Goldiam+International+Ltd+Opens+14th+ORIGEM+Retail+Store+at+South+City+Mall%2C+Kolkata&newsId=f67762d1-6f06-41ff-a3ba-118defa1a7aa&token=ZjY3NzYyZDEtNmYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f67762d1-6f06-41ff-a3ba-118defa1a7aa</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:36:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Goldiam International Ltd has opened its 14th retail store under the brand name ‘ORIGEM’ at South City Mall, Kolkata. This development aligns with the company’s long-term strategy of expanding its retail presence and strengthening customer engagement across key markets. The new store is located at Unit No S 210 A, South City Mall, municipal Premises no. 375, prince Anwar Shah Road, Kolkata — 700068.</p><ul><li>Goldiam International Ltd has opened its 14th retail store under the brand name ‘ORIGEM’.</li><li>The new store is located at South City Mall, Kolkata.</li><li>This development aligns with the company’s long-term strategy of expanding its retail presence.</li><li>The new store is aimed at strengthening customer engagement across key markets.</li><li>The exact location of the store is Unit No S 210 A, South City Mall, municipal Premises no. 375, prince Anwar Shah Road, Kolkata — 700068.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7e8acda4-3e5d-40b2-8ec9-2d300cdfaa65.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GOLDIAM INTERNATIONAL LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VBL] Varun Beverages Ltd Announces Q4 &amp; FY2025 Results, Recommends Dividend of 70.50, and Plans to Invest in Solar Power</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Varun+Beverages+Ltd&title=Varun+Beverages+Ltd+Announces+Q4+%26+FY2025+Results%2C+Recommends+Dividend+of+70.50%2C+and+Plans+to+Invest+in+Solar+Power&newsId=427e50f6-b84d-47ab-a75f-7d52bec94bb1&token=NDI3ZTUwZjYtYjg0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">427e50f6-b84d-47ab-a75f-7d52bec94bb1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:36:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Varun Beverages Ltd has announced its audited financial results for the quarter and financial year ended December 31, 2025. The company has recommended a final dividend of 70.50 per equity share for the financial year 2025, subject to the approval of equity shareholders. The board has also approved the continuation of Mr. Abhiram Seth as a Non-Executive Independent Director, subject to shareholder approval. Additionally, the company plans to invest up to 30% of its equity share capital in FPEL HR2 Energy Private Limited to obtain solar power for captive consumption. The 31st AGM of the company will be held on April 1, 2026, through Video Conferencing / Other Audio Video Means facility.</p><ul><li>Varun Beverages announces Q4 &amp; FY2025 results</li><li>Recommends final dividend of 70.50 per equity share</li><li>Approves continuation of Mr. Abhiram Seth as Non-Executive Independent Director</li><li>Plans to invest up to 30% equity share capital in FPEL HR2 Energy Private Limited for solar power</li><li>31st AGM to be held on April 1, 2026, through Video Conferencing / Other Audio Video Means facility</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/feac011f-15ca-4923-a2d9-ae7c93094358.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Varun Beverages Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MPL] MPL Plastics Ltd to Review and Approve Q4 Results of FY2025-2026 on Feb 10, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MPL+Plastics+Limited&title=MPL+Plastics+Ltd+to+Review+and+Approve+Q4+Results+of+FY2025-2026+on+Feb+10%2C+2026&newsId=f843aaca-ea09-47e7-bb46-dbc875960e24&token=Zjg0M2FhY2EtZWEw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f843aaca-ea09-47e7-bb46-dbc875960e24</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>MPL Plastics Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 10, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025. The meeting is in accordance with Regulation 29 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The results will be reviewed by the Audit Committee prior to the meeting.</p><ul><li>MPL Plastics Ltd to review and approve Q4 results of FY2025-2026</li><li>Meeting scheduled on 10th February, 2026</li><li>Results to be reviewed by the Audit Committee</li><li>In accordance with Regulation 29 of the SEBI Listing Regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/703d5002-eb90-4139-a0b2-4fb7d41d4e67.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MPL Plastics Limited | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FFPL] Foundry Fuel Products Ltd to Approve Un-audited Financial Results for Q4 2025 in February Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=FOUNDRY+FUEL+PRODUCTS+LTD.&title=Foundry+Fuel+Products+Ltd+to+Approve+Un-audited+Financial+Results+for+Q4+2025+in+February+Board+Meeting&newsId=fe51daf8-293e-4aa3-ada7-c2f982e69b2e&token=ZmU1MWRhZjgtMjkz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe51daf8-293e-4aa3-ada7-c2f982e69b2e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Foundry Fuel Products Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 12, 2026, to consider and approve the Un-audited Financial Results for the quarter ended 31.12.2025. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the company, which was closed on January 1, 2026, will remain closed till 48 hours after the announcement of the Unaudited Financial Results. This is in compliance with the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Foundry Fuel Products Ltd to consider and approve Un-audited Financial Results for Q4 2025</li><li>Board Meeting scheduled on February 12, 2026</li><li>Trading window to remain closed till 48 hours after the announcement of the Unaudited Financial Results</li><li>Compliance with SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fd26f24f-9236-4d5a-9f87-b14fb9da181e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: FOUNDRY FUEL PRODUCTS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MVGJL] Manoj Vaibhav Gems N Jewellers Ltd to Approve Q4 2025 Financial Results on Feb 10, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Manoj+Vaibhav+Gems+N+Jewellers+Ltd&title=Manoj+Vaibhav+Gems+N+Jewellers+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+2025+Financial+Results+on+Feb+10%2C+2026&newsId=8269bce8-091a-4b7f-b308-6e81faa69f45&token=ODI2OWJjZTgtMDkx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8269bce8-091a-4b7f-b308-6e81faa69f45</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Manoj Vaibhav Gems N Jewellers Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 10, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. This meeting is pursuant to Regulation 33 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The trading window for all designated persons and their immediate relatives will remain closed from the date of the meeting until 48 hours after the board meeting.</p><ul><li>Manoj Vaibhav Gems N Jewellers Ltd to consider and approve unaudited financial results for Q4 2025</li><li>Meeting scheduled on February 10, 2026, as per Regulation 33 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Trading window for all designated persons and their immediate relatives to remain closed till February 12, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/74fc19d4-ae45-405d-bb0d-cb993fc56710.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Manoj Vaibhav Gems N Jewellers Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>