<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:50:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[JSWENERGY] JSW Energy Receives Trading Approvals for 95,23,809 Equity Shares on Preferential Basis</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JSW+Energy+Ltd&title=JSW+Energy+Receives+Trading+Approvals+for+95%2C23%2C809+Equity+Shares+on+Preferential+Basis&newsId=c9898ee6-77e5-49b6-a9c5-e42a0ef6ce52&token=Yzk4OThlZTYtNzdl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9898ee6-77e5-49b6-a9c5-e42a0ef6ce52</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>JSW Energy Ltd. has received trading approvals from BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange of India Limited for 95,23,809 equity shares allotted on a preferential basis to JTPM Metal Traders Limited, a member of the promoter group of the Company. The shares, with a face value of Rs. 10/- each and a premium of Rs. 515/-, will be listed on the Exchange from February 27, 2026. The lock-in details for these shares are until September 9, 2027.</p><ul><li>JSW Energy receives trading approvals for 95,23,809 equity shares</li><li>Shares allotted on a preferential basis to promoter group member JTPM Metal Traders Limited</li><li>Shares to be listed on the Exchange from February 27, 2026</li><li>Face value of Rs. 10/- each and a premium of Rs. 515/-</li><li>Lock-in details until September 9, 2027</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ad8907ac-009e-4ddd-95f7-f902787d7ad9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JSW Energy Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHAYONAENG] Shayona Engineering Ltd. Appoints Compliance Officer, Approves Credit Facilities, and Adopts Policies</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shayona+Engineering+Ltd&title=Shayona+Engineering+Ltd.+Appoints+Compliance+Officer%2C+Approves+Credit+Facilities%2C+and+Adopts+Policies&newsId=c79a1c63-ef1b-458d-aa0c-cddb20037bcf&token=Yzc5YTFjNjMtZWYx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c79a1c63-ef1b-458d-aa0c-cddb20037bcf</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:47:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shayona Engineering Limited announced that its Board of Directors met on February 26, 2026, and approved several key matters. The Board approved the appointment of a Compliance Officer in accordance with Regulation 6 of SEBI LODR. They also confirmed the constitution of Board Committees in compliance with the Companies Act, 2013 and SEBI LODR, and adopted the Charters / Terms of Reference of the Board Committees. The Terms and Conditions of Appointment of Independent Directors were approved and adopted. Various policies and codes as applicable under SEBI LODR and other applicable laws were also approved and adopted. The Board approved the transfer of existing credit facilities and the availing of additional credit facilities. The meeting commenced at 03:00 p.m. and concluded at 6:55 p.m.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Compliance Officer</li><li>Constitution of Board Committees</li><li>Adoption of Charters / Terms of Reference of the Board Committees</li><li>Approval of Terms and Conditions of Appointment of Independent Directors</li><li>Approval of various policies and codes</li><li>Transfer of existing credit facilities and availing of additional credit facilities</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f5dbaee2-1e09-4b23-adb0-177c7ea765ef.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shayona Engineering Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NBCC] NBCC (India) Ltd Secures Rs. 775.27 Cr. Contracts for Comprehensive Redevelopment of DDA Staff Quarters</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NBCC+%28India%29+Ltd&title=NBCC+%28India%29+Ltd+Secures+Rs.+775.27+Cr.+Contracts+for+Comprehensive+Redevelopment+of+DDA+Staff+Quarters&newsId=bb971faf-bd21-43f1-b676-2db0e0dec255&token=YmI5NzFmYWYtYmQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb971faf-bd21-43f1-b676-2db0e0dec255</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:42:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>NBCC (India) Limited has been awarded two contracts for the comprehensive redevelopment of DDA staff quarters located at Old Delhi Rajinder Nagar and Safdarjung Development Area, New Delhi. The combined value of the projects is approximately Rs. 775.27 crore, excluding the marketing fee. The contracts are in the normal course of business for the company. The projects will be executed on a self-sustainable model, with a portion of the developed built-up area sold to generate funds for the development, while the remaining area will be handed over to DDA for their staff use.</p><ul><li>NBCC (India) Ltd has been awarded contracts worth approximately Rs. 775.27 crore for the redevelopment of DDA staff quarters.</li><li>The projects will be executed on a self-sustainable model.</li><li>The redevelopment will take place at Old Delhi Rajinder Nagar and Safdarjung Development Area, New Delhi.</li><li>The combined area to be developed is around 165,560 SQM (excluding external development).</li><li>The projects are in the normal course of business for NBCC (India) Ltd.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/74c2e8a3-b5d2-4d10-b9ff-03f2703f6f6b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NBCC (India) Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GEMAROMA] GEM Aromatics Receives $1Mn Export Orders from USA &amp; Europe, Commences Manufacturing of Additional Products</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Gem+Aromatics+Ltd&title=GEM+Aromatics+Receives+%241Mn+Export+Orders+from+USA+%26+Europe%2C+Commences+Manufacturing+of+Additional+Products&newsId=f7b4723d-9a42-46dd-b7c3-790a5a3c4811&token=ZjdiNDcyM2QtOWE0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7b4723d-9a42-46dd-b7c3-790a5a3c4811</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:32:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>GEM Aromatics Ltd has announced receiving export orders worth USD 1 Mn from customers across the USA and Europe. The company has also commenced commercial production of additional products, including WS05 (Cooling Agents) and Safranal (Citral Derivatives) at its Dahej facility. The manufacturing of Catalyst for MEHQ is progressing as planned and expected to be completed by Q4FY26. These developments are in line with the company&apos;s strategic focus on product diversification and strengthening its manufacturing capabilities.</p><ul><li>Received export orders worth USD 1 Mn from customers across the USA and Europe</li><li>Commenced commercial production of additional products, including WS05 (Cooling Agents) and Safranal (Citral Derivatives) at its Dahej facility</li><li>Manufacturing of Catalyst for MEHQ is progressing as planned and expected to be completed by Q4FY26</li><li>Strategic focus on product diversification and strengthening its manufacturing capabilities</li><li>Improving global trade environment and easing of tariff related headwinds</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f85baa5d-d0b7-400b-b00d-c8f7455bf65f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Gem Aromatics Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TRIVENIENT] Triveni Enterprises Ltd: Appointment of Ms. Sujata Yash Patil as Additional Director and Resignation of Ms. Pintu</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Triveni+Enterprises+Ltd&title=Triveni+Enterprises+Ltd%3A+Appointment+of+Ms.+Sujata+Yash+Patil+as+Additional+Director+and+Resignation+of+Ms.+Pintu&newsId=ed3f9905-0183-431a-9c3e-3a6691d345aa&token=ZWQzZjk5MDUtMDE4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed3f9905-0183-431a-9c3e-3a6691d345aa</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Triveni Enterprises Ltd announced the appointment of Ms. Sujata Yash Patil as an Additional Director (Non-Executive Independent Director) for a term of 5 years, effective from 26th February 2026 to 27th February 2031. Ms. Patil holds a B.Com degree and has over 25 years of experience in finance, taxation, corporate governance, strategy, and regulatory compliance. She has previously worked with reputed organizations and has held key managerial positions. On the other hand, Ms. Pintu has resigned from her position as Non-Executive Independent Director due to personal reasons, effective from the close of business hours on 26th February 2026.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Ms. Sujata Yash Patil as Additional Director (Non-Executive Independent Director) for a term of 5 years.</li><li>Ms. Patil holds a B.Com degree and has over 25 years of experience in finance, taxation, corporate governance, strategy, and regulatory compliance.</li><li>Resignation of Ms. Pintu as Non-Executive Independent Director due to personal reasons.</li><li>Ms. Pintu&apos;s resignation is effective from the close of business hours on 26th February 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9c52e636-301c-4d12-9302-b621f370188e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Triveni Enterprises Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PVP] Independent Director, Mr. Gautam Shahi, Resigns from PVP Ventures Ltd Due to Increasing Professional Commitments</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PVP+VENTURES+LTD.&title=Independent+Director%2C+Mr.+Gautam+Shahi%2C+Resigns+from+PVP+Ventures+Ltd+Due+to+Increasing+Professional+Commitments&newsId=351e2d29-093b-443a-ba8a-fab26ee2ed41&token=MzUxZTJkMjktMDkz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">351e2d29-093b-443a-ba8a-fab26ee2ed41</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>PVP Ventures Ltd announced the resignation of its Independent Director, Mr. Gautam Shahi, via an email dated 26th February 2026. Mr. Shahi tendered his resignation due to his increasing professional commitments, which will be effective from the close of business hours on 28th February 2026. He will also cease to be a Member of the Committees of the Board of the Company. Mr. Shahi confirmed that there are no material reasons for his resignation other than those stated in his resignation letter.</p><ul><li>Mr. Gautam Shahi resigns from the position of Independent Director on the Board of PVP Enterprises.</li><li>His resignation is due to a significant increase in professional commitments in his legal practice.</li><li>Mr. Shahi&apos;s resignation will be effective from the close of business hours on 28th February 2026.</li><li>Mr. Shahi has confirmed that there are no other material reasons for his resignation.</li><li>PVP Ventures Ltd announced the resignation in compliance with the applicable provisions of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/35a32ad4-dd77-4b03-90b8-9b463ffffd97.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PVP VENTURES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TATASTEEL] Tata Steel Acquires 261,90,47,620 Equity Shares in T Steel Holdings Pte. Ltd for USD 264 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TATA+STEEL+LTD.&title=Tata+Steel+Acquires+261%2C90%2C47%2C620+Equity+Shares+in+T+Steel+Holdings+Pte.+Ltd+for+USD+264+Million&newsId=4c5358b1-5984-4b6f-b184-b567204624ee&token=NGM1MzU4YjEtNTk4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4c5358b1-5984-4b6f-b184-b567204624ee</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tata Steel Ltd has acquired an equity stake in T Steel Holdings Pte. Ltd (TSHP), a wholly owned foreign subsidiary of the company. The acquisition was made on February 26, 2026, for USD 264 million (approximately INR 2,401.50 crore). Post acquisition, TSHP will continue to be a wholly owned foreign subsidiary of Tata Steel. This disclosure is made in compliance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Tata Steel acquires 261,90,47,620 equity shares in T Steel Holdings Pte. Ltd.</li><li>The acquisition is for a total consideration of USD 264 million (approximately INR 2,401.50 crore).</li><li>T Steel Holdings Pte. Ltd. is a wholly owned foreign subsidiary of Tata Steel.</li><li>The acquisition was made on February 26, 2026.</li><li>The disclosure is made in compliance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/741f9237-28d3-4874-998a-b2e591fba287.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TATA STEEL LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TULSI] Tulsi Extrusions Ltd to Approve Q1 2025-26 Financial Results on March 6, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Tulsi+Extrusions+Ltd&title=Tulsi+Extrusions+Ltd+to+Approve+Q1+2025-26+Financial+Results+on+March+6%2C+2026&newsId=f1e0efe8-0c26-457e-a31d-903eefa3d116&token=ZjFlMGVmZTgtMGMy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f1e0efe8-0c26-457e-a31d-903eefa3d116</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tulsi Extrusions Ltd has announced a Board of Directors meeting on March 6, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter ended June 30, 2025. The meeting will take place at the company&apos;s registered office in Jalgaon, MH.</p><ul><li>Tulsi Extrusions Ltd has scheduled a Board of Directors meeting on March 6, 2026.</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the unaudited standalone financial results for Q1 2025-26.</li><li>The meeting will be held at the company&apos;s registered office in Jalgaon, MH.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1d46472b-423c-40a4-9c44-4f41008253f1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Tulsi Extrusions Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TRIVENIENT] Triveni Enterprises Ltd Appoints Ms. Sujata Yash Patil as Additional Director and Records Resignation of Ms. Pintu</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Triveni+Enterprises+Ltd&title=Triveni+Enterprises+Ltd+Appoints+Ms.+Sujata+Yash+Patil+as+Additional+Director+and+Records+Resignation+of+Ms.+Pintu&newsId=c10034df-6043-4860-8a4f-00daaab894fd&token=YzEwMDM0ZGYtNjA0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c10034df-6043-4860-8a4f-00daaab894fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Triveni Enterprises Ltd has appointed Ms. Sujata Yash Patil as an Additional Director (Non-Executive Independent Director) for a term of 5 years, effective from 26th February 2026 to 27th February 2031. Ms. Patil holds a B.Com degree and has over 25 years of experience in finance, taxation, corporate governance, strategy, and regulatory compliance. She has previously worked with reputed organizations and has held key managerial positions. On the other hand, Ms. Pintu has resigned from her position as a Non-Executive Non-Independent Director due to personal reasons, with effect from the close of business hours on 26th February 2026.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Ms. Sujata Yash Patil as Additional Director for a 5-year term</li><li>Ms. Patil holds a B.Com degree and has over 25 years of experience in various fields</li><li>Ms. Pintu resigns from her position as a Non-Executive Non-Independent Director</li><li>Ms. Pintu&apos;s resignation is due to personal reasons</li><li>Resignation effective from the close of business hours on 26th February 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/917005d5-1ae8-4bbb-9f14-c84b2e36b530.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Triveni Enterprises Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ATLANTAELE] Atlanta Electricals Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Consider Conversion of Subsidiary to Public Limited Company</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Atlanta+Electricals+Ltd&title=Atlanta+Electricals+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Consider+Conversion+of+Subsidiary+to+Public+Limited+Company&newsId=c7f0891c-e44c-409b-8d92-fc7095c5e784&token=YzdmMDg5MWMtZTQ0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7f0891c-e44c-409b-8d92-fc7095c5e784</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 15:21:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Subsidiaries</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Atlanta Electricals Ltd has informed the BSE that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on 03/03/2026. The agenda includes the consideration and approval of the conversion of Atlanta Trafo Private Limited, a wholly owned subsidiary, from a Private Limited Company to a Public Limited Company. This decision is in compliance with Regulation 29 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Atlanta Electricals Ltd has scheduled a Board Meeting for 03/03/2026</li><li>The meeting will consider the conversion of Atlanta Trafo Private Limited to a Public Limited Company</li><li>The conversion is in compliance with Regulation 29 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/acd30924-6740-4af9-9ee7-b0568d2e9033.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Atlanta Electricals Ltd | Category: Subsidiaries</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>