<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:54:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[BIOCON] Biocon obtains approval for weight management drug, Liraglutide, in the United States</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BIOCON+LTD.&title=Biocon+obtains+approval+for+weight+management+drug%2C+Liraglutide%2C+in+the+United+States&newsId=f22bb283-4862-4af5-b408-9e1d911ec6e1&token=ZjIyYmIyODMtNDg2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f22bb283-4862-4af5-b408-9e1d911ec6e1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>USFDA</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Biocon Limited, an innovation-led global biopharmaceuticals company, announced it has received approval from the U.S. FDA for its complex formulation Liraglutide Injection, 18 mg/3 mL (6 mg/mL) single-patient-use prefilled pens (gSaxenda®). The drug-device combination formulation is used in the treatment of chronic weight management, indicated as an adjunct to a reduced-calorie diet and increased physical activity. The approval reinforces Biocon&apos;s commitment to expanding access to critical therapies for patients globally, with the U.S. being an important market in this strategy. The total addressable market opportunity for GLP-1 in weight loss in the U.S. was US $127 million as of December 2025.</p><ul><li>Biocon received approval from the U.S. FDA for Liraglutide Injection, gSaxenda®</li><li>gSaxenda® is a drug-device combination formulation used in chronic weight management</li><li>GLP-1 therapies represent a significant growth driver for Biocon</li><li>The U.S. is an important market for Biocon&apos;s GLP-1 strategy</li><li>The total addressable market opportunity for GLP-1 in weight loss in the U.S. was US $127 million as of December 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e844c347-ffbd-44e1-980a-c8b657efd8af.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BIOCON LTD. | Category: USFDA</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PRABHA] Prabha Energy Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Consider Rights Issue Terms on Feb 27, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Prabha+Energy+Ltd&title=Prabha+Energy+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Consider+Rights+Issue+Terms+on+Feb+27%2C+2026&newsId=967785c3-b1ff-4f07-8551-4239f93ea1be&token=OTY3Nzg1YzMtYjFm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">967785c3-b1ff-4f07-8551-4239f93ea1be</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:41:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Right Issue</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Prabha Energy Ltd has informed the BSE that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on 27/02/2026. The meeting will inter alia, consider and approve the terms and conditions of the rights issue, including the determination of the issue price, issue size, record date, and Rights Entitlement ratio. The approval is subject to the receipt of in-principle approval from the stock exchange or other regulatory authorities. The meeting will also consider other business items, if any.</p><ul><li>Prabha Energy Ltd schedules a Board Meeting on 27/02/2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the terms and conditions of the rights issue</li><li>The rights issue includes the determination of the issue price, issue size, record date, and Rights Entitlement ratio</li><li>The approval is subject to the receipt of in-principle approval from the stock exchange or other regulatory authorities</li><li>The company will also consider other business items, if any</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1edc14a1-19b9-4c99-8d02-974dbffb75e1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Prabha Energy Ltd | Category: Right Issue</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CAPILLARY] Capillary Technologies India Ltd to Acquire Session M Inc. for $20 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Capillary+Technologies+India+Ltd&title=Capillary+Technologies+India+Ltd+to+Acquire+Session+M+Inc.+for+%2420+Million&newsId=2abc7e90-eb14-4f64-a8a9-0a88e33b0752&token=MmFiYzdlOTAtZWIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2abc7e90-eb14-4f64-a8a9-0a88e33b0752</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:36:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Capillary Technologies India Ltd has approved an investment in its Wholly Owned Subsidiary, Capillary Pte. Ltd., for the purpose of acquiring 100% shareholding in Session M Inc., a wholly owned subsidiary of Mastercard Inc., and its wholly owned subsidiary, Session M Czech Republic s.r.o. The acquisition is subject to customary conditions precedent and applicable regulatory approvals. The acquisition is part of Capillary’s inorganic growth plans to strengthen its presence in the North American, LATAM loyalty markets and adds to our APAC portfolio. The base consideration is $20 Million, subject to customary closing adjustments towards net debt, working capital and other adjustments as set out in the definitive agreements.</p><ul><li>Capillary Technologies India Ltd to acquire Session M Inc. for $20 Million</li><li>Acquisition includes Session M Czech Republic s.r.o.</li><li>Part of Capillary’s inorganic growth plans to strengthen presence in North American, LATAM loyalty markets and APAC portfolio</li><li>Subject to customary conditions precedent and regulatory approvals</li><li>Base consideration of $20 Million, subject to customary closing adjustments</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/81f702b2-6c27-43ec-8577-a2d394ba2388.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Capillary Technologies India Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DICIND] DIC India Ltd. Reappoints Mr. Adnan Wajhat Ahmad as Independent Director, Declares Final Dividend, and Appoints Cost Auditor</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DIC+INDIA+LTD.&title=DIC+India+Ltd.+Reappoints+Mr.+Adnan+Wajhat+Ahmad+as+Independent+Director%2C+Declares+Final+Dividend%2C+and+Appoints+Cost+Auditor&newsId=05cd8183-7aee-49a5-966d-e2d7c8a34fbc&token=MDVjZDgxODMtN2Fl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05cd8183-7aee-49a5-966d-e2d7c8a34fbc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:32:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>DIC India Ltd. has announced the reappointment of Mr. Adnan Wajhat Ahmad as an Independent Director for a second term of 3 years, subject to the approval of the members in the ensuing AGM. The company has also declared a final dividend of Rs. 3/- per equity share for the financial year ended December 31, 2025. Furthermore, the Board has appointed M/s. Chandra Wadhwa &amp; Co as the Cost Auditor of the company for the financial year 2026, subject to the approval of the equity shareholders at the 78th AGM. The 78th AGM will be held on March 23, 2026, through video conferencing or other audio-video means.</p><ul><li>Reappointment of Mr. Adnan Wajhat Ahmad as Independent Director</li><li>Declaration of final dividend for the financial year ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Appointment of M/s. Chandra Wadhwa &amp; Co as Cost Auditor for the financial year 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f6cbd834-5570-439d-a39c-1e10ba71481c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DIC INDIA LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[A2ZINFRA] A2Z Infra Engineering Ltd. Settles INR 142.05 Cr. Debt with Indian Bank through One Time Settlement</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=A2Z+Infra+Engineering+Limited&title=A2Z+Infra+Engineering+Ltd.+Settles+INR+142.05+Cr.+Debt+with+Indian+Bank+through+One+Time+Settlement&newsId=6d757851-64cb-4a0b-ad12-1b3b04b166fa&token=NmQ3NTc4NTEtNjRj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d757851-64cb-4a0b-ad12-1b3b04b166fa</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Loan</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>A2Z Infra Engineering Ltd. has signed a Full Cash One Time Settlement (OTS) with Indian Bank for a total settlement consideration of INR 50.0 Cr. The settlement is towards the debt of INR 142.05 Cr. that the company and its associate companies had availed from the bank. The company has been working to reduce its debt burden and has now settled with Indian Bank under a bilateral arrangement.</p><ul><li>A2Z Infra Engineering Ltd. has signed a Full Cash One Time Settlement (OTS) with Indian Bank for a total settlement consideration of INR 50.0 Cr.</li><li>The settlement is towards the debt of INR 142.05 Cr. that the company and its associate companies had availed from the bank.</li><li>The company has been working to reduce its debt burden and has now settled with Indian Bank under a bilateral arrangement.</li><li>The payment of INR 50.0 Cr. shall be made in installments over a period of 90 days.</li><li>In case of non-deposit of entire OTS amount within 90 days, an additional cure period of 90 days shall be allowed along with interest at 12.25% p.a. for the delayed period from the respective due dates.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d7cd9092-c996-4ee1-bc34-5685b521b67a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: A2Z Infra Engineering Limited | Category: Loan</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EMSLIMITED] EMS Ltd. to Consider Fundraising Proposal Through Various Securities</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=EMS+Ltd&title=EMS+Ltd.+to+Consider+Fundraising+Proposal+Through+Various+Securities&newsId=e2fb2a88-bc44-42fe-899e-ffc0e67dfa38&token=ZTJmYjJhODgtYmM0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e2fb2a88-bc44-42fe-899e-ffc0e67dfa38</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:17:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>EMS Ltd. has informed the BSE that the Board of Directors will meet on February 27, 2026, to consider and approve a proposal for raising funds. The fundraising may be executed through issuance of equity shares, GDRs, ADRs, FCCBs, convertible debentures, preference shares, or any other convertible securities. The company may use methods such as public issue, preferential allotment, private placement, or QIP. The fundraising is subject to regulatory and statutory approvals and shareholder approval. The Trading Window Closure Period commences from the date of this intimation till 48 hours after the closure of the meeting on February 27, 2026, in accordance with the Company&apos;s Code of Conduct for Prohibition of Insider Trading.</p><ul><li>EMS Ltd. to consider a fundraising proposal on February 27, 2026</li><li>Fundraising to be executed through issuance of various securities</li><li>The company may use methods such as public issue, preferential allotment, private placement, or QIP for fundraising</li><li>Fundraising is subject to regulatory, statutory, and shareholder approvals</li><li>Trading Window Closure Period commences from the date of this intimation till 48 hours after the closure of the meeting on February 27, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f6979930-9090-4908-a6dc-d42bee06b5a6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: EMS Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BAJAJELEC] Bajaj Electricals Ltd. Appoints Rahul Pundir as Chief Supply Chain Officer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BAJAJ+ELECTRICALS+LTD.-%24&title=Bajaj+Electricals+Ltd.+Appoints+Rahul+Pundir+as+Chief+Supply+Chain+Officer&newsId=45f2317c-de4a-434d-8da9-d4a43eab0a53&token=NDVmMjMxN2MtZGU0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">45f2317c-de4a-434d-8da9-d4a43eab0a53</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:12:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bajaj Electricals Ltd. has announced the appointment of Rahul Pundir as the Chief Supply Chain Officer, effective March 2, 2026. Pundir, who brings over 24 years of global leadership experience, is recognized for leading digital transformation programs and building high-performance organizations. He has delivered significant cost-to-serve value, margin expansion, and capital savings at P&amp;G Japan. Pundir holds an MBA from IM Mumbai and a degree in Mechanical Engineering, and has further strengthened his expertise through a PG Certification in Digital Manufacturing &amp; Smart Factories from IISc Bangalore and the Senior Executive Development Program at the University of Tennessee, USA.</p><ul><li>Rahul Pundir appointed as Chief Supply Chain Officer of Bajaj Electricals Ltd.</li><li>Pundir brings over 24 years of global leadership experience.</li><li>Recognized for leading digital transformation programs and building high-performance organizations.</li><li>Delivered significant cost-to-serve value, margin expansion, and capital savings at P&amp;G Japan.</li><li>Holds an MBA from IM Mumbai and a degree in Mechanical Engineering.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1c8c1597-2650-4873-a9e3-0fd2715013a3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BAJAJ ELECTRICALS LTD.-$ | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DICIND] DIC India Ltd Announces Record Date for Dividend and AGM Voting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DIC+INDIA+LTD.&title=DIC+India+Ltd+Announces+Record+Date+for+Dividend+and+AGM+Voting&newsId=b6c08fc0-4485-4aef-9d6f-918f07d084a1&token=YjZjMDhmYzAtNDQ4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6c08fc0-4485-4aef-9d6f-918f07d084a1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:11:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In a recent board meeting, DIC India Ltd has decided on the record date for dividend and voting in the Annual General Meeting (AGM). The 78th AGM will be held on March 23, 2026, through Video Conference / Other Audio Visual Means. The record date for determining entitlement of members to final dividend for the financial year ended December 31, 2025, is March 16, 2026. The book closure will be effective from March 17, 2026, to March 23, 2026.</p><ul><li>DIC India Ltd has set the record date for dividend and AGM voting on March 16, 2026.</li><li>The 78th AGM will be conducted via Video Conference / Other Audio Visual Means on March 23, 2026.</li><li>The book closure will be in effect from March 17, 2026, to March 23, 2026.</li><li>The final dividend, if approved at the AGM, will be paid within statutory timelines after deducting tax at source.</li><li>The decision was made in a board meeting held on February 24, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b512dd81-0281-453e-81a3-865d829af79d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DIC INDIA LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[5PAISA] 5paisa Capital Ltd. to Raise Funds through Rights Issue of up to INR 4,750.00 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=5paisa+Capital+Ltd&title=5paisa+Capital+Ltd.+to+Raise+Funds+through+Rights+Issue+of+up+to+INR+4%2C750.00+Million&newsId=59568af4-85f8-4953-afbc-bff25c0d6045&token=NTk1NjhhZjQtODVm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59568af4-85f8-4953-afbc-bff25c0d6045</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:07:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>5paisa Capital Ltd. has approved the raising of funds through the issuance of fully paid-up equity shares by way of a rights issue to eligible equity shareholders. The Rights Issue will not exceed INR 4,750.00 million, subject to regulatory approvals. The Rights Issue Committee will determine the specific terms, including issue price and rights entitlement ratio, and disclose them in due course.</p><ul><li>5paisa Capital Ltd. to raise funds through Rights Issue</li><li>Issue amount not to exceed INR 4,750.00 million</li><li>Funds to be raised by issuing fully paid-up equity shares</li><li>Rights Issue subject to regulatory approvals</li><li>Rights Issue Committee to determine specific terms</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fb637be1-59ae-4e38-a004-6e59b3e47e60.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: 5paisa Capital Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BELLACASA] Bella Casa Fashion &amp; Retail Ltd Reconstitutes Board Committees After Director&apos;s Resignation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Bella+Casa+Fashion+%26+Retail+Ltd&title=Bella+Casa+Fashion+%26+Retail+Ltd+Reconstitutes+Board+Committees+After+Director%27s+Resignation&newsId=cf3031ab-5bf6-4ac0-a57f-fdecb14bb8d0&token=Y2YzMDMxYWItNWJm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cf3031ab-5bf6-4ac0-a57f-fdecb14bb8d0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bella Casa Fashion &amp; Retail Ltd has reconstituted its Board Committees following the resignation of Mrs. Nivedita Ravindra Sarda and the appointment of Mrs. Bharti Rastogi as an Additional Non-Executive Independent Director. The reconstitution was approved at a Board Meeting held on February 24, 2026. The new Shareholder’s / Investors Grievance Committee includes Mr. Nitin Mathur as the Chairperson, Mrs. Bharti Rastogi as a Member, and Mr. Saurav Sir as a Member. The Nomination and Remuneration/Compensation Committee includes Mrs. Bharti Rastogi as the Chairperson, Mr. Govind Saboo as a Member, and Mr. Nitin Mathur as a Member. The terms of reference of the Committees remain unchanged.</p><ul><li>Bella Casa Fashion &amp; Retail Ltd reconstitutes Board Committees</li><li>Mrs. Nivedita Ravindra Sarda resigns from the company</li><li>Mrs. Bharti Rastogi appointed as Additional Non-Executive Independent Director</li><li>New Shareholder’s / Investors Grievance Committee formed</li><li>New Nomination and Remuneration/Compensation Committee formed</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/638c9718-0b77-4e0e-ae38-a3ed30eaf009.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Bella Casa Fashion & Retail Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>