<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:59:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[TIRUMALCHM] Thirumalai Chemicals Ltd to Consider Un-Audited Financials for Q4 2025 in February 2026 Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=THIRUMALAI+CHEMICALS+LTD.&title=Thirumalai+Chemicals+Ltd+to+Consider+Un-Audited+Financials+for+Q4+2025+in+February+2026+Board+Meeting&newsId=b2a610f4-6743-4c20-ad31-7d746827da0d&token=YjJhNjEwZjQtNjc0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b2a610f4-6743-4c20-ad31-7d746827da0d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Thirumalai Chemicals Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 14, 2026, to consider and approve the Un-Audited Financials for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. This meeting is in compliance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, as amended from time to time. The announcement serves as an information and record update for the stakeholders.</p><ul><li>Thirumalai Chemicals Ltd to consider Un-Audited Financials for Q4 2025</li><li>Board Meeting scheduled on February 14, 2026</li><li>In compliance with Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Meeting to consider and approve the Un-Audited Financials for the quarter ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Announcement serves as an information and record update for the stakeholders</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/63bb678f-18a4-4dd7-82f6-af305893f9d1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: THIRUMALAI CHEMICALS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KABSON] Kabsons Industries Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KABSONS+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Kabsons+Industries+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=6b4762e3-b8ff-4fe1-8c62-85c3a8c31901&token=NmI0NzYyZTMtYjhm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6b4762e3-b8ff-4fe1-8c62-85c3a8c31901</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:58:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kabsons Industries Ltd has reported its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The company&apos;s total income for the quarter is Rs. 1,068.15 lakhs, with expenses amounting to Rs. 1,070.92 lakhs, resulting in a loss before tax of Rs. 2.77 lakhs. The company has also reported a loss for the period from continuing operations of Rs. 2.77 lakhs.</p><ul><li>Kabsons Industries Ltd has reported a loss before tax of Rs. 2.77 lakhs for the quarter ended 31st December, 2025.</li><li>The company has reported a loss for the period from continuing operations of Rs. 2.77 lakhs.</li><li>The financial results have been prepared in accordance with Indian Accounting Standards (Ind AS) prescribed under Section 133 of the Companies Act 2013.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1f4603c2-c387-40bb-830d-26e357207d8b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KABSONS INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HOTLSILV] H S India Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=H.S.INDIA+LTD.&title=H+S+India+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025&newsId=4586ab2b-fd52-41c2-8ee1-3adeeb368fea&token=NDU4NmFiMmItZmQ1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4586ab2b-fd52-41c2-8ee1-3adeeb368fea</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:57:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>H S India Ltd, a company in the hospitality sector, has reported its un-audited results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The Board of Directors approved these results in a meeting held on 10th February 2026. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at Rs. 99.28 lakhs for the quarter and Rs. 2538.29 lakhs for the nine months period. The net profit for the period is Rs. 42 lakhs. The earnings per equity share (EPS) for the quarter is Rs. 0.38 and for the nine months period is Rs. 0.07. The company&apos;s only segment of activity is &apos;Hotelier&apos;. The Standalone Unaudited Financial Results are available on the BSE Limited and the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>H S India Ltd reports Q3 and nine months results for 2025</li><li>Revenue from operations stands at Rs. 99.28 lakhs for the quarter</li><li>Net profit for the period is Rs. 42 lakhs</li><li>EPS for the quarter is Rs. 0.38 and for the nine months period is Rs. 0.07</li><li>The company&apos;s only segment of activity is &apos;Hotelier&apos;</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1a4d023f-d569-4c4e-b61c-cb2d2c29875a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: H.S.INDIA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TAHMARENT] Tahmar Enterprises Ltd to Approve Q3 Results on Feb 14, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Tahmar+Enterprises+Ltd&title=Tahmar+Enterprises+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+Results+on+Feb+14%2C+2026&newsId=969d44c2-6d18-4a20-bd15-92cad3f6075e&token=OTY5ZDQ0YzItNmQx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">969d44c2-6d18-4a20-bd15-92cad3f6075e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:54:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tahmar Enterprises Ltd has announced a Board meeting on February 14, 2026, at its Corporate Office in Goa. The agenda includes the approval of Un-Audited Financial Results (Standalone) for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, and the Limited Review Report on the same. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the company by the designated persons and their immediate relatives was closed from January 01, 2026, till 48 hours after the Board Meeting.</p><ul><li>Tahmar Enterprises Ltd scheduled a Board Meeting on February 14, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve Un-Audited Financial Results for Q3 2025</li><li>The Limited Review Report on the Un-Audited Financial Results will also be approved</li><li>Trading Window for dealing in the securities of the company was closed from January 01, 2026, till 48 hours after the Board Meeting</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d25993bb-75f0-4f40-9128-64c06fd4bb7c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Tahmar Enterprises Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AHCL] Anlon Healthcare Limited Reports 20x EBITDA Growth and Strongly Positive PAT in Q3 FY26; Completes Strategic Acquisitions</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Anlon+Healthcare+Ltd&title=Anlon+Healthcare+Limited+Reports+20x+EBITDA+Growth+and+Strongly+Positive+PAT+in+Q3+FY26%3B+Completes+Strategic+Acquisitions&newsId=f0ca0dd7-5fb0-4872-aa02-afe69254c32a&token=ZjBjYTBkZDctNWZi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0ca0dd7-5fb0-4872-aa02-afe69254c32a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:53:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Anlon Healthcare Limited, a leading manufacturer of high-purity pharmaceutical intermediates and active pharmaceutical ingredients (APIs), announced its unaudited financial results for Q3 and 9M FY26. The company reported strong growth in revenue, profitability, and margins, driven by robust R&amp;D execution and strategic capacity expansion initiatives. Anlon also completed strategic acquisitions, expanding its consolidated manufacturing capacity and strengthening its operational and regulatory capabilities.</p><ul><li>Anlon Healthcare Limited reports 20x EBITDA growth and strongly positive PAT in Q3 FY26</li><li>Company records Total Income of INR 35.78 crore in Q3 FY26, representing a YoY growth of 281.5%</li><li>EBITDA at INR 12.54 crore and Profit After Tax of INR 5.15 crore in Q3 FY26</li><li>Acquired 67.48% equity stake in Apiqo Organics Private Limited for INR 5.40 crore</li><li>Acquisition of Bizotic Lifescience pending, expected to become a subsidiary upon completion</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fa5bc43f-743f-45ed-ab6d-94aa6e68b886.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Anlon Healthcare Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EVERLON] Everlon Financials Ltd Approves Q3 Results for Dec 2025, Reports 1,583.37 Lakhs in Revenue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=EVERLON+SYNTHETICS+LTD.&title=Everlon+Financials+Ltd+Approves+Q3+Results+for+Dec+2025%2C+Reports+1%2C583.37+Lakhs+in+Revenue&newsId=73c89eca-a604-4d88-a4c5-e27ea2f49ced&token=NzNjODllY2EtYTYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73c89eca-a604-4d88-a4c5-e27ea2f49ced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:53:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Everlon Financials Ltd, formerly known as Everlon Synthetics Limited, announced its un-audited financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The company reported a revenue from operations of 1,583.37 lakhs. The board of directors approved the results in a meeting that commenced at 11.35 a.m. and concluded at 11.55 a.m. on 10th February 2026. The company is currently evaluating the impact of the new Labour Codes. The financial results have been prepared in accordance with Ind AS 34, the Companies Act, 2013, and the SEBI Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations 2015.</p><ul><li>Everlon Financials Ltd reported a revenue from operations of 1,583.37 lakhs for Q3 ended 31st December 2025.</li><li>The board of directors approved the un-audited financial results in a meeting on 10th February 2026.</li><li>The company is currently evaluating the impact of the new Labour Codes.</li><li>The financial results have been prepared in accordance with Ind AS 34, the Companies Act, 2013, and the SEBI Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d24284ba-e853-444f-9973-ab5c56dfa94a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: EVERLON SYNTHETICS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LUXIND] Lux Industries Ltd: No Price Sensitive Information Behind Volume Surge</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Lux+Industries+Ltd&title=Lux+Industries+Ltd%3A+No+Price+Sensitive+Information+Behind+Volume+Surge&newsId=94753444-e749-4659-a18e-bf869a3f98fe&token=OTQ3NTM0NDQtZTc0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">94753444-e749-4659-a18e-bf869a3f98fe</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:53:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Lux Industries Ltd has clarified a query regarding the increase in volume of its shares on the exchanges. The company stated that it is in compliance with all applicable regulations of the Securities Exchange Board of India and has been promptly informing the stock exchanges about all events, announcements, and price sensitive information. Although there has been a noticeable spurt in volume recently, the company believes there is no undisclosed or price sensitive information that could influence the price or volume behavior of its shares at the moment.</p><ul><li>Lux Industries Ltd has responded to a query regarding the increase in volume of its shares on the exchanges.</li><li>The company is in compliance with all applicable regulations of the Securities Exchange Board of India.</li><li>There is no undisclosed or price sensitive information that could influence the price or volume behavior of Lux Industries Ltd&apos;s shares at present.</li><li>The company has been promptly informing the stock exchanges about all events, announcements, and price sensitive information.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/79d91967-f486-407d-ab3f-e9933c353909.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Lux Industries Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KABSON] Kabsons Industries Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KABSONS+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Kabsons+Industries+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=1ce0920a-aaba-4b78-a6ad-55c752c2e542&token=MWNlMDkyMGEtYWFi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1ce0920a-aaba-4b78-a6ad-55c752c2e542</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kabsons Industries Ltd, with BSE Scrip Code KABSON/524675, has released its unaudited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The results were approved in a Board Meeting on 10th February, 2026. The company is primarily engaged in trading in LPG and leasing out bottling plants temporarily. The financial results have been prepared in accordance with Indian Accounting Standards (Ind AS) and other recognized accounting principles and policies.</p><ul><li>Revenue for the quarter ended 31st December 2025 is Rs. 1,068.15 lakhs.</li><li>Total expenses for the quarter ended 31st December 2025 are Rs. 1,118.23 lakhs.</li><li>Profit before tax for the quarter ended 31st December 2025 is Rs. (50.08) lakhs.</li><li>Profit for the period from continuing operations for the quarter ended 31st December 2025 is Rs. (50.08) lakhs.</li><li>The company has assessed the financial implications of changes in labour codes, which resulted in an increase in employee benefit expenses.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4eb63b33-20ad-42c5-b204-438891b834e4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KABSONS INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VISIONCO] Vision Corporation Ltd to Approve Q4 Results on Feb 13, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VISION+CORPORATION+LTD.&title=Vision+Corporation+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+Results+on+Feb+13%2C+2026&newsId=19c3b21d-6c5d-4850-bd3a-0eb7ff23782b&token=MTljM2IyMWQtNmM1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19c3b21d-6c5d-4850-bd3a-0eb7ff23782b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:52:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vision Corporation Ltd has scheduled a Board Meeting on February 13, 2026, to consider and approve the Un-Audited Standalone Financial Results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The Trading Window for dealing in Securities of the Company has been closed from January 1, 2026, and will reopen after 48 hours of declaration of un-audited Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Vision Corporation Ltd to consider and approve Un-Audited Standalone Financial Results for Q4 2025</li><li>Trading Window for dealing in Securities of the Company closed from January 1, 2026</li><li>Trading Window to reopen after 48 hours of declaration of un-audited Financial Results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/264cdd98-02e5-44af-abeb-83b4e7623894.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VISION CORPORATION LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HOTLSILV] HS India Ltd. Approves Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=H.S.INDIA+LTD.&title=HS+India+Ltd.+Approves+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=2dce583b-bed2-462e-a39b-941b358d93e4&token=MmRjZTU4M2ItYmVk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2dce583b-bed2-462e-a39b-941b358d93e4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:51:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>HS India Ltd. held its Board Meeting No. 2025-26/4 on 10th February, 2026, to consider and approve the Statement of Un-audited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December, 2025. The company, which operates in the hotelier segment, has reported revenue from operations, other income, and various expenses. The net profit for the period stands at Rs. 42 lakhs.</p><ul><li>HS India Ltd. approves Q3 and nine months financial results for 2025.</li><li>Revenue from operations reported for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December, 2025.</li><li>The company operates in the hotelier segment.</li><li>Net profit for the period stands at Rs. 42 lakhs.</li><li>Financial results prepared in accordance with Indian Accounting Standards (Ind AS)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/81467d63-4317-4255-a5a1-b2cee5d30d3e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: H.S.INDIA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>