<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 04:01:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[WOCKPHARMA] Wockhardt Files Marketing Authorisation Application for Novel Antibiotic WCK 5222 with European Medicines Agency</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=WOCKHARDT+LTD.&title=Wockhardt+Files+Marketing+Authorisation+Application+for+Novel+Antibiotic+WCK+5222+with+European+Medicines+Agency&newsId=9e5aa58b-8f2e-45ed-91cf-f29212e37535&token=OWU1YWE1OGItOGYy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e5aa58b-8f2e-45ed-91cf-f29212e37535</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 03:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Wockhardt Limited, a leading pharmaceutical company, has successfully filed a Marketing Authorisation Application (MAA) with the European Medicines Agency (EMA) for its novel antibiotic, WCK 5222. The EMA is responsible for the scientific evaluation of new medicines across 30 countries. WCK 5222, a fixed-dose combination of Zidebactam (1 g) and Cefepime (2 g), is eligible for Accelerated Assessment, reflecting the unmet medical need addressed by the product. The New Drug Application (NDA) on WCK 5222 is already under fast-track review by the US FDA. The priority review status granted to WCK 5222 underscores the global urgency to make effective treatment options available for patients suffering from life-threatening multi-drug resistant infections. Zaynich®, the brand name for WCK 5222, is the first New Chemical Entity (NCE) discovered and developed in India to be submitted for pan-European marketing authorisation.</p><ul><li>Wockhardt has filed a Marketing Authorisation Application (MAA) for its novel antibiotic, WCK 5222, with the European Medicines Agency (EMA).</li><li>WCK 5222 is a fixed-dose combination of Zidebactam (1 g) and Cefepime (2 g).</li><li>WCK 5222 is eligible for Accelerated Assessment by the EMA, reflecting the unmet medical need addressed by the product.</li><li>The New Drug Application (NDA) on WCK 5222 is already under fast-track review by the US FDA.</li><li>Zaynich®, the brand name for WCK 5222, is the first New Chemical Entity (NCE) discovered and developed in India to be submitted for pan-European marketing authorisation.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e5f45527-2fa1-4a53-a141-4e1aeeac4aa3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: WOCKHARDT LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LAXMIMACH] LMW Ltd to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q4 2025 in Board Meeting on 28th January 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LAKSHMI+MACHINE+WORKS+LTD.&title=LMW+Ltd+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q4+2025+in+Board+Meeting+on+28th+January+2026&newsId=76fbd833-7b66-403a-92f5-d8ced094b8c1&token=NzZmYmQ4MzMtN2I2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76fbd833-7b66-403a-92f5-d8ced094b8c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 03:39:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>LMW Ltd has scheduled a Board of Directors meeting on 28th January 2026 to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and period ended 31st December 2025. The trading window will be closed from 1st January 2026 to 30th January 2026 (both days inclusive) as per Regulation 46 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The Notice of Board Meeting is being posted on the Company’s website as required.</p><ul><li>LMW Ltd to consider and approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q4 2025</li><li>Board Meeting scheduled on 28th January 2026</li><li>Trading window to be closed from 1st January to 30th January 2026</li><li>Regulation 46 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015 to be followed</li><li>Notice of Board Meeting to be posted on the Company’s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/984737dc-4d5c-4d5d-a3c7-afeffb3107e6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LAKSHMI MACHINE WORKS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UNIMECH] Unimech Aerospace Subsidiary Secures INR 72.20 Crore Order from NPCIL</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Unimech+Aerospace+and+Manufacturing+Ltd&title=Unimech+Aerospace+Subsidiary+Secures+INR+72.20+Crore+Order+from+NPCIL&newsId=4d94c5cb-ff6a-45c7-91a1-454a203ae7bb&token=NGQ5NGM1Y2ItZmY2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d94c5cb-ff6a-45c7-91a1-454a203ae7bb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 03:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Innomech Aerospace Toolings Pvt Ltd, a wholly owned subsidiary of Unimech Aerospace and Manufacturing Ltd, has been awarded an order worth INR 72.20 crores from Nuclear Power Corporation of India Limited (NPCIL). The order is for the supply and delivery of Support Equipment for Tarapur Atomic Power Station Power Station Unit-3&amp;4. The order is to be executed in staggered deliveries up to December 2028.</p><ul><li>Unimech Aerospace&apos;s subsidiary bags order worth INR 72.20 crores</li><li>Order from Nuclear Power Corporation of India Limited (NPCIL)</li><li>Supply and delivery of Support Equipment for Tarapur Atomic Power Station Power Station Unit-3&amp;4</li><li>Staggered deliveries up to December 2028</li><li>Deal is not a related party transaction</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0cdee9d5-1fc2-42c2-be25-c951cf1ee1ad.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Unimech Aerospace and Manufacturing Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WELCORP] Welspun Corp Secures Rs 3,100 Crore Export Order for Large Diameter Coated Line Pipes</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Welspun+Corp+Limited&title=Welspun+Corp+Secures+Rs+3%2C100+Crore+Export+Order+for+Large+Diameter+Coated+Line+Pipes&newsId=914f010e-91b9-4cf3-a779-c9798942f12a&token=OTE0ZjAxMGUtOTFi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">914f010e-91b9-4cf3-a779-c9798942f12a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 03:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Welspun Corp Ltd has announced the receipt of a new export order for supply of large diameter coated line pipes for supply in Americas. This order, along with additional orders booked in India since the last announcement in Sept &apos;25, amounts to Rs 3,100 Crore. The consolidated global order book now stands at Rs 23,460 Crore (equivalent to US$ 2.6 billion, approx.), providing clear business visibility and continuity for both India and USA assets. The order book will be executed during FY26, FY27 and FY28.</p><ul><li>Welspun Corp secures a new export order for large diameter coated line pipes worth Rs 3,100 Crore</li><li>Additional orders booked in India since Sept &apos;25 amount to Rs 3,100 Crore</li><li>Consolidated global order book stands at Rs 23,460 Crore (equivalent to US$ 2.6 billion, approx.)</li><li>Order book to be executed during FY26, FY27 and FY28</li><li>Order provides clear business visibility and continuity for both India and USA assets</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/10274ca4-1ac6-4d7b-834b-ff713b6d32b9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Welspun Corp Limited | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GLITTEKG] Acquirers to Acquire up to 26% Equity Share Capital in Glittek Granites Ltd for INR 8,53,87,500 through Open Offer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GLITTEK+GRANITES+LTD.&title=Acquirers+to+Acquire+up+to+26%25+Equity+Share+Capital+in+Glittek+Granites+Ltd+for+INR+8%2C53%2C87%2C500+through+Open+Offer&newsId=b5b2180b-41d0-4d94-bbb4-a6bda1119aa2&token=YjViMjE4MGItNDFk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5b2180b-41d0-4d94-bbb4-a6bda1119aa2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 02:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Open Offer</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vivro Financial Services Pvt. Ltd. has submitted a Public Announcement for the attention of the public shareholders of Glittek Granites Ltd. The Acquirers, represented by Maheshkumar Jatashankar Thanki, Bhargav Girjashankar Thanki, Bhavin Harihar Thanki, Kalpana Ashwinkumar Thanki, Hema Bhargav Thanki, and Gautam Ashwinkumar Thanki, along with Rawmin Mining and Industries Private Limited (PAC), intend to acquire up to 67,50,000 Equity Shares of Glittek Granites Ltd from public shareholders. This acquisition represents 26% of the Equity Share Capital of the Target Company and is valued at INR 8,53,87,500, assuming full acceptance. The Offer Price is INR 12.65 per Offer Share, and the Offer Size is 67,50,000 Equity Shares. The Offer is not subject to any minimum level of acceptance and is a triggered offer in compliance with Regulations 3(1) and 4 of the SEBI (SAST) Regulations.</p><ul><li>Acquirers to acquire up to 26% Equity Share Capital in Glittek Granites Ltd</li><li>Offer Size of INR 8,53,87,500, assuming full acceptance</li><li>Offer Price of INR 12.65 per Offer Share</li><li>Not subject to any minimum level of acceptance</li><li>Triggered offer in compliance with Regulations 3(1) and 4 of the SEBI (SAST) Regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/CDDD3883-E647-40D2-834B-3B703AF596C9-075608.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GLITTEK GRANITES LTD. | Category: Open Offer</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SOFTBPO] Northvale Capital Partners Pte Limited to Acquire 60.00% Stake in Softbpo Global Services Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SOFTBPO+GLOBAL+SERVICES+LTD.&title=Northvale+Capital+Partners+Pte+Limited+to+Acquire+60.00%25+Stake+in+Softbpo+Global+Services+Ltd&newsId=d7665ea4-7571-4d8b-9db2-da19e4dda155&token=ZDc2NjVlYTQtNzU3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7665ea4-7571-4d8b-9db2-da19e4dda155</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 02:22:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Northvale Capital Partners Pte Limited, along with other parties, has entered into a Share Purchase Agreement with AHA Holdings Private Limited for the acquisition of 90,000 equity shares of Softbpo Global Services Ltd, representing 60.00% of the voting equity share capital. The acquirer has announced an open offer for up to 60,000 equity shares at a price of Rs. 10.00 per share. The offer is in compliance with the SEBI (SAST) Regulations and is not subject to any minimum level of acceptance.</p><ul><li>Northvale Capital Partners Pte Limited to acquire 60.00% stake in Softbpo Global Services Ltd</li><li>Acquirer to purchase 90,000 equity shares from AHA Holdings Private Limited</li><li>Open offer for up to 60,000 equity shares at a price of Rs. 10.00 per share</li><li>Offer not subject to any minimum level of acceptance</li><li>Compliance with the SEBI (SAST) Regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/037D7319-3417-4D2A-9AF5-F0A5EC4D24C6-075014.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SOFTBPO GLOBAL SERVICES LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HONAUT] Honeywell Automation India Ltd. to Approve Q3 and 9M Financial Results on Feb 2, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HONEYWELL+AUTOMATION+INDIA+LTD.&title=Honeywell+Automation+India+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q3+and+9M+Financial+Results+on+Feb+2%2C+2026&newsId=d08aa5c4-e844-4cb2-ab60-4c743c4bb8fc&token=ZDA4YWE1YzQtZTg0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d08aa5c4-e844-4cb2-ab60-4c743c4bb8fc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 02:12:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Honeywell Automation India Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 2, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting is held in accordance with Regulation 29(1)(a) of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. Additionally, the Trading Window for dealing in the Equity Shares of the Company by the Designated Persons will be closed from January 1, 2026, till the expiry of 48 hours from the date the aforesaid Financial Results are made public, i.e., Wednesday, February 4, 2026.</p><ul><li>Honeywell Automation India Ltd. to consider and approve Q3 and 9M financial results for 2025</li><li>Board Meeting scheduled on February 2, 2026</li><li>Trading Window for Designated Persons to remain closed from January 1, 2026, to February 4, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c77c1124-d5b9-411a-8b80-5e1915564ac2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HONEYWELL AUTOMATION INDIA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KALYANKJIL] Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd Reports 42% Revenue Growth in Q3 FY2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kalyan+Jewellers+India+Ltd&title=Kalyan+Jewellers+India+Ltd+Reports+42%25+Revenue+Growth+in+Q3+FY2026&newsId=1d5c46fe-a66a-474e-bf49-a9124e1b7afe&token=MWQ1YzQ2ZmUtYTY2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d5c46fe-a66a-474e-bf49-a9124e1b7afe</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 02:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd has reported a consolidated revenue growth of approximately 42% in Q3 FY2026 compared to the same period in the previous financial year. The India operations witnessed a revenue growth of approximately 42%, driven by strong festive demand and robust demand post-Diwali. The international operations recorded a revenue growth of approximately 36%, with the Middle East contributing approximately 28% of the revenue. The digital-first jewellery platform, Candere, recorded a revenue growth of approximately 147%. The company launched a total of 36 showrooms across India, the United Kingdom, and Candere during the quarter.</p><ul><li>Consolidated revenue growth of approximately 42% in Q3 FY2026</li><li>Revenue growth of approximately 42% in India operations</li><li>Revenue growth of approximately 36% in international operations</li><li>Approximately 28% revenue growth in Middle East operations</li><li>Approximately 147% revenue growth in Candere</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0afe91ac-a797-4fed-88d1-c917a4b25601.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JONJUA] Jonjua Overseas Ltd. Announces Record Date for Bonus Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jonjua+Overseas+Ltd&title=Jonjua+Overseas+Ltd.+Announces+Record+Date+for+Bonus+Issue&newsId=ffba8a17-11d2-42dd-847d-aa96e4679fb9&token=ZmZiYThhMTctMTFk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ffba8a17-11d2-42dd-847d-aa96e4679fb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 00:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Bonus</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jonjua Overseas Ltd. has announced the record date for a bonus issue. The record date is set as Friday, 23-January-2026. The deemed date of allotment is 27 January, 2026 and the Bonus Shares will be available for trading on the next working day, i.e. 28 January, 2026. The Company will submit the necessary documents to the Depository for credit of the Bonus Equity Shares in the Depository System by Tuesday, January 27th, 2026, 12:00 p.m. The dates are subject to approval from various authorities including BSE.</p><ul><li>Jonjua Overseas Ltd. announces record date for bonus issue.</li><li>Record date set as Friday, 23-January-2026.</li><li>Deemed date of allotment is 27 January, 2026.</li><li>Bonus Shares will be available for trading on 28 January, 2026.</li><li>Company to submit necessary documents to Depository by 27th January, 2026, 12:00 p.m.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4467d3f8-53eb-45ee-bc97-fe5025679202.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jonjua Overseas Ltd | Category: Bonus</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PDSL] PDS Ltd Subsidiary Poetic Brands Divests 20% Stake in Mambo Leisure</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PDS+Ltd&title=PDS+Ltd+Subsidiary+Poetic+Brands+Divests+20%25+Stake+in+Mambo+Leisure&newsId=aec5a8df-4440-4663-b719-0ed828a4dd14&token=YWVjNWE4ZGYtNDQ0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aec5a8df-4440-4663-b719-0ed828a4dd14</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>PDS Limited has announced the disinvestment of its subsidiary, Poetic Brands Limited, UK&apos;s entire 20% equity stake in Mambo Leisure Masters Limited, United Kingdom. This decision is part of the ongoing rationalisation of the corporate structure within the PDS Group. The transaction, which has been undertaken in line with the Company’s strategic and economic objectives, became effective on January 6, 2026. Mambo Leisure has ceased to be a step-down associate of the Company consequent to the completion of this transaction.</p><ul><li>PDS Limited&apos;s subsidiary, Poetic Brands Limited, UK divests its entire 20% equity stake in Mambo Leisure Masters Limited, UK</li><li>Transaction is part of the ongoing rationalisation of the corporate structure within the PDS Group</li><li>The transaction became effective on January 6, 2026</li><li>Mambo Leisure has ceased to be a step-down associate of the Company</li><li>The disclosure is as per Schedule III of the SEBI Listing Regulations and SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/CFD/PoD2/CIR/P/0155 dated November 11, 2024</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6affa67f-2b5e-45c0-b006-67bb311e9151.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PDS Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>