<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:43:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[MORGAN] SEBI Imposes Fine on Morgan Ventures Ltd for Late RPT Disclosure but Later Waives It Off</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MORGAN+VENTURES+LTD.&title=SEBI+Imposes+Fine+on+Morgan+Ventures+Ltd+for+Late+RPT+Disclosure+but+Later+Waives+It+Off&newsId=b101a2a6-3f45-44d0-8f99-13309b408f39&token=YjEwMWEyYTYtM2Y0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b101a2a6-3f45-44d0-8f99-13309b408f39</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Morgan Ventures Ltd, a company based in New Delhi, India, received a notice from BSE Limited (BSE) regarding a fine of Rs. 5900/- for a one-day delay in submitting a Related Party Transaction (RPT) disclosure. The delay was due to technical issues in BSE&apos;s filing system. The company made a representation to BSE to waive the fine, which was accepted. The fine was waived off after the Internal Regulatory Oversight and Review Group (IRORG) reviewed the case and considered the company&apos;s written representation.</p><ul><li>Morgan Ventures Ltd received a fine from BSE for late RPT disclosure.</li><li>The fine was imposed due to a one-day delay caused by technical issues in BSE&apos;s filing system.</li><li>The company made a representation to BSE to waive the fine.</li><li>The fine was waived off after review by the IRORG.</li><li>The waiver was based on the facts of the case and the company&apos;s written representation.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/35062e97-8b12-4b39-8a9c-475706516ee6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MORGAN VENTURES LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KARURVYSYA] Karur Vysya Bank Q3 FY &apos;26: Net Profit Up 25%, NIM Expands to 3.99%, Fresh Slippages Down</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KARUR+VYSYA+BANK+LTD.&title=Karur+Vysya+Bank+Q3+FY+%2726%3A+Net+Profit+Up+25%25%2C+NIM+Expands+to+3.99%25%2C+Fresh+Slippages+Down&newsId=4b49d70a-55ed-46f7-9aa1-683060ca91b9&token=NGI0OWQ3MGEtNTVl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4b49d70a-55ed-46f7-9aa1-683060ca91b9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Karur Vysya Bank Ltd has reported a 25% year-on-year increase in net profit for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The bank&apos;s net interest margins expanded to 3.99%, a 22 basis points increase from the previous quarter. Fresh slippages were down to 0.63% on an annualized basis. The bank&apos;s total business reached INR2,11,647 crores, reflecting a year-on-year increase of 16%. Advances and deposits grew by 17% and 16%, respectively, on a year-on-year basis. The bank&apos;s liability business constitutes 54% of the total business. Recoveries from written-off accounts amounted to INR179 crores during the quarter. The cost-to-income ratio for the 9-month period ended was 43.98%.</p><ul><li>Net profit up 25% year-on-year</li><li>NIM expands to 3.99%</li><li>Fresh slippages down to 0.63% on an annualized basis</li><li>Total business reaches INR2,11,647 crores</li><li>Recoveries from written-off accounts at INR179 crores</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/FDC126A1-8CF7-48A8-A394-6E7AC87939C0-120702.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KARUR VYSYA BANK LTD. | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASHOKALC] Aeonx Digital Technology Ltd to Consider and Approve Q3 and Nine Month Results for 2025 in February 2026 Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ASHOK+ALCO-CHEM+LTD.&title=Aeonx+Digital+Technology+Ltd+to+Consider+and+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Month+Results+for+2025+in+February+2026+Board+Meeting&newsId=ab697563-7dde-4d4f-b3d6-78fc9912a3a0&token=YWI2OTc1NjMtN2Rk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab697563-7dde-4d4f-b3d6-78fc9912a3a0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Aeonx Digital Technology Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 4, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. This meeting is in accordance with Regulation 29 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Aeonx Digital Technology Ltd scheduled a Board Meeting on 04/02/2026</li><li>The meeting aims to consider and approve the un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5a0210d7-9bb4-4c08-b554-303fb0e67c30.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ASHOK ALCO-CHEM LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RELIGARE] India Ratings &amp; Research Upgrades Credit Rating of Care Health Insurance, a Subsidiary of Religare Enterprises Ltd to IND AA-/ Stable</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RELIGARE+ENTERPRISES+LTD.&title=India+Ratings+%26+Research+Upgrades+Credit+Rating+of+Care+Health+Insurance%2C+a+Subsidiary+of+Religare+Enterprises+Ltd+to+IND+AA-%2F+Stable&newsId=7d47b9bb-ae0c-44b0-a576-740b1e4f509a&token=N2Q0N2I5YmItYWUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7d47b9bb-ae0c-44b0-a576-740b1e4f509a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Religare Enterprises Ltd has announced that India Ratings &amp; Research Private Limited (Ind-Ra) has upgraded the Credit Rating of Care Health Insurance Limited, a material subsidiary of the company, to IND AA-/ Stable. This upgrade was communicated by Ind-Ra on January 29, 2026. The press release regarding this upgrade can be accessed at https://www.indiaratings.co.in/pressrelease/81268.</p><ul><li>India Ratings &amp; Research upgrades Credit Rating of Care Health Insurance Limited to IND AA-/ Stable</li><li>Care Health Insurance is a material subsidiary of Religare Enterprises Ltd</li><li>The upgrade was communicated on January 29, 2026</li><li>The press release can be accessed at https://www.indiaratings.co.in/pressrelease/81268</li><li>This upgrade is a positive sign for Religare Enterprises Ltd and its subsidiaries</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4d117783-a5a2-4716-adaa-890a3d328569.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RELIGARE ENTERPRISES LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KUMPFIN] Kumbhat Financial Services Ltd to Approve Q4 Results on Feb 9, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KUMBHAT+FINANCIAL+SERVICES+LTD.&title=Kumbhat+Financial+Services+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+Results+on+Feb+9%2C+2026&newsId=5dd358f0-12c4-4343-88fa-a49c44133d2e&token=NWRkMzU4ZjAtMTJj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5dd358f0-12c4-4343-88fa-a49c44133d2e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:39:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kumbhat Financial Services Ltd has scheduled a Board meeting on February 9, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The meeting will also take note of the limited review from statutory auditors, accept the resignation of Mr. Mohanraj S, the Company Secretary, and appoint a new Company Secretary. Any other matter with the approval of the chairman will also be discussed.</p><ul><li>Kumbhat Financial Services Ltd to approve Q4 results on Feb 9, 2026</li><li>Unaudited financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025 to be approved</li><li>Limited review from statutory auditors to be taken note of</li><li>Resignation of Mr. Mohanraj S, the Company Secretary to be accepted</li><li>Appointment of a new Company Secretary</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2fea3799-8ca1-4b7d-8274-6ee34f37146e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KUMBHAT FINANCIAL SERVICES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STANBIK] Stanbik Agro Ltd: Resignation of Company Secretary cum Compliance Officer and Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Stanbik+Agro+Ltd&title=Stanbik+Agro+Ltd%3A+Resignation+of+Company+Secretary+cum+Compliance+Officer+and+Independent+Director&newsId=99952e5c-8f19-4032-b349-920bfc555f5e&token=OTk5NTJlNWMtOGYx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">99952e5c-8f19-4032-b349-920bfc555f5e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:37:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Stanbik Agro Ltd has announced the resignation of Ms. Pooja Manthan Patel from the post of Company Secretary cum Compliance Officer and Ms. Arzoo Rabari from the post of Independent Director, effective from 30th January, 2026. The resignation of Ms. Pooja Manthan Patel is due to better opportunity elsewhere, while Ms. Arzoo Rabari has resigned due to personal reasons and other professional commitments. The Board Meeting was held on 30th January, 2026, from 11.30 AM to 12.00 PM.</p><ul><li>Resignation of Ms. Pooja Manthan Patel from the post of Company Secretary cum Compliance Officer.</li><li>Resignation of Ms. Arzoo Rabari from the post of Independent Director.</li><li>Both resignations are effective from 30th January, 2026.</li><li>Ms. Pooja Manthan Patel has resigned due to better opportunity elsewhere.</li><li>Ms. Arzoo Rabari has resigned due to personal reasons and other professional commitments.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a0ad7429-f2b1-49ce-b075-930036a89211.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Stanbik Agro Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDAG] Indag Rubber Ltd. to Approve Q3 FY2025-26 Financial Results on Feb 12, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDAG+RUBBER+LTD.-%24&title=Indag+Rubber+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q3+FY2025-26+Financial+Results+on+Feb+12%2C+2026&newsId=6afc0249-0cd7-42c0-b3df-2f43cfb5ddb5&token=NmFmYzAyNDktMGNk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6afc0249-0cd7-42c0-b3df-2f43cfb5ddb5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indag Rubber Ltd. has informed the BSE that their Board of Directors will meet on February 12, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025 (Standalone &amp; Consolidated). The meeting is in accordance with Regulation 29 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. Additionally, in compliance with SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, the trading window was closed from January 01, 2026, and will reopen on February 15, 2026.</p><ul><li>Indag Rubber Ltd. to consider and approve unaudited financial results for Q3 FY2025-26</li><li>Board Meeting scheduled on 12th February 2026</li><li>The trading window closed from 1st January 2026 to 14th February 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/94597b71-5e7f-4095-94b9-ea8cc4eb8ac2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDAG RUBBER LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PVSL] Popular Vehicles And Services Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on Feb 10, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Popular+Vehicles+and+Services+Ltd&title=Popular+Vehicles+And+Services+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+Feb+10%2C+2026&newsId=3878cdea-cc5d-4cab-ae08-1d89aa066dbb&token=Mzg3OGNkZWEtY2M1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3878cdea-cc5d-4cab-ae08-1d89aa066dbb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:33:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Popular Vehicles And Services Ltd has announced a meeting of its Board of Directors on February 10, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. This is in accordance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations 2015. The trading window for dealing in the shares of the company by its &apos;Designated Persons&apos; will be closed from January 1, 2026, till the expiry of forty-eight (48) hours after the declaration of the un-audited financial results to the public.</p><ul><li>Popular Vehicles And Services Ltd to consider and approve Q3 and nine months financial results on Feb 10, 2026</li><li>Meeting scheduled in accordance with SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations 2015</li><li>Trading window for &apos;Designated Persons&apos; to be closed from Jan 1, 2026, till 48 hours after public declaration of results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3f31eaa1-1fe5-4e00-b3d9-30edf89e9a79.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Popular Vehicles and Services Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CENTUM] Centum Electronics Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q3 FY26 Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CENTUM+ELECTRONICS+LTD.&title=Centum+Electronics+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+FY26+Financial+Results&newsId=9671f3a8-9126-4dfc-9496-59e81d5b57ef&token=OTY3MWYzYTgtOTEy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9671f3a8-9126-4dfc-9496-59e81d5b57ef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Centum Electronics Ltd has informed the BSE that their Board of Directors will meet on February 6, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the third quarter ended December 31, 2025. This notice is pursuant to the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The &apos;Trading Window&apos; for dealing in the securities of the Company will remain closed for all Designated Persons, their immediate relatives, and connected persons of the Company till February 8, 2026. The Company has also scheduled an earnings call with investors and analysts on February 9, 2026, to discuss the Company’s financial and operational performance for the Third quarter ended December 31, 2025.</p><ul><li>Centum Electronics Ltd Board Meeting scheduled on February 6, 2026, to approve Q3 FY26 financial results.</li><li>Trading Window for dealing in securities of the Company closed till February 8, 2026, for Designated Persons and connected persons.</li><li>Earnings call with investors and analysts scheduled on February 9, 2026, to discuss the Company’s Q3 FY26 performance.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/aad2a744-16dd-43d9-bbc4-189504856c93.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CENTUM ELECTRONICS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LAKSELEC] Lakshmi Electrical Control Systems Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Unaudited Financial Results for FY2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LAKSHMI+ELECTRICAL+CONTROL+SYSTEMS+LTD.&title=Lakshmi+Electrical+Control+Systems+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+FY2025-26&newsId=5af76f1c-19f9-44df-9d60-1fde1b5d6f44&token=NWFmNzZmMWMtMTlm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5af76f1c-19f9-44df-9d60-1fde1b5d6f44</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Lakshmi Electrical Control Systems Ltd has reported its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The results were approved by the Board of Directors in a meeting held on 30th January 2026. The company has also reviewed the impact of the new Labour Codes notified by the Government of India on 21st November 2025, and has presented the incremental impact as Statutory impact of new Labour Codes under Exceptional Items in the statement of profit and loss for the period ended December 31, 2025.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the nine months ended 31st December 2025 is Rs. 17,352.74 lakhs</li><li>Profit before tax for the nine months ended 31st December 2025 is Rs. 246.93 lakhs</li><li>Total comprehensive income for the nine months ended 31st December 2025 is Rs. 1,734.89 lakhs</li><li>The company has presented the incremental impact of the new Labour Codes as Statutory impact of new Labour Codes under Exceptional Items in the statement of profit and loss</li><li>The Statutory Auditors have carried out a limited review of the above results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fdbb95dc-2eb3-45ed-a7ee-c421c1a224ff.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LAKSHMI ELECTRICAL CONTROL SYSTEMS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>