<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:59:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[BLOOM] Bloom Dekor Ltd: 20th CoC Meeting Approves Resolutions &amp; Ratifies Expenses</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BLOOM+DEKOR+LTD.-%24&title=Bloom+Dekor+Ltd%3A+20th+CoC+Meeting+Approves+Resolutions+%26+Ratifies+Expenses&newsId=d8839bbc-ddd7-4ca8-b96c-ad0aae1d2e87&token=ZDg4MzliYmMtZGRk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d8839bbc-ddd7-4ca8-b96c-ad0aae1d2e87</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The 20th Committee of Creditors (CoC) Meeting of Bloom Dekor Ltd was successfully convened on 5th February 2026. The meeting discussed various matters as per the Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code, 2016. Key decisions include the approval and ratification of the appointment of Thakkar and Pahwa, Advocates, for filing the Interlocutory Application to intimate the Adjudicating Authority regarding assignment of debt. The CoC also approved and ratified the receipts and payments pertaining to the CIRP period, the renewal of Property Insurance of the Corporate Debtor, and the expenses incurred by the Resolution Professional towards courier expenses, advocate professional fees, and Form EA charges. The last date for submission of the Resolution Plan by the Resolution Applicant was also extended till 12th February 2026.</p><ul><li>20th CoC Meeting approves various resolutions and ratifies expenses</li><li>Appointment of Thakkar and Pahwa, Advocates, approved for filing Interlocutory Application</li><li>Receipts and payments pertaining to the CIRP period approved and ratified</li><li>Property Insurance of the Corporate Debtor renewed</li><li>Last date for submission of Resolution Plan extended till 12th February 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f7b47cbc-4d17-4111-ba8a-720ba5c99a08.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BLOOM DEKOR LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MUZALI] Muzali Arts Ltd. Reports Q3 and Nine Months Ended Dec 31, 2025 Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Muzali+Arts+Ltd&title=Muzali+Arts+Ltd.+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+Dec+31%2C+2025+Financial+Results&newsId=90f756e6-2415-423f-a3fb-b7bd4877bd3e&token=OTBmNzU2ZTYtMjQx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90f756e6-2415-423f-a3fb-b7bd4877bd3e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Muzali Arts Ltd. has reported its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations, other income, total income, and expenses are stated in the Indian Accounting Standards (Ind AS) as per the Companies Act, 2013. The company is primarily engaged in one business segment. The financial results have been reviewed and recommended to the Board of Directors by the Audit Committee and subsequently approved by the Board. The company has not been able to present consolidated financial statements since June&apos; 21 due to the unavailability of subsidiary financial data. The company has determined that it does not possess significant control and power over its subsidiary, Jalan Jalan Collection Inc., and will account for the investment as per Ind AS 109 - Financial Instrument.</p><ul><li>Muzali Arts Ltd. reported its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue from operations, other income, total income, and expenses are reported in accordance with the Indian Accounting Standards (Ind AS) as per the Companies Act, 2013.</li><li>The company is primarily engaged in one business segment.</li><li>The financial results have been reviewed and approved by the Board of Directors.</li><li>The company has determined that it does not possess significant control and power over its subsidiary, Jalan Jalan Collection Inc., and will account for the investment as per Ind AS 109 - Financial Instrument.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e04146b6-c17a-4b2f-bdb4-d5fbc36a1953.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Muzali Arts Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NELCAST] Nelcast Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Unaudited Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NELCAST+LTD.&title=Nelcast+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=f71ccc64-52bf-4e9f-a5da-d8a7a94ac60e&token=ZjcxY2NjNjQtNTJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f71ccc64-52bf-4e9f-a5da-d8a7a94ac60e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:56:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Nelcast Ltd, an Iron Castings company, has reported its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 32,962.01 lakhs and 97,119.52 lakhs for the quarter and nine months ended respectively. The net profit for the quarter is 159,020 lakhs and 2,374.86 lakhs for the nine months. The company&apos;s subsidiary, NC Energy Limited, has not commenced its commercial operations yet.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter is 32,962.01 lakhs</li><li>Net profit for the quarter is 159,020 lakhs</li><li>Revenue from operations for the nine months is 97,119.52 lakhs</li><li>Net profit for the nine months is 2,374.86 lakhs</li><li>Company&apos;s subsidiary, NC Energy Limited, has not commenced its commercial operations yet</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/76c48331-bafb-4253-af51-7427eb17395d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NELCAST LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZJEETMAC] Jeet Machine Tools Ltd. Reports Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025, Net Profit Up by 11.29%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JEET+MACHINE+TOOLS+LTD.&title=Jeet+Machine+Tools+Ltd.+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Net+Profit+Up+by+11.29%25&newsId=03ed8cd9-954c-4aa4-a233-c24fa1dc4112&token=MDNlZDhjZDktOTU0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03ed8cd9-954c-4aa4-a233-c24fa1dc4112</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:55:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jeet Machine Tools Ltd. has reported its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s net profit for the nine-month period increased by 11.29% compared to the same period last year. The Board of Directors approved the unaudited financial results at its meeting on February 09, 2026. The revenue from operations stands at Rs. 3,68,824 lakhs for the nine-month period. The total income for the same period is Rs. 4,25,824 lakhs. The profit before tax for the nine-month period is Rs. 39,560 lakhs. The company&apos;s total comprehensive income for the period is Rs. 330,970 lakhs.</p><ul><li>Net profit increased by 11.29% compared to the same period last year.</li><li>Revenue from operations stands at Rs. 3,68,824 lakhs for the nine-month period.</li><li>Total income for the nine-month period is Rs. 4,25,824 lakhs.</li><li>Profit before tax for the nine-month period is Rs. 39,560 lakhs.</li><li>Total comprehensive income for the period is Rs. 330,970 lakhs.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9dfa3ae7-7bae-4226-8fa6-58d1137e002e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JEET MACHINE TOOLS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TTIENT] TTI Enterprise Ltd Receives Request for Reclassification from Promoter Group to Public Category</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TTI+Enterprise+Ltd&title=TTI+Enterprise+Ltd+Receives+Request+for+Reclassification+from+Promoter+Group+to+Public+Category&newsId=8c282022-4427-4d8e-93f1-cfda161b5812&token=OGMyODIwMjItNDQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c282022-4427-4d8e-93f1-cfda161b5812</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:55:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>TTI Enterprise Ltd has received requests for reclassification from the Promoter and Promoter Group category to the Public category under the provisions of the SEBI LODR Regulations, 2015. The requests were received from KALARIKKAL CHANDRASEKHARAN and BINDU KANAKAVALLY PRATHAPAN, who currently hold no shares in the company and do not intend to claim any rights in the company as promoters in the future. The reclassification is subject to the approval of the Board of Directors and the Stock Exchanges.</p><ul><li>TTI Enterprise Ltd received requests for reclassification from Promoter and Promoter Group to Public category</li><li>Requests received from KALARIKKAL CHANDRASEKHARAN and BINDU KANAKAVALLY PRATHAPAN</li><li>Neither KALARIKKAL CHANDRASEKHARAN nor BINDU KANAKAVALLY PRATHAPAN hold any shares in the company</li><li>Reclassification subject to approval of Board of Directors and Stock Exchanges</li><li>KALARIKKAL CHANDRASEKHARAN and BINDU KANAKAVALLY PRATHAPAN do not intend to claim any rights in the company as promoters</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a24679ca-bc55-4b5f-898c-e8d1a0581a89.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TTI Enterprise Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VISVEN] Vishvprabha Ventures Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Discuss Q3 and Nine Months Results of FY2025-2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vishvprabha+Ventures+Ltd&title=Vishvprabha+Ventures+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Discuss+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+of+FY2025-2026&newsId=decada5c-31c2-4d47-9553-d50b417ebf35&token=ZGVjYWRhNWMtMzFj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">decada5c-31c2-4d47-9553-d50b417ebf35</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vishvprabha Ventures Ltd, a company listed on the BSE, has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 14, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited Standalone &amp; Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended as on December 31, 2025. The meeting is being held in compliance with Regulation 29 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations 2015. The trading window for designated persons of the company will remain closed until 48 hours after the publication of the un-audited financial results.</p><ul><li>Vishvprabha Ventures Ltd to discuss Q3 and nine months results of FY2025-2026 in a Board meeting on February 14, 2026</li><li>The meeting is being held in compliance with Regulation 29 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations 2015</li><li>The unaudited Standalone &amp; Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended as on December 31, 2025, will be considered and approved</li><li>The trading window for designated persons of the company will remain closed until 48 hours after the publication of the un-audited financial results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b43055bf-ab84-4e3f-a321-42fc94f3a63e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vishvprabha Ventures Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WMINIMT] Western Ministil Ltd Approves Q3 Results, Appoints Two New Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=WESTERN+MINISTIL+LTD.&title=Western+Ministil+Ltd+Approves+Q3+Results%2C+Appoints+Two+New+Directors&newsId=e2ce2921-445b-4179-8aa4-292ec94d9008&token=ZTJjZTI5MjEtNDQ1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e2ce2921-445b-4179-8aa4-292ec94d9008</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:51:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Western Ministil Ltd, a company based in Mumbai, has approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended on 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s board of directors also approved the appointment of Mr. Kalpesh Naginbhai Patel and Mrs. Vandana Kalpesh Patel as additional directors. The company&apos;s financial results indicate a understated loss due to non-provision of interest on borrowing from a related party and a material uncertainty casting significant doubt on the company’s ability to continue as a going concern.</p><ul><li>Western Ministil Ltd approved the unaudited financial results for Q3 2025</li><li>The company&apos;s board approved the appointment of two new directors</li><li>Non-provision of interest on borrowing from a related party led to understated loss</li><li>Material uncertainty exists casting significant doubt on the company’s ability to continue as a going concern</li><li>The company is exploring revival of its business and other fresh business opportunities</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b84bb9c6-31e6-44e9-9915-7fe0da7b6302.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: WESTERN MINISTIL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UNIPARTS] Uniparts India Ltd Declares Second Interim Dividend of Rs. 7 per Share for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Uniparts+India+Ltd&title=Uniparts+India+Ltd+Declares+Second+Interim+Dividend+of+Rs.+7+per+Share+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=5646fa96-8d62-46bd-bed9-06434b372844&token=NTY0NmZhOTYtOGQ2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5646fa96-8d62-46bd-bed9-06434b372844</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Uniparts India Ltd has declared a second interim dividend of Rs. 7 per equity share for the Financial Year 2025-26. The record date for determining the shareholders who will be entitled to the interim dividend is February 16, 2026. The dividend will be paid within 30 days from the date of declaration.</p><ul><li>Uniparts India Ltd has declared a second interim dividend of Rs. 7 per equity share for the Financial Year 2025-26.</li><li>The record date for determining the shareholders who will be entitled to the interim dividend is February 16, 2026.</li><li>The dividend will be paid within 30 days from the date of declaration.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4ba87615-3d16-42f3-87f0-f4b2edd0854d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Uniparts India Ltd | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PNCINFRA] PNC Infratech Pays Fine for Delayed RPT Disclosure Submission</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PNC+Infratech+Ltd&title=PNC+Infratech+Pays+Fine+for+Delayed+RPT+Disclosure+Submission&newsId=a7f2da93-1a07-4ac6-8074-284b4896f144&token=YTdmMmRhOTMtMWEw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a7f2da93-1a07-4ac6-8074-284b4896f144</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:50:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>PNC Infratech Ltd. has paid a fine of Rs. 35,400 including GST to BSE for delaying the submission of Related Party Transactions (RPT) disclosure under Integrated Financials for the half year ended September 30, 2025. The delay in submission led to a fine as per SEBI Master Circular No. SEBI/HO/CFD/PoD2/CIR/P/0155 dated 11th November 2024. The Board has advised to be more cautious and ensure timely compliance in the future.</p><ul><li>PNC Infratech Ltd. pays fine of Rs. 35,400 to BSE for delaying RPT disclosure submission.</li><li>The delay in submission was due to non-compliance with Regulation 23(9) of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</li><li>The Company has paid the fine within 15 days of the BSE email and there are no outstanding dues.</li><li>The Board has advised to be more cautious and ensure timely compliance in the future.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0bdf5132-41cf-40d9-a843-205ea9171724.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PNC Infratech Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KOHINOOR] Kohinoor Foods Ltd. Settles OTS Amount of Rs. 227.45 Cr., Requests Release of Securities</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KOHINOOR+FOODS+LTD.&title=Kohinoor+Foods+Ltd.+Settles+OTS+Amount+of+Rs.+227.45+Cr.%2C+Requests+Release+of+Securities&newsId=b71538d3-1440-4ffa-b9f4-9dfcfd2344e1&token=YjcxNTM4ZDMtMTQ0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b71538d3-1440-4ffa-b9f4-9dfcfd2344e1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 12:47:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kohinoor Foods Ltd. has paid the entire Out of Court Settlement (OTS) amount of Rs. 227.45 Cr. plus delayed period interest @ MCLR (1 Yr)+2% w.e.f. 01.10.24 to the consortium lenders. The company has requested the lenders to release all securities charged to the Bank and issue No Dues / No Objection Certificates (NOCs) in its favor. This disclosure is in continuation to the company&apos;s previous letters dated December 23, 2024, February 14, 2025, March 31, 2025, and April 22, 2025.</p><ul><li>Kohinoor Foods Ltd. settles OTS amount of Rs. 227.45 Cr. plus interest</li><li>Company requests release of all securities charged to the Bank</li><li>Request for No Dues / No Objection Certificates (NOCs) in favor of the Company</li><li>Disclosure is in continuation to the company&apos;s previous letters from 2024 to 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3ab49231-f499-476f-b6d6-134088a489bc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KOHINOOR FOODS LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>