<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 01:52:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ACCEL] Accel Ltd. Approves Standalone and Consolidated Unaudited Financial Results for Q4 2025, Announces Progress of Accel Infinium 1 &amp; 2 Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Accel+Ltd&title=Accel+Ltd.+Approves+Standalone+and+Consolidated+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q4+2025%2C+Announces+Progress+of+Accel+Infinium+1+%26+2+Projects&newsId=2c5d08c5-3676-4d34-a998-b538f2d21eec&token=MmM1ZDA4YzUtMzY3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2c5d08c5-3676-4d34-a998-b538f2d21eec</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Accel Ltd. announced the approval of its standalone and consolidated unaudited financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s Board of Directors took note of the significant progress in the leasing operations of Accel Infinium 1 and authorized the implementation of the Accel Infinium 2 project. The Accel Infinium 2 project will have a capacity of approximately 500,000 sq. ft. of premium IT space and is expected to be completed by July 2028. This expansion is part of the company&apos;s strategic initiative to strengthen its Realty division.</p><ul><li>Approval of standalone and consolidated unaudited financial results for Q4 2025</li><li>Significant progress in the leasing operations of Accel Infinium 1</li><li>Authorization of Accel Infinium 2 project with a capacity of approximately 500,000 sq. ft. of premium IT space</li><li>Targeted completion of Accel Infinium 2 by July 2028</li><li>Expansion to strengthen the Realty division</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5e70bfb3-ce9d-4878-84b8-85e98fda9690.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Accel Ltd | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NIITMTS] NIIT MTS and St. Charles Consulting Group Announce 2026 Global Learning Transformation Benchmark Survey Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NIIT+Learning+Systems+Ltd&title=NIIT+MTS+and+St.+Charles+Consulting+Group+Announce+2026+Global+Learning+Transformation+Benchmark+Survey+Results&newsId=382a3b9e-361e-452d-a302-c760e650df6e&token=MzgyYTNiOWUtMzYx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">382a3b9e-361e-452d-a302-c760e650df6e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>NIIT MTS and St. Charles Consulting Group have released the 2026 Global Learning Transformation Benchmark Survey. The survey, which draws on insights from Chief Learning Officers, Talent, and HR leaders across Global 500 industries and regions, offers one of the most detailed views to date of how organizations are modernizing L&amp;D, deploying artificial intelligence, and preparing for a skills-based future. The research highlights the challenges and opportunities in aligning learning and development with the rapid rise of AI-enabled learning.</p><ul><li>NIIT MTS and St. Charles Consulting Group announce the 2026 Global Learning Transformation Benchmark Survey results</li><li>The survey reveals accelerating ambition and persistent readiness gaps in learning as AI reshapes work</li><li>The research is designed for leaders building a future-ready workforce amid the rapid rise of AI-enabled learning</li><li>The study evaluates maturity, progress, and challenges across five essential areas, including skills &amp; talent architecture, AI-enabled learning readiness, priority-execution alignment, learning-business credibility, and operating model evolution</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/03e49c15-a950-4f38-89f2-309b628ff210.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NIIT Learning Systems Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IIFL] IIFL Finance Ltd. Approves 2,000 Crores NCD Issue with 100% Security Cover</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IIFL+Finance+Ltd&title=IIFL+Finance+Ltd.+Approves+2%2C000+Crores+NCD+Issue+with+100%25+Security+Cover&newsId=8147bdf3-d08a-4c41-a42c-0e2537d41c31&token=ODE0N2JkZjMtZDA4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8147bdf3-d08a-4c41-a42c-0e2537d41c31</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:01:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>On February 12, 2026, IIFL Finance Ltd.&apos;s Finance Committee approved the issue of secured, rated, listed, redeemable, non-convertible debentures (NCDs) worth up to 2,000 crores. The NCDs, with a base issue size of 500 crores and an oversubscription limit of up to 31,500 crores, will be issued in tranches under the shelf limit of 32,000 crores. The NCDs will be secured by a first-ranking charge over the company&apos;s receivables, book debts, loans, advances, and current assets, maintaining a 100% security cover. The company will pay interest over the agreed coupon rate in case of delays in allotment, refunds, listing, dematerialized credit, execution of Debenture Trust Deed, payment of interest, and redemption of principal amount beyond the time limits prescribed under applicable statutory and/or regulatory requirements.</p><ul><li>IIFL Finance Ltd. approved a public issue of secured, rated, listed, redeemable, non-convertible debentures (NCDs) worth up to 2,000 crores.</li><li>The NCDs will be issued in tranches under the shelf limit of 32,000 crores, with a base issue size of 500 crores and an oversubscription limit of up to 31,500 crores.</li><li>The NCDs will be secured by a first-ranking charge over the company&apos;s receivables, book debts, loans, advances, and current assets, maintaining a 100% security cover.</li><li>The company will pay interest over the agreed coupon rate in case of delays in allotment, refunds, listing, dematerialized credit, execution of Debenture Trust Deed, payment of interest, and redemption of principal amount beyond the time limits prescribed under applicable statutory and/or regulatory requirements.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/729aa144-3736-4cd4-9210-2781ab4809b7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IIFL Finance Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RTFL] Real Touch Finance Ltd. Approves Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended Dec 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Real+Touch+Finance+Ltd&title=Real+Touch+Finance+Ltd.+Approves+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+Dec+2025&newsId=6cf0da93-6339-4e29-8a8e-d5dac0287959&token=NmNmMGRhOTMtNjMz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6cf0da93-6339-4e29-8a8e-d5dac0287959</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:55:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Real Touch Finance Ltd. has approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The meeting was held on 12th February 2026 and the results were approved after the recommendation of the Audit Committee. The company has prepared the financial results in accordance with Indian Accounting Standard 34 and other applicable accounting principles.</p><ul><li>Unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended Dec 2025 approved</li><li>Reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors</li><li>Prepared in accordance with Indian Accounting Standard 34 and other applicable accounting principles</li><li>Limited review conducted by the statutory auditors of the Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e48602a4-564f-4862-92a3-3a3c1b98382c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Real Touch Finance Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LICI] LIC Reports 16.68% YoY Growth in Profit After Tax for 9MFY26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Life+Insurance+Corporation+of+India&title=LIC+Reports+16.68%25+YoY+Growth+in+Profit+After+Tax+for+9MFY26&newsId=016bf601-dc70-4dbb-b96e-0da7bddcebe9&token=MDE2YmY2MDEtZGM3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">016bf601-dc70-4dbb-b96e-0da7bddcebe9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC) reported a 16.68% year-on-year growth in Profit After Tax (PAT) for the nine months ended December 31st, 2025. The total premium income increased by 9.02% YoY to Rs. 3,71,293 Crore. The individual new business premium income grew by 5.89% YoY to Rs. 44,941 Crore. The renewal premium income for individual business increased by 6.75% YoY to Rs. 1,91,050 Crore. The total individual premium income, including renewals, grew by 6.58% YoY to Rs. 2,35,991 Crore. The total group premium increased by 13.56% YoY to Rs. 1,35,302 Crore. The profit after tax was Rs. 33,998 Crore as compared to Rs. 29,138 Crore for the same period last year. The net VNB grew by 27.96% YoY to Rs. 8,288 Crore.</p><ul><li>16.68% YoY growth in Profit After Tax for 9MFY26</li><li>9.02% YoY increase in total premium income</li><li>5.89% YoY growth in individual new business premium income</li><li>6.75% YoY increase in renewal premium income for individual business</li><li>27.96% YoY growth in net VNB</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/315382f7-76e8-42ba-b8bb-a6546f54c273.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Life Insurance Corporation of India | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PRIMAIN] Prima Industries Ltd. Announces Q3 2025 Financial Results, Including Redemption of Preference Shares and New Allotment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PRIMA+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Prima+Industries+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+2025+Financial+Results%2C+Including+Redemption+of+Preference+Shares+and+New+Allotment&newsId=ac88bfb3-0cdb-4cff-b67d-74bad8a33150&token=YWM4OGJmYjMtMGNk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac88bfb3-0cdb-4cff-b67d-74bad8a33150</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:50:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Prima Industries Ltd. has announced its un-audited financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 1712 million, 1776 million, and 2073 million for the quarter, nine months, and year ended 31st December 2025 respectively. The company has also announced the redemption of 10% Non-Convertible Redeemable Preference Shares (Unlisted) and its further issue as per Section 55(3) of Companies, Act 2013. The Board has approved the allotment of 51,97,403 preference shares to Ayyappa Roller Flour Mills Limited.</p><ul><li>Prima Industries Ltd. announces Q3 2025 financial results</li><li>Revenue from operations stands at 1712 million, 1776 million, and 2073 million for the quarter, nine months, and year ended 31st December 2025 respectively</li><li>Company announces redemption of 10% Non-Convertible Redeemable Preference Shares (Unlisted)</li><li>Further issue of preference shares approved by the Board</li><li>51,97,403 preference shares allotted to Ayyappa Roller Flour Mills Limited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/90f0d118-a0ed-4c10-b7e3-d810542af775.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PRIMA INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AJCON] Ajcon Global Services Ltd Approves Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 &amp; Nine Months Ended 31.12.2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AJCON+GLOBAL+SERVICES+LTD.&title=Ajcon+Global+Services+Ltd+Approves+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Ended+31.12.2025&newsId=21269dcd-b44d-4719-8d3b-6b5b25b376a7&token=MjEyNjlkY2QtYjQ0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21269dcd-b44d-4719-8d3b-6b5b25b376a7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:49:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ajcon Global Services Ltd has approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31.12.2025 in its board meeting. The meeting was conducted on 12.02.2026 from 02:30 P.M. to 04:15 P.M. (IST). The trading window for dealings in security will remain closed for 48 hours from the declaration of results. The company&apos;s statutory auditors, Bhatter &amp; Company, have issued a limited review report on the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results.</p><ul><li>Ajcon Global Services Ltd has approved the unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31.12.2025.</li><li>The trading window for dealings in security will remain closed for 48 hours from the declaration of results.</li><li>Bhatter &amp; Company has issued a limited review report on the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b16ace52-bfe7-443d-8aa4-ed90518a2ca6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AJCON GLOBAL SERVICES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RASRESOR] Ras Resorts &amp; Apart Hotels Ltd Reports Q3 FY2025-26 Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RAS+RESORTS+%26+APART+HOTELS+LTD.&title=Ras+Resorts+%26+Apart+Hotels+Ltd+Reports+Q3+FY2025-26+Financial+Results&newsId=3bcdeb4b-eb3d-41f8-bc18-6990d2466cfd&token=M2JjZGViNGItZWIz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3bcdeb4b-eb3d-41f8-bc18-6990d2466cfd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ras Resorts &amp; Apart Hotels Ltd has reported its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The total revenue stands at Rs. 1,322.71 lakhs, with a net profit of Rs. 396.97 lakhs. The company is in the process of evaluating the full impact of the new labour codes announced by the Government of India.</p><ul><li>Total revenue for the quarter is Rs. 1,322.71 lakhs.</li><li>Net profit for the quarter is Rs. 396.97 lakhs.</li><li>The company is evaluating the impact of new labour codes announced by the Government of India.</li><li>The financial results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/87ab340c-711d-4cac-9788-591b444cbc2d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RAS RESORTS & APART HOTELS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ARUNIS] Arunis Abode Ltd. Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025, Changes Joint Statutory Auditors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Arunis+Abode+Ltd&title=Arunis+Abode+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Changes+Joint+Statutory+Auditors&newsId=7da83422-1913-410a-8174-f873536d9565&token=N2RhODM0MjItMTkx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7da83422-1913-410a-8174-f873536d9565</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:48:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Arunis Abode Ltd., now known as Kalind Limited, announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The company&apos;s board approved the results and the limited review report from the statutory auditors. The board also considered and approved the resignation of M/s. Mishra Karwa &amp; Co., Chartered Accountants as the Joint Statutory Auditors. The trading window will remain closed till the end of 48 hours from the conclusion of the board meeting or the results being made public.</p><ul><li>Approval of unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December, 2025</li><li>Resignation of M/s. Mishra Karwa &amp; Co., Chartered Accountants as Joint Statutory Auditors</li><li>Trading window to remain closed till the end of 48 hours from conclusion of board meeting or results being made public</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1e5d5196-2a2d-4d87-abb7-00d1b5e26b16.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Arunis Abode Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DIGISPICE] Digispice Technologies Ltd. Reports Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Digispice+Technologies+Ltd-%24&title=Digispice+Technologies+Ltd.+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=162ae7ef-a53c-42dc-9197-dff3a49bfa92&token=MTYyYWU3ZWYtYTUz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">162ae7ef-a53c-42dc-9197-dff3a49bfa92</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 21:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Digispice Technologies Ltd. has released its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The results were approved by the Board of Directors and the Audit Committee in a meeting on February 12, 2026. The company reported a profit after tax of (281.23) crores for the nine months ended December 31, 2025, and a total comprehensive income for the period/year of (283.28) crores.</p><ul><li>Profit after tax for the nine months ended December 31, 2025: (281.23) crores</li><li>Total comprehensive income for the period/year: (283.28) crores</li><li>Reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors</li><li>Prepared in accordance with India Accounting Standards</li><li>Discontinuation of Digital Technology Services Business</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8d61c76b-22a7-46be-b006-f66ac20a6b57.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Digispice Technologies Ltd-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>