<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 15:16:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SPICEISL] Spice Islands Industries Ltd. Receives First Export Order from UAE Worth INR 13.8 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SPICE+ISLANDS+APPARELS+LTD.-%24&title=Spice+Islands+Industries+Ltd.+Receives+First+Export+Order+from+UAE+Worth+INR+13.8+Million&newsId=4b948b87-9115-4847-8a54-0bf930bc87fd&token=NGI5NDhiODctOTEx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4b948b87-9115-4847-8a54-0bf930bc87fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Spice Islands Industries Ltd. has announced its first international purchase order from Emazing Deals, UAE, for the supply of perfumes, amounting to USD 166,136 (INR 13.8 million). The company will execute this order by placing a corresponding purchase order with Sterling Perfumes Industries LLC, UAE, the owner of the globally recognized fragrance brand ARMAF. This strategic milestone marks the beginning of the company&apos;s Global Trade vertical, focusing on fragrances, personal care, and lifestyle products. The management believes this order reflects international confidence in their execution capabilities and signals their intent to expand into global markets, particularly across the Middle East and other high-growth regions.</p><ul><li>Spice Islands Industries Ltd. receives first international purchase order from Emazing Deals, UAE, worth INR 13.8 million.</li><li>The order will be executed by placing a corresponding purchase order with Sterling Perfumes Industries LLC, UAE, the owner of the ARMAF brand.</li><li>This strategic milestone marks the beginning of the company&apos;s Global Trade vertical.</li><li>The focus is on fragrances, personal care, and lifestyle products.</li><li>The management sees this order as a reflection of international confidence in their execution capabilities and an intent to expand into global markets.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2ea73fcf-3d9c-4c57-ae7f-a2fbeb17f2f4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SPICE ISLANDS APPARELS LTD.-$ | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CUPIDALBV] Cupid Breweries And Distilleries Ltd to Approve Q2 and Q3 Financial Results on January 29, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Cupid+Breweries+And+Distilleries+Ltd&title=Cupid+Breweries+And+Distilleries+Ltd+to+Approve+Q2+and+Q3+Financial+Results+on+January+29%2C+2026&newsId=d30c63fe-47d8-4f7a-adaf-264152330114&token=ZDMwYzYzZmUtNDdk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d30c63fe-47d8-4f7a-adaf-264152330114</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:01:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cupid Breweries And Distilleries Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 29, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and half year ended September 30, 2025, along with the Limited Review Report of the Auditor. The Board will also consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, along with the Limited Review Report of the Auditor. The information will be made available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Cupid Breweries And Distilleries Ltd to consider and approve Q2 and Q3 financial results for the year 2025</li><li>The meeting is scheduled for January 29, 2026</li><li>The results will be accompanied by the Limited Review Report of the Auditor</li><li>The information will be made available on the company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5d8a0d4b-3ecc-4242-837c-a403b97f3d52.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Cupid Breweries And Distilleries Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VINYOFL] Vinyoflex Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q4 Results of 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VINYOFLEX+LTD.&title=Vinyoflex+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q4+Results+of+2025&newsId=21d57361-cd6d-46b1-ba7e-66fdd7417851&token=MjFkNTczNjEtY2Q2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21d57361-cd6d-46b1-ba7e-66fdd7417851</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vinyoflex Ltd has announced a Board of Directors meeting on February 09, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The meeting is in accordance with Regulation 29 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The trading window for dealing in securities of the Company will be closed for the Designated Persons from January 01, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of the Unaudited Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Vinyoflex Ltd scheduled a Board of Directors meeting on February 09, 2026, to approve Q4 results of 2025.</li><li>The meeting is in accordance with Regulation 29 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li><li>The trading window for dealing in securities of the Company will be closed for the Designated Persons from January 01, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of the Unaudited Financial Results.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bb8812d0-a24a-44aa-b62a-95b8c6fb6e99.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VINYOFLEX LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GARGI] PNGS Gargi Fashion Jewellery Ltd Opens New Exclusive Brand Store</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PNGS+Gargi+Fashion+Jewellery+Ltd&title=PNGS+Gargi+Fashion+Jewellery+Ltd+Opens+New+Exclusive+Brand+Store&newsId=f0299696-70e1-4b12-97d6-a9aa2073e719&token=ZjAyOTk2OTYtNzBl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0299696-70e1-4b12-97d6-a9aa2073e719</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>PNGS Gargi Fashion Jewellery Ltd has announced the opening of its new exclusive brand store at Unit No 4, B Wing, Ground Floor of Nyati Plaza of Project Nyati Enthral, S. No 12, Hissa No 1A, Kharadi, Pune, Maharashtra -411014. This announcement was made on January 25, 2026, in accordance with Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirement) Rules, 2015.</p><ul><li>PNGS Gargi Fashion Jewellery Ltd has opened a new exclusive brand store</li><li>The store is located at Unit No 4, B Wing, Ground Floor of Nyati Plaza of Project Nyati Enthral, S. No 12, Hissa No 1A, Kharadi, Pune, Maharashtra -411014</li><li>The opening was announced on January 25, 2026</li><li>The announcement was made in accordance with Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirement) Rules, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2124e3f4-e437-4aa3-96e9-fbd1eae366d2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PNGS Gargi Fashion Jewellery Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EVERESTIND] Everest Industries Extends Land Sale Timeline to March 31, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=EVEREST+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Everest+Industries+Extends+Land+Sale+Timeline+to+March+31%2C+2026&newsId=299e7150-622c-4e0e-953d-130beb3f2647&token=Mjk5ZTcxNTAtNjIy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">299e7150-622c-4e0e-953d-130beb3f2647</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Everest Industries Ltd. has announced an extension of the timeline for the sale of its land at Podanur. The sale, which was earlier estimated to be concluded on the day of the announcement, has been extended till March 31, 2026. This extension is due to the progress of needed government approvals and has been mutually agreed upon by the Company and G Square Realtors Private Limited. This intimation is given pursuant to Regulation 30 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Everest Industries extends the timeline for land sale at Podanur till March 31, 2026</li><li>The extension is due to the progress of needed government approvals</li><li>The decision has been mutually agreed upon by the Company and G Square Realtors Private Limited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/656f5fed-79a3-4432-a2e3-4c1d1c5f88e6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: EVEREST INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AADHARHFC] Blackstone-led Consortium to Acquire 25.82% Stake in Aadhar Housing Finance for $5.3 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Aadhar+Housing+Finance+Ltd&title=Blackstone-led+Consortium+to+Acquire+25.82%25+Stake+in+Aadhar+Housing+Finance+for+%245.3+Billion&newsId=15df204e-2fbf-4605-ac99-e28ffb672335&token=MTVkZjIwNGUtMmZi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">15df204e-2fbf-4605-ac99-e28ffb672335</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>A consortium led by BCP Asia IT Holdco VII PTE. LTD., a private limited company incorporated under the laws of Singapore, and including Blackstone Capital Partners (CYM) IX AIV-F L.P. and Blackstone Capital Partners Asia ITL.P., both exempted limited partnerships registered under the laws of Cayman Islands, has made a cash offer to acquire up to 11,35,25,761 fully paid-up equity shares of face value of INR 10 each of Aadhar Housing Finance Limited, representing 25.82% of the expanded voting share capital of the company. The offer price is INR 469.97 per equity share along with the applicable interest of INR 2.71 per equity share. The offer is not a conditional offer and is not subject to any minimum level of acceptance. It is also not a competing offer. The offer is being made in compliance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011 and subsequent amendments thereto. The offer is not subject to any statutory or regulatory approvals other than as set out in Part C (Statutory and Other Approvals) of Section VIII (Terms and Conditions of the Open Offer) which have now been received.</p><ul><li>Blackstone-led consortium to acquire 25.82% stake in Aadhar Housing Finance</li><li>Offer price is INR 469.97 per equity share along with INR 2.71 interest</li><li>Not a conditional or competing offer</li><li>Compliant with Securities and Exchange Board of India regulations</li><li>Subject to certain statutory and regulatory approvals</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ca488181-d7b3-4bdd-93ac-92cc15bf4162.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PWASML] Prakash Woollen &amp; Synthetic Mills Ltd to Approve Un-Audited Financial Results on Feb 4, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Prakash+Woollen+%26+Synthetic+Mills+Ltd&title=Prakash+Woollen+%26+Synthetic+Mills+Ltd+to+Approve+Un-Audited+Financial+Results+on+Feb+4%2C+2026&newsId=42a76f0b-bc73-4f4f-969b-969ebafbbb77&token=NDJhNzZmMGItYmM3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42a76f0b-bc73-4f4f-969b-969ebafbbb77</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 10:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Prakash Woollen &amp; Synthetic Mills Ltd has announced a Board Meeting on February 4, 2026, to consider and approve the Un-Audited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in securities of the company, which was closed on January 1, 2026, will open after 48 hours after the declaration of the Un-Audited Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Prakash Woollen &amp; Synthetic Mills Ltd to hold a Board Meeting on February 4, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the Un-Audited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities of the company was closed on January 1, 2026, and will open after 48 hours after the declaration of the Un-Audited Financial Results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4e4971f3-202e-4b24-9539-5c3e8491f88c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Prakash Woollen & Synthetic Mills Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UCOBANK] UCO Bank Branches and Offices May Be Affected by UFBU Strike on 27.01.2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=UCO+BANK&title=UCO+Bank+Branches+and+Offices+May+Be+Affected+by+UFBU+Strike+on+27.01.2026&newsId=6bd92fb9-f15e-4b0b-a2dc-95ca025f38d6&token=NmJkOTJmYjktZjE1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6bd92fb9-f15e-4b0b-a2dc-95ca025f38d6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 10:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Strike</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>UCO Bank has been informed by the Indian Banks’ Association (IBA) that the United Forum of Bank Unions (UFBU) and the All India Bank Officer&apos;s Association (AIBOA) have issued a strike notice for 27th January, 2026, to support their demands. Although the bank is taking measures to ensure smooth functioning of its branches and offices on the day of the strike, should the strike take place, the operations of these branches and offices may be impacted. This information is being shared in compliance with Regulation 30 of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>UFBU and AIBOA have issued a strike notice for 27th January, 2026</li><li>The strike is to support their demands</li><li>UCO Bank is taking steps for smooth functioning on the day of the strike</li><li>Potential impact on UCO Bank branches and offices if the strike materializes</li><li>Disclosure in compliance with Regulation 30 of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/de3e24eb-c4bf-46be-acad-19ee902e4616.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: UCO BANK | Category: Strike</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AVANTEL] Avantel Ltd. Approves Un-audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AVANTEL+LTD.&title=Avantel+Ltd.+Approves+Un-audited+Standalone+and+Consolidated+Financial+Results+for+Q3+2025&newsId=a7204990-8e70-4da9-8805-dc9860cdcfa7&token=YTcyMDQ5OTAtOGU3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a7204990-8e70-4da9-8805-dc9860cdcfa7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:02:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Avantel Ltd. approved the Un-audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the Third Quarter ended December 31, 2025. The results were reviewed by the Audit Committee and the Statutory Auditors. The company operates in a single segment and the results pertain to this segment. The financial results are available on the company&apos;s website and on the BSE and NSE websites.</p><ul><li>Avantel Ltd. approved the Un-audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 2025.</li><li>The results were reviewed by the Audit Committee and the Statutory Auditors.</li><li>The company operates in a single segment.</li><li>The financial results are available on the company&apos;s website and on the BSE and NSE websites.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/74cf51f8-a41b-4b43-8769-c4b33c7d52c7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AVANTEL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AVANTEL] Avantel Ltd. Announces Un-Audited Financial Results for Q3 2025, Revenue Up by 41.32%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AVANTEL+LTD.&title=Avantel+Ltd.+Announces+Un-Audited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+2025%2C+Revenue+Up+by+41.32%25&newsId=c14ef7da-2ce7-4eda-a7b2-2ba6d50bc7ae&token=YzE0ZWY3ZGEtMmNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c14ef7da-2ce7-4eda-a7b2-2ba6d50bc7ae</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Avantel Ltd. has announced its un-audited financial results for the third quarter ended December 31, 2025. The Board of Directors approved the un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results. The total revenue from operations has increased by 41.32% compared to the same period last year. The company operates in a single segment and the results pertain to this segment. The financial results are available on the company&apos;s website and the websites of BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange of India Limited.</p><ul><li>Un-Audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results approved for Q3 2025</li><li>Total Revenue from Operations increased by 41.32% compared to Q3 2024</li><li>Company operates in a single segment</li><li>Financial results available on company&apos;s website and stock exchange websites</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6413e3de-a3fe-4ab2-a8c3-82081168b874.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AVANTEL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>