<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 15:16:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ORIENTTR] Orient Tradelink Ltd Allots 1,83,998 Equity Shares at INR 22 Each, Increasing Paid-up Equity Share Capital</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ORIENT+TRADELINK+LTD.&title=Orient+Tradelink+Ltd+Allots+1%2C83%2C998+Equity+Shares+at+INR+22+Each%2C+Increasing+Paid-up+Equity+Share+Capital&newsId=658a1bb3-f683-4676-a61c-e685e79bba58&token=NjU4YTFiYjMtZjY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">658a1bb3-f683-4676-a61c-e685e79bba58</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 14:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Orient Tradelink Ltd has allotted 1,83,998 equity shares of INR 10 each at a price of INR 22 per share, comprising of a premium of INR 12 per share. This allotment was made in accordance with the provisions of Chapter V of the SEBI (Issue of Capital and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2018. The allottees include both promoters and non-promoters. This allotment has increased the company&apos;s paid-up equity share capital from INR 35,76,79,060 to INR 35,95,19,040.</p><ul><li>Orient Tradelink Ltd has allotted 1,83,998 equity shares at INR 22 each, comprising of a premium of INR 12 per share.</li><li>The allotment was made in accordance with the provisions of Chapter V of the SEBI (Issue of Capital and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2018.</li><li>The allottees include both promoters and non-promoters.</li><li>This allotment has increased the company&apos;s paid-up equity share capital from INR 35,76,79,060 to INR 35,95,19,040.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a36419b7-3a52-46ae-83dc-546f03a825e8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ORIENT TRADELINK LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ORIENTTR] Orient Tradelink Ltd Allots 1,83,998 Equity Shares at INR 22 Each, Increasing Paid-up Equity Share Capital</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ORIENT+TRADELINK+LTD.&title=Orient+Tradelink+Ltd+Allots+1%2C83%2C998+Equity+Shares+at+INR+22+Each%2C+Increasing+Paid-up+Equity+Share+Capital&newsId=766b43ca-245f-4621-994a-01ee58bdd240&token=NzY2YjQzY2EtMjQ1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">766b43ca-245f-4621-994a-01ee58bdd240</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 14:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Orient Tradelink Ltd has allotted 1,83,998 equity shares of INR 10 each at a price of INR 22 per share, comprising of a premium of INR 12 per share. This allotment was made in accordance with the provisions of Chapter V of the SEBI (Issue of Capital and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2018. The allottees include both promoters and non-promoters. This allotment has increased the company&apos;s paid-up equity share capital from INR 35,76,79,060 to INR 35,95,19,040.</p><ul><li>Orient Tradelink Ltd has allotted 1,83,998 equity shares at INR 22 each, comprising of a premium of INR 12 per share.</li><li>The allotment was made in accordance with the provisions of Chapter V of the SEBI (Issue of Capital and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2018.</li><li>The allottees include both promoters and non-promoters.</li><li>This allotment has increased the company&apos;s paid-up equity share capital from INR 35,76,79,060 to INR 35,95,19,040.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b07b6b4a-6383-4a70-88d6-45a3fdaf23a8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ORIENT TRADELINK LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SIGNATURE] Signatureglobal (India) Ltd Reports Q3 FY26 Key Operational Updates with Moderated Pre-Sales and Improved Collections</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Signatureglobal+%28India%29+Ltd&title=Signatureglobal+%28India%29+Ltd+Reports+Q3+FY26+Key+Operational+Updates+with+Moderated+Pre-Sales+and+Improved+Collections&newsId=306656d7-955f-4835-af25-40eb94221e67&token=MzA2NjU2ZDctOTU1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">306656d7-955f-4835-af25-40eb94221e67</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 13:31:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Signatureglobal (India) Ltd has released its key operational updates for Q3 FY26. The company achieved pre-sales of INR 20.2 bn in Q3 FY26, lower than the previous year&apos;s Q3 and 9MFY26 figures due to a softer market environment. However, sales realization increased to INR 15,182 per sq. ft. in 9MFY26 from INR 12,457 per sq. ft. in FY25. Collections improved to INR 12.3 bn in Q3 FY26 and INR 30.9 bn in 9MFY26. Net debt stands at INR 10.2 bn at the end of 9MFY26. The balance sheet remains healthy, and good collections are expected to help the company get back on the growth path soon.</p><ul><li>Pre-sales for Q3 FY26 stand at INR 20.2 bn, a decrease from the previous year&apos;s Q3 and 9MFY26 figures.</li><li>Sales realization increased to INR 15,182 per sq. ft. in 9MFY26 compared to INR 12,457 per sq. ft. in FY25.</li><li>Collections improved to INR 12.3 bn in Q3 FY26 and INR 30.9 bn in 9MFY26.</li><li>Net debt stands at INR 10.2 bn at the end of 9MFY26.</li><li>The company&apos;s balance sheet remains healthy, and good collections are expected to support growth in the near future.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/52c0466d-2113-44a6-858d-c4a7d91239d9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Signatureglobal (India) Ltd | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHKARTP] Shree Karthik Papers Ltd: Promoters Confirm No Encumbrance on Shares as of Dec 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHREE+KARTHIK+PAPERS+LTD.&title=Shree+Karthik+Papers+Ltd%3A+Promoters+Confirm+No+Encumbrance+on+Shares+as+of+Dec+31%2C+2025&newsId=4d53023e-c563-4690-bef1-d4c4f8b905a2&token=NGQ1MzAyM2UtYzU2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d53023e-c563-4690-bef1-d4c4f8b905a2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 13:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shree Karthik Papers Ltd has filed a statement under regulation 30 of Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations 2011 as on 31/12/2025. The promoters, holding 1,42,41,700 equity shares (74.52%), have confirmed that they have not made any encumbrance, directly or indirectly, on the shares held by them in the company during the quarter ended 31/12/2025. Furthermore, as of December 31, 2025, no shares of the company are encumbered or pledged by the promoters.</p><ul><li>Shree Karthik Papers Ltd files statement under regulation 30 of Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations 2011</li><li>Promoters confirm no encumbrance on shares as of Dec 31, 2025</li><li>Promoters hold 1,42,41,700 equity shares (74.52%)</li><li>No shares encumbered or pledged as of Dec 31, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/eb12ff01-2a58-4c01-99ef-270df58f71f2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHREE KARTHIK PAPERS LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MEDPLUS] Medplus Health Services Subsidiary Faces Two-Day Drug License Suspension in Karnataka</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Medplus+Health+Services+Ltd&title=Medplus+Health+Services+Subsidiary+Faces+Two-Day+Drug+License+Suspension+in+Karnataka&newsId=f58e376f-ea4a-40f2-a18f-43ac77459bf8&token=ZjU4ZTM3NmYtZWE0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f58e376f-ea4a-40f2-a18f-43ac77459bf8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 13:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Medplus Health Services Ltd. has announced that its subsidiary, Optival Health Solutions Private Limited, has received a suspension order for a Drug License of a store situated in the state of Karnataka. The suspension is under Rule 65 of the Drugs and Cosmetics Act, 1940 and Drugs and Cosmetics Rules, 1945. The order was received on 10.01.2026 and will result in a potential revenue loss of approximately Rs~0.74 lacs for the two-day period. The order was passed by the Assistant Director, Drugs Control Administration, Madikeri Circle, Madikeri, Karnataka, and Virajpet, Karnataka. The details of the matter are available on the company&apos;s website, as well as on the websites of BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange of India Ltd.</p><ul><li>Medplus Health Services&apos; subsidiary, Optival Health Solutions Private Limited, has received a suspension order for a Drug License.</li><li>The suspension is for a store situated in Karnataka and is under Rule 65 of the Drugs and Cosmetics Act, 1940 and Drugs and Cosmetics Rules, 1945.</li><li>The suspension will result in a potential revenue loss of approximately Rs~0.74 lacs for the two-day period.</li><li>The order was passed by the Assistant Director, Drugs Control Administration, Madikeri Circle, Madikeri, Karnataka, and Virajpet, Karnataka.</li><li>The details of the matter are available on the company&apos;s website, as well as on the websites of BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange of India Ltd.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9e45b241-70e2-4b6c-afb8-4462eba3b6b1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Medplus Health Services Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IOC] Indian Oil Corporation Ltd Announces Changes in Senior Management Personnel</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDIAN+OIL+CORPORATION+LTD.&title=Indian+Oil+Corporation+Ltd+Announces+Changes+in+Senior+Management+Personnel&newsId=89967917-17e1-4850-90a3-fa1ed9424558&token=ODk5Njc5MTctMTdl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">89967917-17e1-4850-90a3-fa1ed9424558</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 11:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indian Oil Corporation Ltd has announced changes in its senior management personnel. The new appointees include Manas Ranjan Dwibedy, Prakash Abraham, Sanjib Biswas, G R K Murthy, R R Raje, Samarendra Nath Jha, R. Ravichandran, Sarvesh Kumar, and Nitin Bhatnagar. The new executives bring a combined experience of over 300 years in various fields such as Fire &amp; Safety, HR, Industrial Engineering, Mechanical Engineering, Electrical Engineering, Chemical Engineering, and Finance. This move is seen as a strategic move by the company to strengthen its leadership and management.</p><ul><li>Indian Oil Corporation Ltd announces changes in senior management personnel</li><li>Manas Ranjan Dwibedy appointed as Executive Director (H,S&amp;E), Corporate Office</li><li>Prakash Abraham appointed as Executive Director (Employee Relations), Corporate Office</li><li>Sanjib Biswas appointed as Director (MO-LPG), Grade ‘I’ OISD, Noida</li><li>G R K Murthy appointed as Executive Director (Projects), Refineries HQ</li><li>R R Raje appointed as Executive Director (HR), Refineries HQ</li><li>Samarendra Nath Jha appointed as Executive Director (CC &amp; Branding), Corporate Office</li><li>R. Ravichandran appointed as Executive Director (Operations), Marketing Head Office</li><li>Nitin Bhatnagar appointed as Executive Director &amp; State Head, IndianOil AOD State Office</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a0746e31-c766-4cf9-a5ff-e9df7954d7d2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDIAN OIL CORPORATION LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CHCL] Cian Healthcare Ltd to Approve Un-audited Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 and H1 of FY 2025-26 on Jan 14, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Cian+Healthcare+Ltd&title=Cian+Healthcare+Ltd+to+Approve+Un-audited+Consolidated+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+H1+of+FY+2025-26+on+Jan+14%2C+2026&newsId=ec9ff4d0-b411-4e0b-96d3-763cba7d1b8a&token=ZWM5ZmY0ZDAtYjQx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ec9ff4d0-b411-4e0b-96d3-763cba7d1b8a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 10:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cian Healthcare Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 14, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and half year ended on September 30, 2025. The meeting will also approve the Limited Review Reports issued by the Statutory Auditors of the Company, M/s. SS R C A &amp; Co., Chartered Accountants. The company is an ISO 9001:2015 and WHO GMP certified entity, with its registered office in Pune and manufacturing unit in Haridwar, Uttarakhand.</p><ul><li>Cian Healthcare Ltd to approve un-audited Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 and H1 of FY 2025-26 on Jan 14, 2026</li><li>The meeting will also approve the Limited Review Reports issued by the Statutory Auditors of the Company, M/s. SS R C A &amp; Co., Chartered Accountants</li><li>Cian Healthcare Ltd is an ISO 9001:2015 and WHO GMP certified entity</li><li>The company&apos;s registered office is in Pune and manufacturing unit is in Haridwar, Uttarakhand</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5391e11b-fbe6-4379-88ba-4740b6d28b3d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Cian Healthcare Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TRIMURTHI] Novelix Pharmaceuticals Appoints Ms. Sridevi Belide as Non-Executive Non-Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Trimurthi+Ltd&title=Novelix+Pharmaceuticals+Appoints+Ms.+Sridevi+Belide+as+Non-Executive+Non-Independent+Director&newsId=cd077a57-2584-466b-b9df-98e429d83499&token=Y2QwNzdhNTctMjU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd077a57-2584-466b-b9df-98e429d83499</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 10:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Novelix Pharmaceuticals Ltd. has announced the appointment of Ms. Sridevi Belide as a Non-Executive Non-Independent Director. The appointment was approved in an Extra Ordinary General Meeting held on 09th January, 2026. Ms. Belide, a medical professional with an MBBS degree, brings her expertise in healthcare and scientific understanding to corporate leadership. She is not related to any of the directors and is not debarred from holding the office of Director by any SEBI order or any other such authority.</p><ul><li>Ms. Sridevi Belide appointed as Non-Executive Non-Independent Director</li><li>Appointment approved in Extra Ordinary General Meeting on 09th January, 2026</li><li>Ms. Belide is a medical professional with an MBBS degree</li><li>Ms. Belide is not related to any of the directors</li><li>Ms. Belide is not debarred from holding the office of Director by any SEBI order or any other such authority</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/35c562d1-6be6-4f63-ae47-663c09f992ea.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Trimurthi Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BCG] Brightcom Group&apos;s Weekly Update: Insightful Presentation on Digital Advertising Market Structure</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Brightcom+Group+Ltd&title=Brightcom+Group%27s+Weekly+Update%3A+Insightful+Presentation+on+Digital+Advertising+Market+Structure&newsId=b3d61776-c508-4dfe-a015-60d7b99ba1df&token=YjNkNjE3NzYtYzUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3d61776-c508-4dfe-a015-60d7b99ba1df</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Brightcom Group Ltd. has released the next explanatory presentation in a series, providing background information on the digital advertising market structure, operating mechanisms, and industry context. This presentation is intended solely as reference material and does not contain any forward-looking statements, financial guidance, or projections. The presentation highlights the digital advertising market&apos;s size, its growing significance, and the differences between digital and traditional advertising. The digital advertising market is structured around software platforms and consists of advertisers, brands, publishers, platforms, technology, agencies, and networks that allocate budgets, connect demand and supply, and measure outcomes.</p><ul><li>Digital advertising now represents the majority of global advertising spend.</li><li>Global advertising expenditure has exceeded $1.5 trillion.</li><li>Digital advertising is measurable, addressable, and automated, making it different from traditional media.</li><li>The digital advertising market operates through software platforms and consists of various players such as advertisers, publishers, platforms, technology, agencies, and networks.</li><li>Nearly all incremental growth in advertising is digital.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/df17aae3-33fc-46f0-8e91-6acb07b79675.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Brightcom Group Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SPARC] Sun Pharma Advanced Research Company to Raise Funds and Approve Employee Stock Option Scheme</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SUN+PHARMA+ADVANCED+RESEARCH+COMPANY+LTD.&title=Sun+Pharma+Advanced+Research+Company+to+Raise+Funds+and+Approve+Employee+Stock+Option+Scheme&newsId=a63df017-c49b-4a76-a12a-cad4ad4f9e66&token=YTYzZGYwMTctYzQ5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a63df017-c49b-4a76-a12a-cad4ad4f9e66</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 08:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sun Pharma Advanced Research Company Ltd has informed BSE that the meeting of the Board of Directors of the Company is scheduled on 14/01/2026. The agenda includes considering and approving the proposal for raising funds by the Company through a preferential issue of securities to an identified member of the promoter group. The Company also plans to approve the Employee Stock Option Scheme in terms of Securities and Exchange Board of India (Share Based Employee Benefits and Sweat Equity) Regulations, 2021. The Trading Window for dealing in shares of the Company has been closed effective from January 01, 2026.</p><ul><li>Sun Pharma Advanced Research Company to raise funds through preferential issue of securities</li><li>The funds will be raised from an identified member of the promoter group</li><li>The Company also plans to approve the Employee Stock Option Scheme</li><li>The decision is subject to approval from members of the Company, NSE, and BSE</li><li>Trading Window for dealing in shares of the Company has been closed since January 01, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ec968440-0f0b-4e0b-9ee4-5932039e9fa2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SUN PHARMA ADVANCED RESEARCH COMPANY LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>