<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:41:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[DHOOTIN] Dhoot Industrial Finance Ltd to Approve Q3 Results on Feb 11, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DHOOT+INDUSTRIAL+FINANCE+LTD.&title=Dhoot+Industrial+Finance+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+Results+on+Feb+11%2C+2026&newsId=d3ae328f-6e5c-4239-b3c6-7158abff42f0&token=ZDNhZTMyOGYtNmU1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3ae328f-6e5c-4239-b3c6-7158abff42f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dhoot Industrial Finance Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 11, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone Financial Results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in securities of the company for designated persons, including employees and directors, has been closed from January 1, 2026, and will remain closed until February 13, 2026, in accordance with the Code of Practice and Procedures for Fair Disclosure of Unpublished Price Sensitive Information of the company and SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Dhoot Industrial Finance Ltd to consider and approve Unaudited Standalone Financial Results for Q3 2025-2026</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities closed from January 1, 2026, to February 13, 2026, for designated persons</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/79dd67eb-2c1f-470f-9f74-b7bff94eed10.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DHOOT INDUSTRIAL FINANCE LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ICRA] ICRA Ltd Reports 35.3% Increase in Q3 FY2026 Revenue from Operations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ICRA+LTD.&title=ICRA+Ltd+Reports+35.3%25+Increase+in+Q3+FY2026+Revenue+from+Operations&newsId=5eb2e645-2c84-41ba-890c-c3063c134361&token=NWViMmU2NDUtMmM4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5eb2e645-2c84-41ba-890c-c3063c134361</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:41:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>ICRA Limited announced its results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The consolidated revenue from operations increased by 35.3% to ₹ 163.6 crore for the third quarter, while the profit before exceptional items and tax increased by 10.9%. The revenue performance for the quarter includes the consolidation impact of Fintellix acquisition, while profitability for the quarter includes amortisation of intangibles recognised. The company has recognised a one-time exceptional charge related to the implementation of the new Labour Codes. The adjusted PBT for the nine months ended December 2025 increased by 15.4%.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations up by 35.3% in Q3 FY2026</li><li>Profit before tax (PBT) up by 10.9% in Q3 FY2026</li><li>Adjusted PBT for 9M FY2026 up by 15.4%</li><li>Fintellix acquisition boosts ICRA&apos;s capabilities in risk analytics</li><li>ICRA recognised as the Best Company under the Small and Emerging Category in ICSI CSR Awards</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/910c3ada-e25c-497f-8a2f-8ca233dea64b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ICRA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASALCBR] Associated Alcohols &amp; Breweries Ltd to Approve Q4 Results for 2025 in Board Meeting on Feb 4, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ASSOCIATED+ALCOHOLS+%26+BREWERIES+LTD.&title=Associated+Alcohols+%26+Breweries+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+Results+for+2025+in+Board+Meeting+on+Feb+4%2C+2026&newsId=6c4f4e68-71e9-4ade-aee9-b701ca27c6f9&token=NmM0ZjRlNjgtNzFl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c4f4e68-71e9-4ade-aee9-b701ca27c6f9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Associated Alcohols &amp; Breweries Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 4, 2026, to consider and approve the Standalone Unaudited Financial Results and Limited Review Report for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The Consolidated Unaudited Financial Results and Limited Review Report for the same quarter will also be considered and approved. The meeting will take place at the company&apos;s registered/corporate office in Indore, MP. The trading window for dealing in securities of the company, which was closed from January 1, 2026, will open after 48 hours from the conclusion of the board meeting.</p><ul><li>Associated Alcohols &amp; Breweries Ltd to consider and approve Q4 results for 2025</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities to open after 48 hours from the board meeting</li><li>Meeting scheduled on February 4, 2026, at the company&apos;s registered/corporate office in Indore</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/061eba2e-a27b-438c-b36b-219d8fb2f9b8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ASSOCIATED ALCOHOLS & BREWERIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SYMPHONY] Symphony Ltd Declares 100% Interim Dividend, Rolls Back Divestment Process, and Announces Changes in Key Managerial Personnel</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Symphony+Limited&title=Symphony+Ltd+Declares+100%25+Interim+Dividend%2C+Rolls+Back+Divestment+Process%2C+and+Announces+Changes+in+Key+Managerial+Personnel&newsId=aaff5845-2a63-477c-a20f-78fef997d159&token=YWFmZjU4NDUtMmE2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aaff5845-2a63-477c-a20f-78fef997d159</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:38:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Symphony Ltd, a leading air-cooling company, has declared a 100% interim dividend for the financial year 2025-26. The company had initiated a divestment process for its subsidiaries in Australia and Mexico, but due to unfavorable market conditions, the process has been rolled back. The company has also announced changes in its key managerial personnel, with Mr. Amit Kumar resigning from his position as Executive Director and Group Chief Executive Officer.</p><ul><li>Declared 100% interim dividend for the financial year 2025-26</li><li>Rolled back divestment process for subsidiaries in Australia and Mexico</li><li>Change in Key Managerial Personnel: Mr. Amit Kumar resigns as Executive Director and Group Chief Executive Officer</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/eaf22ce5-60b8-4112-99c1-977012348ead.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Symphony Limited | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IDFCFIRSTB] IDFC First Bank Ltd Announces Schedule of Institutional Investors Meetings for 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IDFC+First+Bank+Ltd&title=IDFC+First+Bank+Ltd+Announces+Schedule+of+Institutional+Investors+Meetings+for+2026&newsId=efa0efa2-71b9-4b6f-9192-9d7578108b0f&token=ZWZhMGVmYTItNzFi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">efa0efa2-71b9-4b6f-9192-9d7578108b0f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:38:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>IDFC First Bank Ltd has announced the schedule of various institutional investors meetings for the year 2026. The meetings will be held with Goldman Sachs, ICICI Securities, JM Financial India, Nuvama, Manthan-Systematix, Axis Capital, and IIFL. The meetings will be held in virtual and physical formats in Mumbai, India and Singapore. The bank will use the Investor Presentation for Q3-FY26 for these meetings.</p><ul><li>IDFC First Bank Ltd announces schedule of institutional investors meetings for 2026.</li><li>Meetings will be held with Goldman Sachs, ICICI Securities, JM Financial India, Nuvama, Manthan-Systematix, Axis Capital, and IIFL.</li><li>Meetings will be held in virtual and physical formats in Mumbai, India and Singapore.</li><li>Bank will use the Investor Presentation for Q3-FY26 for these meetings.</li><li>Schedule is subject to change due to exigencies on the part of the Investors/Company.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/97a59617-8049-49b0-9727-b8d2e7a00f48.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IDFC First Bank Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JK AGRI] JK Agri Genetics Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on Feb 4, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JK+Agri+Genetics+Ltd&title=JK+Agri+Genetics+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+Feb+4%2C+2026&newsId=36224101-3351-4112-b1c8-8f892da7c63b&token=MzYyMjQxMDEtMzM1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">36224101-3351-4112-b1c8-8f892da7c63b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:38:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>JK Agri Genetics Ltd has announced a Board Meeting on February 4, 2026, to consider and approve the Standalone and Consolidated Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s trading window will be closed from January 1, 2026, and will reopen on February 7, 2026, in accordance with the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulation, 2015.</p><ul><li>JK Agri Genetics Ltd to approve Q3 and nine months financial results on Feb 4, 2026</li><li>Trading window to remain closed from Jan 1, 2026, to Feb 6, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8f84e35b-3de4-4597-b96d-bc25ad22117a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JK Agri Genetics Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDUSFINL] Indus Finance Ltd Announces Q3 Results for FY2025-26, Reports Profit Before Tax</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Indus+Finance+Ltd&title=Indus+Finance+Ltd+Announces+Q3+Results+for+FY2025-26%2C+Reports+Profit+Before+Tax&newsId=d1875e48-e7cb-4faa-9e11-009ba34173f6&token=ZDE4NzVlNDgtZTdj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d1875e48-e7cb-4faa-9e11-009ba34173f6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:38:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indus Finance Ltd has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The company reported a profit before tax of INR 263.92 crores for the nine months ended 31st December 2025. The results were reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors on 28th January 2026.</p><ul><li>Indus Finance Ltd reported a profit before tax of INR 263.92 crores for the nine months ended 31st December 2025.</li><li>The results were reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors on 28th January 2026.</li><li>The company operates only in one segment.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/44f89b1c-6062-4afb-815c-9cc25ab9976e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Indus Finance Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PROGREXV] Progrex Ventures Ltd: No Funds Raised in Q4 2023</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Progrex+Ventures+Ltd&title=Progrex+Ventures+Ltd%3A+No+Funds+Raised+in+Q4+2023&newsId=7add73ed-29c6-4134-94cc-ac4ef56c3cda&token=N2FkZDczZWQtMjlj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7add73ed-29c6-4134-94cc-ac4ef56c3cda</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:37:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Progrex Ventures Ltd has declared that they did not raise any funds from public issue, right issue, or preferential shares during the quarter ended on 31-12-2023. This statement is in accordance with Regulation 32(1) of the SEBI (LODR) Regulation 2015. Therefore, the Statement of Deviation or Variation in Public Issue Right Issue Preferential Issue QIP etc. under Regulation 32(1) of SLBI (LODR) Regulations 2015 for the year ended on 31-12-2025 is not applicable to the company.</p><ul><li>Progrex Ventures Ltd did not raise any funds from public issue, right issue, or preferential shares during Q4 2023</li><li>The company&apos;s statement is in accordance with Regulation 32(1) of the SEBI (LODR) Regulation 2015</li><li>The Statement of Deviation or Variation in Public Issue Right Issue Preferential Issue QIP etc. under Regulation 32(1) of SLBI (LODR) Regulations 2015 for the year ended on 31-12-2025 is not applicable to the company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/799f49a1-40e5-4d07-a6f0-7c14491bb3ea.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Progrex Ventures Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KOTIC] Kothari Industrial Corporation Ltd Appoints Mr. Ravikumar Perumal as Independent Director and Grants Employee Stock Options</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KOTHARI+INDUSTRIAL+CORPORATION+LTD.&title=Kothari+Industrial+Corporation+Ltd+Appoints+Mr.+Ravikumar+Perumal+as+Independent+Director+and+Grants+Employee+Stock+Options&newsId=a93a8f52-8897-46f2-aea1-da42341949d2&token=YTkzYThmNTItODg5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a93a8f52-8897-46f2-aea1-da42341949d2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:37:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kothari Industrial Corporation Ltd has announced the appointment of Mr. Ravikumar Perumal as an Independent Director at the Extra-ordinary General Meeting (EGM7) held on 27.01.2026. The members have also approved the grant of employee stock options under the KICL Employee Stock Option Scheme 2025 (KICL ESOP 2025) to eligible employees of the company&apos;s subsidiary companies or associate companies. The company had previously provided relevant details regarding the appointment of the Independent Director as required by Regulation 30 of the Listing Regulations and the Master Circular issued by SEBI.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Ravikumar Perumal as an Independent Director</li><li>Grant of employee stock options under KICL ESOP 2025 to eligible employees of subsidiary or associate companies</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d85ba5ff-f6c3-4ee1-808b-34d4376710d9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KOTHARI INDUSTRIAL CORPORATION LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[M&amp;MFIN] Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Financial Services Ltd Reports Q3FY26 Financial Results: Loan Book Grew by 12% YoY, Profit After Tax Remained Resilient</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MAHINDRA+%26+MAHINDRA+FINANCIAL+SERVICES+LTD.&title=Mahindra+%26+Mahindra+Financial+Services+Ltd+Reports+Q3FY26+Financial+Results%3A+Loan+Book+Grew+by+12%25+YoY%2C+Profit+After+Tax+Remained+Resilient&newsId=9bca975f-89bc-468b-b64f-6cd858b69672&token=OWJjYTk3NWYtODli</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9bca975f-89bc-468b-b64f-6cd858b69672</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 12:35:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>The Board of Directors of Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Financial Services Limited (Mahindra Finance / MMFSL) announced the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025 (Q3 FY26). The Company’s loan book grew by 12% YoY and disbursements grew 7% YoY. MMFSL Profit After Tax (PAT) remained resilient despite the absorption of labour code impact for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. NIM expanded YoY during the quarter supported by higher Fee Income and lower Cost of Funds. MMFSL’s Asset quality remained within the guided range, with GS3 at 3.80% and GS2+GS3 at 9.20%. The credit cost for quarter ended December 31, 2025, was at 1.3%.</p><ul><li>Loan book grew by 12% YoY and disbursements grew 7% YoY</li><li>Profit After Tax (PAT) remained resilient despite the absorption of labour code impact</li><li>NIM expanded YoY during the quarter supported by higher Fee Income and lower Cost of Funds</li><li>Asset quality remained within the guided range, with GS3 at 3.80% and GS2+GS3 at 9.20%</li><li>Credit cost for quarter ended December 31, 2025, was at 1.3%</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6fb1be18-f0fd-4511-8b9a-2ebc895775ad.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MAHINDRA & MAHINDRA FINANCIAL SERVICES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>