<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 09:17:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[IDBI] IDBI Bank Ltd Reports Q3 FY 2026 Net Profit of ₹ 1,935 Crore, 12% YoY Total Business Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IDBI+BANK+LTD.&title=IDBI+Bank+Ltd+Reports+Q3+FY+2026+Net+Profit+of+%E2%82%B9+1%2C935+Crore%2C+12%25+YoY+Total+Business+Growth&newsId=c06fc159-0451-42f2-8b23-e5b88104356c&token=YzA2ZmMxNTktMDQ1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c06fc159-0451-42f2-8b23-e5b88104356c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 09:11:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>IDBI Bank Ltd has announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The bank recorded a net profit of ₹ 1,935 crore, representing a significant increase from the previous year. The total business stood at ₹ 5,46,643 crore, indicating a YoY growth of 12%. Total deposits and net advances also saw a YoY growth of 9% and 15% respectively. The bank&apos;s CRAR stands at 24.63%, with a YoY growth of 265 bps, and the gross NPA is down to 2.57%, representing a YoY reduction of 100 bps. The provision coverage ratio is at 99.33%. The bank also reported improved operating performance and business growth, with a focus on security and fraud risk management.</p><ul><li>Net Profit of ₹ 1,935 crore, a YoY increase of 12%</li><li>Total Business of ₹ 5,46,643 crore, indicating a YoY growth of 12%</li><li>Total Deposits of ₹ 3,07,858 crore, representing a YoY growth of 9%</li><li>Net Advances of ₹ 2,38,786 crore, indicating a YoY growth of 15%</li><li>CRAR at 24.63%, with a YoY growth of 265 bps</li><li>Gross NPA down to 2.57%, representing a YoY reduction of 100 bps</li><li>Provision Coverage Ratio at 99.33%</li><li>IDBI Bank recognized as the ‘Best Private Sector Bank- Highest Throughput &amp; Digital Adoption’ by M1 Xchange at the SAMAAH event</li><li>IDBI Bank conferred with the ET BFSI Exceller 2025 Award for Excellence in Security and Fraud Risk Management</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1cf96c9c-84cf-422b-a73b-6357a4c14963.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IDBI BANK LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[OSWAYRN] Oswal Yarns Ltd Announces Q3 Results for 2025, Net Loss Shrinks</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=OSWAL+YARNS+LTD.&title=Oswal+Yarns+Ltd+Announces+Q3+Results+for+2025%2C+Net+Loss+Shrinks&newsId=f297f061-65de-48ad-9495-2c908d5393a5&token=ZjI5N2YwNjEtNjVk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f297f061-65de-48ad-9495-2c908d5393a5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 09:11:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Oswal Yarns Ltd, a prominent player in the textile industry, has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s net loss has shrunk compared to the previous year, indicating a positive trend. The Board of Directors reviewed the financial results during their meeting on 17th January 2026.</p><ul><li>Net loss for the quarter reduced compared to the same period last year.</li><li>Board of Directors reviewed and approved the unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025.</li><li>The review was conducted by Subash Vipan &amp; Co., a peer-reviewed firm of Chartered Accountants.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d0c4611e-681c-46ab-8062-7dbf90c23386.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: OSWAL YARNS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LGEINDIA] LG Electronics India Ltd. Receives Mega Expansion Eligibility Certificate from Government of Maharashtra</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LG+Electronics+India+Ltd&title=LG+Electronics+India+Ltd.+Receives+Mega+Expansion+Eligibility+Certificate+from+Government+of+Maharashtra&newsId=dcb3c323-831c-43f5-9b92-a5122b68191c&token=ZGNiM2MzMjMtODMx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dcb3c323-831c-43f5-9b92-a5122b68191c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 09:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Pursuant to Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, LG Electronics India Ltd. has received an eligibility certificate for mega expansion under the electronics policy 2016 from the Government of Maharashtra, Directorate of Industries. The approval is for an investment of INR 705.74 Crores for the period 01 November, 2017 to 30 October, 2024 under the Mega category. This approval entitles the company to receive incentives in the form of SGST refund, electricity duty exemption, stamp duty exemption, refund of employee’s contribution to EPF, power tariff subsidy and exemption from payment of property tax. The incentive amount of INR 705.74 Crores is valid for the period 01 May, 2025 to 30 April, 2040, subject to an overall annual limit of INR 47.04 Crores.</p><ul><li>LG Electronics India Ltd. has received an eligibility certificate for mega expansion under the electronics policy 2016 from the Government of Maharashtra, Directorate of Industries.</li><li>The approval is for an investment of INR 705.74 Crores for the period 01 November, 2017 to 30 October, 2024 under the Mega category.</li><li>The incentives include SGST refund, electricity duty exemption, stamp duty exemption, refund of employee’s contribution to EPF, power tariff subsidy and exemption from payment of property tax.</li><li>The incentive amount of INR 705.74 Crores is valid for the period 01 May, 2025 to 30 April, 2040.</li><li>The overall annual limit of INR 47.04 Crores.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/20dfc3f8-bc57-4c69-903d-8d3f93f60b51.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LG Electronics India Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GCSL] Gretex Corporate Services Ltd Approves Allotment of 1,05,541 Equity Shares to Non-Promoter Warrant Holders</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Gretex+Corporate+Services+Ltd&title=Gretex+Corporate+Services+Ltd+Approves+Allotment+of+1%2C05%2C541+Equity+Shares+to+Non-Promoter+Warrant+Holders&newsId=2d7a3114-19ca-4b34-a5d9-34184b50550e&token=MmQ3YTMxMTQtMTlj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2d7a3114-19ca-4b34-a5d9-34184b50550e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 09:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gretex Corporate Services Ltd has approved the allotment of 1,05,541 equity shares to non-promoter warrant holders at an issue price of Rs. 379/- (including premium of Rs. 369/-). The warrant holders have also become entitled to 94,986 bonus equity shares, which shall be released from the demat suspense account and credited to the allottee’s demat account simultaneously with the allotment of equity shares. The equity shares allotted on exercise of conversion of Warrants shall rank pari passu in all respects with the existing equity shares of the Company.</p><ul><li>Gretex Corporate Services Ltd approves allotment of 1,05,541 equity shares to non-promoter warrant holders.</li><li>The allotment is at an issue price of Rs. 379/- (including premium of Rs. 369/-).</li><li>Warrant holders also become entitled to 94,986 bonus equity shares.</li><li>The bonus equity shares will be released from the demat suspense account and credited to the allottee’s demat account simultaneously with the allotment of equity shares.</li><li>The equity shares allotted on exercise of conversion of Warrants shall rank pari passu in all respects with the existing equity shares of the Company.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/99f8c237-3fc5-494b-a5e7-75a30b337caa.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Gretex Corporate Services Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DIACABS] Diamond Power Infrastructure Receives Letter of Intent Worth Rs. 52 Crores from Enrich Energy</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Diamond+Power+Infrastructure+Limited-%24&title=Diamond+Power+Infrastructure+Receives+Letter+of+Intent+Worth+Rs.+52+Crores+from+Enrich+Energy&newsId=d10986d7-6d58-423a-a16a-3904ab870e2f&token=ZDEwOTg2ZDctNmQ1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d10986d7-6d58-423a-a16a-3904ab870e2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 08:54:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Diamond Power Infrastructure Limited has received a letter of intent from Enrich Energy Private Limited for the supply of power cables worth Rs. 52,48,49,012/- inclusive of GST. The order is to be executed by May 2026. This order does not fall under related party transactions and none of the promoter/promoter group/group companies have any interest in the entity that awarded the order.</p><ul><li>Diamond Power Infrastructure received a letter of intent from Enrich Energy Private Limited.</li><li>The order is for the supply of power cables worth Rs. 52 crores inclusive of GST.</li><li>The order is to be executed by May 2026.</li><li>The order does not fall under related party transactions.</li><li>None of the promoter/promoter group/group companies have any interest in the entity that awarded the order.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6d08c7cd-63ce-45fe-9f56-c7a0a5c3a0d7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Diamond Power Infrastructure Limited-$ | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ARAVALIS] Aravali Securities &amp; Finance Ltd Authorizes Director to Sign Unaudited Financial Results for Q4 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ARAVALI+SECURITIES+%26+FINANCE+LTD.&title=Aravali+Securities+%26+Finance+Ltd+Authorizes+Director+to+Sign+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q4+2025&newsId=ae507e51-18ba-447f-8602-808251ce3ee6&token=YWU1MDdlNTEtMThi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae507e51-18ba-447f-8602-808251ce3ee6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 08:41:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Aravali Securities &amp; Finance Ltd has authorized Ms. Malvika Poddar, Director of the Company, to sign the Unaudited Standalone Financial Results together with the Limited Review Report thereon for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. This authorization comes after the resignation of Mr. Ranjan Kumar Poddar, Managing Director and Chairperson of the Company, to ensure compliance with the provisions of Regulation 33 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Aravali Securities &amp; Finance Ltd has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter ended 31/12/2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue for the quarter is not explicitly stated in the document.</li><li>Ms. Malvika Poddar has been authorized to sign the unaudited financial results and the limited review report.</li><li>The authorization comes after the resignation of Mr. Ranjan Kumar Poddar, the former Managing Director and Chairperson.</li><li>The company&apos;s financial results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d679aef2-db23-4774-8fc6-5cf3a58906b8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ARAVALI SECURITIES & FINANCE LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VEL] Vaxfab Enterprises Ltd Acquires Controlling Stake in Satvat Agro LLP, Making it a Subsidiary</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vaxfab+Enterprises+Ltd&title=Vaxfab+Enterprises+Ltd+Acquires+Controlling+Stake+in+Satvat+Agro+LLP%2C+Making+it+a+Subsidiary&newsId=b2dfa06e-bb7d-49ee-944e-b153a8b50385&token=YjJkZmEwNmUtYmI3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b2dfa06e-bb7d-49ee-944e-b153a8b50385</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 08:41:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vaxfab Enterprises Limited has announced the acquisition of a controlling stake in Satvat Agro LLP, thereby making it a subsidiary. The details of this acquisition are disclosed in ANNEXURE-A, as per the requirements of Regulation 30 of SEBI LODR and SEBI Circular SEBI/HO/CFD/CFD-PoD-1/P/CIR/2023/123, dated 13th July, 2023. This announcement is for information and record purposes.</p><ul><li>Vaxfab Enterprises Ltd has acquired a controlling stake in Satvat Agro LLP</li><li>Satvat Agro LLP has become a subsidiary of Vaxfab Enterprises Ltd</li><li>The acquisition details are disclosed in ANNEXURE-A</li><li>The acquisition is in line with Regulation 30 of SEBI LODR and SEBI Circular SEBI/HO/CFD/CFD-PoD-1/P/CIR/2023/123, dated 13th July, 2023</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/75275cc5-9437-4c9d-8bbb-5f72855d001b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vaxfab Enterprises Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JAIBALAJI] Jai Balaji Industries Ltd Reports on Re-lodgement of Transfer Requests for December 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JAI+BALAJI+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Jai+Balaji+Industries+Ltd+Reports+on+Re-lodgement+of+Transfer+Requests+for+December+2025&newsId=58f56408-6bdd-4b89-b4ce-fbbc5323d56a&token=NThmNTY0MDgtNmJk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58f56408-6bdd-4b89-b4ce-fbbc5323d56a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 08:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jai Balaji Industries Ltd has released a monthly report on the re-lodgement of transfer requests of physical shares for December 2025. The report, received from the Registrar and Share Transfer Agent of the Company, M/s Maheshwari Datamatics Private Limited, confirms the status of requests received from shareholders for the re-lodgement of transfer requests for physical shares under the special window provided by the SEBI Circular dated 2nd July, 2025. The report includes the number of requests received, processed, approved, and rejected during December 2025, along with the average time taken for processing these requests.</p><ul><li>Jai Balaji Industries Ltd releases monthly report on re-lodgement of transfer requests of physical shares for December 2025.</li><li>Report received from Registrar and Share Transfer Agent, M/s Maheshwari Datamatics Private Limited.</li><li>Details of requests received, processed, approved, and rejected during December 2025.</li><li>Average time taken for processing requests during December 2025.</li><li>Compliance with SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSDPoD/P/CIR/2025/97 dated 2nd July 2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/70840899-f916-4093-a781-ab2bd828629f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JAI BALAJI INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ALBERTDA] Albert David Ltd Announces Resignation of Senior Management Personnel</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ALBERT+DAVID+LTD.-%24&title=Albert+David+Ltd+Announces+Resignation+of+Senior+Management+Personnel&newsId=ee0373a7-41e5-4ae7-8cba-366ba7143dda&token=ZWUwMzczYTctNDFl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee0373a7-41e5-4ae7-8cba-366ba7143dda</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 08:21:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Albert David Ltd has announced the resignation of Mrs. Snehal Tushar Bhosale, Executive Assistant (EA) to Managing Director &amp; CEO, due to personal reasons, effective from the close of business hours on January 16, 2026.</p><ul><li>Mrs. Snehal Tushar Bhosale has resigned from her position as Executive Assistant (EA) to Managing Director &amp; CEO of Albert David Ltd.</li><li>The resignation is due to personal reasons.</li><li>The effective date of resignation is the close of business hours on January 16, 2026.</li><li>Albert David Ltd is a part of the Kothari Group and manufactures Allopathic &amp; Herbal Formulations, IV infusions &amp; Medical Disposables.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d2c3e6a1-323d-4e80-ab14-be052a4d09db.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ALBERT DAVID LTD.-$ | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CRYOGENIC] Cryogenic Ogs Ltd to Incorporate Wholly-Owned Subsidiary in UAE and Enter Lease Agreement with Related Parties</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Cryogenic+Ogs+Ltd&title=Cryogenic+Ogs+Ltd+to+Incorporate+Wholly-Owned+Subsidiary+in+UAE+and+Enter+Lease+Agreement+with+Related+Parties&newsId=60201db4-81e7-4ae9-953c-f651e236a009&token=NjAyMDFkYjQtODFl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60201db4-81e7-4ae9-953c-f651e236a009</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 08:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cryogenic Ogs Ltd announced that its Board of Directors, at their meeting on 17th January 2026, considered and approved the incorporation of a wholly-owned subsidiary in the United Arab Emirates (UAE) with an investment of approximately AED 1,75,000. The company also approved entering into a lease agreement with related parties for a period of 30 years at Navi Jithardi, Taluka Karjan, District Vadodara, subject to compliance with applicable laws and regulations.</p><ul><li>Incorporation of a wholly-owned subsidiary in UAE with an investment of approximately AED 1,75,000</li><li>Entering into a lease agreement with related parties for a period of 30 years at Navi Jithardi, Taluka Karjan, District Vadodara</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2d9c484f-f923-4c23-9ab3-f44abf6a3937.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Cryogenic Ogs Ltd | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>