<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:19:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[JMJFIN] JMJ Fintech Ltd. Announces Corrigendum to First and Final Call Notice for Rights Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JMJ+Fintech+Ltd&title=JMJ+Fintech+Ltd.+Announces+Corrigendum+to+First+and+Final+Call+Notice+for+Rights+Issue&newsId=a7f2c415-e94a-4c1e-918b-039c1f80eb9c&token=YTdmMmM0MTUtZTk0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a7f2c415-e94a-4c1e-918b-039c1f80eb9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Rights Issue</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>JMJ Fintech Ltd. has announced a corrigendum to the First and Final Call Notice for its rights issue. The payment period for the First and Final Call Money has been revised to commence on Tuesday, January 13, 2026, instead of Wednesday, January 07, 2026, and will continue until Tuesday, January 27, 2026. The partly paid-up equity shares were allotted on Thursday, August 21, 2025, and the balance amount of Rs. 7.35 per partly paid-up equity share is payable on the First and Final Call. The trading of the partly paid-up equity shares of the Company has been suspended on the Stock Exchange with effect from Friday, December 19, 2025. Eligible Shareholders who pay the First and Final Call on their Rights Equity Shares can expect credit of the fully paid-up equity shares of the Company and the commencement of trading on such fully paid-up equity shares within a period of 7-8 weeks from the last date for making the payment of First and Final Call i.e., within 7-8 weeks from Tuesday, January 27, 2026.</p><ul><li>JMJ Fintech Ltd. announces corrigendum to First and Final Call Notice for rights issue.</li><li>Payment period for First and Final Call Money revised to commence on Tuesday, January 13, 2026, and continue until Tuesday, January 27, 2026.</li><li>Partly paid-up equity shares allotted on Thursday, August 21, 2025, and balance amount of Rs. 7.35 per share payable on First and Final Call.</li><li>Trading of partly paid-up equity shares of the Company suspended on the Stock Exchange with effect from Friday, December 19, 2025.</li><li>Eligible Shareholders who pay the First and Final Call on their Rights Equity Shares can expect credit of fully paid-up equity shares within 7-8 weeks from Tuesday, January 27, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fe0910bd-c244-4812-a50c-df14706d97cf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JMJ Fintech Ltd | Category: Rights Issue</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DEEDEV] Dee Development Engineers Ltd: CFO Resigns, New CFO Appointed</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Dee+Development+Engineers+Ltd&title=Dee+Development+Engineers+Ltd%3A+CFO+Resigns%2C+New+CFO+Appointed&newsId=5eccff77-3b12-441c-b4ef-048d1d85e809&token=NWVjY2ZmNzctM2Ix</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5eccff77-3b12-441c-b4ef-048d1d85e809</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:02:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dee Development Engineers Ltd announced the resignation of its Chief Financial Officer, Mr. Sameer Agarwal, due to personal professional priorities and future career plans. His resignation is effective from the close of business hours on 5th January, 2026. The company has appointed Mr. Brham Prakash Yadav as the new Chief Financial Officer and Key Managerial Personnel, with effect from 7th January, 2026. Mr. Yadav is a seasoned professional with over 30 years of experience in finance, accounts, treasury, taxation, and board-level financial management.</p><ul><li>Mr. Sameer Agarwal has resigned as Chief Financial Officer of Dee Development Engineers Ltd.</li><li>His resignation is effective from the close of business hours on 5th January, 2026.</li><li>Mr. Brham Prakash Yadav has been appointed as the new Chief Financial Officer and Key Managerial Personnel.</li><li>Mr. Yadav has over 30 years of experience in finance, accounts, treasury, taxation, and board-level financial management.</li><li>His appointment is effective from 7th January, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2c11dce8-e16e-4e18-abe1-ba3f0f37c64b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Dee Development Engineers Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GODREJIND] Godrej Industries Ltd Incorporates Wholly Owned Subsidiary: Godrej Investment Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GODREJ+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Godrej+Industries+Ltd+Incorporates+Wholly+Owned+Subsidiary%3A+Godrej+Investment+Limited&newsId=3b0a566b-c24e-4b93-9adf-58db5cfd4be0&token=M2IwYTU2NmItYzI0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b0a566b-c24e-4b93-9adf-58db5cfd4be0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Godrej Industries Ltd has incorporated a Wholly Owned Subsidiary named Godrej Investment Limited on January 5, 2026. The new subsidiary will be engaged in the business of financial services. Godrej Industries Ltd will hold 100% of the shareholding in Godrej Investment Limited. The subsidiary is yet to commence its business operations.</p><ul><li>Godrej Industries Ltd incorporates a Wholly Owned Subsidiary, Godrej Investment Limited</li><li>Godrej Investment Limited will operate in the financial services business</li><li>Godrej Industries Ltd will hold 100% shareholding in Godrej Investment Limited</li><li>Godrej Investment Limited is yet to commence business operations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6499716e-4b50-4ab2-8b3d-0f5f0c4fbc69.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GODREJ INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SENCO] Senco Gold Achieves 31% Sales Growth in First 9 Months of FY26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Senco+Gold+Ltd&title=Senco+Gold+Achieves+31%25+Sales+Growth+in+First+9+Months+of+FY26&newsId=58d72406-3b7a-4a67-8894-c97dca3e7971&token=NThkNzI0MDYtM2I3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58d72406-3b7a-4a67-8894-c97dca3e7971</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Senco Gold Limited has reported a 31% YoY growth in sales and revenue for the first nine months of FY26. The growth was led by targeted festive campaigns, new design launches, and intensive customer engagement during key festive periods. The company launched 16 new showrooms, including 11 franchises and 5 company-owned stores. Despite the rise in gold prices, Senco Gold is optimistic about achieving 25%+ YoY growth for FY26, driven by the popularity of its franchise model and a robust pipeline for the upcoming year.</p><ul><li>Senco Gold achieved a 31% YoY growth in sales and revenue for the first nine months of FY26.</li><li>The company launched 16 new showrooms, including 11 franchises and 5 company-owned stores.</li><li>Targeted festive campaigns, new design launches, and intensive customer engagement during key festive periods contributed to the growth.</li><li>Despite the rise in gold prices, Senco Gold is optimistic about achieving 25%+ YoY growth for FY26.</li><li>The company&apos;s robust pipeline and the popularity of its franchise model are expected to drive the growth in the upcoming year.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/46c08dd8-d0c9-4079-9539-9d56a0953b33.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Senco Gold Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KRATOSENER] Lords Mark Industries Secures US FDA Registration for Over 150 Orthopaedic Surgical Products</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KRATOS+ENERGY+%26+INFRASTRUCTURE+LTD.&title=Lords+Mark+Industries+Secures+US+FDA+Registration+for+Over+150+Orthopaedic+Surgical+Products&newsId=1b29aa3b-55dd-4ee5-8ca9-adb1a0a9681a&token=MWIyOWFhM2ItNTVk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b29aa3b-55dd-4ee5-8ca9-adb1a0a9681a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>USFDA</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Lords Mark Industries Ltd, formerly known as Lords Mark India Limited and Kratos Energy &amp; Infrastructure Limited, has achieved a significant milestone by securing US FDA registrations for more than 150 orthopaedic surgical products. The company&apos;s manufacturing facility in Silvassa operates in compliance with internationally benchmarked production protocols and quality management systems, meeting the regulatory requirements prescribed by the US FDA. The US FDA-listed portfolio includes a wide range of orthopaedic and rehabilitation products. This achievement reflects the company&apos;s regulatory discipline, manufacturing strength, and long-term vision to position India as a trusted source of globally compliant healthcare solutions. This development significantly strengthens the company&apos;s access to highly regulated international markets and enhances opportunities for institutional supplies, hospital partnerships, and export growth through its US-based subsidiary, Lords Mark Global LLC.</p><ul><li>Lords Mark Industries Ltd has secured US FDA registrations for more than 150 orthopaedic surgical products.</li><li>The company&apos;s manufacturing facility in Silvassa operates in compliance with internationally benchmarked production protocols and quality management systems.</li><li>The US FDA-listed portfolio includes a wide range of orthopaedic and rehabilitation products.</li><li>This achievement reflects the company&apos;s regulatory discipline and long-term vision to position India as a trusted source of globally compliant healthcare solutions.</li><li>This development significantly strengthens the company&apos;s access to highly regulated international markets and enhances opportunities for institutional supplies, hospital partnerships, and export growth.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/16b2dd97-4bd5-41e3-81b2-3d4c15180625.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KRATOS ENERGY & INFRASTRUCTURE LTD. | Category: USFDA</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[7TEC] Saven Technologies Ltd Reports on Re-lodgement of Physical Share Transfer Requests as of December 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SAVEN+TECHNOLOGIES+LTD.&title=Saven+Technologies+Ltd+Reports+on+Re-lodgement+of+Physical+Share+Transfer+Requests+as+of+December+2025&newsId=da530315-6886-4871-b1af-f7b5332c96f4&token=ZGE1MzAzMTUtNjg4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">da530315-6886-4871-b1af-f7b5332c96f4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:01:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Saven Technologies Ltd has summarized the status of re-lodgement of physical share transfer requests as of December 31, 2025, in accordance with the SEBI circular no. SEBI/HO/MIRSD-POD/P/CIR/2025/97 dated 2nd July, 2025. The report came from the company&apos;s Registrar and Share Transfer Agent (RTA) — XL Softech Systems Limited. The data provided includes the number of requests received, approved, and processed during the month, as well as the average time taken for processing. This information is intended for stock exchange records and communication.</p><ul><li>Saven Technologies Ltd provided a summary of physical share transfer requests as of December 2025.</li><li>The report was compiled based on the SEBI circular no. SEBI/HO/MIRSD-POD/P/CIR/2025/97 dated 2nd July, 2025.</li><li>The data was received from the company&apos;s RTA, XL Softech Systems Limited.</li><li>The summary includes the number of requests received, approved, and processed during the month.</li><li>The average time taken for processing of requests is also provided.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9e6e6fa4-805c-463f-9413-3828d18fd057.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SAVEN TECHNOLOGIES LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DEEDEV] Dee Development Engineers Ltd Appoints New Chief Financial Officer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Dee+Development+Engineers+Ltd&title=Dee+Development+Engineers+Ltd+Appoints+New+Chief+Financial+Officer&newsId=3397eee7-5610-4d9b-984c-31a6c214f17f&token=MzM5N2VlZTctNTYx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3397eee7-5610-4d9b-984c-31a6c214f17f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:01:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dee Development Engineers Ltd has announced the appointment of Mr. Brham Prakash Yadav as the new Chief Financial Officer and Key Managerial Personnel, effective from 7th January, 2026. This comes after the resignation of Mr. Sameer Agarwal due to personal professional priorities and future career plans. Mr. Yadav brings over 30 years of experience in finance, accounts, treasury, taxation, and board-level financial management.</p><ul><li>Mr. Sameer Agarwal has resigned as Chief Financial Officer due to personal professional priorities and future career plans.</li><li>Mr. Brham Prakash Yadav has been appointed as the new Chief Financial Officer and Key Managerial Personnel, effective from 7th January, 2026.</li><li>Mr. Yadav has over 30 years of experience in finance, accounts, treasury, taxation, and board-level financial management.</li><li>Mr. Yadav has extensive experience in IPO processes, private equity, fund raising, banking &amp; treasury, working capital management, Ind AS &amp; IFRS, internal financial controls, inventory control, capex and opex control, financial reporting &amp; consolidation, secretarial compliances, and direct &amp; indirect taxation.</li><li>Mr. Yadav has successfully handled private debt funding of ₹400 crore, multiple plant acquisitions, large greenfield and brownfield projects, restructuring of supplier payment terms, enhancement of working capital limits, term loan funding, and recovery/utilisation of significant amounts under MAT and GST.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8bc396f6-d8c0-471d-9160-872684cf2e74.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Dee Development Engineers Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PURPLEFIN] Purple Finance Ltd Allots Subordinated Debentures Worth INR 5 Crores to Mr. Anil Prithviraj Kumar</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Purple+Finance+Ltd&title=Purple+Finance+Ltd+Allots+Subordinated+Debentures+Worth+INR+5+Crores+to+Mr.+Anil+Prithviraj+Kumar&newsId=7619eb63-3c19-48b3-b3e6-3fb719f63a06&token=NzYxOWViNjMtM2Mx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7619eb63-3c19-48b3-b3e6-3fb719f63a06</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:54:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Purple Finance Ltd has announced the allotment of 500 Subordinated, Unsecured, Unrated, Unlisted, Redeemable, Transferable, INR Denominated Non-Convertible Debentures to Mr. Anil Prithviraj Kumar. The total value of the debentures is INR 5,00,00,000 (Indian Rupees Five Crores Only). The tenure of the instrument is 61 months, with the date of allotment on January 06, 2026, and the date of maturity on February 06, 2031. The coupon/interest offered is 12.50% per annum, payable monthly. The principal amounts will be payable by the Company on the Final Redemption Date.</p><ul><li>Purple Finance Ltd allots debentures worth INR 5 Crores to Mr. Anil Prithviraj Kumar</li><li>The debentures are Subordinated, Unsecured, Unrated, Unlisted, Redeemable, Transferable, INR Denominated Non-Convertible Debentures</li><li>The tenure of the instrument is 61 months</li><li>The coupon/interest offered is 12.50% per annum, payable monthly</li><li>The principal amounts will be payable by the Company on the Final Redemption Date</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/abe4c5ef-41f3-417b-beac-66d49e4e9e4b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Purple Finance Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PNB] Punjab National Bank Fined Rs. 4,85,000 by Reserve Bank of India</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PUNJAB+NATIONAL+BANK&title=Punjab+National+Bank+Fined+Rs.+4%2C85%2C000+by+Reserve+Bank+of+India&newsId=477ed551-715e-4245-bb0c-f96d88095608&token=NDc3ZWQ1NTEtNzE1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">477ed551-715e-4245-bb0c-f96d88095608</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:41:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Punjab National Bank has been imposed a penalty of Rs. 4,85,000 by the Reserve Bank of India. The penalty is a result of a contravention related to shortage of notes at a Currency Chest. The bank is requested to take note of this disclosure made under Regulation 30 of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Punjab National Bank has been fined Rs. 4,85,000 by the Reserve Bank of India.</li><li>The penalty is due to a contravention related to shortage of notes at a Currency Chest.</li><li>The bank is requested to take note of this disclosure made under Regulation 30 of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/683a4580-c0a3-4f05-9839-13dd05a9238b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PUNJAB NATIONAL BANK | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DEEDEV] Dee Development Engineers Ltd: New CFO Appointed After Resignation of Previous Officer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Dee+Development+Engineers+Ltd&title=Dee+Development+Engineers+Ltd%3A+New+CFO+Appointed+After+Resignation+of+Previous+Officer&newsId=01a67605-505e-46a4-b08c-942b5ba14a69&token=MDFhNjc2MDUtNTA1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01a67605-505e-46a4-b08c-942b5ba14a69</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:41:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In a recent board meeting held on 6th January, 2026, Dee Development Engineers Ltd announced the resignation of Mr. Sameer Agarwal as Chief Financial Officer (CFO) and Key Managerial Personnel, effective from close of business hours on 5th January, 2026. Mr. Agarwal resigned due to personal professional priorities and future career plans. The board has approved the appointment of Mr. Brham Prakash Yadav as the new CFO and Key Managerial Personnel, with effect from 7th January, 2026. Mr. Yadav is a seasoned professional with over 30 years of experience in finance, accounts, treasury, taxation, and board-level financial management in large manufacturing organizations. He was previously associated with Munjal Auto Industries Limited as Chief Financial Officer.</p><ul><li>Resignation of Mr. Sameer Agarwal as CFO and Key Managerial Personnel.</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Brham Prakash Yadav as the new CFO and Key Managerial Personnel.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e0c7ec67-a7a5-4a5f-9da4-233be8aca2b4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Dee Development Engineers Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>