<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:40:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[M&amp;M] Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Reports 18% Growth in Auto Sales and 35% Growth in Tractor Sales for February 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MAHINDRA+%26+MAHINDRA+LTD.&title=Mahindra+%26+Mahindra+Reports+18%25+Growth+in+Auto+Sales+and+35%25+Growth+in+Tractor+Sales+for+February+2026&newsId=dfeb1762-c018-4a11-895e-d1bc0a73dd84&token=ZGZlYjE3NjItYzAx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dfeb1762-c018-4a11-895e-d1bc0a73dd84</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Ltd., one of India’s leading automotive companies, announced that its overall auto sales for the month of February 2026 stood at 97,177 vehicles, a growth of 18% including exports. In the Utility Vehicles segment, Mahindra sold 60,018 vehicles in the domestic market, a growth of 19% and overall, 60,685 vehicles, including exports. The domestic sales for Commercial Vehicles stood at 24,585, a growth of 10%. Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Ltd.’s Farm Equipment Business (FEB) reported a robust growth of 35% in domestic tractor sales for February 2026, with total tractor sales (Domestic + Exports) at 34,133 units.</p><ul><li>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra reported an 18% growth in overall auto sales for February 2026, with 97,177 vehicles sold.</li><li>The Utility Vehicles segment saw a 19% growth, with 60,018 vehicles sold in the domestic market.</li><li>Commercial Vehicles and 3 Wheelers sales increased by 10% in the domestic market.</li><li>Mahindra&apos;s Farm Equipment Business reported a 35% growth in domestic tractor sales for February 2026.</li><li>Total tractor sales (Domestic + Exports) for Mahindra&apos;s Farm Equipment Business stood at 34,133 units for February 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/525bbeb1-55b6-41f1-977b-e83a335c96fb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MAHINDRA & MAHINDRA LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDSOYA] SEBI LODR Regulations: Securities Appellate Tribunal Directs Deposit of Rs. 2,06,000 from Apollo Ingredients (Formerly Indsoya Ltd) and Defreezing of Promoters&apos; Demat Accounts</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDSOYA+LTD.&title=SEBI+LODR+Regulations%3A+Securities+Appellate+Tribunal+Directs+Deposit+of+Rs.+2%2C06%2C000+from+Apollo+Ingredients+%28Formerly+Indsoya+Ltd%29+and+Defreezing+of+Promoters%27+Demat+Accounts&newsId=f0d39072-2677-44c9-8307-7ee5f4f26980&token=ZjBkMzkwNzItMjY3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0d39072-2677-44c9-8307-7ee5f4f26980</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:31:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Securities Appellate Tribunal, Mumbai has passed an interim order in the matter of Apollo Ingredients Limited (Formerly Known as Indsoya Limited) versus BSE Limited. The Company had filed an appeal challenging the rejection by BSE Limited of its waiver application in respect of fines imposed by the Exchange. The Tribunal has admitted the appeal, condoned the delay of 69 days, and directed the Company to deposit Rs. 2,06,000 under protest. The Tribunal has also ordered the defreezing of promoters’ demat accounts subject to such deposit. The deposited amount will be kept in an interest-bearing account by BSE and will be subject to the final outcome of the appeal. The matter is listed for further hearing on June 18, 2026. This order does not have any material impact on the financial position, operations, or other activities of the Company, except to the extent of the deposit of Rs. 2,06,000, which remains subject to final adjudication of the Appeal.</p><ul><li>Securities Appellate Tribunal has admitted the appeal filed by Apollo Ingredients (Formerly Indsoya Ltd) challenging the rejection of its waiver application by BSE Limited</li><li>The Tribunal has condoned the delay of 69 days and directed the Company to deposit Rs. 2,06,000 under protest</li><li>The Tribunal has ordered the defreezing of promoters’ demat accounts subject to such deposit</li><li>The deposited amount will be kept in an interest-bearing account by BSE and will be subject to the final outcome of the appeal</li><li>The matter is listed for further hearing on June 18, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/167fe060-5696-4167-8ee8-04ee4343134a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDSOYA LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ABCAPITAL] Aditya Birla Sun Life Insurance Limited&apos;s ₹ 464.81 Crore Tax Demand Nullified by Assessing Officer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Aditya+Birla+Capital+Ltd&title=Aditya+Birla+Sun+Life+Insurance+Limited%27s+%E2%82%B9+464.81+Crore+Tax+Demand+Nullified+by+Assessing+Officer&newsId=3e6dc3d8-0609-42f6-9ec7-bb50355e973e&token=M2U2ZGMzZDgtMDYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e6dc3d8-0609-42f6-9ec7-bb50355e973e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Aditya Birla Capital Ltd. has announced that the Income Tax Appellate Tribunal (ITAT), Mumbai Bench remanded a tax-related matter back to the Assessing Officer (A.O.) for further examination and verification regarding Aditya Birla Sun Life Insurance Limited (ABSLI). The A.O. has now accepted ABSLI&apos;s claim and nullified the entire demand of ₹ 464.81 crore pertaining to AY 21-22.</p><ul><li>Aditya Birla Sun Life Insurance Limited&apos;s ₹ 464.81 crore tax demand nullified by Assessing Officer</li><li>Income Tax Appellate Tribunal (ITAT), Mumbai Bench remanded the matter back to the A.O. for further examination</li><li>Assessing Officer accepted ABSLI&apos;s claim and nullified the tax demand</li><li>Tax demand pertains to Assessment Year 21-22</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d2d49f4a-577c-47c8-852d-7e4d534c089e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Aditya Birla Capital Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RECLTD] REC Ltd Announces Superannuation of Executive Director Dharmendra Nagpal</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=REC+Ltd&title=REC+Ltd+Announces+Superannuation+of+Executive+Director+Dharmendra+Nagpal&newsId=c0310ad5-fef0-4294-88a0-09efd652ec75&token=YzAzMTBhZDUtZmVm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c0310ad5-fef0-4294-88a0-09efd652ec75</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>REC Ltd has announced a change in its Senior Management. Shri Dharmendra Nagpal, the Executive Director of the company, will be superannuating on March 1, 2026. This change is in accordance with Regulation 30 read with Schedule III of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>REC Ltd announces the superannuation of Executive Director, Dharmendra Nagpal.</li><li>Dharmendra Nagpal will be superannuating on March 1, 2026.</li><li>This change is in accordance with SEBI regulations.</li><li>The change is in the Senior Management level of the company.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b02c45f0-24a7-4d67-b1c3-531c6ca86f9d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: REC Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MOIL] Moil Ltd Announces 5% Price Hike for Majority of Manganese Ore Grades in February 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MOIL+LTD.&title=Moil+Ltd+Announces+5%25+Price+Hike+for+Majority+of+Manganese+Ore+Grades+in+February+2026&newsId=7984a164-ee22-4077-9fb8-af8f55d24737&token=Nzk4NGExNjQtZWUy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7984a164-ee22-4077-9fb8-af8f55d24737</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Moil Ltd, stock code NSE — MOIL, BSE - 533286, has announced a revision in the prices of different grades of Manganese Ore for the month of February 2026, effective from 01.02.2026. The prices of all Ferro grades of manganese ore with Manganese content of Mn- 44% and above, SMGR (Mn-30%), Fines grades, and all Chemical grades have been increased by 5%. The prices of SMGR (Mn 25%) grades, SMGR (Mn 20%) grades, and certain Metal Mandi Fines have been continued from the previous month. The basic price of EMD has also remained unchanged. However, the price of UKF532, a type of Metal Mandi Fines, has been increased by 10%.</p><ul><li>5% price increase for Ferro grades of manganese ore with Mn- 44% and above</li><li>5% price increase for SMGR (Mn-30%), Fines grades, and all Chemical grades</li><li>Prices of SMGR (Mn 25%) grades, SMGR (Mn 20%) grades, and certain Metal Mandi Fines continued from the previous month</li><li>10% price increase for UKF532</li><li>Unchanged basic price of EMD</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c8ec97e9-2815-4b18-964d-714613da0359.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MOIL LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NFL] Retirement of National Fertilizers Ltd&apos;s Director (Finance) and CFO, Shri Hira Nand</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NATIONAL+FERTILIZERS+LTD.&title=Retirement+of+National+Fertilizers+Ltd%27s+Director+%28Finance%29+and+CFO%2C+Shri+Hira+Nand&newsId=bb847bbb-d14d-46ce-8222-5d404d393c51&token=YmI4NDdiYmItZDE0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb847bbb-d14d-46ce-8222-5d404d393c51</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>National Fertilizers Ltd (NFL) has announced the retirement of its Director (Finance) and CFO, Shri Hira Nand, as per the regulations of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015. The retirement took effect on 01.03.2026, following his superannuation on 28.02.2026. Shri Hira Nand ceased to be a Director and CFO of NFL from the date of his retirement.</p><ul><li>Shri Hira Nand, Director (Finance) and CFO of National Fertilizers Ltd, has retired.</li><li>The retirement took effect on 01.03.2026 following his superannuation on 28.02.2026.</li><li>Shri Hira Nand ceased to be a Director and CFO of NFL from the date of his retirement.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5ef647b2-c73c-4977-b782-978926bbd838.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NATIONAL FERTILIZERS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RCF] Rashtriya Chemicals and Fertilizers Ltd Announces Senior Management Change: General Manager Sonawane to Superannuate in 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RASHTRIYA+CHEMICALS+%26+FERTILIZERS+LTD.&title=Rashtriya+Chemicals+and+Fertilizers+Ltd+Announces+Senior+Management+Change%3A+General+Manager+Sonawane+to+Superannuate+in+2026&newsId=8958cbf2-14e6-4b46-9cb5-de6f4dc6c716&token=ODk1OGNiZjItMTRl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8958cbf2-14e6-4b46-9cb5-de6f4dc6c716</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rashtriya Chemicals and Fertilizers Ltd has announced a change in its Senior Management. Mr. Anupam Sonawane, the General Manager of Purchase, Contract Cell, MS &amp; IT, will be superannuating on March 1, 2026. This information is shared in accordance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, for the records and kind information of all stakeholders.</p><ul><li>Rashtriya Chemicals and Fertilizers Ltd announces a change in Senior Management</li><li>Mr. Anupam Sonawane, General Manager of Purchase, Contract Cell, MS &amp; IT, to superannuate on March 1, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/df96539e-876a-46f3-9305-c5d14c4e2575.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RASHTRIYA CHEMICALS & FERTILIZERS LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GAIL] Deepak Gupta Assumes Charge as Chairman and Managing Director of Gail (India) Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GAIL+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Deepak+Gupta+Assumes+Charge+as+Chairman+and+Managing+Director+of+Gail+%28India%29+Ltd&newsId=3859c54d-e49a-416b-9c94-307da8613d23&token=Mzg1OWM1NGQtZTQ5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3859c54d-e49a-416b-9c94-307da8613d23</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shri Deepak Gupta, a Mechanical Engineer from Delhi College of Engineering, has taken over as Chairman and Managing Director of Gail (India) Ltd. He has over 35 years of experience in the Oil &amp; Gas value chain and has been leading the execution of multiple high-impact initiatives at GAIL. He also oversees the operation and maintenance of GAIL&apos;s vast network of natural gas and LPG pipelines. Gupta has been instrumental in many digital transformation initiatives and has played a pivotal role in strategic goal setting and corporate governance in GAIL&apos;s JVs. He has also led many large cross-functional teams to execute landmark projects under complex and challenging conditions.</p><ul><li>Shri Deepak Gupta assumes charge as Chairman and Managing Director of Gail (India) Ltd.</li><li>Gupta has over 35 years of experience in the Oil &amp; Gas value chain.</li><li>He is leading the execution of multiple high-impact initiatives at GAIL.</li><li>Gupta oversees the operation and maintenance of GAIL&apos;s vast network of natural gas and LPG pipelines.</li><li>He has played a pivotal role in strategic goal setting and corporate governance in GAIL&apos;s JVs.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4d565944-c9b5-4772-95c8-d4f2aa6f4e2a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GAIL (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ESCORTS] Escorts Kubota Ltd Reports 20.4% Growth in Tractor Sales and 4.8% Rise in Construction Equipment Sales in February 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Escorts+Kubota+Ltd&title=Escorts+Kubota+Ltd+Reports+20.4%25+Growth+in+Tractor+Sales+and+4.8%25+Rise+in+Construction+Equipment+Sales+in+February+2026&newsId=ead61c6a-efa9-426c-a0d9-2697e19348e0&token=ZWFkNjFjNmEtZWZh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ead61c6a-efa9-426c-a0d9-2697e19348e0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Escorts Kubota Limited Agri Machinery Business sold 10,339 tractors in February 2026, a 20.4% growth compared to 8,590 tractors sold in February 2025. Domestic tractor sales contributed significantly to the growth with a 22.1% increase. The construction equipment business also experienced a steady growth of 4.8% in February 2026. The positive trend is expected to continue due to favorable government policies, GST reduction, and a promising outlook for the Rabi season.</p><ul><li>Escorts Kubota Limited reported a 20.4% growth in tractor sales in February 2026</li><li>Domestic tractor sales increased by 22.1%</li><li>Construction equipment sales grew by 4.8% in February 2026</li><li>The positive trend is expected to continue due to favorable government policies and a promising outlook for the Rabi season</li><li>The company is committed to excellence in engineering, innovation in products, and development of market-relevant technologies</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7dc7a7f9-9082-45c7-973d-cb42f294027e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Escorts Kubota Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GAIL] Gail (India) Ltd: Shri Sandeep Kumar Gupta Superannuates as Chairman and Managing Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GAIL+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Gail+%28India%29+Ltd%3A+Shri+Sandeep+Kumar+Gupta+Superannuates+as+Chairman+and+Managing+Director&newsId=891e4803-f4ac-4802-805c-498e94ef7634&token=ODkxZTQ4MDMtZjRh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">891e4803-f4ac-4802-805c-498e94ef7634</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 06:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gail (India) Ltd has announced that Shri Sandeep Kumar Gupta ceased to be Chairman and Managing Director of the Company with effect from 01.03.2026. This announcement comes following his superannuation on 28.02.2026 from the services of GAIL.</p><ul><li>Shri Sandeep Kumar Gupta has superannuated from his position as Chairman and Managing Director of Gail (India) Ltd.</li><li>His tenure ended on 01.03.2026, following his superannuation from GAIL on 28.02.2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b61e2753-5907-402d-87e3-af6f71921e98.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GAIL (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>