<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 18:28:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[UNIABEXAL] Uni Abex Alloy Products Ltd Receives Rs. 257.88 Crore from Land Sale in Thane</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=UNI+ABEX+ALLOY+PRODUCTS+LTD.&title=Uni+Abex+Alloy+Products+Ltd+Receives+Rs.+257.88+Crore+from+Land+Sale+in+Thane&newsId=bc9d4941-7e7d-4729-a639-fcc0ecfb4ea0&token=YmM5ZDQ5NDEtN2U3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc9d4941-7e7d-4729-a639-fcc0ecfb4ea0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 17:11:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Sale</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Uni Abex Alloy Products Ltd has informed about the completion of the sale of its land at Thane. The company has received the entire sale proceeds of approximately Rs. 257.88 crore, which includes an advance amount of Rs. 48.85 crore and an additional amount of Rs. 13.65 crore for an additional area of 2,008 sq mts. Post this sale, the company now holds only a marginal area of 2,520 sq mtrs of Thane Land.</p><ul><li>Uni Abex Alloy Products Ltd has completed the sale of its land at Thane</li><li>The company has received the entire sale proceeds of approximately Rs. 257.88 crore</li><li>This includes an advance amount of Rs. 48.85 crore and an additional amount of Rs. 13.65 crore for an additional area of 2,008 sq mts</li><li>Post sale, the company now holds only a marginal area of 2,520 sq mtrs of Thane Land</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/367ba6f9-5ece-44b4-a69e-e91c25ff5654.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: UNI ABEX ALLOY PRODUCTS LTD. | Category: Sale</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HEG] HEG Ltd. Violates SEBI Regulations: Designated Persons&apos; Trading Infringements</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HEG+LTD.&title=HEG+Ltd.+Violates+SEBI+Regulations%3A+Designated+Persons%27+Trading+Infringements&newsId=bbdc79e0-7358-43e0-b5ee-811a5604994e&token=YmJkYzc5ZTAtNzM1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bbdc79e0-7358-43e0-b5ee-811a5604994e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 17:02:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>HEG Ltd. has reported violations of the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, and its Code of Conduct for Regulating, Monitoring &amp; Reporting Trading by Insiders. The violations were committed by designated persons in accordance with SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/ISD/ISD/CIR/P/2020/135 dated July 23, 2020. The violations include trading without pre-clearance, contra trade, and non-disclosure of transactions to the Company. The Company has advised the concerned persons to sell their entire equity shares of HEG Limited and deposit the sale proceeds into the designated account of the SEBI. The Company has also directed the concerned persons to inform their Portfolio Management Services (PMS) provider or broker to place the scrip of HEG Limited on the restricted/negative list.</p><ul><li>HEG Ltd. reports violations of SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, and its Code of Conduct for Regulating, Monitoring &amp; Reporting Trading by Insiders.</li><li>Designated persons committed violations involving trading without pre-clearance, contra trade, and non-disclosure of transactions to the Company.</li><li>Company directs concerned persons to sell their entire equity shares of HEG Limited and deposit the sale proceeds into the designated account of the SEBI.</li><li>Company advises concerned persons to inform their PMS provider or broker to place the scrip of HEG Limited on the restricted/negative list.</li><li>Corrective and preventive measures are taken to ensure regulatory compliance, uphold corporate governance, and maintain market integrity.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e9c28a64-1874-4479-b328-142d19838066.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HEG LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GRERENEW] GRE Renew Enertech Ltd Appoints M/s Vivek J. Vakharia &amp; Associates as Secretarial Auditor for Five Financial Years</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GRE+Renew+Enertech+Ltd&title=GRE+Renew+Enertech+Ltd+Appoints+M%2Fs+Vivek+J.+Vakharia+%26+Associates+as+Secretarial+Auditor+for+Five+Financial+Years&newsId=d985c883-f0e2-4e80-a24b-d1d10f932c87&token=ZDk4NWM4ODMtZjBl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d985c883-f0e2-4e80-a24b-d1d10f932c87</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:41:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Expansion</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>GRE Renew Enertech Ltd has appointed M/s Vivek J. Vakharia &amp; Associates, Practicing Company Secretaries, as the Secretarial Auditor of the Company for one term of five (5) consecutive financial years, i.e., from FY 2025-26 to FY 2029-30. The appointment is subject to approval of the Members of the Company at the ensuing Annual General Meeting. M/s Vivek J. Vakharia &amp; Associates is a Peer Reviewed Firm of Practicing Company Secretaries with extensive experience in Corporate, Securities and Regulatory laws.</p><ul><li>GRE Renew Enertech Ltd appoints M/s Vivek J. Vakharia &amp; Associates as Secretarial Auditor</li><li>The appointment is for a term of five (5) consecutive financial years from FY 2025-26 to FY 2029-30</li><li>The appointment is subject to approval of the Members at the ensuing Annual General Meeting</li><li>M/s Vivek J. Vakharia &amp; Associates is a Peer Reviewed Firm of Practicing Company Secretaries</li><li>The firm specializes in listing of securities on recognized stock exchanges and provides periodic and event-based compliances under various SEBI regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ae52d307-4190-4264-8b23-8d2dbf724cca.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GRE Renew Enertech Ltd | Category: Expansion</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VADILALIND] Vadilal Industries Independent Director, Shivakumar Dega, Resigns Over Non-Compliance with Minimum Wage Act</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VADILAL+INDUSTRIES+LTD.-%24&title=Vadilal+Industries+Independent+Director%2C+Shivakumar+Dega%2C+Resigns+Over+Non-Compliance+with+Minimum+Wage+Act&newsId=021cc1da-d2a1-49bb-a58a-2c023162d54e&token=MDIxY2MxZGEtZDJh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">021cc1da-d2a1-49bb-a58a-2c023162d54e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Vadilal Industries Ltd. announced the resignation of its independent director, Mr. Shivakumar Dega, due to the company&apos;s non-compliance with the Minimum Wages Act 1948 and Code of Wages 2019. Mr. Dega expressed his concerns in his resignation letter dated February 17, 2026, stating that the company has been paying its factory workers less than the minimum wage, which is a serious offence under Indian law. This violation has resulted in potential legal action for forced labour under Article 23 of the Indian Constitution. Despite raising the issue in several meetings and putting it down in writing, the board has not acted in the interests of all shareholders and the factory workers. The company is trying to stretch this liability over 2 to 4 years, which Mr. Dega strongly opposes. The board, however, seems unhappy with Mr. Dega for raising the minimum wage issue.</p><ul><li>Vadilal Industries independent director, Mr. Shivakumar Dega, resigns over non-compliance with Minimum Wages Act 1948 and Code of Wages 2019.</li><li>Company has been paying its factory workers less than the minimum wage, a serious offence under Indian law.</li><li>Potential legal action for forced labour under Article 23 of the Indian Constitution.</li><li>Despite raising the issue in several meetings, the board has not acted in the interests of all shareholders and the factory workers.</li><li>Company trying to stretch this liability over 2 to 4 years, which Mr. Dega strongly opposes.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b0290b9a-88bf-421a-8657-a3a1ad0ffb5f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VADILAL INDUSTRIES LTD.-$ | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DELPHIFX] Delphi World Money Ltd: Board Approves Q3 Results, Next Phase of Travel Business Growth, and Seeks Shareholder Approval for Certain Decisions</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Delphi+World+Money+Ltd&title=Delphi+World+Money+Ltd%3A+Board+Approves+Q3+Results%2C+Next+Phase+of+Travel+Business+Growth%2C+and+Seeks+Shareholder+Approval+for+Certain+Decisions&newsId=40f9b7e0-ca0a-45b2-a907-0414fa33d75d&token=NDBmOWI3ZTAtY2Ew</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40f9b7e0-ca0a-45b2-a907-0414fa33d75d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:13:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Delphi World Money Ltd. announced its Q3 results, approved the next phase of growth for its travel, hospitality, and related businesses, and sought shareholder approval for various management decisions through a postal ballot. The company reported a net profit after tax from continued operations of ₹236 crore and other comprehensive income of ₹2648 crore. The Board also addressed certain observations from the Limited Review Report and noted a material related party transaction that required shareholder approval.</p><ul><li>Delphi World Money Ltd. reported a net profit after tax from continued operations of ₹236 crore for Q3 ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The company announced other comprehensive income of ₹2648 crore for the same period.</li><li>The Board approved the next phase of growth for the company&apos;s travel, hospitality, and related businesses.</li><li>Delphi World Money Ltd. seeks shareholder approval for various management decisions through a postal ballot.</li><li>The company addressed certain observations from the Limited Review Report and noted a material related party transaction requiring shareholder approval.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9894886f-0651-433c-b60e-a6cf42d1ad12.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Delphi World Money Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DELPHIFX] Delphi World Money Ltd: Board Approves Q3 Results, Next Phase of Travel Business Growth, and Seeks Shareholder Approval for Certain Decisions</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Delphi+World+Money+Ltd&title=Delphi+World+Money+Ltd%3A+Board+Approves+Q3+Results%2C+Next+Phase+of+Travel+Business+Growth%2C+and+Seeks+Shareholder+Approval+for+Certain+Decisions&newsId=629c50ca-a91c-4f00-990b-8c167327e0ef&token=NjI5YzUwY2EtYTkx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">629c50ca-a91c-4f00-990b-8c167327e0ef</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:13:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Delphi World Money Ltd, in its recent board meeting, approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The board also discussed the next phase of growth for the company&apos;s travel, hospitality, and related businesses, and sought shareholder approval for various management decisions through a postal ballot. The company is taking steps to enhance operational alignment, optimize structural efficiency, and expand market reach for both domestic and international operations.</p><ul><li>Delphi World Money Ltd announced its unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The board discussed the next phase of growth for the company&apos;s travel, hospitality, and related businesses.</li><li>The company is seeking shareholder approval for various management decisions through a postal ballot.</li><li>Delphi World Money Ltd is focusing on enhancing operational alignment, optimizing structural efficiency, and expanding market reach.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ce61a842-de99-40f3-89d9-ae113b37e6ff.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Delphi World Money Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GRERENEW] GRE Renew Enertech Ltd Appoints M/s. P.C. Rathod &amp; Co. as Internal Auditor for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GRE+Renew+Enertech+Ltd&title=GRE+Renew+Enertech+Ltd+Appoints+M%2Fs.+P.C.+Rathod+%26+Co.+as+Internal+Auditor+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=76adf070-4773-4a0e-b16b-b58b6ab4dd7b&token=NzZhZGYwNzAtNDc3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76adf070-4773-4a0e-b16b-b58b6ab4dd7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Expansion</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>GRE Renew Enertech Ltd, formerly known as GRE Renew Enertech Private Limited, has appointed M/s. P.C. Rathod &amp; Co., Chartered Accountants, Ahmedabad as the Internal Auditor for the Financial Year 2025-26. The appointment was approved at the Board of Directors meeting held on 21 February 2026. M/s. P.C. Rathod &amp; Co. is a firm registered with the Institute of Chartered Accountants of India with nearly 50 years of professional experience in audit and assurance services. The firm has a strong reputation in the field and is empanelled with the Comptroller and Auditor General of India and various banks. It provides a wide range of professional services including Internal Audit, Statutory Audit, Tax Audit, Bank Audit, Financial Reporting &amp; Various Advisory Services.</p><ul><li>GRE Renew Enertech Ltd appoints M/s. P.C. Rathod &amp; Co. as Internal Auditor for FY 2025-26</li><li>The appointment was approved at the Board of Directors meeting held on 21 February 2026</li><li>M/s. P.C. Rathod &amp; Co. is a firm with nearly 50 years of professional experience in audit and assurance services</li><li>The firm is empanelled with the Comptroller and Auditor General of India and various banks</li><li>M/s. P.C. Rathod &amp; Co. provides a wide range of professional services including Internal Audit, Statutory Audit, Tax Audit, Bank Audit, Financial Reporting &amp; Various Advisory Services</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1dfacf8d-dbd9-4bba-8be1-c384536dd1f9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GRE Renew Enertech Ltd | Category: Expansion</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STANCAP] Standard Capital Markets Ltd Redeems Rs 850000000 Worth of 10% Secured Non-Convertible Debentures</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=STANDARD+CAPITAL+MARKETS+LTD.&title=Standard+Capital+Markets+Ltd+Redeems+Rs+850000000+Worth+of+10%25+Secured+Non-Convertible+Debentures&newsId=a7def725-fff7-4dc1-a368-3d117f6f203b&token=YTdkZWY3MjUtZmZm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a7def725-fff7-4dc1-a368-3d117f6f203b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 16:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Standard Capital Markets Ltd has successfully redeemed its 8500 NCDs, amounting to Rs 850000000, in compliance with Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosures Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The redemption was approved by the Board of Directors in a circulation held on February 21, 2026. The Secured, Unlisted, Unrated, Redeemable Non-convertible Debentures, with a face value of Rs. 100,000/-, were allotted to the holder during the period from 30th October, 2024 to 14th February, 2025. The Company has undertaken this redemption as per the terms and conditions laid down at the time of issue. The balance post redemption of 10% Secured Non-Convertible Debentures is now 48,702 Debentures.</p><ul><li>Standard Capital Markets Ltd redeemed Rs 850000000 worth of 10% Secured Non-Convertible Debentures.</li><li>The redemption was approved by the Board of Directors in a circulation held on February 21, 2026.</li><li>The Debentures were allotted to the holder from 30th October, 2024 to 14th February, 2025.</li><li>The redemption was undertaken as per the terms and conditions laid down at the time of issue.</li><li>The balance post redemption of 10% Secured Non-Convertible Debentures is now 48,702 Debentures.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/13a051fa-f59a-4cce-badb-3674217c9fca.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: STANDARD CAPITAL MARKETS LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GRERENEW] GRE Renew Enertech Ltd Approves Transfer of Ownership for Partially Developed Solar Power Project</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GRE+Renew+Enertech+Ltd&title=GRE+Renew+Enertech+Ltd+Approves+Transfer+of+Ownership+for+Partially+Developed+Solar+Power+Project&newsId=17c8e6f0-a38a-4560-ac6d-89ded1a7af26&token=MTdjOGU2ZjAtYTM4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17c8e6f0-a38a-4560-ac6d-89ded1a7af26</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>GRE Renew Enertech Ltd has approved the transfer of ownership and execution of a settlement agreement with Mehsana Dairy and Food Products Limited for a partially developed solar power project. The transfer is due to the withdrawal of the party from the project. Upon completion, the project will be recognized in the company&apos;s books as stock-in-trade or project work-in-progress, pending its onward sale and execution of the balance Engineering, Procurement and Construction (EPC) scope. The company has also received board approval for the proposed onward sale or transfer of the said partially developed solar power project to an identified potential client, subject to finalization and execution of definitive agreements.</p><ul><li>GRE Renew Enertech Ltd approves transfer of ownership for a partially developed solar power project.</li><li>The transfer is due to the withdrawal of Mehsana Dairy and Food Products Limited from the project.</li><li>Upon completion, the project will be recognized in the company&apos;s books as stock-in-trade or project work-in-progress.</li><li>The company has received board approval for the proposed onward sale or transfer of the project to an identified potential client.</li><li>The transfer and proposed sale are in the ordinary course of business of the company.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7fcd5ef7-1e56-4931-aab0-2b59306b98bf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GRE Renew Enertech Ltd | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VASWANI] Vaswani Industries Ltd: Board Meeting for Q3 FY 2025-26 Financial Results Rescheduled</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VASWANI+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Vaswani+Industries+Ltd%3A+Board+Meeting+for+Q3+FY+2025-26+Financial+Results+Rescheduled&newsId=2270064a-bc4c-44a3-a3f1-7daac9562940&token=MjI3MDA2NGEtYmM0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2270064a-bc4c-44a3-a3f1-7daac9562940</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:21:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vaswani Industries Ltd has announced the rescheduling of their Board Meeting, initially planned for February 13, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The meeting could not be concluded due to non-finalisation of the financial statements, leading to its cancellation. The new date for the Board Meeting is Saturday, February 28, 2026. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the company will remain closed for all Directors, Key Managerial Personnel, Designated Employees, and other Covered Persons under the Company’s Code of Conduct for Prevention of Insider Trading till 48 hours after the conclusion of the Board Meeting, i.e., up to March 01, 2026.</p><ul><li>Vaswani Industries Ltd reschedules Board Meeting to February 28, 2026, for Q3 FY 2025-26 financial results approval.</li><li>The initial Board Meeting on February 13, 2026, could not be concluded due to non-finalisation of financial statements and was subsequently cancelled.</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the company&apos;s securities to remain closed till 48 hours after the Board Meeting, i.e., up to March 01, 2026.</li><li>The unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, will be considered and approved during the rescheduled Board Meeting.</li><li>Directors, Key Managerial Personnel, Designated Employees, and other Covered Persons under the Company’s Code of Conduct for Prevention of Insider Trading are affected by the trading window closure.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4d51ad3d-54a2-4962-9246-8411bca1cd3a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VASWANI INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>