<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:36:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[AEQUS] Aequs Limited Executes Letter of Subscription for Joint Venture with Ajna Aerospace &amp; Defence Private Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Aequs+Ltd&title=Aequs+Limited+Executes+Letter+of+Subscription+for+Joint+Venture+with+Ajna+Aerospace+%26+Defence+Private+Limited&newsId=b5135fab-bf0d-463a-95c0-30063da61f35&token=YjUxMzVmYWItYmYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5135fab-bf0d-463a-95c0-30063da61f35</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Aequs Limited has executed a Letter of Subscription (LOS) on February 27, 2026, pursuant to a Joint Venture Agreement and Shareholders’ Agreement dated January 16, 2026. The agreement is with Accel India VIII (Mauritius) Ltd, Vagus Defence Tech &amp; Aerospace Fund, and Ajna Aerospace &amp; Defence Private Limited. Aequs will invest INR 10,01,00,000 in Ajna Aerospace &amp; Defence Private Limited (AADPL) for a 33.33% shareholding on a fully diluted basis. AADPL is a newly incorporated company involved in sourcing, acquiring, licensing intellectual property rights for unmanned aerial vehicles, developing own IP, and manufacturing, assembling, testing, marketing, and selling unmanned aerial vehicles and related products in India and internationally.</p><ul><li>Aequs Limited has executed a Letter of Subscription (LOS) for a Joint Venture with Ajna Aerospace &amp; Defence Private Limited.</li><li>The investment amount is INR 10,01,00,000 for a 33.33% shareholding on a fully diluted basis.</li><li>Ajna Aerospace &amp; Defence Private Limited is a newly incorporated company involved in unmanned aerial vehicles and related products.</li><li>The joint venture is part of Aequs Limited&apos;s growth strategy seeking attractive inorganic opportunities.</li><li>Ajna Aerospace &amp; Defence Private Limited has a presence in India.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/09ab6488-b7ef-4414-bff1-077c9aa2be9c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Aequs Ltd | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SJS] S.J.S. Enterprises Ltd Acquires 2.08% Stake in DB Renews Private Limited for INR 72 Lakhs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=S.J.S.+Enterprises+Ltd&title=S.J.S.+Enterprises+Ltd+Acquires+2.08%25+Stake+in+DB+Renews+Private+Limited+for+INR+72+Lakhs&newsId=5295467f-23e9-4f7c-a00c-76302511ef22&token=NTI5NTQ2N2YtMjNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5295467f-23e9-4f7c-a00c-76302511ef22</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>S.J.S. Enterprises Ltd has entered into a Share Purchase, Shareholders’ Agreement and Energy Purchase Agreement with M/s. Doddanavar Global Energy Private Limited and M/s. DB Renews Private Limited. The company has subscribed to 28,800 equity shares of face value of INR 250/- each of M/s DB Renews Private Limited, amounting to a total consideration of INR 72,00,000/-. This represents 2.08% of the Equity Share Capital of M/s. DB Renews Private Limited. DB Renews Private Limited is a private company incorporated under the Companies Act, 1956 on November 18, 2011, to setup Wind Generation Power Plant. The company is a subsidiary of M/s. Doddanavar Global Energy Private Limited with a turnover of INR 24.08 Crore in FY 2024-25.</p><ul><li>S.J.S. Enterprises Ltd acquires 2.08% stake in DB Renews Private Limited</li><li>Total consideration of INR 72,00,000/- for 28,800 equity shares</li><li>DB Renews Private Limited is a wind power generation company</li><li>Post-acquisition, S.J.S. Enterprises Ltd will become a captive consumer</li><li>DB Renews Private Limited is a subsidiary of Doddanavar Global Energy Private Limited with a turnover of INR 24.08 Crore in FY 2024-25</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/81fd0c0f-f62e-413f-8b7c-964f7e702608.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: S.J.S. Enterprises Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ORIENTCQ] AG Ventures Ltd. Appoints Mr. Dhruv Ranjan as Additional Non-Executive, Non-Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ORIENTAL+CARBON+%26+CHEMICALS+LTD.-%24&title=AG+Ventures+Ltd.+Appoints+Mr.+Dhruv+Ranjan+as+Additional+Non-Executive%2C+Non-Independent+Director&newsId=e5c49b14-ed22-4f5e-8f5d-77e5c5410fc2&token=ZTVjNDliMTQtZWQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5c49b14-ed22-4f5e-8f5d-77e5c5410fc2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:33:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of AG Ventures Ltd. has approved the appointment of Mr. Dhruv Ranjan as an Additional Director designated as a Non-Executive, Non-Independent Director, effective February 27, 2026. Mr. Ranjan holds an MBA degree and has nearly a decade of experience in venture capital. He has been associated with Anicut Capital’s early-stage investment platform and is currently part of the Investor Relations team at Anicut Capital. Mr. Ranjan is not related to any Director of the Company and is not debarred from holding the office of Director by virtue of any order of SEBI or any other authority.</p><ul><li>AG Ventures Ltd. has appointed Mr. Dhruv Ranjan as an Additional Director.</li><li>Mr. Ranjan will serve as a Non-Executive, Non-Independent Director.</li><li>Mr. Ranjan has nearly a decade of experience in venture capital.</li><li>He is currently part of the Investor Relations team at Anicut Capital.</li><li>Mr. Ranjan is not related to any Director of the Company and is not debarred from holding the office of Director.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/83827c0d-2cde-437c-b0a0-100f782f2aa3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ORIENTAL CARBON & CHEMICALS LTD.-$ | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ORIENTBELL] Sarla Daga Acquires Shares in Orient Bell Ltd., Increasing Holdings to 15.55%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ORIENT+BELL+LIMITED-%24&title=Sarla+Daga+Acquires+Shares+in+Orient+Bell+Ltd.%2C+Increasing+Holdings+to+15.55%25&newsId=6e3095a3-de9e-491c-9075-93d1b840cd9f&token=NmUzMDk1YTMtZGU5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6e3095a3-de9e-491c-9075-93d1b840cd9f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sarla Daga, a promoter of Orient Bell Ltd., has disclosed her shareholding under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. Daga has acquired 0.02% additional shares, increasing her total holding from 15.48% to 15.55%. The acquisition took place on the National Stock Exchange of India Ltd. and BSE Ltd. The total equity share capital and total voting capital of the company have slightly increased after the acquisition.</p><ul><li>Sarla Daga, a promoter of Orient Bell Ltd., has acquired additional shares.</li><li>The acquisition increased Daga&apos;s holding from 15.48% to 15.55%.</li><li>The acquisition took place on the National Stock Exchange of India Ltd. and BSE Ltd.</li><li>The total equity share capital and total voting capital of the company have slightly increased.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1FF74FEB_916B_4BA0_9349_D3DC62185E98_144922.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ORIENT BELL LIMITED-$ | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GROVY] Grovy India Ltd Files ITAT Appeal Against INR 119.24 Lakhs Tax Demand</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Grovy+India+Ltd&title=Grovy+India+Ltd+Files+ITAT+Appeal+Against+INR+119.24+Lakhs+Tax+Demand&newsId=9301efce-e8b2-4730-b6d6-ad2465e56bb3&token=OTMwMWVmY2UtZThi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9301efce-e8b2-4730-b6d6-ad2465e56bb3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Grovy India Ltd has filed an appeal before the Income Tax Appellate Tribunal (ITAT) against the order passed by the Commissioner of Income Tax (Appeals) under Section 250 of the Income-tax Act, 1961. The order pertains to a tax demand of INR 119.24 Lakhs, comprising INR 78.00 Lakhs towards tax and INR 41.24 Lakhs towards interest. This disclosure is in compliance with the applicable provisions of Schedule III of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Grovy India Ltd has filed an appeal with the Income Tax Appellate Tribunal (ITAT)</li><li>The appeal is against an order passed by the Commissioner of Income Tax (Appeals) under Section 250 of the Income-tax Act, 1961</li><li>The order pertains to a tax demand of INR 119.24 Lakhs</li><li>The tax demand includes INR 78.00 Lakhs towards tax and INR 41.24 Lakhs towards interest</li><li>The disclosure is in compliance with the applicable provisions of Schedule III of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/81d4b37a-9b57-4908-80cb-0bae1c18d1d1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Grovy India Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZYDUSLIFE] Zydus Lifesciences Announces Successful Clinical Development of Pembrolizumab Biosimilar FYB206, Marking a Milestone Toward USFDA Filing</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Zydus+Lifesciences+Ltd&title=Zydus+Lifesciences+Announces+Successful+Clinical+Development+of+Pembrolizumab+Biosimilar+FYB206%2C+Marking+a+Milestone+Toward+USFDA+Filing&newsId=7d8a0fde-5f5b-4d06-8530-6f7b84e04590&token=N2Q4YTBmZGUtNWY1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7d8a0fde-5f5b-4d06-8530-6f7b84e04590</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:28:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>USFDA</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Zydus Lifesciences, an innovation-led life-sciences company, has announced the successful clinical development of its Pembrolizumab biosimilar, FYB206. The pivotal Dahlia pharmacokinetic study has demonstrated pharmacokinetic equivalence with the oncology blockbuster drug Keytruda®. Zydus has in-licensed FYB206 exclusively from Formycon AG for the U.S. and Canadian markets. The positive clinical data marks a key milestone in the collaboration between Zydus and Formycon, reflecting their shared commitment to expand access to affordable, life-saving oncology treatments. Formycon is now focusing on completing all development activities to finalize the documents for regulatory approval, with the aim of making FYB206 available as soon as possible after the exclusivity of the reference drug expires.</p><ul><li>Zydus Lifesciences has successfully completed the clinical development of its Pembrolizumab biosimilar, FYB206.</li><li>The pivotal Dahlia pharmacokinetic study has demonstrated pharmacokinetic equivalence with the oncology blockbuster drug Keytruda®.</li><li>Zydus has in-licensed FYB206 exclusively from Formycon AG for the U.S. and Canadian markets.</li><li>Formycon is focusing on completing all development activities to finalize the documents for regulatory approval.</li><li>The aim is to make FYB206 available as soon as possible after the exclusivity of the reference drug expires.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/46be72f3-9095-4dd4-a9a9-e1e42cfdbacd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Zydus Lifesciences Ltd | Category: USFDA</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CAMEXLTD] Nahata Khushii Rajesh Acquires 0.03% Stake in Camex Ltd Through Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CAMEX+LTD.&title=Nahata+Khushii+Rajesh+Acquires+0.03%25+Stake+in+Camex+Ltd+Through+Open+Market&newsId=753c2088-b607-4f4d-87a7-ed31bac59e3c&token=NzUzYzIwODgtYjYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">753c2088-b607-4f4d-87a7-ed31bac59e3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:25:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Nahata Khushii Rajesh has purchased 3460 equity shares of Camex Ltd, amounting to 0.03% of the company&apos;s total share capital. This acquisition was made through the open market, as per the disclosure under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</p><ul><li>Nahata Khushii Rajesh purchased 3460 equity shares of Camex Ltd.</li><li>The acquisition amounts to 0.03% of Camex Ltd&apos;s total share capital.</li><li>The purchase was made through the open market.</li><li>The total equity share capital of Camex Ltd is Rs. 10,20,87,000.</li><li>The acquisition was disclosed under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0434CA75_EEED_4F69_A9BF_F044D7E4E2F4_145154.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CAMEX LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SKYGOLD] Sky Gold &amp; Diamonds Ltd. Monetizes Land Asset, Shifts to Asset-Light Expansion Model</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sky+Gold+Ltd&title=Sky+Gold+%26+Diamonds+Ltd.+Monetizes+Land+Asset%2C+Shifts+to+Asset-Light+Expansion+Model&newsId=0ce71dbe-f8ff-4fb0-907d-43c57e00fe29&token=MGNlNzFkYmUtZjhm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ce71dbe-f8ff-4fb0-907d-43c57e00fe29</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:25:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Sky Gold &amp; Diamonds Ltd, one of India’s fastest-growing B2B jewellery manufacturers, has announced a strategic shift in its capacity expansion roadmap under its Sky Gold 3.0 vision. The company has decided to monetize the land it had acquired for a greenfield manufacturing facility and transition to a more agile, asset-light expansion model. This strategic shift is expected to enable faster execution, improved capital efficiency, and reduced borrowings by over 20% in FY27. The company is also committed to ensuring growth and cash flow progress in tandem, targeting to become net debt free by FY30.</p><ul><li>Sky Gold &amp; Diamonds Ltd to monetize land worth INR 105 crore, shifting to an asset-light expansion model.</li><li>The strategic shift is expected to improve capital efficiency and reduce borrowings by over 20% in FY27.</li><li>The company will scale capacity through leased manufacturing facilities, enabling faster execution.</li><li>Sky Gold remains committed to ensuring growth and cash flow progress in tandem, targeting to become net debt free by FY30.</li><li>The proposed land sale is targeted for completion within six months, with a commitment from the promoter family to acquire the land if the transaction is not concluded within this period.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ebda18c2-9bf8-4b06-aa66-1aaebb71ddfe.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sky Gold Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TEAMLEASE] Mirae Asset Mutual Fund Acquires 0.95% Stake in TeamLease Services Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TeamLease+Services+Ltd&title=Mirae+Asset+Mutual+Fund+Acquires+0.95%25+Stake+in+TeamLease+Services+Ltd&newsId=a26d181a-473a-4064-a8cb-975de259ee4e&token=YTI2ZDE4MWEtNDcz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a26d181a-473a-4064-a8cb-975de259ee4e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:25:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mirae Asset Mutual Fund has acquired 160,000 shares carrying voting rights in TeamLease Services Ltd, amounting to 0.95% of the total share capital. This acquisition was made on February 26, 2026. Before the acquisition, Mirae Asset Mutual Fund held 6.88% of the total share capital. After the acquisition, their holding increased to 7.83%. This acquisition was made through the open market.</p><ul><li>Mirae Asset Mutual Fund acquires 0.95% stake in TeamLease Services Ltd</li><li>160,000 shares carrying voting rights acquired</li><li>Acquisition made on February 26, 2026</li><li>Total holding increases to 7.83%</li><li>Open market acquisition</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/95DDA1CA_2197_414E_99D2_B5F506B8AA66_144702.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TeamLease Services Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CAMEXLTD] Nahata Khushii Rajesh Acquires 0.03% Stake in Camex Ltd for Rs. 10,20,87,000</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CAMEX+LTD.&title=Nahata+Khushii+Rajesh+Acquires+0.03%25+Stake+in+Camex+Ltd+for+Rs.+10%2C20%2C87%2C000&newsId=48755620-09de-43ae-8ecd-1c6e94d14c0c&token=NDg3NTU2MjAtMDlk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48755620-09de-43ae-8ecd-1c6e94d14c0c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 09:23:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Nahata Khushii Rajesh has purchased 2731 equity shares of Camex Ltd through open market, amounting to 0.03% of the total diluted share/voting capital. The purchase was made for a total amount of Rs. 10,20,87,000, which consists of 1,02,08,700 equity shares of Rs. 10/- each. Before the sale/purchase, Nahata Khushii Rajesh held 0.24% of the total share/voting capital. After the acquisition, the holding has increased to 0.26%.</p><ul><li>Nahata Khushii Rajesh acquires 0.03% stake in Camex Ltd</li><li>Purchase made through open market for Rs. 10,20,87,000</li><li>Acquisition consists of 1,02,08,700 equity shares of Rs. 10/- each</li><li>Before the acquisition, Nahata Khushii Rajesh held 0.24% of the total share/voting capital</li><li>After the acquisition, the holding has increased to 0.26%</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/F00C3588_DEE2_4AF7_9A8D_6B0AAA7B776C_145032.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CAMEX LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>