<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:36:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[INDRAIND] Bluegod Entertainment Ltd. Approves Rights Issue of 10,54,24,650 Shares at Rs. 3.00 Each</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Indra+Industries+Ltd&title=Bluegod+Entertainment+Ltd.+Approves+Rights+Issue+of+10%2C54%2C24%2C650+Shares+at+Rs.+3.00+Each&newsId=7d74cf33-ac1e-42d2-a9fc-c5fe8dff25ea&token=N2Q3NGNmMzMtYWMx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7d74cf33-ac1e-42d2-a9fc-c5fe8dff25ea</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:22:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>The Board of Directors of Bluegod Entertainment Limited, at their meeting held on 28th February, 2026, approved the terms of a Rights Issue. The company will issue 10,54,24,650 fully paid-up equity shares at a price of Rs. 3.00 each, which includes a securities premium of Rs. 2.00 per equity share, amounting to a total issue size of Rs. 31,62,73,950. The record date for the Rights Issue is 6th March, 2026, and the Rights Issue period is from 12th March, 2026 to 19th March, 2026. The company has also executed a Term Sheet with Absolute Legends Sports Private Limited for the transfer of Intellectual Property Rights related to Legends League Cricket. However, the company has decided not to proceed with the acquisition or operation of any team in the Legends Cricket League at this stage.</p><ul><li>Bluegod Entertainment Ltd. approves Rights Issue of 10,54,24,650 shares at Rs. 3.00 each</li><li>Issue price includes a securities premium of Rs. 2.00 per equity share</li><li>Record date set as 6th March, 2026</li><li>Rights Issue period from 12th March, 2026 to 19th March, 2026</li><li>Company executes Term Sheet with Absolute Legends Sports Private Limited for transfer of Intellectual Property Rights related to Legends League Cricket</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/13dadbe2-ffee-4388-91b2-ae395f0a240e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Indra Industries Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHILINDORE] Sayaji Hotels (Indore) Ltd: Operational Creditor Seeks Withdrawal of Insolvency Petition</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sayaji+Hotels+%28Indore%29+Ltd&title=Sayaji+Hotels+%28Indore%29+Ltd%3A+Operational+Creditor+Seeks+Withdrawal+of+Insolvency+Petition&newsId=205aacec-224a-4b00-8440-a1a1bafcb212&token=MjA1YWFjZWMtMjI0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">205aacec-224a-4b00-8440-a1a1bafcb212</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:21:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Sayaji Hotels (Indore) Ltd has received an application from Ujaas Energy Limited, an operational creditor, for the withdrawal of a petition filed under Section 9 of the Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code, 2016. The petition was initially filed before the Hon&apos;ble National Company Law Tribunal, Indore Bench. The application for withdrawal was filed on February 27, 2026, under Rule 8 of the Insolvency and Bankruptcy (Application to Adjudicating Authority) Rules, 2016, and Rule 11 of the NCLT Rules, 2016. The order for withdrawal and dismissal of the petition is awaited. The company will keep the Bombay Stock Exchange informed about the outcome of the application and any further material developments.</p><ul><li>Ujaas Energy Limited, an operational creditor, has applied for the withdrawal of a petition filed against Sayaji Hotels (Indore) Ltd.</li><li>The petition was filed under Section 9 of the Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code, 2016.</li><li>The application for withdrawal was filed on February 27, 2026, under the Insolvency and Bankruptcy (Application to Adjudicating Authority) Rules, 2016, and NCLT Rules, 2016.</li><li>The order for withdrawal and dismissal of the petition is awaited.</li><li>Sayaji Hotels (Indore) Ltd will keep the Bombay Stock Exchange informed about the outcome and any further developments.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bf344254-4de9-408f-a78b-744a7d66be9d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sayaji Hotels (Indore) Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NLCINDIA] NLC India Ltd Fined Rs. 5,42,800 by BSE for Non-Compliance with SEBI Regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NLC+India+Ltd&title=NLC+India+Ltd+Fined+Rs.+5%2C42%2C800+by+BSE+for+Non-Compliance+with+SEBI+Regulations&newsId=c4e0eb71-afb5-40f2-b50f-ee022e434133&token=YzRlMGViNzEtYWZi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4e0eb71-afb5-40f2-b50f-ee022e434133</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>NLC India Ltd has received a notice from BSE Limited for non-compliance with the provisions of Regulation 17(1) of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015, specifically for failing to appoint a Women Director. The BSE has imposed a fine of Rs. 5,42,800 each for this non-compliance. The Company has requested BSE to waive these fines, stating that the power to appoint Directors on the Board of Directors of the Company vests with the President of India and the non-compliance was not attributable to any negligence or default on the part of the Company. The fines have no impact on the operations or other activities of the Company, and the total financial implication is limited to the fines imposed by BSE.</p><ul><li>NLC India Ltd fined Rs. 5,42,800 by BSE for non-compliance with SEBI regulations</li><li>Non-compliance pertains to the failure to appoint a Women Director</li><li>Company has requested BSE to waive the fines</li><li>The fines are not attributable to any negligence or default on the part of the Company</li><li>The fines have no impact on the operations or other activities of the Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d1d12de4-fc3a-46fc-a820-d37cc2f6ed1d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NLC India Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TRL] Taylormade Renewables Ltd. Approves Issue of 10,00,000 Fully Convertible Warrants at Rs. 123 Each</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Taylormade+Renewables+Ltd&title=Taylormade+Renewables+Ltd.+Approves+Issue+of+10%2C00%2C000+Fully+Convertible+Warrants+at+Rs.+123+Each&newsId=dba7723d-5442-498a-8773-32674ddce467&token=ZGJhNzcyM2QtNTQ0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dba7723d-5442-498a-8773-32674ddce467</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:11:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Taylormade Renewables Ltd. has approved the issue of up to 10,00,000 (Ten Lakh) Fully Convertible Warrants at a price of Rs. 123 each. The warrants, each convertible into one fully paid-up equity share of the Company, will be issued to specified investors on a preferential basis. The proceeds from the issue will be utilized towards the implementation and commercialization of the Company’s patented Sugar Manufacturing Technology. The Company may undertake further fund-raising in subsequent phases to support large-scale commercialization of the technology, subject to applicable approvals.</p><ul><li>Taylormade Renewables Ltd. to issue up to 10,00,000 Fully Convertible Warrants</li><li>Warrants to be issued at a price of Rs. 123 each</li><li>Proceeds to be utilized towards the implementation and commercialization of the Company’s patented Sugar Manufacturing Technology</li><li>Company may undertake further fund-raising in subsequent phases</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2be56af5-5a7e-494e-afb7-b44d172a80d1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Taylormade Renewables Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NMSRESRC] NMS Global Ltd&apos;s EGM: Preferential Issue of Convertible Equity Warrants &amp; Director Appointments Approved</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NMS+Resources+Global+Ltd&title=NMS+Global+Ltd%27s+EGM%3A+Preferential+Issue+of+Convertible+Equity+Warrants+%26+Director+Appointments+Approved&newsId=52129921-6a11-43c9-8f89-8f8a157cf5e9&token=NTIxMjk5MjEtNmEx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">52129921-6a11-43c9-8f89-8f8a157cf5e9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>NMS Global Ltd held an Extraordinary General Meeting (EGM) on February 28, 2026, through video conferencing. The meeting, initially scheduled for 11:00 AM, started at 11:15 AM due to a technical glitch and concluded at 11:45 AM. The meeting was chaired by Mr. Pankaj Chander, and 43 shareholders attended via video conferencing. The meeting was held to discuss and approve the following items: 1. Issue of Convertible Equity Warrants on a preferential basis to non-promoters for cash consideration, 2. Appointment of Ms. Meenakshi Gupta as a Non Independent Non Executive Director, and 3. Increase in Authorised Share Capital of the Company and consequent alteration of Capital Clause of Memorandum of Association of the Company. The results of the voting on these resolutions, along with the Scrutinizer’s Report, were intimated to the BSE, Metropolitan Stock Exchange of India Limited, the Registrar of Companies, NCT of Delhi &amp; Haryana, and were placed on the Company’s website and on the website of Central Depository Services (India) Limited within 2 working days of the EGM.</p><ul><li>NMS Global Ltd conducted an EGM on February 28, 2026, to discuss and approve key business items.</li><li>The meeting was held through video conferencing and was chaired by Mr. Pankaj Chander.</li><li>43 shareholders attended the meeting via video conferencing.</li><li>Key items on the agenda included the preferential issue of Convertible Equity Warrants, the appointment of a new Non Independent Non Executive Director, and an increase in Authorised Share Capital.</li><li>The results of the voting on these resolutions were shared with relevant authorities and posted on the company&apos;s website.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cdc59901-7cd1-4f31-9700-5936512b0aa2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NMS Resources Global Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHARDFI] Eco Hotels And Resorts: Reminder for Payment of First Call Money on Partly Paid-Up Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHARAD+FIBRES+%26+YARN+PROCESSORS+LTD.&title=Eco+Hotels+And+Resorts%3A+Reminder+for+Payment+of+First+Call+Money+on+Partly+Paid-Up+Equity+Shares&newsId=3b16cefe-bb15-4bfe-989d-f47ae79e6853&token=M2IxNmNlZmUtYmIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b16cefe-bb15-4bfe-989d-f47ae79e6853</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 12:01:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Payment Reminder</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Eco Hotels And Resorts Ltd has issued a reminder for payment of First Call Money on partly paid-up equity shares. This reminder is for the outstanding 40,08,641 partly paid-up equity shares of the Company which were allotted on September 26, 2025. The First Call amount is Rs. 3.80 per partly paid-up equity share, comprising Rs.2.50 towards face value and Rs. 1.30 towards securities premium. The Reminder Notice for payment of first call will be sent to the holders of such partly paid-up equity shares on which the First Call money remains unpaid. The period for payment of the first call money pursuant to the Reminder Notice for payment of first call is from Thursday, 19% March, 2026 up to Thursday, 0274 April, 2026 (both days inclusive).</p><ul><li>Eco Hotels And Resorts Ltd has issued a reminder for payment of First Call Money on partly paid-up equity shares.</li><li>The reminder is for the outstanding 40,08,641 partly paid-up equity shares of the Company allotted on September 26, 2025.</li><li>The First Call amount is Rs. 3.80 per partly paid-up equity share, comprising Rs.2.50 towards face value and Rs. 1.30 towards securities premium.</li><li>The Reminder Notice for payment of first call will be sent to the holders of such partly paid-up equity shares on which the First Call money remains unpaid.</li><li>The period for payment of the first call money pursuant to the Reminder Notice for payment of first call is from Thursday, 19% March, 2026 up to Thursday, 0274 April, 2026 (both days inclusive).</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4eb4ffda-d668-4cc9-8d37-bfa9a436ae8f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHARAD FIBRES & YARN PROCESSORS LTD. | Category: Payment Reminder</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[REGENCY] Regency Fincorp Ltd. Approves Issuance of INR 25 Crores Non-Convertible Debentures</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Regency+Fincorp+Ltd&title=Regency+Fincorp+Ltd.+Approves+Issuance+of+INR+25+Crores+Non-Convertible+Debentures&newsId=a58e5a0e-7194-400f-bdca-0fba021bd9f1&token=YTU4ZTVhMGUtNzE5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a58e5a0e-7194-400f-bdca-0fba021bd9f1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 11:58:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Regency Fincorp Ltd. announced the outcome of their Board Meeting held on 28th February 2026. The Board approved the revised term sheet for the issuance of 25000 units of Listed, Secured, Rated, Non-Convertible Debentures (NCD) worth INR 25,00,00,000 on a private placement basis. The NCDs are divided into a Base Issue of 15000 units for INR 15,00,00,000 and a Green Shoe Option of 10000 units for INR 10,00,00,000. Credora Partners Private Limited has been appointed as the Merchant Banker for this issuance.</p><ul><li>Regency Fincorp Ltd. to issue 25000 units of Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs)</li><li>Total worth of the NCDs is INR 25,00,00,000</li><li>The NCDs are divided into a Base Issue and a Green Shoe Option</li><li>Credora Partners Private Limited appointed as the Merchant Banker</li><li>The NCDs will be listed on BSE Limited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/69501f54-7512-42ab-bc9c-7d6776fda500.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Regency Fincorp Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDRAIND] Bluegod Entertainment Ltd Fixes Record Date for Rights Issue Entitlements</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Indra+Industries+Ltd&title=Bluegod+Entertainment+Ltd+Fixes+Record+Date+for+Rights+Issue+Entitlements&newsId=66e0212d-089d-4c7f-a43b-6632646cc28d&token=NjZlMDIxMmQtMDg5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66e0212d-089d-4c7f-a43b-6632646cc28d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 11:54:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Right Issue</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bluegod Entertainment Ltd has announced Friday, 06 March, 2026 as the record date for the purpose of determining the equity shareholders who shall be entitled to receive the Rights Entitlement in the Rights Issue. The company has made necessary arrangements with NSDL and CDSL for the credits of the Rights Entitlements in dematerialized form in the demat account of the eligible equity shareholders as on the Record Date. The Rights Entitlement of the eligible equity shareholders as on the Record Date, shall be credited prior to the issue opening date, in the respective demat account of the eligible equity shareholders.</p><ul><li>Bluegod Entertainment Ltd fixes record date for Rights Issue</li><li>Record date set as 06 March, 2026</li><li>Rights Entitlements to be credited in demat accounts of eligible shareholders</li><li>NSDL and CDSL to facilitate the credits</li><li>Rights Entitlements to be credited prior to the issue opening date</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e60713e5-c62f-426a-91c6-ab7b33c1860a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Indra Industries Ltd | Category: Right Issue</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RGF] RGF Capital Markets Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Consider Share Capital Increase and Fund Raising</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RGF+Capital+Markets+Ltd&title=RGF+Capital+Markets+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Consider+Share+Capital+Increase+and+Fund+Raising&newsId=3a20561c-095d-4010-a566-435f7471c667&token=M2EyMDU2MWMtMDk1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a20561c-095d-4010-a566-435f7471c667</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 11:54:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>RGF Capital Markets Ltd has informed the BSE that its Board of Directors will meet on March 06, 2026, to consider various agenda items. The key items include increasing the authorized share capital, evaluating the raising of funds through equity shares or other eligible securities, and any other business with the chair&apos;s permission and majority of directors. The company&apos;s Trading Window for dealing in securities will be closed for all Designated Persons from March 01, 2026, reopening 48 hours after the meeting&apos;s conclusion.</p><ul><li>RGF Capital Markets Ltd to consider increasing authorized share capital</li><li>The company will evaluate fundraising through equity shares or other eligible securities</li><li>Trading Window to be closed for all Designated Persons from March 01, 2026</li><li>The window will reopen 48 hours after the Board meeting concludes on March 06, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c301d5e2-c2db-4934-a109-21622ef1f898.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RGF Capital Markets Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RGF] RGF Capital Markets Ltd Appoints Mrs. Basanti Roy and Mr. Sanjib Dutta as Additional Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RGF+Capital+Markets+Ltd&title=RGF+Capital+Markets+Ltd+Appoints+Mrs.+Basanti+Roy+and+Mr.+Sanjib+Dutta+as+Additional+Directors&newsId=2210284e-90e2-4e06-b26b-4ac657caf571&token=MjIxMDI4NGUtOTBl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2210284e-90e2-4e06-b26b-4ac657caf571</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 11:52:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>RGF Capital Markets Ltd has appointed Mrs. Basanti Roy and Mr. Sanjib Dutta as Additional Directors under the Non-Executive - Independent category. Mrs. Roy has been appointed for a second term of 5 years, subject to necessary approval. Mr. Dutta has also been appointed for a second term of 5 years, subject to necessary approval. The appointments were made during the Board meeting held on February 28, 2025. The Board also approved the reconstitution of all the Committees of the Company.</p><ul><li>RGF Capital Markets Ltd has appointed Mrs. Basanti Roy as an Additional Director under the Non-Executive - Independent category for a second term of 5 years.</li><li>Mr. Sanjib Dutta has been appointed as an Additional Director under the Non-Executive - Independent category for a second term of 5 years.</li><li>The appointments were made during the Board meeting held on February 28, 2025.</li><li>The Board also approved the reconstitution of all the Committees of the Company.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e1dc6606-579e-497b-9d55-042ce36eca99.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RGF Capital Markets Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>