<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 09:25:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[TRIL] Transformers and Rectifiers (India) Ltd: New CEO Appointed, Q3 and Q9 Results Approved in Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TRANSFORMERS+AND+RECTIFIERS+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Transformers+and+Rectifiers+%28India%29+Ltd%3A+New+CEO+Appointed%2C+Q3+and+Q9+Results+Approved+in+Board+Meeting&newsId=7545a972-6908-4dc7-a95a-338a96d76bad&token=NzU0NWE5NzItNjkw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7545a972-6908-4dc7-a95a-338a96d76bad</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 09:25:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Transformers and Rectifiers (India) Ltd, a company based in Gujarat, India, announced the outcomes of its Board Meeting held on 08th January, 2026. The meeting resulted in the approval of the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The company also announced the resignation of Mr. Mukul Srivastava as the Chief Executive Officer (CEO) due to personal reasons and the appointment of Mr. Satyen J. Mamtora, the Managing Director, as the new CEO. The meeting was held at the company&apos;s registered office in Moraiya, Taluka: Sanand, Dist. Anmedabad - 382213, Gujarat, INDIA.</p><ul><li>Approval of Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 and Q9 of FY2025-2026</li><li>Resignation of Mr. Mukul Srivastava as CEO due to personal reasons</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Satyen J. Mamtora as the new CEO and Managing Director</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/36de1b06-4817-4303-be01-edc61f853bae.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TRANSFORMERS AND RECTIFIERS (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TATAELXSI] Tata Elxsi Ltd Provides Clarification on Volume Movement with No Material Impact</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TATA+ELXSI+LTD.&title=Tata+Elxsi+Ltd+Provides+Clarification+on+Volume+Movement+with+No+Material+Impact&newsId=af87effa-d822-4275-9b6c-81af05a9f2e4&token=YWY4N2VmZmEtZDgy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">af87effa-d822-4275-9b6c-81af05a9f2e4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 09:25:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tata Elxsi Ltd has issued a clarification letter regarding the movement in volume of its scrip. The company confirmed that there is no impending information or undisclosed material event that could significantly impact the price or volume of the company&apos;s security. The recent market activity and volatility are reflective of current market dynamics and investor sentiment. Tata Elxsi remains committed to transparent and timely disclosures as per SEBI regulations.</p><ul><li>Tata Elxsi Ltd provides clarification on volume movement</li><li>No impending information or undisclosed material event</li><li>Market activity and volatility reflect current market dynamics and investor sentiment</li><li>Tata Elxsi remains committed to transparent and timely disclosures</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cd2c580e-0c3f-4603-9fb4-cb069f3c034a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TATA ELXSI LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TRIL] Transformers and Rectifiers (India) Ltd: New Labor Codes Impact, Resignation &amp; Appointment of CEO</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TRANSFORMERS+AND+RECTIFIERS+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Transformers+and+Rectifiers+%28India%29+Ltd%3A+New+Labor+Codes+Impact%2C+Resignation+%26+Appointment+of+CEO&newsId=0eff81b1-222a-4781-a528-a0f42e43b2ee&token=MGVmZjgxYjEtMjIy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0eff81b1-222a-4781-a528-a0f42e43b2ee</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 09:23:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Transformers and Rectifiers (India) Ltd has reported its UFR as of 31.12.2025 Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results. The Board approved the results, which will be uploaded on the company&apos;s website. The company announced the resignation of Mr. Mukul Srivastava as the CEO due to personal reasons and appointed Mr. Satyen J. Mamtora as the new CEO. The company also discussed the impact of the New Labor Codes on gratuity liability, recognizing it as an expense in the current quarter.</p><ul><li>Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December, 2025</li><li>Resignation of Mr. Mukul Srivastava as CEO due to personal reasons</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Satyen J. Mamtora as the new CEO</li><li>Impact of New Labor Codes on gratuity liability recognized as an expense</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1d5419bd-05d7-4661-a61c-409e02f502a4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TRANSFORMERS AND RECTIFIERS (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASMS] Bartronics India Ltd. Announces Board Meeting Outcomes: Proposed Investment in Shree Naga Narasimha Private Limited &amp; Capital Reclassification</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BARTRONICS+INDIA+LTD.&title=Bartronics+India+Ltd.+Announces+Board+Meeting+Outcomes%3A+Proposed+Investment+in+Shree+Naga+Narasimha+Private+Limited+%26+Capital+Reclassification&newsId=ebf4ed8a-b475-4c36-8997-338edbbb1494&token=ZWJmNGVkOGEtYjQ3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ebf4ed8a-b475-4c36-8997-338edbbb1494</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 09:22:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bartronics India Ltd. held a board meeting on 8th January, 2026, where they discussed and approved several business items. The key highlights include the reclassification of authorized share capital, creation of mortgage/charge on assets, and an investment proposal of up to INR 3,00,00,000 in Shree Naga Narasimha Private Limited for acquiring up to 51% of its equity share capital. The investment is subject to completion of due diligence and execution of definitive agreements. The company also amended the Notice of Postal Ballot for obtaining shareholders’ approval on certain incidental matters.</p><ul><li>Reclassification of authorized share capital</li><li>Creation of mortgage/charge on assets</li><li>Proposed investment of up to INR 3,00,00,000 in Shree Naga Narasimha Private Limited</li><li>Acquisition of up to 51% equity share capital of Shree Naga Narasimha Private Limited</li><li>Amendment of Notice of Postal Ballot</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d9a50d44-a74c-43b8-a01a-3db9c1198399.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BARTRONICS INDIA LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TAINWALCHM] Tainwala Chemicals and Plastics (India) Ltd Reports on Re-lodgment of Transfer Requests for December 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TAINWALA+CHEMICALS+%26+PLASTICS+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Tainwala+Chemicals+and+Plastics+%28India%29+Ltd+Reports+on+Re-lodgment+of+Transfer+Requests+for+December+2025&newsId=675e170a-e306-422c-b2d6-d246f1397078&token=Njc1ZTE3MGEtZTMw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">675e170a-e306-422c-b2d6-d246f1397078</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 09:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tainwala Chemicals and Plastics (India) Ltd has released a re-lodgment report for the month ended December 31, 2025. The report, received from the company&apos;s Registrar and Share Transfer Agent, MUFG Intime India Private Limited, provides details of re-lodgement of transfer requests of physical shares in the prescribed format. The report is available on the company&apos;s website and stock exchanges have been informed about the same.</p><ul><li>Tainwala Chemicals and Plastics (India) Ltd has released a re-lodgment report for December 2025.</li><li>The report provides details of re-lodgement of transfer requests of physical shares in the prescribed format.</li><li>The report is available on the company&apos;s website.</li><li>Stock exchanges have been informed about the re-lodgment report.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2b3663cc-bdf9-409f-b864-f4480b2c73bb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TAINWALA CHEMICALS & PLASTICS (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CAMLINFINE] Camlin Fine Sciences Ltd Clarifies on Volume Movement</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CAMLIN+FINE+SCIENCES+LTD.&title=Camlin+Fine+Sciences+Ltd+Clarifies+on+Volume+Movement&newsId=50d5bf26-cb06-499a-aaa1-f59633672a59&token=NTBkNWJmMjYtY2Iw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50d5bf26-cb06-499a-aaa1-f59633672a59</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 09:18:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Camlin Fine Sciences Ltd has clarified on the volume movement of its shares as requested by BSE Surveillance. The company has consistently informed the stock exchanges about all events and information that could impact its operations or performance, in accordance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015. However, due to the freely traded nature of the company&apos;s equity shares on the Stock Exchanges, it cannot comment on the movement in the price or volume of its Equity Shares.</p><ul><li>Camlin Fine Sciences Ltd has clarified on volume movement of its shares</li><li>The company has informed stock exchanges about events and information as per Regulation 30 of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Camlin&apos;s equity shares are freely traded on Stock Exchanges</li><li>The company cannot comment on price or volume movement of its Equity Shares</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fe60d0c4-051e-40d1-8e87-614a7b3421e1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CAMLIN FINE SCIENCES LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BAJAJCON*] Bajaj Consumer Care Ltd to Approve Q3 Results for 2025 in Board Meeting on Jan 21, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Bajaj+Consumer+Care+Ltd&title=Bajaj+Consumer+Care+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+Results+for+2025+in+Board+Meeting+on+Jan+21%2C+2026&newsId=81fad7b2-4fa7-4fc9-af35-bce8c7985523&token=ODFmYWQ3YjItNGZh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">81fad7b2-4fa7-4fc9-af35-bce8c7985523</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 09:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bajaj Consumer Care Ltd has announced a Board Meeting scheduled on January 21, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results (Standalone and Consolidated) for the third quarter ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will also approve the notice as per Regulation 29 and 33 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The &apos;Trading Window&apos; for dealing in securities of the Company will be closed for all &apos;Designated Persons&apos; from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the announcement of the Unaudited Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Bajaj Consumer Care Ltd to hold a Board Meeting on January 21, 2026</li><li>The meeting will approve the Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 2025</li><li>Trading Window for Designated Persons to remain closed from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the results announcement</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/402bfbc4-f6ee-4706-9ff1-3ec95e72f6de.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Bajaj Consumer Care Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KFINTECH] KFin Technologies Ltd Receives Request for Re-classification from Promoter to Public Category</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KFin+Technologies+Ltd&title=KFin+Technologies+Ltd+Receives+Request+for+Re-classification+from+Promoter+to+Public+Category&newsId=31448c09-20d8-49b6-83ba-a8f99fb7c008&token=MzE0NDhjMDktMjBk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">31448c09-20d8-49b6-83ba-a8f99fb7c008</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 09:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Corporate Action</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>KFin Technologies Ltd has received a request from House of Anita Dongre Private Limited (HADPL) for re-classification from the &apos;Promoter(s) Group&apos; category to the &apos;Public&apos; category. HADPL, which was previously part of the &apos;Promoter(s) Group&apos;, has divested its entire stake in the Company and is no longer related to the Promoter(s) Group. The request will be placed before the Board of Directors for consideration. The re-classification is in accordance with Regulation 31A of the LODR Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>KFin Technologies Ltd received a request for re-classification from House of Anita Dongre Private Limited</li><li>HADPL has divested its entire stake in the Company and is no longer related to the Promoter(s) Group</li><li>The request will be placed before the Board of Directors for consideration</li><li>The re-classification is in accordance with Regulation 31A of the LODR Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/032d38f0-9b59-4de7-8651-9f3b1ff7af07.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KFin Technologies Ltd | Category: Corporate Action</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TATATECH] Tata Technologies: No Pending Information or Material Event Impacting Security Prices</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Tata+Technologies+Ltd&title=Tata+Technologies%3A+No+Pending+Information+or+Material+Event+Impacting+Security+Prices&newsId=32535f2f-23ea-4b13-a6cc-cd6371619f58&token=MzI1MzVmMmYtMjNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32535f2f-23ea-4b13-a6cc-cd6371619f58</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 09:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In response to a query seeking clarification on significant increase in price/volume movement of Tata Technologies Limited, the company confirmed that as of January 8, 2026, there is no pending information or undisclosed material event likely to have a significant impact on the price or trading volume of the company&apos;s securities. The recent market movements and volatility are in line with prevailing market conditions and investor sentiment. Tata Technologies remains committed to ensuring transparent and timely disclosures in compliance with SEBI regulations.</p><ul><li>Tata Technologies confirms no pending information or undisclosed material events impacting security prices</li><li>Company&apos;s response addresses clarification sought on significant increase in price/volume movement</li><li>Market movements and volatility are in line with prevailing market conditions and investor sentiment</li><li>Tata Technologies remains committed to transparent and timely disclosures as per SEBI regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b8cbb684-7cfd-41f1-a5ed-15d381de7fa5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Tata Technologies Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AVROIND] Avro India Leads Waste-to-Wealth Shift with India’s Largest Flexible Plastic Recycling Unit</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Avro+India+Ltd&title=Avro+India+Leads+Waste-to-Wealth+Shift+with+India%E2%80%99s+Largest+Flexible+Plastic+Recycling+Unit&newsId=0171a34e-8c84-478b-b6f2-a19e8999ab3b&token=MDE3MWEzNGUtOGM4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0171a34e-8c84-478b-b6f2-a19e8999ab3b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 09:04:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Avro India Limited, a leading manufacturer of plastic-moulded furniture, has launched a state-of-the-art greenfield recycling facility in Ghaziabad under its subsidiary AVRO Recycling Limited. The facility houses India’s largest flexible plastic recycling plant with a current processing capacity of 500 MTPM, which is set to scale up in the future. The company has invested ₹25 crore in the recycling plant and plans to invest an additional ₹30 crore by FY 2027. Avro has developed a proprietary system to upcycle difficult-to-process plastic waste at scale, addressing one of India’s most complex environmental challenges. The recycled granules are used in the manufacture of high-value end products, including plastic furniture, air coolers, washing machines, automotive components, and other industrial and consumer applications. Avro India has emerged as the largest and most reliable organised player in the flexible plastic recycling space, offering consistent volumes at industrial scale, addressing the supply gap of high-quality recycled raw materials due to Extended Producer Responsibility (EPR) norms.</p><ul><li>Avro India launched India&apos;s largest flexible plastic recycling plant with a capacity of 500 MTPM</li><li>The recycling plant is set to scale up in the future with an additional investment of ₹30 crore by FY 2027</li><li>Avro has developed a proprietary system to upcycle difficult-to-process plastic waste at scale</li><li>The recycled granules are used in the manufacture of high-value end products</li><li>Avro India has emerged as the largest and most reliable organised player in the flexible plastic recycling space</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d194c48a-c99b-4e1b-a7a8-91bad4416eec.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Avro India Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>