<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 21:27:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[GODIGIT] Go Digit General Insurance Ltd Faces GST Search Regulations Inspection</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Go+Digit+General+Insurance+Ltd&title=Go+Digit+General+Insurance+Ltd+Faces+GST+Search+Regulations+Inspection&newsId=0646c82c-1407-4770-8f0c-58b35c4e0524&token=MDY0NmM4MmMtMTQw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0646c82c-1407-4770-8f0c-58b35c4e0524</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Go Digit General Insurance Ltd has disclosed a search conducted by the Directorate General of Goods &amp; Service Tax Intelligence, Gurugram Zonal Unit pursuant to Regulation 30 read with Para A of Part A of Schedule Il of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The search commenced on 5th February 2026 and concluded on 6th February 2026. The company does not foresee any material impact on its financials, operations, or other activities due to this search.</p><ul><li>Go Digit General Insurance Ltd faced a search conducted by the Directorate General of Goods &amp; Service Tax Intelligence, Gurugram Zonal Unit.</li><li>The search commenced on 5th February 2026 and concluded on 6th February 2026.</li><li>No official document has been issued regarding any adverse findings.</li><li>Summons have been issued to representatives of the Company to appear before the Authority for further questioning and statements.</li><li>The company does not foresee any material impact on its financials, operations, or other activities due to this search.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/946b73c0-894a-47bb-9abf-cb6c75836bf6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Go Digit General Insurance Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EXCELSOFT] Excelsoft Technologies Ltd Announces Q3 Results, Changes in Senior Management, and KMP Appointments</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Excelsoft+Technologies+Ltd&title=Excelsoft+Technologies+Ltd+Announces+Q3+Results%2C+Changes+in+Senior+Management%2C+and+KMP+Appointments&newsId=edc0ddd3-3e69-42f1-9124-028a8089ac77&token=ZWRjMGRkZDMtM2U2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">edc0ddd3-3e69-42f1-9124-028a8089ac77</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:41:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Excelsoft Technologies Ltd has announced its un-audited financial results for the third quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue stands at INR 1,631.64 million, with a profit before tax of INR 318.34 million. The board also approved changes in the designation of Senior Management Personnel and announced the resignation of the Company Secretary and Compliance Officer, along with the appointment of a new Company Secretary, Chief Compliance Officer, and Chief Investor Relations Officer.</p><ul><li>Excelsoft Technologies Ltd reports a revenue of INR 1,631.64 million for Q3 2025</li><li>The company records a profit before tax of INR 318.34 million for the quarter</li><li>Changes in the designation of Senior Management Personnel announced</li><li>Resignation of Company Secretary and Compliance Officer confirmed</li><li>Appointment of new Company Secretary, Chief Compliance Officer, and Chief Investor Relations Officer approved</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1f7244fe-c527-4b34-b702-302f4d657571.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Excelsoft Technologies Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[METSL] Maestros Electronics Secures Rs. 1.99 Crore Order from MD National Health Mission Jaipur</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Maestros+Electronics+%26+Telecommunications+Systems+Ltd&title=Maestros+Electronics+Secures+Rs.+1.99+Crore+Order+from+MD+National+Health+Mission+Jaipur&newsId=3b555ce1-f480-4ac7-8639-796ce2ef96cb&token=M2I1NTVjZTEtZjQ4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b555ce1-f480-4ac7-8639-796ce2ef96cb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Maestros Electronics &amp; Telecommunications Systems Ltd has announced that it has received a purchase order from MD National Health Mission Jaipur for the supply of 378 pieces of METSL 12 Channels ECG Machine. The contract is governed by the General Terms and Conditions and is valued at Rs. 1,99,52,730 exclusive of applicable taxes. The order is to be executed between February 03, 2026, and December 31, 2027. Neither the promoter of the company nor the promoter group/group companies have any interest in the entity that awarded the order.</p><ul><li>Maestros Electronics has received a purchase order from MD National Health Mission Jaipur</li><li>The order is for the supply of 378 pieces of METSL 12 Channels ECG Machine</li><li>The contract value is Rs. 1,99,52,730 exclusive of applicable taxes</li><li>The order is to be executed between February 03, 2026, and December 31, 2027</li><li>Neither the promoter of the company nor the promoter group/group companies have any interest in the entity that awarded the order</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ad9dc8e6-bf96-4b59-b4a8-6e8b3b9b7c7d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Maestros Electronics & Telecommunications Systems Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VALLABHSQ] Vallabh Steels Ltd. to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on 13th February, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VALLABH+STEELS+LTD.-%24&title=Vallabh+Steels+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+13th+February%2C+2026&newsId=836c90bc-f310-4450-800e-9efa698f91ba&token=ODM2YzkwYmMtZjMx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">836c90bc-f310-4450-800e-9efa698f91ba</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:21:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vallabh Steels Ltd. has announced a Board of Directors meeting on 13th February, 2026 to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ending 31st December, 2025. The meeting is scheduled in accordance with Regulation 29(1) of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. Additionally, in line with the Company’s Code of Conduct for Prevention of Insider Trading, the Trading Window for dealing in securities of the Company will be closed from 1st January, 2026 until 48 hours after the declaration of the Unaudited Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Vallabh Steels Ltd. to approve Q3 and nine months financial results on 13th February, 2026</li><li>The meeting is scheduled in accordance with Regulation 29(1) of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Trading Window for dealing in securities of the Company will be closed from 1st January, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5741f4f7-5cdd-4879-b4ef-26e515c8ab57.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VALLABH STEELS LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HCG] HealthCare Global Enterprises Ltd. Reports 13% YoY Revenue Growth in Q3FY26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HealthCare+Global+Enterprises+Ltd&title=HealthCare+Global+Enterprises+Ltd.+Reports+13%25+YoY+Revenue+Growth+in+Q3FY26&newsId=a6a44453-1937-4887-8cdf-69270ff981ee&token=YTZhNDQ0NTMtMTkz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a6a44453-1937-4887-8cdf-69270ff981ee</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:21:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>HealthCare Global Enterprises Ltd. (HCG), India’s largest dedicated cancer hospital network, has announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company reported a 13% YoY increase in revenue from operations, amounting to Rs. 6,331 Mn in Q3FY26. The adjusted EBITDA for the quarter was Rs. 1,108 Mn, marking a 20% YoY growth. The adjusted EBITDA margin stood at 17.5%, indicating a 98 bps YoY expansion. The adjusted PAT (Post IND AS) was Rs. 70 Mn, down from Rs. 371 Mn in the same period last year. The company remains committed to delivering high-quality oncology care and advancing clinical research in the field of cancer care.</p><ul><li>13% YoY growth in revenue from operations in Q3FY26</li><li>20% YoY increase in adjusted EBITDA in Q3FY26</li><li>98 bps YoY expansion in adjusted EBITDA margin in Q3FY26</li><li>Normalized adjusted PAT (Post IND AS) of Rs. 70 Mn in Q3FY26</li><li>Continued focus on delivering high-quality oncology care and advancing clinical research</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2223dcd3-1e4b-43c9-8183-0d41eea248d4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HealthCare Global Enterprises Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EROSMEDIA] Eros International Media Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025 on Feb 13, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=EROS+INTERNATIONAL+MEDIA+LTD.&title=Eros+International+Media+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025+on+Feb+13%2C+2026&newsId=44c58f6b-a343-4179-b2a6-ed9b503aa35b&token=NDRjNThmNmItYTM0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">44c58f6b-a343-4179-b2a6-ed9b503aa35b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Eros International Media Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 13, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting is scheduled in accordance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, and the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015. The trading window for dealing in the company&apos;s securities will be closed from January 01, 2026, to 48 hours after the announcement of the financial results for the quarter ended 31st December, 2025.</p><ul><li>Eros International Media Ltd to approve Q3 and nine months results for 2025 on Feb 13, 2026</li><li>Meeting scheduled in accordance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the company&apos;s securities will be closed from January 01, 2026, to 48 hours after the announcement of the financial results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f9d3f298-dd84-406e-82c5-1ca12c2fdaf4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: EROS INTERNATIONAL MEDIA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KSHITIJ] Kshitij Investments Ltd to Approve Q4 Results, Avail WHR Loan, and Other Matters in Board Meeting on Feb 11, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kshitij+Investments+Ltd&title=Kshitij+Investments+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+Results%2C+Avail+WHR+Loan%2C+and+Other+Matters+in+Board+Meeting+on+Feb+11%2C+2026&newsId=581e6188-d7dc-41e1-8b63-67b39d2f317f&token=NTgxZTYxODgtZDdk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">581e6188-d7dc-41e1-8b63-67b39d2f317f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kshitij Investments Ltd has scheduled a Board of Directors meeting on 11th February 2026 to consider and approve various matters. The agenda includes the following key points: (1) consideration and approval of the un-audited financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025 along with the Limited Review Report, (2) approval of availing WHR loan/credit facilities from Central Bank of India and authorization of Mr. Rahul Agrawal and Mr. Rohit Agrawal as authorized signatories, and (3) any other matter with the permission of the Chair. This meeting is being conducted in compliance with Regulation 29(1) (a) of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Kshitij Investments Ltd to consider and approve Q4 FY2025-26 financial results</li><li>Company to approve availing WHR loan/credit facilities from Central Bank of India</li><li>Mr. Rahul Agrawal and Mr. Rohit Agrawal authorized as signatories for loan/credit facilities</li><li>Meeting to be held on 11th February 2026, 4:00 PM IST</li><li>Compliance with Securities and Exchange Board of India regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9ac93263-290f-43ca-bfc2-81801f335234.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kshitij Investments Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KALPATARU] Kalpataru Ltd&apos;s IPO Proceeds Utilization in Line with Objectives, Reports CARE Ratings</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kalpataru+Ltd&title=Kalpataru+Ltd%27s+IPO+Proceeds+Utilization+in+Line+with+Objectives%2C+Reports+CARE+Ratings&newsId=9171442e-19c6-4c6e-a43b-66e8a059b84c&token=OTE3MTQ0MmUtMTlj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9171442e-19c6-4c6e-a43b-66e8a059b84c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>CARE Ratings, the Monitoring Agency for Kalpataru Ltd&apos;s IPO, has issued a report for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The report states that the utilization of the issue proceeds is in line with the objects disclosed in the Offer Document. The issue size was Rs. 1,590 crore, and there have been no material deviations or unfavorable events affecting the viability of these objects.</p><ul><li>Kalpataru Ltd&apos;s IPO proceeds utilization is in line with the objects disclosed in the Offer Document.</li><li>No material deviations or unfavorable events affecting the viability of these objects have been observed.</li><li>The Monitoring Agency, CARE Ratings, has not found any conflict of interest in its relationship with the issuer.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fe040a2f-7181-4454-9fda-f87e4234198b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kalpataru Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LEMONTREE] Lemon Tree Hotels Ltd Grants 99,16,000 Stock Appreciation Rights Units</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Lemon+Tree+Hotels+Ltd&title=Lemon+Tree+Hotels+Ltd+Grants+99%2C16%2C000+Stock+Appreciation+Rights+Units&newsId=a2abb033-7959-452c-a767-d1908e3e5aec&token=YTJhYmIwMzMtNzk1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2abb033-7959-452c-a767-d1908e3e5aec</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:11:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Lemon Tree Hotels Ltd has granted 99,16,000 Stock Appreciation Rights Units (SAR Units) to eligible employees under the LTHL Stock Appreciation Rights Scheme - 2024. The SAR Price is Rs. 129.37/- Per SAR Unit. The vested SAR Units can be exercised by grantees within the exercise period of 1 year from the vesting date. The scheme is administered by the Nomination and Remuneration Committee and will be implemented through a direct route for extending benefits to employees.</p><ul><li>Grant of 99,16,000 SAR Units to eligible employees</li><li>SAR Price is Rs. 129.37/- Per SAR Unit</li><li>Vested SAR Units can be exercised within 1 year from the vesting date</li><li>Administered by the Nomination and Remuneration Committee</li><li>Implemented through a direct route for extending benefits to employees</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bdaed372-cba1-4452-830c-c10767f553f2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Lemon Tree Hotels Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KALPATARU] Kalpataru Ltd Authorises Company Secretary to Determine Materiality of Events for Disclosure</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kalpataru+Ltd&title=Kalpataru+Ltd+Authorises+Company+Secretary+to+Determine+Materiality+of+Events+for+Disclosure&newsId=457da5be-7c16-48a4-bc73-801cd2ccf2fc&token=NDU3ZGE1YmUtN2Mx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">457da5be-7c16-48a4-bc73-801cd2ccf2fc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kalpataru Ltd announced that its Board of Directors, at a meeting held on February 6, 2026, authorised Mr. Gajendra Mewara, Company Secretary and Compliance Officer, to determine materiality of an event or information for the purpose of making the necessary disclosures to the stock exchanges under Regulation 30 of SEBI Listing Regulations. The company also listed the Key Managerial Personnel who are authorised to determine materiality of an event or information for disclosure purposes.</p><ul><li>Kalpataru Ltd Board authorises Company Secretary to determine materiality of events for disclosure</li><li>Key Managerial Personnel listed for determining materiality of events or information for disclosure</li><li>Event in line with Regulation 30 of SEBI Listing Regulations</li><li>Meeting held on February 6, 2026</li><li>Disclosure aimed at ensuring transparency and compliance with listing regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ae91d07e-b78e-49a8-998a-63515c221785.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kalpataru Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>