<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 21:20:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[REDINGTON] Redington Ltd. Receives Favorable Order Quashing INR 136.25 Cr Demand for Assessment Year 2021-22</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Redington+Ltd&title=Redington+Ltd.+Receives+Favorable+Order+Quashing+INR+136.25+Cr+Demand+for+Assessment+Year+2021-22&newsId=d44df0d1-db93-449e-84e0-9d90173c2947&token=ZDQ0ZGYwZDEtZGI5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d44df0d1-db93-449e-84e0-9d90173c2947</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:41:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Redington Ltd. has announced that it has received a favorable order from the Commissioner of Income Tax (Appeals) for the Assessment Year 2021-22. The order quashes the demand of INR 136.25 Cr raised by the Assessing officer for the said Assessment Year. The company had previously informed the Stock Exchange about the receipt of the assessment order for Assessment Year 2021-2022 along with a notice of demand for INR 136.25 Cr from the Income Tax Department. After contesting the demand before the appropriate appellate authorities, the company has now obtained a favorable order.</p><ul><li>Redington Ltd. receives a favorable order from the Commissioner of Income Tax (Appeals) for the Assessment Year 2021-22.</li><li>The order quashes the demand of INR 136.25 Cr raised by the Assessing officer for the said Assessment Year.</li><li>The company had previously informed the Stock Exchange about the receipt of the assessment order and demand.</li><li>The company contested the demand before the appropriate appellate authorities.</li><li>The company has now obtained a favorable order.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a8caa702-c731-4479-92d1-394154f73d55.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Redington Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MINDSPACE] Mindspace Business Parks REIT to Meet Investors in IIFL Conference</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Mindspace+Business+Parks+REIT&title=Mindspace+Business+Parks+REIT+to+Meet+Investors+in+IIFL+Conference&newsId=c00635fb-b174-477b-adb2-d6bd23f0c50f&token=YzAwNjM1ZmItYjE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c00635fb-b174-477b-adb2-d6bd23f0c50f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mindspace Business Parks REIT has announced that its management team will meet investors, including institutional investors, in a conference organized by IIFL Capital Trident BKC in Mumbai on February 24, 2026. The meetings will be in a group setting and one-on-one with individual investors. The presentation to be used by the management at this conference is available on the REIT&apos;s website. Please note that the meetings are subject to change due to changes on the part of the investors, organizers, or management team.</p><ul><li>Mindspace Business Parks REIT to meet investors in IIFL conference</li><li>Conference scheduled for February 24, 2026, in Mumbai</li><li>Meetings will be in group and one-on-one settings</li><li>Presentation available on REIT&apos;s website</li><li>Meetings subject to change due to changes in investors, organizers, or management team</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d9e8e52c-ec45-4837-b206-f1ffa2c10489.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Mindspace Business Parks REIT | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CUBEINVIT] Cube Highways Trust Approves Change in Sponsor and Conversion to Public Infrastructure Investment Trust</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Cube+Highways+Trust&title=Cube+Highways+Trust+Approves+Change+in+Sponsor+and+Conversion+to+Public+Infrastructure+Investment+Trust&newsId=e68ef695-b982-4005-a777-99556e1859a9&token=ZTY4ZWY2OTUtYjk4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e68ef695-b982-4005-a777-99556e1859a9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Cube Highways Trust has approved a change in sponsor and the conversion of the trust from a private listed infrastructure investment trust to a public infrastructure investment trust. The approval was given by unitholders with the requisite majority through remote e-voting and physical ballot papers conducted as part of a postal ballot process. The resolutions approved include the change in sponsor, conversion of the trust, acquisition of assets from Cube Highways and Infrastructure V Pte. Ltd., and the repeal of the list of specified matters.</p><ul><li>Approval of change in sponsor of Cube Highways Trust</li><li>Conversion of Cube Highways Trust from private to public</li><li>Approval for acquisition of assets from Cube Highways and Infrastructure V Pte. Ltd.</li><li>Repeal of the list of specified matters</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3588ffc6-0393-4ed7-a50d-ec24d1741518.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Cube Highways Trust | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADITYA] Aditya Ispat Ltd. Approves Slump Sale of Non-alloy Steel Business to Mitigate Losses</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADITYA+ISPAT+LTD.&title=Aditya+Ispat+Ltd.+Approves+Slump+Sale+of+Non-alloy+Steel+Business+to+Mitigate+Losses&newsId=0943ccd2-5589-449c-82e3-0c2827fdbe9a&token=MDk0M2NjZDItNTU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0943ccd2-5589-449c-82e3-0c2827fdbe9a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:05:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Aditya Ispat Ltd. held a Board Meeting on February 20, 2026, and approved the sale of its manufacturing and trading activity of Non-alloy steel through slump sale on a going concern basis. This decision is part of an internal restructuring of the business operations, aiming to mitigate the losses incurred in the last couple of quarters. The slump sale is expected to be executed in due course, with the consideration to be decided later. The trading activity of alloy steel will remain with the Company as a going concern post the completion of the sale. The proposed transaction is subject to fulfilment of conditions precedents, necessary approvals, and further approval of the shareholders.</p><ul><li>Aditya Ispat Ltd. approved the slump sale of Non-alloy steel business</li><li>Sale is part of an internal restructuring to mitigate losses</li><li>Consideration for the sale to be decided later</li><li>Trading activity of alloy steel to remain with the Company</li><li>Subject to fulfilment of conditions precedents, necessary approvals, and shareholder approval</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9cac0a6c-b33b-46e0-987a-2d2534b9831b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADITYA ISPAT LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADITYA] Aditya Ispat Ltd. Approves Slump Sale of Non-alloy Steel Business to Mitigate Losses</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADITYA+ISPAT+LTD.&title=Aditya+Ispat+Ltd.+Approves+Slump+Sale+of+Non-alloy+Steel+Business+to+Mitigate+Losses&newsId=b36dde87-c743-471a-8bf0-ca902b2fe435&token=YjM2ZGRlODctYzc0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b36dde87-c743-471a-8bf0-ca902b2fe435</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 17:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Aditya Ispat Ltd. held a board meeting on February 20, 2026, to discuss the mitigation of losses incurred in the last couple of quarters. After extensive deliberation, the board approved the proposal for the sale of the manufacturing and trading activity of Non-alloy steel through slump sale on a going concern basis at a lump sum purchase consideration. The trading activity of alloy steel will remain with the company. The board has instructed the management to place the valuation report before the Audit Committee for their review and recommendation. The completion of the proposed transaction is subject to fulfilment of conditions precedents and further approval of the shareholders of the Company.</p><ul><li>Aditya Ispat Ltd. held a board meeting to discuss the mitigation of losses.</li><li>The board approved the proposal for the sale of Non-alloy steel business through slump sale.</li><li>The trading activity of alloy steel will remain with the company.</li><li>The board has instructed the management to place the valuation report before the Audit Committee.</li><li>The completion of the proposed transaction is subject to shareholders&apos; approval.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4ab3971d-26c9-4395-9be3-f9808e38323b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADITYA ISPAT LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADITYA] Aditya Ispat Ltd. Approves Slump Sale of Non-alloy Steel Business to Mitigate Losses</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADITYA+ISPAT+LTD.&title=Aditya+Ispat+Ltd.+Approves+Slump+Sale+of+Non-alloy+Steel+Business+to+Mitigate+Losses&newsId=c483f0c1-3588-4578-b5c4-1f600cbabf78&token=YzQ4M2YwYzEtMzU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c483f0c1-3588-4578-b5c4-1f600cbabf78</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Aditya Ispat Ltd. held a board meeting on February 20, 2026, where they considered and noted the valuation report of the company and a detailed action taken report. After extensive deliberation, the board approved the proposal for the sale of the manufacturing and trading activity of Non-alloy steel through slump sale on a going concern basis at a lump sum purchase consideration. The trading activity of alloy steel will remain with the company. The board has instructed the management to place the valuation report before the Audit Committee for their review and recommendation. The completion of the proposed transaction is subject to fulfilment of conditions precedents and further approval of the shareholders.</p><ul><li>Aditya Ispat Ltd. approved the slump sale of Non-alloy steel business</li><li>The sale is aimed at mitigating the losses incurred by the company</li><li>The trading activity of alloy steel will remain with the company</li><li>The sale is subject to approval from regulatory/statutory authorities</li><li>The sale is subject to further conditions imposed by any person or authority</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/68c4b44f-b6c9-4788-9024-1f1f031ebc9f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADITYA ISPAT LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WEWORK] WeWork India Management Ltd to Add 3100 Desks in Bengaluru by September 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=WeWork+India+Management+Ltd&title=WeWork+India+Management+Ltd+to+Add+3100+Desks+in+Bengaluru+by+September+2026&newsId=15d23a18-2739-4fd4-b034-6fd99bffa0bf&token=MTVkMjNhMTgtMjcz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">15d23a18-2739-4fd4-b034-6fd99bffa0bf</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:44:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Expansion</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>WeWork India Management Ltd, formerly known as WeWork India Management Private Limited, has entered into a lease deed for capacity addition in Bengaluru, admeasuring 1,69,485 square feet. This will result in an increase in its operational capacity by approximately 3100 desks. The proposed capacity is to be added tentatively on or before September, 2026. The investment required for this capacity addition is approximately INR 42 Crore, which will be financed through debt and internal accruals. The rationale behind this move is to cater to incremental demand and to enhance the Company’s operational capacity in line with business growth.</p><ul><li>WeWork India Management Ltd to add approximately 3100 desks in Bengaluru</li><li>Capacity addition to be completed tentatively by September, 2026</li><li>Investment of approximately INR 42 Crore required for capacity addition</li><li>Capacity addition to be financed through debt and internal accruals</li><li>Capacity addition aimed at catering to incremental demand and enhancing operational capacity</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/60615c40-c276-45a7-b113-c168881c096b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: WeWork India Management Ltd | Category: Expansion</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SBILIFE] SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd Receives Order from Joint Commissioner of State Tax (Appeal) I, Mumbai, Maharashtra under Section 107 of MGST and CGST Act 2017</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SBI+Life+Insurance+Company+Ltd&title=SBI+Life+Insurance+Company+Ltd+Receives+Order+from+Joint+Commissioner+of+State+Tax+%28Appeal%29+I%2C+Mumbai%2C+Maharashtra+under+Section+107+of+MGST+and+CGST+Act+2017&newsId=d9427e72-a68a-4a48-9596-d81e76a8ef25&token=ZDk0MjdlNzItYTY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d9427e72-a68a-4a48-9596-d81e76a8ef25</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:37:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd has received an order from the Joint Commissioner of State tax (Appeal) I, Mumbai, Maharashtra under Section 107 of the MGST and CGST Act 2017 on February 20, 2026 at 7:19 P.M. The order partially upholds the tax demand raised under Form GST DRC 07. The company had earlier disclosed the tax demand on April 30, 2024, which was Rs. 288,66,57,520/-. However, after the appellate authority&apos;s decision, the confirmed demand now stands at Rs. 1,59,44,96,372/-. The company will file an appeal before the Competent Authority / Appellate Tribunal against the said order in accordance with the applicable provisions under Goods and Service Tax Act.</p><ul><li>SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd has received an order from the Joint Commissioner of State tax (Appeal) I, Mumbai, Maharashtra under Section 107 of the MGST and CGST Act 2017.</li><li>The order partially upholds the tax demand raised under Form GST DRC 07.</li><li>The earlier disclosed tax demand was Rs. 288,66,57,520/-, which has now been confirmed as Rs. 1,59,44,96,372/- after the appellate authority&apos;s decision.</li><li>The company will file an appeal before the Competent Authority / Appellate Tribunal against the said order.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c11178c2-6e0d-4bce-b51c-3467956ba715.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LYKALABS] Lyka Labs Amalgamation Scheme: NCLT Reserves Order After FEMA Compliance Submission</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LYKA+LABS+LTD.&title=Lyka+Labs+Amalgamation+Scheme%3A+NCLT+Reserves+Order+After+FEMA+Compliance+Submission&newsId=d39b359d-05b9-49f6-8272-ac2c094c7d23&token=ZDM5YjM1OWQtMDVi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d39b359d-05b9-49f6-8272-ac2c094c7d23</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:31:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Lyka Labs Ltd. has updated the status of its amalgamation scheme with Lyka Exports Limited. The Hon’ble National Company Law Tribunal, Ahmedabad Bench has taken up the application and affidavit filed by the Company regarding FEMA compliance for examination. The Company&apos;s counsel has submitted that the compliance affidavit has been provided as directed by the Tribunal regarding the Import Export Code and FEMA guidelines. The NCLT has reserved the order. The intimation along with the copy of the order is available on the Company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Lyka Labs and Lyka Exports amalgamation scheme update</li><li>NCLT taken up the application and affidavit for FEMA compliance examination</li><li>Company&apos;s counsel submitted compliance affidavit for Import Export Code and FEMA guidelines</li><li>NCLT has reserved the order</li><li>Order details available on the Company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/938897fb-40fe-4191-a553-ac99086c84b3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LYKA LABS LTD. | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BLUECLOUDS] Blue Cloud Softech Solutions Ltd. Adjourns Board Meeting for Further Consideration of Proposed Acquisition</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Blue+Cloud+Softech+Solutions+Ltd&title=Blue+Cloud+Softech+Solutions+Ltd.+Adjourns+Board+Meeting+for+Further+Consideration+of+Proposed+Acquisition&newsId=e72cd94e-4ccf-48e6-84cf-b1a6cf060c8c&token=ZTcyY2Q5NGUtNGNj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e72cd94e-4ccf-48e6-84cf-b1a6cf060c8c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 16:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Blue Cloud Softech Solutions Ltd. announced that the Board of Directors meeting held on February 20th, 2026, was adjourned to enable further deliberations and consideration of additional information in relation to the proposed acquisition. The adjourned meeting is scheduled for February 23rd, 2026, to discuss and evaluate the proposal for acquiring 100% equity stake in a company via share swap. The acquisition is subject to necessary approvals from shareholders, stock exchanges, and other authorities, and fulfillment of customary conditions precedent. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company by Designated Persons and their immediate relatives remains closed till 48 hours after the outcome of the adjourned Board Meeting is made public.</p><ul><li>Blue Cloud Softech Solutions Ltd. adjourns Board Meeting to consider additional information for the proposed acquisition</li><li>Acquisition of 100% equity stake in a company via share swap</li><li>Subject to necessary approvals from shareholders, stock exchanges, and other authorities</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities of the Company by Designated Persons and their immediate relatives remains closed</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ae67ac55-10da-4bcf-ad83-822ce1713126.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Blue Cloud Softech Solutions Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>