<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 09:24:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ARMAN] Arman Holdings Ltd Appoints Mrs. Krishna Hareshbhai Bhatt as New Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Arman+Holdings+Ltd&title=Arman+Holdings+Ltd+Appoints+Mrs.+Krishna+Hareshbhai+Bhatt+as+New+Independent+Director&newsId=85846e4a-aaf1-45b5-8233-90b15326ce9e&token=ODU4NDZlNGEtYWFm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85846e4a-aaf1-45b5-8233-90b15326ce9e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 09:23:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Arman Holdings Ltd announced the appointment of Mrs. Krishna Hareshbhai Bhatt as an Additional Director designated as a Non-Executive Independent Director. The appointment is for a term of 5 consecutive years, subject to the approval of the company&apos;s members. Mrs. Bhatt is highly skilled and result-driven, with over five years of experience in the secretarial and legal fields. She is also a director of Boss Packaging Solutions Limited and 7NR Retails Private Limited. The appointment follows the resignation of Mr. Neel Sanjaykumar Singapuri as a Non-Executive Independent Director, effective from 15/01/2026.</p><ul><li>Arman Holdings Ltd appoints Mrs. Krishna Hareshbhai Bhatt as a new Independent Director.</li><li>Mrs. Bhatt has over five years of experience in the secretarial and legal fields.</li><li>She is also a director of Boss Packaging Solutions Limited and 7NR Retails Private Limited.</li><li>The appointment is subject to the approval of the company&apos;s members.</li><li>The resignation of Mr. Neel Sanjaykumar Singapuri as a Non-Executive Independent Director was noted.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/be338ddb-0e7d-4ed5-9752-32362d6208f4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Arman Holdings Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UDAYJEW] Uday Jewellery Industries Ltd to Utilize Surplus Funds and Avail Inter-Corporate Deposit</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Uday+Jewellery+Industries+Ltd&title=Uday+Jewellery+Industries+Ltd+to+Utilize+Surplus+Funds+and+Avail+Inter-Corporate+Deposit&newsId=ecddd076-6ddd-4723-8235-3b6e767341dd&token=ZWNkZGQwNzYtNmRk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ecddd076-6ddd-4723-8235-3b6e767341dd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 09:20:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Uday Jewellery Industries Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 21st January 2026 to consider and approve several matters. The agenda includes the utilization of surplus funds, including margins maintained for hedging and risk management purposes, for investment in shares and/or securities of other companies up to an amount not exceeding INR 10,00,00,000. Additionally, the Board will consider approving a proposal for availing Inter-Corporate Deposit(s) from Sanghi Jewellers Private Limited, a related party, for an aggregate amount not exceeding INR 10,00,00,000. The meeting will also address any other related matters as required under the Companies Act, 2013 and SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Uday Jewellery Industries Ltd to utilize surplus funds for investment in shares and/or securities of other companies</li><li>The company to avail Inter-Corporate Deposit(s) from a related party, Sanghi Jewellers Private Limited</li><li>The total amount for investment and deposit not to exceed INR 10,00,00,000</li><li>The meeting of the Board of Directors to be held on 21st January 2026</li><li>The company to treat the Inter-Corporate Deposit as a Related Party Transaction in accordance with Section 188 and other applicable provisions of the Companies Act, 2013</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a0daab6e-81d5-4880-bd6a-56ff6a270975.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Uday Jewellery Industries Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TATACAP] Tata Capital Ltd Changes Name of Joint Statutory Auditor to M S K A &amp; Associates LLP</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Tata+Capital+Ltd&title=Tata+Capital+Ltd+Changes+Name+of+Joint+Statutory+Auditor+to+M+S+K+A+%26+Associates+LLP&newsId=4b5e9461-2735-4a1c-834c-0737b005d68f&token=NGI1ZTk0NjEtMjcz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4b5e9461-2735-4a1c-834c-0737b005d68f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 09:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tata Capital Limited has informed the stock exchange about the change of name of its Joint Statutory Auditor. The firm M S K A &amp; Associates, which was a chartered accountants firm, has converted itself into a Limited Liability Partnership (LLP) under the provisions of the Limited Liability Partnership Act, 2008. The new name of the auditor is M S K A &amp; Associates LLP, Chartered Accountants with effect from January 13, 2026. The ICAI Firm Registration Number is 105047W/W101187.</p><ul><li>Tata Capital Ltd has changed the name of its Joint Statutory Auditor</li><li>The auditor firm M S K A &amp; Associates has converted into a Limited Liability Partnership (LLP)</li><li>The new name of the auditor is M S K A &amp; Associates LLP, Chartered Accountants</li><li>The change is effective from January 13, 2026</li><li>The ICAI Firm Registration Number is 105047W/W101187</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/997fc3da-cfd3-4ac2-846f-e29da72bdfc6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Tata Capital Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NTPC] NTPC Ltd Subsidiary Declares Commercial Operation of 300MW Solar PV Project in Rajasthan</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NTPC+LTD.&title=NTPC+Ltd+Subsidiary+Declares+Commercial+Operation+of+300MW+Solar+PV+Project+in+Rajasthan&newsId=533ee8a0-abde-41c3-a3ee-5cb345dc97a0&token=NTMzZWU4YTAtYWJk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">533ee8a0-abde-41c3-a3ee-5cb345dc97a0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 09:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>NTPC Ltd, through its subsidiary NTPC Green Energy Limited (NGEL), has declared the commercial operation of the first part capacity of 300MW out of 500MW Bhadla Solar PV Project in Rajasthan, operated by its stepdown subsidiary NTPC Renewable Energy Limited. This brings the total installed and commercial capacity of the NTPC group to 87,287 MW and 86,207 MW respectively.</p><ul><li>NTPC Ltd subsidiary, NTPC Green Energy Limited (NGEL), declares commercial operation of 300MW out of 500MW Bhadla Solar PV Project in Rajasthan.</li><li>Project operated by NTPC Renewable Energy Limited, a stepdown subsidiary of NTPC Limited.</li><li>Total installed and commercial capacity of NTPC group now at 87,287 MW and 86,207 MW respectively.</li><li>NTPC Green Energy Limited Group&apos;s current commercial capacity at 8010.28 MW.</li><li>Total installed capacity of the NGEL Group increases to 8310.28 MW with the addition of this new capacity.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/768658fb-dad6-4d21-b4e5-b4a80a67f79c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NTPC LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ANSALBU] Ansal Buildwell Ltd. to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on February 11, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ANSAL+BUILDWELL+LTD.-%24&title=Ansal+Buildwell+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+February+11%2C+2026&newsId=f78940f9-82a0-4d51-baf1-774f88cc1ea3&token=Zjc4OTQwZjktODJh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f78940f9-82a0-4d51-baf1-774f88cc1ea3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 09:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ansal Buildwell Ltd. has announced a meeting of its Board of Directors on February 11, 2026, at the Conference Room, 118, UFF, Prakashdeep, 7. Tolstoy Marg, New Delhi-1 10 001. The agenda of the meeting includes the consideration and approval of the Standalone and Consolidated Unaudited Financial Results of the Company for the quarter and nine months ended 31* December 2025.</p><ul><li>Ansal Buildwell Ltd. is set to approve its Q3 and nine months financial results on February 11, 2026.</li><li>The meeting will be held at the Conference Room, 118, UFF, Prakashdeep, 7. Tolstoy Marg, New Delhi-1 10 001.</li><li>The Board will consider and approve the Standalone and Consolidated Unaudited Financial Results of the Company for the quarter and nine months ended 31* December 2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6e553e13-e805-48c6-aff8-664f15350c10.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ANSAL BUILDWELL LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NUTRICIRCLE] Nutricircle Ltd: Resignation of Company Secretary and Appointment of New Company Secretary</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Nutricircle+Ltd&title=Nutricircle+Ltd%3A+Resignation+of+Company+Secretary+and+Appointment+of+New+Company+Secretary&newsId=c3a7fbe6-6600-4415-a050-a1b21662c0bb&token=YzNhN2ZiZTYtNjYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c3a7fbe6-6600-4415-a050-a1b21662c0bb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 09:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In a recent Board Meeting, Nutricircle Ltd announced the resignation of Mrs. Daljeet Kaur as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer due to personal reasons. The Board has approved the appointment of Ms. Aakansha Vaid as the new Company Secretary and Compliance Officer. The company also confirmed that there is no Unpublished Price Sensitive Information (UPSI) and the recent price movement is not supported by any financials or other reasons. The Promoter and Key Management Personnel (KMP) have not dealt with the scrip of the company directly or indirectly.</p><ul><li>Resignation of Mrs. Daljeet Kaur as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer</li><li>Appointment of Ms. Aakansha Vaid as the new Company Secretary and Compliance Officer</li><li>No Unpublished Price Sensitive Information (UPSI)</li><li>Price movement not supported by any financials or other reasons</li><li>Promoter and KMP have not dealt with the scrip of the company directly or indirectly</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/783f25f4-84ed-4c5d-a155-992fc3d52b67.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Nutricircle Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MONGIPA] Moongipa Capital Finance Ltd Announces Q3 and 9M 2025 Results with Limited Review Report</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MOONGIPA+CAPITAL+FINANCE+LTD.&title=Moongipa+Capital+Finance+Ltd+Announces+Q3+and+9M+2025+Results+with+Limited+Review+Report&newsId=0aa6f68b-b2bc-4841-8580-bee9ef96d2d1&token=MGFhNmY2OGItYjJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0aa6f68b-b2bc-4841-8580-bee9ef96d2d1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 09:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Moongipa Capital Finance Ltd has announced its unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The Board of Directors approved the results in a meeting on January 15, 2026, along with the Limited Review Report issued by the Statutory Auditors. The company&apos;s total revenue from operations for the quarter is Rs. 144.74 Lakhs and the profit before tax stands at Rs. 190.78 Lakhs. The earnings per share (EPS) is Rs. 2.15 (not annualised). The company&apos;s net profit margin is 14.15% and the total debts to total assets ratio is 0.701. The EPS for the nine months ended December 31, 2025, is Rs. 6.71 (not annualised).</p><ul><li>Moongipa Capital Finance Ltd announced its unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The Board of Directors approved the results in a meeting on January 15, 2026.</li><li>The total revenue from operations for the quarter is Rs. 144.74 Lakhs.</li><li>The profit before tax stands at Rs. 190.78 Lakhs.</li><li>The earnings per share (EPS) is Rs. 2.15 (not annualised).</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/05f5a862-ea81-4a9a-9121-d3417b8b8f40.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MOONGIPA CAPITAL FINANCE LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GODREJPROP] Godrej Properties Emerges as India&apos;s Largest Listed Residential Real Estate Developer for Second Consecutive Year</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Godrej+Properties+Ltd&title=Godrej+Properties+Emerges+as+India%27s+Largest+Listed+Residential+Real+Estate+Developer+for+Second+Consecutive+Year&newsId=98cbfe00-02a1-4d91-b0a8-412df35a3b9c&token=OThjYmZlMDAtMDJh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98cbfe00-02a1-4d91-b0a8-412df35a3b9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 09:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Godrej Properties Limited (GPL) has emerged as the largest listed residential real estate developer in India in Calendar Year 2025 for the second consecutive year, based on key operating metrics of booking value and cash collections. The company sold 16,428 homes with a total saleable area of 27.26 million sq. ft., supported by 41 successful project launches across India. Booking value grew 19% year-on-year to INR 34,171 crore, representing a CAGR of approximately 44% between CY 2022 and CY 2025. Collections for the year increased 28% to INR 18,979 crore, translating into a three-year CAGR of 35%.</p><ul><li>GPL sold 16,428 homes with a total saleable area of 27.26 million sq. ft.</li><li>41 successful project launches across India</li><li>Booking value grew 19% year-on-year to INR 34,171 crore</li><li>Collections increased 28% to INR 18,979 crore</li><li>Achieved a CAGR of approximately 44% in booking value and 35% in collections between CY 2022 and CY 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/318e0d30-d5ab-469e-bf88-5e357a06b0cf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Godrej Properties Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MONGIPA] Moongipa Capital Finance Ltd Confirms No Deviation in Rights Issue Proceeds Utilization</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MOONGIPA+CAPITAL+FINANCE+LTD.&title=Moongipa+Capital+Finance+Ltd+Confirms+No+Deviation+in+Rights+Issue+Proceeds+Utilization&newsId=deaa50c2-86ea-4e89-b0ab-6a594a261787&token=ZGVhYTUwYzItODZl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">deaa50c2-86ea-4e89-b0ab-6a594a261787</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 09:07:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Moongipa Capital Finance Ltd, in accordance with Regulation 32 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, has confirmed that there is no deviation in the use of proceeds from the Rights Issue. The company raised 1,527.40 Lakhs on January 02, 2025, and has fully utilized these funds in the quarter ended June 30, 2025, as per the Letter of Offer dated November 27, 2024. The Statement of Deviation was reviewed by the Audit Committee and found to be Nil.</p><ul><li>Moongipa Capital Finance Ltd confirms no deviation in Rights Issue proceeds utilization</li><li>Raised 1,527.40 Lakhs on January 02, 2025</li><li>Funds fully utilized in the quarter ended June 30, 2025</li><li>Statement of Deviation reviewed by the Audit Committee</li><li>Nil deviation found</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/eb23dd18-16d5-48be-884e-872fc831bda4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MOONGIPA CAPITAL FINANCE LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NUTRICIRCLE] Nutricircle Ltd: Board Meeting Approves Resignation of Company Secretary and Appoints New One</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Nutricircle+Ltd&title=Nutricircle+Ltd%3A+Board+Meeting+Approves+Resignation+of+Company+Secretary+and+Appoints+New+One&newsId=0b8f5b63-8012-4709-932c-e35cef2e3208&token=MGI4ZjViNjMtODAx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b8f5b63-8012-4709-932c-e35cef2e3208</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 09:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Nutricircle Ltd, in a board meeting held on 15th January 2026, took on record the resignation of Mrs. Daljeet Kaur as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer due to personal reasons. The board also approved the appointment of Ms. Aakansha Vaid as the new Company Secretary and Compliance Officer. The company has confirmed that there is no Unpublished Price Sensitive Information (UPSI) and the promoter and KMP have not dealt with the scrip of the company directly or indirectly.</p><ul><li>Resignation of Mrs. Daljeet Kaur as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer</li><li>Appointment of Ms. Aakansha Vaid as the new Company Secretary and Compliance Officer</li><li>No Unpublished Price Sensitive Information (UPSI)</li><li>Promoter and KMP have not dealt with the scrip of the company directly or indirectly</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/636c4d29-8d8b-4e76-a1ba-baf368907453.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Nutricircle Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>