<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 21:17:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[AVG] AVG Logistics Enters Liquid Logistics Through Train, Aiming to Enhance Safe and Reliable Chemical Transportation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AVG+Logistics+Ltd&title=AVG+Logistics+Enters+Liquid+Logistics+Through+Train%2C+Aiming+to+Enhance+Safe+and+Reliable+Chemical+Transportation&newsId=3560fda2-d3be-41be-a9ef-28c93fd9f9ac&token=MzU2MGZkYTItZDNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3560fda2-d3be-41be-a9ef-28c93fd9f9ac</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 20:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>AVG Logistics Ltd. has launched the transportation of liquid cargo using high-grade ISO tanks on trains, starting from January 07, 2026. This new venture is expected to generate an annual revenue of approximately Rs. 22-24 crore. The company has partnered with Central Warehousing Corporation for the long-term lease of its flatbed train and will offer cost-efficient, environmentally sustainable, and time-bound movement of liquid cargo. This initiative aligns with AVG Logistics’ focus on sustainability and operational efficiency.</p><ul><li>AVG Logistics launched a new business vertical for liquid cargo transportation using high-grade ISO tanks on trains.</li><li>The new venture is expected to generate an annual revenue of approximately Rs. 22-24 crore.</li><li>The company has partnered with Central Warehousing Corporation for the long-term lease of its flatbed train.</li><li>This initiative aims to offer cost-efficient, environmentally sustainable, and time-bound movement of liquid cargo.</li><li>The launch aligns with AVG Logistics’ focus on sustainability and operational efficiency.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3fd43065-d588-47dd-bcb6-43fa153cca0b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AVG Logistics Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RELHOME] Reliance Home Finance Reschedules CoC Meeting, Umesh Balaram Sonkar Appointed as Resolution Professional</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Reliance+Home+Finance+Ltd&title=Reliance+Home+Finance+Reschedules+CoC+Meeting%2C+Umesh+Balaram+Sonkar+Appointed+as+Resolution+Professional&newsId=c14fb477-143d-495f-9c5e-55078bad0e51&token=YzE0ZmI0NzctMTQz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c14fb477-143d-495f-9c5e-55078bad0e51</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:21:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Reliance Home Finance Ltd. has rescheduled the 5th Meeting of the Committee of Creditors (CoC) to January 8, 2026, at 11:30 A.M. (IST) through Video Conferencing. The meeting was initially scheduled for January 7, 2026. Umesh Balaram Sonkar has been appointed as the Resolution Professional in the matter of Reliance Home Finance Limited under Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP).</p><ul><li>Reliance Home Finance Ltd. reschedules the 5th Meeting of the Committee of Creditors (CoC) to January 8, 2026</li><li>The meeting was initially scheduled for January 7, 2026, and will now be held through Video Conferencing</li><li>Umesh Balaram Sonkar appointed as the Resolution Professional in the matter of Reliance Home Finance Limited under CIRP</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f9c87a19-cfb0-4569-8650-124e547e9ad2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Reliance Home Finance Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MOTHERSON] Samvardhana Motherson International Completes Joint Venture with Egtronics Co. Ltd.</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Samvardhana+Motherson+International+Ltd&title=Samvardhana+Motherson+International+Completes+Joint+Venture+with+Egtronics+Co.+Ltd.&newsId=d16ebafa-ff4e-448b-8933-fe6ca4424a47&token=ZDE2ZWJhZmEtZmY0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d16ebafa-ff4e-448b-8933-fe6ca4424a47</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:11:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Samvardhana Motherson International Limited has completed the formation of a joint venture with Egtronics Co. Ltd., a South Korean company. This joint venture, established on January 07, 2026, is designed to design, develop, manufacture, and assemble clean mobility related vehicle electronics. The product portfolio includes DC-DC converters, auxiliary inverters, traction inverters, on-board chargers, power distribution units, or a combination of these for application in automobile and other industries. The equity shareholding of Motherson Egtronics Electronics Solutions Limited, the wholly owned subsidiary of the Company, is held by the Company and Egtronics in the ratio of 51% and 49%, respectively.</p><ul><li>Samvardhana Motherson International Limited has completed a joint venture with Egtronics Co. Ltd.</li><li>The joint venture is established to design, develop, manufacture, and assemble clean mobility related vehicle electronics.</li><li>The product portfolio includes DC-DC converters, auxiliary inverters, traction inverters, on-board chargers, power distribution units, or a combination of these.</li><li>The joint venture is applicable for automobile and other industries.</li><li>The equity shareholding of Motherson Egtronics Electronics Solutions Limited is held by the Company and Egtronics in the ratio of 51% and 49%, respectively.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c5394faa-4962-4b90-9ba9-cbee7a845386.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADORMUL] Thrive Future Habitats Ltd. Confirms Relodgement of Transfer of Physical Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADOR+MULTIPRODUCTS+LTD.&title=Thrive+Future+Habitats+Ltd.+Confirms+Relodgement+of+Transfer+of+Physical+Shares&newsId=47d6500b-6229-4d3d-af5a-2b068e55279d&token=NDdkNjUwMGItNjIy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47d6500b-6229-4d3d-af5a-2b068e55279d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Thrive Future Habitats Ltd. has published a notice on its website to inform shareholders about the relodgement of transfer requests for physical shares. The notice was published in accordance with SEBI Circular SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97. The company received no requests for the relodgement of shares for transfer cum demat for the six-month period from July 07, 2025, till January 06, 2026. The company&apos;s Registrar and Share Transfer Agent, BgSE Financials Limited, also confirmed no requests were received, processed, approved, or rejected during this period.</p><ul><li>Thrive Future Habitats Ltd. publishes notice for relodgement of transfer requests for physical shares.</li><li>Notice published in accordance with SEBI Circular SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97.</li><li>No requests received, processed, approved, or rejected for the six-month period from July 07, 2025, till January 06, 2026.</li><li>Confirmation from the company&apos;s Registrar and Share Transfer Agent, BgSE Financials Limited.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ec03e65b-4962-4a29-8a6b-d17f67bc7a80.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADOR MULTIPRODUCTS LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NEPLOG] Neptune Logitek Invests Rs. 6 Crore in Blithwill Global Warehousing &amp; Infraventures, Utilizes IPO Proceeds Exclusively for Specified Purposes</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Neptune+Logitek+Ltd&title=Neptune+Logitek+Invests+Rs.+6+Crore+in+Blithwill+Global+Warehousing+%26+Infraventures%2C+Utilizes+IPO+Proceeds+Exclusively+for+Specified+Purposes&newsId=21f8a29f-5112-42ee-8e2b-05f8d6cbf838&token=MjFmOGEyOWYtNTEx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21f8a29f-5112-42ee-8e2b-05f8d6cbf838</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:44:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Neptune Logitek Ltd has made an investment of Rs. 2,50,00,000 in Optionally Convertible Redeemable Debentures (OCRDs) of Blithwill Global Warehousing Private Limited and Rs. 3,50,00,000 in OCRDs of Blithwill Global Infraventures Private Limited, totaling to Rs. 6 Crore. This investment has been funded entirely from the company&apos;s internal accruals, with no proceeds from the Initial Public Offer (IPO) utilized. The company is committed to utilizing the entire amount raised through the IPO exclusively for the purposes and objectives specified in the Prospectus, in a disciplined manner.</p><ul><li>Neptune Logitek invests Rs. 6 Crore in Blithwill Global Warehousing &amp; Infraventures</li><li>Investment funded entirely from internal accruals, no IPO proceeds utilized</li><li>Company committed to utilizing IPO proceeds exclusively for specified purposes</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2335767e-a0f9-4e22-b2ce-20e24d12e492.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Neptune Logitek Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FORTISMLR] Fortis Malar Hospitals Ltd: Ignore Earlier Announced Disclosure</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Fortis+Malar+Hospitals+Limited&title=Fortis+Malar+Hospitals+Ltd%3A+Ignore+Earlier+Announced+Disclosure&newsId=f75e5b2c-f032-41eb-a632-ca4e6c1973ea&token=Zjc1ZTViMmMtZjAz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f75e5b2c-f032-41eb-a632-ca4e6c1973ea</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Fortis Malar Hospitals Ltd has released a statement drawing attention to an earlier reported stock exchange announcement on January 2, 2026. The earlier announcement, titled &apos;Disclosure under Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligations &amp; Disclosure Requirements) Regulations 2015 (SEBI Listing Regulations)&apos;, was mistakenly attributed to Fortis Malar Hospitals Ltd, when in fact it pertains to another group company. Shareholders are advised to disregard the aforementioned announcement.</p><ul><li>Fortis Malar Hospitals Ltd has issued a statement regarding an earlier stock exchange announcement.</li><li>The earlier announcement was mistakenly attributed to Fortis Malar Hospitals Ltd.</li><li>The earlier announcement actually pertains to another group company.</li><li>Shareholders are advised to disregard the earlier announcement.</li><li>This update aims to clarify any confusion and keep shareholders informed.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a3547d16-538d-4be9-a448-e3601f9457f3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Fortis Malar Hospitals Limited | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZAGGLE] Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd Enters Agreement with Cubastion Consulting Private Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Zaggle+Prepaid+Ocean+Services+Ltd&title=Zaggle+Prepaid+Ocean+Services+Ltd+Enters+Agreement+with+Cubastion+Consulting+Private+Limited&newsId=e9d3c465-a5d6-4e86-a9cb-d47067b6247b&token=ZTlkM2M0NjUtYTVk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9d3c465-a5d6-4e86-a9cb-d47067b6247b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Partnership</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Limited has entered into an agreement with Cubastion Consulting Private Limited. The agreement is for Zaggle to provide the facility to procure and lease Mobile phones to the Employees of Cubastion Consulting Private Limited through Zaggle’s Employee Purchase Programme. The agreement is domestic and effective until terminated as specified within the agreement.</p><ul><li>Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd has entered into a partnership with Cubastion Consulting Private Limited</li><li>The partnership is for Zaggle to provide the facility to procure and lease Mobile phones to the Employees of Cubastion Consulting Private Limited through Zaggle’s Employee Purchase Programme</li><li>The agreement is domestic and effective until terminated as specified within the agreement</li><li>The partnership does not involve any related party transactions</li><li>The agreement is in line with Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd&apos;s business strategy of expanding its Employee Purchase Programme</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/088b987f-2169-4c8a-9d6a-83468276118e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd | Category: Partnership</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TEAMLEASE] TeamLease Appoints Mr. Vamsikrishna Ithamraju as Chief Digital and Information Officer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TeamLease+Services+Ltd&title=TeamLease+Appoints+Mr.+Vamsikrishna+Ithamraju+as+Chief+Digital+and+Information+Officer&newsId=f02b44ed-4202-4175-b3b7-edf01547f6b7&token=ZjAyYjQ0ZWQtNDIw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f02b44ed-4202-4175-b3b7-edf01547f6b7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:54:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>TeamLease Services Ltd. has appointed Mr. Vamsikrishna Ithamraju as the Chief Digital and Information Officer (CDIO). Mr. Ithamraju, with over two decades of experience in technology leadership, will lead the digital transformational projects and head the technology initiatives for TeamLease&apos;s Employment cluster. He has a strong track record of building and scaling high-performance engineering teams, modernizing legacy platforms, and driving cloud-native and AI-led transformations at scale. He was previously the CTO at Axis Mutual Fund, where he led large, multi-disciplinary technology teams and played a key role in building scalable digital platforms. Mr. Ithamraju holds an MBA in Systems from SP Jain School of Management, Singapore, and is certified in PMP, AWS Solutions Architecture, ITIL, and COBIT. He is also a recipient of multiple industry recognitions, including the IDC CIO100 Award.</p><ul><li>TeamLease appoints Mr. Vamsikrishna Ithamraju as Chief Digital and Information Officer (CDIO)</li><li>Mr. Ithamraju brings over two decades of experience in technology leadership across various sectors</li><li>He has a strong track record of building and scaling high-performance engineering teams</li><li>Mr. Ithamraju was previously the CTO at Axis Mutual Fund</li><li>He holds an MBA in Systems from SP Jain School of Management, Singapore, and is certified in PMP, AWS Solutions Architecture, ITIL, and COBIT</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/afada39f-a5c1-43d4-b873-6e67ce910ea6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TeamLease Services Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BCG] Brightcom Subsidiary, Online Media Solutions, Recognized as &apos;Needle-Moving Player&apos; in Jounce Media Report</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Brightcom+Group+Ltd&title=Brightcom+Subsidiary%2C+Online+Media+Solutions%2C+Recognized+as+%27Needle-Moving+Player%27+in+Jounce+Media+Report&newsId=dadc6a1a-7f6f-4f92-8fac-f860c2c7befc&token=ZGFkYzZhMWEtN2Y2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dadc6a1a-7f6f-4f92-8fac-f860c2c7befc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:47:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Online Media Solutions (OMS), a wholly owned subsidiary of Brightcom Group Limited, has been referenced in Jounce Media’s 2025 industry report. The report analyzes trends in programmatic supply access across the digital advertising ecosystem and notes an approximate 4.9% increase in supply coverage during December-2025 for OMS. This increase reflects ongoing efforts to expand and optimize direct supply integrations across web and mobile app environments. Jounce Media’s research is widely used by participants across the digital advertising ecosystem to track programmatic supply and demand trends, monitor shifts in publisher share, and benchmark performance against peers. Brightcom views this reference as a third-party industry observation, made in the interest of transparency and to keep shareholders informed of relevant industry-level developments relating to the Company’s operating businesses.</p><ul><li>Brightcom Group Ltd&apos;s subsidiary, Online Media Solutions, recognized in Jounce Media’s 2025 industry report</li><li>OMS described as a ‘needle-moving player’ in supply access growth</li><li>Approximately 4.9% increase in supply coverage during December-2025</li><li>Recognition reflects efforts to expand and optimize direct supply integrations across web and mobile app environments</li><li>Jounce Media’s research widely used by participants across the digital advertising ecosystem</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/00cc057a-76c9-4285-b19f-29b1445757db.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Brightcom Group Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHANKARA] Shankara Buildpro Limited Receives Approval for Listing Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shankara+Building+Products+Ltd&title=Shankara+Buildpro+Limited+Receives+Approval+for+Listing+Equity+Shares&newsId=47894a2b-b359-411b-918e-3fade7d3df66&token=NDc4OTRhMmItYjM1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47894a2b-b359-411b-918e-3fade7d3df66</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:41:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shankara Buildpro Limited has received approval from BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange of India Limited for listing and trading of its equity shares, effective January 09, 2026. This information comes after the sanction of the Scheme of Arrangement amongst Shankara Building Products Limited, Shankara Buildpro Limited, and their respective shareholders and creditors by the Hon’ble National Company Law Tribunal, Bengaluru Bench.</p><ul><li>Shankara Buildpro Limited receives approval for listing and trading of its equity shares</li><li>Listing to be effective from January 09, 2026</li><li>Approval received from BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange of India Limited</li><li>This follows the sanction of the Scheme of Arrangement by the Hon’ble National Company Law Tribunal, Bengaluru Bench</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/837f83bc-35ec-414a-a16a-b26f9c5f055c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shankara Building Products Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>