<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:47:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[DBEIL] Deepak Builders and Engineers India Ltd. Seeks Withdrawal of SEBI&apos;s Administrative Warning</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Deepak+Builders+and+Engineers+India+Ltd&title=Deepak+Builders+and+Engineers+India+Ltd.+Seeks+Withdrawal+of+SEBI%27s+Administrative+Warning&newsId=d306465b-9481-459c-b0c4-23f0d9cb440d&token=ZDMwNjQ2NWItOTQ4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d306465b-9481-459c-b0c4-23f0d9cb440d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:42:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Deepak Builders and Engineers India Ltd. has submitted a formal representation to the Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) seeking withdrawal of an Administrative Warning issued by the regulatory body. The company is committed to maintaining the highest standards of corporate governance and regulatory compliance. The Board of Directors has expressed its commitment to full regulatory compliance and has decided to take corrective and preventive measures, including the implementation of a litigation tracking system. The company argues that the warning was issued based on a misunderstanding, as no arbitration proceedings or litigation were initiated at the relevant point of time. The company also asserts that the pre-institution mediation notice received does not amount to the commencement of litigation.</p><ul><li>Deepak Builders and Engineers India Ltd. has submitted a formal representation to SEBI seeking withdrawal of an Administrative Warning.</li><li>The company is committed to maintaining the highest standards of corporate governance and regulatory compliance.</li><li>The Board of Directors has expressed its commitment to full regulatory compliance and has decided to take corrective and preventive measures.</li><li>The company argues that the warning was issued based on a misunderstanding as no arbitration proceedings or litigation were initiated.</li><li>The company asserts that the pre-institution mediation notice received does not amount to the commencement of litigation.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/199a6e48-b9ef-4432-8566-f9c6c2e1a0c4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Deepak Builders and Engineers India Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TEXRAIL] Texmaco Rail &amp; Engineering and RVNL Form Joint Venture to Boost India&apos;s Rail Manufacturing and Global EPC Footprint</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TEXMACO+RAIL+%26+ENGINEERING+LTD.&title=Texmaco+Rail+%26+Engineering+and+RVNL+Form+Joint+Venture+to+Boost+India%27s+Rail+Manufacturing+and+Global+EPC+Footprint&newsId=381faf20-6fb3-449f-ba3e-42fa3c4f1f28&token=MzgxZmFmMjAtNmZi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">381faf20-6fb3-449f-ba3e-42fa3c4f1f28</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:42:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Texmaco Rail &amp; Engineering Ltd. and Rail Vikas Nigam Limited (RVNL) have formalized a strategic partnership by signing a Joint Venture Shareholders’ Agreement. This alliance aims to accelerate India’s rail manufacturing capabilities, strengthen its position as a global infrastructure solutions provider, and deliver sustainable, scalable, and future-ready rail solutions. The joint venture will focus on advanced rolling stock segments, lifecycle maintenance and asset management solutions, and large-scale EPC and turnkey infrastructure projects in India and overseas markets.</p><ul><li>Texmaco Rail &amp; Engineering and RVNL form a strategic joint venture to boost India&apos;s rail manufacturing capabilities and global EPC footprint</li><li>The joint venture aims to deliver sustainable, scalable, and future-ready rail solutions for India and the world</li><li>The partnership focuses on advanced rolling stock segments, lifecycle maintenance, asset management solutions, and large-scale EPC projects in India and overseas markets</li><li>The collaboration leverages Texmaco’s industrial manufacturing scale and export reach with RVNL’s proven execution track record in complex rail EPC projects</li><li>The JV is expected to generate large-scale industrial activity, support domestic MSME ecosystems, and create thousands of skilled jobs across India’s manufacturing corridors</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/548bbb16-e9b9-43c4-9261-0aee9555edba.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TEXMACO RAIL & ENGINEERING LTD. | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PINELABS] Pine Labs Ltd Completes 100% Acquisition of Agya Technologies for INR 13.9 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Pine+Labs+Ltd&title=Pine+Labs+Ltd+Completes+100%25+Acquisition+of+Agya+Technologies+for+INR+13.9+Crores&newsId=465cd299-79eb-48e0-97cf-ad5be2512df8&token=NDY1Y2QyOTktNzll</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">465cd299-79eb-48e0-97cf-ad5be2512df8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:42:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Pine Labs Ltd, a leading technology company, has completed the acquisition of 100% stake in Agya Technologies, a Private Limited Company incorporated under the Companies Act, 2013, on April 26, 2021. Agya Technologies is in the business of online account aggregation for financial information. The acquisition was made for a cash consideration of INR 13,90,00,000. Pine Labs Ltd, through its wholly owned subsidiary BrokenTusk Technologies Private Limited (BTPL), acquired 10,000 equity shares from the existing shareholders of Agya Technologies, thereby increasing its stake from 25.40% to 100%.</p><ul><li>Pine Labs Ltd completes 100% acquisition of Agya Technologies</li><li>Acquisition made for a cash consideration of INR 13,90,00,000</li><li>Agya Technologies is in the business of online account aggregation for financial information</li><li>BrokenTusk Technologies Private Limited (BTPL) acquired 10,000 equity shares</li><li>Agya Technologies becomes a step-down subsidiary of the Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0fb2663f-d157-45fb-8aa5-2f46b8527c49.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Pine Labs Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HOWARHO] Howard Hotels Ltd Fined by BSE for Delay in Board Meeting Approval of Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HOWARD+HOTELS+LTD.&title=Howard+Hotels+Ltd+Fined+by+BSE+for+Delay+in+Board+Meeting+Approval+of+Financial+Results&newsId=f066e5d2-d6eb-4fbd-8ef6-aa7757d45c89&token=ZjA2NmU1ZDItZDZl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f066e5d2-d6eb-4fbd-8ef6-aa7757d45c89</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:42:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Howard Hotels Ltd has been fined by BSE for non-compliance with Regulation 29(2)/29(3) of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015. The non-compliance was due to inadvertent delay in prior intimation of the Board Meeting for approval of financial results for the quarter ended 31st December, 2025. The Board of Directors has noted the oversight and directed the management to strengthen internal compliance monitoring mechanisms to prevent future recurrences. The fine has been remitted by the Company.</p><ul><li>Howard Hotels Ltd fined by BSE for non-compliance with SEBI regulations</li><li>The non-compliance was due to inadvertent delay in prior intimation of the Board Meeting for financial results approval</li><li>The Board of Directors has noted the oversight and directed management to strengthen internal compliance monitoring mechanisms</li><li>The fine has been remitted by the Company</li><li>The fine was levied for non-compliance with Regulation 29(2)/29(3) of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/80f5d07e-82e3-43ca-9a23-91f8770bb994.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HOWARD HOTELS LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PANORAMA] Panorama Studios International Ltd Acquires Airborne Rights of Two Short Films from Minara Film Corp</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Panorama+Studios+International+Ltd&title=Panorama+Studios+International+Ltd+Acquires+Airborne+Rights+of+Two+Short+Films+from+Minara+Film+Corp&newsId=312f2db3-212c-42cb-a5f5-572191203535&token=MzEyZjJkYjMtMjEy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">312f2db3-212c-42cb-a5f5-572191203535</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:41:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Panorama Studios International Ltd has executed an Assignment Agreement with Minara Film Corp to exploit the Airborne Rights (on an exclusive basis) for the entire world including India. The two short films involved are &apos;Pereira House&apos; and &apos;Break the Silence&apos;. &apos;Pereira House&apos; stars Vishwajeet Pradhan, Sanjay Gurbani, Sai Ketan Rao, Shivangi Khedkar, Bhavesh Bhat and others, and is directed by Hemant Chauhan. &apos;Break the Silence&apos; features Anupriya Goenka, Rohit Phatak, Priya Raina, Yukti Kapoor, Rajansh Singhal and others, and is also directed by Hemant Chauhan.</p><ul><li>Panorama Studios International Ltd acquires Airborne Rights of two short films from Minara Film Corp</li><li>The two short films involved are &apos;Pereira House&apos; and &apos;Break the Silence&apos;</li><li>Both films are directed by Hemant Chauhan</li><li>Pereira House stars Vishwajeet Pradhan, Sanjay Gurbani, Sai Ketan Rao, Shivangi Khedkar, Bhavesh Bhat and others</li><li>Break the Silence features Anupriya Goenka, Rohit Phatak, Priya Raina, Yukti Kapoor, Rajansh Singhal and others</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/56ebd322-cfc1-4edf-b06d-eba21204d1f5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Panorama Studios International Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASSOCIATED] Associated Coaters Ltd Reiterates Adherence to SEBI Regulations Amid Share Price Fluctuations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Associated+Coaters+Ltd&title=Associated+Coaters+Ltd+Reiterates+Adherence+to+SEBI+Regulations+Amid+Share+Price+Fluctuations&newsId=0232b2cf-8fda-4e3a-9e9d-dc1ad342ce49&token=MDIzMmIyY2YtOGZk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0232b2cf-8fda-4e3a-9e9d-dc1ad342ce49</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Associated Coaters Ltd has clarified a recent price movement in their securities, stating that the movement is due to market conditions and not under their control. The company has consistently disclosed all events and price sensitive information as required by the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. They reiterate their commitment to keeping the Stock Exchange informed of any necessary information under the said regulations.</p><ul><li>Associated Coaters Ltd has clarified recent price movement in their securities.</li><li>The price movement is attributed to market conditions, not under the company&apos;s control.</li><li>The company has consistently disclosed all events and price sensitive information as required by SEBI regulations.</li><li>They reiterate their commitment to keeping the Stock Exchange informed of any necessary information.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7252edce-8a9a-4080-b15c-b4f2d24e44c0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Associated Coaters Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JAIBALAJI] Jai Balaji Industries Ltd Receives ESG Rating of 60.8 for FY 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JAI+BALAJI+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Jai+Balaji+Industries+Ltd+Receives+ESG+Rating+of+60.8+for+FY+2025&newsId=0170eee2-4f94-4180-853c-c169d35a7398&token=MDE3MGVlZTItNGY5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0170eee2-4f94-4180-853c-c169d35a7398</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:41:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jai Balaji Industries Ltd has been assigned an ESG rating of &apos;60.8&apos; for the financial year 2025 by SES ESG Research Private Limited. This rating is based on the company&apos;s performance on Environmental, Social, and Governance parameters. The company clarifies that they have not engaged SES ESG for this rating and the report is independently prepared by them based on information available in the public domain.</p><ul><li>Jai Balaji Industries Ltd receives an ESG rating of 60.8 for FY 2025</li><li>Rating provided by SES ESG Research Private Limited</li><li>Rating reflects the company&apos;s performance on Environmental, Social, and Governance parameters</li><li>Company did not engage SES ESG for this rating</li><li>Report prepared by SES ESG based on publicly available information</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9d8d8e24-8dc9-4694-8b4b-de36609c02b9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JAI BALAJI INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BARONINF] Baron Infotech Ltd Board Meeting Cancelled Due to Lack of Quorum</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BARON+INFOTECH+LTD.&title=Baron+Infotech+Ltd+Board+Meeting+Cancelled+Due+to+Lack+of+Quorum&newsId=fd20a5e7-e681-4cd4-93db-d8773499ee8f&token=ZmQyMGE1ZTctZTY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd20a5e7-e681-4cd4-93db-d8773499ee8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:41:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In accordance with the Companies Act, 2013 and Secretarial Standards-1 for Board Meetings, the Board Meeting of Baron Infotech Limited, originally scheduled for 13.02.2026, could not be held due to lack of quorum. The meeting stood cancelled as there was no quorum present in the adjourned meeting. This information is for record and compliance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Baron Infotech Limited&apos;s Board Meeting could not be held due to lack of quorum</li><li>The meeting was originally scheduled for 13.02.2026 and was adjourned to 20.02.2026</li><li>The adjourned meeting also could not be held due to lack of quorum</li><li>The meeting stands cancelled in accordance with the Companies Act, 2013 and Secretarial Standards-1 for Board Meetings</li><li>This information is provided for record and compliance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9843195c-1bd5-4a2c-a66f-1325767c39ba.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BARON INFOTECH LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LAHL] Ladam Affordable Housing Ltd. Approves Waiver of Outstanding Loans to Associate Companies</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ladam+Affordable+Housing+Ltd&title=Ladam+Affordable+Housing+Ltd.+Approves+Waiver+of+Outstanding+Loans+to+Associate+Companies&newsId=b5ae0fed-5ba0-471a-ba49-947c2aa5f82e&token=YjVhZTBmZWQtNWJh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5ae0fed-5ba0-471a-ba49-947c2aa5f82e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:39:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>In a recent Board meeting on February 20, 2026, Ladam Affordable Housing Ltd. approved the waiver of outstanding loans granted to its Associate Companies - Ladam Foods Private Limited and Lacon India Limited. The meeting, which started at 5:00 P.M and concluded at 5:30 P.M, also included the consideration and approval of other items. This development is in accordance with Regulation 30 and Schedule 11, Part A of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Ladam Affordable Housing Ltd. approved the waiver of outstanding loans granted to Ladam Foods Private Limited and Lacon India Limited.</li><li>The decision is in accordance with Regulation 30 and Schedule 11, Part A of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li><li>The meeting was held on February 20, 2026, and started at 5:00 P.M, concluding at 5:30 P.M.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6234a8bd-5579-4d9b-9a8b-f7c27fb2baba.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ladam Affordable Housing Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KWIL] Unilever Acquires Majority Shares in Kwality Walls (India) Ltd Through Scheme of Arrangement</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KWIL&title=Unilever+Acquires+Majority+Shares+in+Kwality+Walls+%28India%29+Ltd+Through+Scheme+of+Arrangement&newsId=e2b8f7f1-9d3b-410a-acaa-7bc643db8b64&token=ZTJiOGY3ZjEtOWQz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e2b8f7f1-9d3b-410a-acaa-7bc643db8b64</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Unilever Plc, along with other promoter and promoter entities, has acquired 61.90% of the equity shares in Kwality Walls (India) Ltd. The acquisition was made pursuant to the Scheme of Arrangement for demerger of the Ice Cream Business Undertaking between Hindustan Unilever Limited and Kwality Walls (India) Limited and their respective shareholders. The transaction was exempted from making an open offer under Regulation 10(1)(d)(ii). The equity shares were allotted on 12th December 2025 and listed for trading from 16th February 2026.</p><ul><li>Unilever Plc and other promoter and promoter entities acquire 61.90% shares in Kwality Walls (India) Ltd</li><li>Acquisition made pursuant to the Scheme of Arrangement for demerger of the Ice Cream Business Undertaking</li><li>Exemption from making open offer under Regulation 10(1)(d)(ii)</li><li>Equity shares allotted on 12th December 2025</li><li>Shares listed for trading from 16th February 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/73F3DEF9_463E_4F8B_B5BC_C8263E236970_175850.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KWIL | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>