<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 01:30:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[EXCELSOFT] Excelsoft Technologies Ltd Announces Changes in Senior Management and Key Managerial Personnel</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Excelsoft+Technologies+Ltd&title=Excelsoft+Technologies+Ltd+Announces+Changes+in+Senior+Management+and+Key+Managerial+Personnel&newsId=082a284e-d171-46b3-8da0-26f22900ddb6&token=MDgyYTI4NGUtZDE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">082a284e-d171-46b3-8da0-26f22900ddb6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 00:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Excelsoft Technologies Ltd has announced changes in its senior management and key managerial personnel. The changes in senior management include designation changes for Mr. Jambardi Ramanna Maheshkumar, Mr. Ajay Ramesh, and Mr. Prashanth H M Kulkarni. The company has also announced the resignation of Mr. Venkatesh Dayananda as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer and the appointment of Mr. S.M. Adithya Jain as the new Company Secretary, Chief Compliance Officer, and Chief Investor Relations Officer.</p><ul><li>Changes in the responsibilities and designation of Senior Management Personnel at Excelsoft Technologies Ltd</li><li>Resignation of Mr. Venkatesh Dayananda as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer</li><li>Appointment of Mr. S.M. Adithya Jain as Company Secretary, Chief Compliance Officer, and Chief Investor Relations Officer</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/218bb646-975c-4567-ac2d-68c4e07db57a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Excelsoft Technologies Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EXCELSOFT] Excelsoft Technologies Ltd Reports Q3 FY2025 Financial Results with 2,484.41 Million Total Income</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Excelsoft+Technologies+Ltd&title=Excelsoft+Technologies+Ltd+Reports+Q3+FY2025+Financial+Results+with+2%2C484.41+Million+Total+Income&newsId=c1566dc2-20a1-4b37-8375-e3e20ab1f38d&token=YzE1NjZkYzItMjBh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c1566dc2-20a1-4b37-8375-e3e20ab1f38d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Excelsoft Technologies Ltd, a leading technology company, has reported its financial results for the third quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s total income stood at 2,484.41 Million INR, with a profit for the period of 97.33 Million INR. The board also announced changes in senior management and key managerial personnel. The company&apos;s financial results were reviewed by the audit committee and approved by the board of directors.</p><ul><li>Excelsoft Technologies Ltd reported a total income of 2,484.41 Million INR for Q3 FY2025</li><li>The company&apos;s profit for the period was 97.33 Million INR</li><li>Changes in senior management and key managerial personnel announced</li><li>The financial results were reviewed by the audit committee and approved by the board of directors</li><li>The company&apos;s equity shares were listed on National Stock Exchange of India Limited and BSE Limited on November 26, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/abd490ef-cdb2-4afc-81cd-69ac3aaac7ee.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Excelsoft Technologies Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SEAMECLTD] Seamec Ltd&apos;s Vessel SEAMEC II Charter Hire Period Extended with ONGC Until August 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SEAMEC+LTD.&title=Seamec+Ltd%27s+Vessel+SEAMEC+II+Charter+Hire+Period+Extended+with+ONGC+Until+August+2026&newsId=a21cbd8b-714b-49fb-a34f-6404afccab24&token=YTIxY2JkOGItNzE0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a21cbd8b-714b-49fb-a34f-6404afccab24</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Seamec Ltd has informed about the extension of the charter hire period for its vessel SEAMEC II with ONGC. The contract period is now extended until August 25, 2026. The terms and conditions of the original contract remain unchanged. This announcement was made on February 06, 2026, at 22:33 hours.</p><ul><li>Seamec Ltd&apos;s Vessel SEAMEC II charter hire period extended with ONGC</li><li>Extension until August 25, 2026</li><li>Original contract terms and conditions remain unchanged</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4238c328-8506-41ea-b5dd-9c57e0d76b28.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SEAMEC LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NLCINDIA] NLC India Ltd Issues and Allocates Commercial Paper Worth ₹ 1,300 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NLC+India+Ltd&title=NLC+India+Ltd+Issues+and+Allocates+Commercial+Paper+Worth+%E2%82%B9+1%2C300+Crores&newsId=35cfa8ca-5e5d-48de-a93a-3f4f00fa9974&token=MzVjZmE4Y2EtNWU1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">35cfa8ca-5e5d-48de-a93a-3f4f00fa9974</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 22:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>NLC India Ltd has issued and allotted 26,000 Nos. of Commercial Paper, each with a face value of ₹ 5,00,000. The total value of these commercial papers amounts to ₹ 1,300 crores, divided into two parts: ₹ 800 crores and ₹ 500 crores. This disclosure is in accordance with Regulation 30 and 51 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>NLC India Ltd has issued and allotted 26,000 Commercial Papers.</li><li>Each Commercial Paper has a face value of ₹ 5,00,000.</li><li>The total value of the Commercial Papers is ₹ 1,300 crores.</li><li>The Commercial Papers are issued in two parts: ₹ 800 crores and ₹ 500 crores.</li><li>This disclosure is in accordance with SEBI regulations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7487b53b-886e-4ebd-9a9f-97a77ebadea1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NLC India Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GODIGIT] Go Digit General Insurance Ltd Faces GST Search Regulations Inspection</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Go+Digit+General+Insurance+Ltd&title=Go+Digit+General+Insurance+Ltd+Faces+GST+Search+Regulations+Inspection&newsId=0646c82c-1407-4770-8f0c-58b35c4e0524&token=MDY0NmM4MmMtMTQw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0646c82c-1407-4770-8f0c-58b35c4e0524</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Go Digit General Insurance Ltd has disclosed a search conducted by the Directorate General of Goods &amp; Service Tax Intelligence, Gurugram Zonal Unit pursuant to Regulation 30 read with Para A of Part A of Schedule Il of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The search commenced on 5th February 2026 and concluded on 6th February 2026. The company does not foresee any material impact on its financials, operations, or other activities due to this search.</p><ul><li>Go Digit General Insurance Ltd faced a search conducted by the Directorate General of Goods &amp; Service Tax Intelligence, Gurugram Zonal Unit.</li><li>The search commenced on 5th February 2026 and concluded on 6th February 2026.</li><li>No official document has been issued regarding any adverse findings.</li><li>Summons have been issued to representatives of the Company to appear before the Authority for further questioning and statements.</li><li>The company does not foresee any material impact on its financials, operations, or other activities due to this search.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/946b73c0-894a-47bb-9abf-cb6c75836bf6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Go Digit General Insurance Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EXCELSOFT] Excelsoft Technologies Ltd Announces Q3 Results, Changes in Senior Management, and KMP Appointments</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Excelsoft+Technologies+Ltd&title=Excelsoft+Technologies+Ltd+Announces+Q3+Results%2C+Changes+in+Senior+Management%2C+and+KMP+Appointments&newsId=edc0ddd3-3e69-42f1-9124-028a8089ac77&token=ZWRjMGRkZDMtM2U2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">edc0ddd3-3e69-42f1-9124-028a8089ac77</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:41:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Excelsoft Technologies Ltd has announced its un-audited financial results for the third quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue stands at INR 1,631.64 million, with a profit before tax of INR 318.34 million. The board also approved changes in the designation of Senior Management Personnel and announced the resignation of the Company Secretary and Compliance Officer, along with the appointment of a new Company Secretary, Chief Compliance Officer, and Chief Investor Relations Officer.</p><ul><li>Excelsoft Technologies Ltd reports a revenue of INR 1,631.64 million for Q3 2025</li><li>The company records a profit before tax of INR 318.34 million for the quarter</li><li>Changes in the designation of Senior Management Personnel announced</li><li>Resignation of Company Secretary and Compliance Officer confirmed</li><li>Appointment of new Company Secretary, Chief Compliance Officer, and Chief Investor Relations Officer approved</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1f7244fe-c527-4b34-b702-302f4d657571.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Excelsoft Technologies Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[METSL] Maestros Electronics Secures Rs. 1.99 Crore Order from MD National Health Mission Jaipur</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Maestros+Electronics+%26+Telecommunications+Systems+Ltd&title=Maestros+Electronics+Secures+Rs.+1.99+Crore+Order+from+MD+National+Health+Mission+Jaipur&newsId=3b555ce1-f480-4ac7-8639-796ce2ef96cb&token=M2I1NTVjZTEtZjQ4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b555ce1-f480-4ac7-8639-796ce2ef96cb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Maestros Electronics &amp; Telecommunications Systems Ltd has announced that it has received a purchase order from MD National Health Mission Jaipur for the supply of 378 pieces of METSL 12 Channels ECG Machine. The contract is governed by the General Terms and Conditions and is valued at Rs. 1,99,52,730 exclusive of applicable taxes. The order is to be executed between February 03, 2026, and December 31, 2027. Neither the promoter of the company nor the promoter group/group companies have any interest in the entity that awarded the order.</p><ul><li>Maestros Electronics has received a purchase order from MD National Health Mission Jaipur</li><li>The order is for the supply of 378 pieces of METSL 12 Channels ECG Machine</li><li>The contract value is Rs. 1,99,52,730 exclusive of applicable taxes</li><li>The order is to be executed between February 03, 2026, and December 31, 2027</li><li>Neither the promoter of the company nor the promoter group/group companies have any interest in the entity that awarded the order</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ad9dc8e6-bf96-4b59-b4a8-6e8b3b9b7c7d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Maestros Electronics & Telecommunications Systems Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VALLABHSQ] Vallabh Steels Ltd. to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on 13th February, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VALLABH+STEELS+LTD.-%24&title=Vallabh+Steels+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+13th+February%2C+2026&newsId=836c90bc-f310-4450-800e-9efa698f91ba&token=ODM2YzkwYmMtZjMx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">836c90bc-f310-4450-800e-9efa698f91ba</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:21:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vallabh Steels Ltd. has announced a Board of Directors meeting on 13th February, 2026 to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ending 31st December, 2025. The meeting is scheduled in accordance with Regulation 29(1) of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. Additionally, in line with the Company’s Code of Conduct for Prevention of Insider Trading, the Trading Window for dealing in securities of the Company will be closed from 1st January, 2026 until 48 hours after the declaration of the Unaudited Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Vallabh Steels Ltd. to approve Q3 and nine months financial results on 13th February, 2026</li><li>The meeting is scheduled in accordance with Regulation 29(1) of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Trading Window for dealing in securities of the Company will be closed from 1st January, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5741f4f7-5cdd-4879-b4ef-26e515c8ab57.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VALLABH STEELS LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HCG] HealthCare Global Enterprises Ltd. Reports 13% YoY Revenue Growth in Q3FY26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HealthCare+Global+Enterprises+Ltd&title=HealthCare+Global+Enterprises+Ltd.+Reports+13%25+YoY+Revenue+Growth+in+Q3FY26&newsId=a6a44453-1937-4887-8cdf-69270ff981ee&token=YTZhNDQ0NTMtMTkz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a6a44453-1937-4887-8cdf-69270ff981ee</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:21:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>HealthCare Global Enterprises Ltd. (HCG), India’s largest dedicated cancer hospital network, has announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company reported a 13% YoY increase in revenue from operations, amounting to Rs. 6,331 Mn in Q3FY26. The adjusted EBITDA for the quarter was Rs. 1,108 Mn, marking a 20% YoY growth. The adjusted EBITDA margin stood at 17.5%, indicating a 98 bps YoY expansion. The adjusted PAT (Post IND AS) was Rs. 70 Mn, down from Rs. 371 Mn in the same period last year. The company remains committed to delivering high-quality oncology care and advancing clinical research in the field of cancer care.</p><ul><li>13% YoY growth in revenue from operations in Q3FY26</li><li>20% YoY increase in adjusted EBITDA in Q3FY26</li><li>98 bps YoY expansion in adjusted EBITDA margin in Q3FY26</li><li>Normalized adjusted PAT (Post IND AS) of Rs. 70 Mn in Q3FY26</li><li>Continued focus on delivering high-quality oncology care and advancing clinical research</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2223dcd3-1e4b-43c9-8183-0d41eea248d4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HealthCare Global Enterprises Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EROSMEDIA] Eros International Media Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025 on Feb 13, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=EROS+INTERNATIONAL+MEDIA+LTD.&title=Eros+International+Media+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025+on+Feb+13%2C+2026&newsId=44c58f6b-a343-4179-b2a6-ed9b503aa35b&token=NDRjNThmNmItYTM0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">44c58f6b-a343-4179-b2a6-ed9b503aa35b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 17:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Eros International Media Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 13, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting is scheduled in accordance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, and the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015. The trading window for dealing in the company&apos;s securities will be closed from January 01, 2026, to 48 hours after the announcement of the financial results for the quarter ended 31st December, 2025.</p><ul><li>Eros International Media Ltd to approve Q3 and nine months results for 2025 on Feb 13, 2026</li><li>Meeting scheduled in accordance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the company&apos;s securities will be closed from January 01, 2026, to 48 hours after the announcement of the financial results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f9d3f298-dd84-406e-82c5-1ca12c2fdaf4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: EROS INTERNATIONAL MEDIA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>