<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 04:07:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[OSWALPUMPS] Oswal Pumps Secures Rs. 119.92 Crore Solar Pump Order under PM-KUSUM B Scheme</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Oswal+Pumps+Ltd&title=Oswal+Pumps+Secures+Rs.+119.92+Crore+Solar+Pump+Order+under+PM-KUSUM+B+Scheme&newsId=dd97215f-f21f-43f3-852e-2402bcf81edd&token=ZGQ5NzIxNWYtZjIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd97215f-f21f-43f3-852e-2402bcf81edd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 04:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Oswal Pumps Ltd has received a Letter of Award from Karnataka Renewable Energy Development Limited for 214 Surface Solar Agriculture Pumps Set and 3049 Submersible Solar Agriculture Pump Sets for the entire state of Karnataka under Component-B of PM-KUSUM scheme. The total value of the pumps is approximately Rs. 119.92 Crore (inclusive of GST). The order involves design, manufacture, supply, transport, installation, testing, and commissioning of solar agriculture pumps, along with system warranty, repair, maintenance, and remote monitoring for 5 years. The installation and commissioning, along with RMS integration and submission of invoices and documents, are to be carried out on or before March 31, 2026.</p><ul><li>Oswal Pumps has secured an order worth approximately Rs. 119.92 Crore from Karnataka Renewable Energy Development Limited under the PM-KUSUM B Scheme.</li><li>The order involves the supply and installation of 3,263 Off-Grid DC Solar Photovoltaic Water Pumping Systems across Karnataka.</li><li>The pumps will be in 3 HP, 5 HP, 7.5 HP, and 10 HP capacities, supporting sustainable irrigation and promoting renewable energy in the agricultural sector.</li><li>This order strengthens Oswal Pumps&apos; position as a leading player in the solar pumping solutions segment and reflects its strong execution capabilities and manufacturing expertise.</li><li>The project is expected to further strengthen Oswal Pumps&apos; presence in Karnataka and enable deeper market penetration.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3a451768-5f27-4969-9e09-da44860c7608.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Oswal Pumps Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LT] L&amp;T Secures Contract for India&apos;s Biggest Pumped Storage Project</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LARSEN+%26+TOUBRO+LTD.&title=L%26T+Secures+Contract+for+India%27s+Biggest+Pumped+Storage+Project&newsId=e0d1c2c1-3ab1-4b7d-b38e-4b3bceae7841&token=ZTBkMWMyYzEtM2Fi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0d1c2c1-3ab1-4b7d-b38e-4b3bceae7841</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 04:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>The Heavy Civil Infrastructure business vertical of L&amp;T has secured a large order from Torrent Energy Storage Solutions Pvt Ltd for the construction of India&apos;s biggest pumped storage project - the 3000 MW Saidongar-1 Pumped Storage Project (PSP) in Raigad, Maharashtra. The scope of the contract includes design, engineering and execution of all civil and hydro-mechanical jobs associated with the project. This order is a testament to L&amp;T’s unmatched capability in delivering complex hydroelectric/pumped storage projects of national importance and reinforces L&amp;T’s position as a trusted partner for large-scale, high-capacity pumped storage solutions. Pumped storage projects like Saidongar-1 are vital to ensuring grid stability and meeting peak power demand.</p><ul><li>L&amp;T secures contract for India&apos;s biggest pumped storage project worth 3000 MW</li><li>The project is expected to enhance grid reliability and energy security for Maharashtra and beyond</li><li>L&amp;T&apos;s unmatched capability in delivering complex hydroelectric/pumped storage projects highlighted</li><li>The project reinforces L&amp;T’s position as a trusted partner for large-scale, high-capacity pumped storage solutions</li><li>Pumped storage projects are vital for grid stability and meeting peak power demand</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4897edea-8042-412d-b0be-92997271ac30.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LARSEN & TOUBRO LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IL&amp;FSTRANS] IL&amp;FS Transportation Networks Ltd. Receives Demand Notice for Rs. 96,96,046 Service Tax Liability from Assistant Commissioner of CGST &amp; C. Ex., Division-IV</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IL%26FS+Transportation+Networks+Ltd&title=IL%26FS+Transportation+Networks+Ltd.+Receives+Demand+Notice+for+Rs.+96%2C96%2C046+Service+Tax+Liability+from+Assistant+Commissioner+of+CGST+%26+C.+Ex.%2C+Division-IV&newsId=cc09218b-08cb-4584-b6c4-69c3e7c537f0&token=Y2MwOTIxOGItMDhj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cc09218b-08cb-4584-b6c4-69c3e7c537f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 04:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>IL&amp;FS Transportation Networks Ltd. has received a Demand Notice from the Assistant Commissioner of CGST &amp; C. Ex., Division-IV, Mumbai East, for an outstanding Service Tax liability along with penalty but excluding interest amounting to Rs. 96,96,046 for the Financial Year 2016-17. The company is currently reviewing the notice and assessing the next steps. There is no material impact on the financials, operations, or other activities of the company.</p><ul><li>IL&amp;FS Transportation Networks Ltd. received a Demand Notice for Service Tax liability and penalty</li><li>The total outstanding amount is Rs. 96,96,046 for the Financial Year 2016-17</li><li>The company is reviewing the notice and assessing the next steps</li><li>No material impact on financials, operations, or other activities of the company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bd8d1bb4-a159-435c-9e9f-148cc670324a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IL&FS Transportation Networks Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BPCL] Bharat Petroleum Subsidiary Discovers Oil in Abu Dhabi&apos;s Onshore Block 1, Investing USD 166 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BHARAT+PETROLEUM+CORPORATION+LTD.&title=Bharat+Petroleum+Subsidiary+Discovers+Oil+in+Abu+Dhabi%27s+Onshore+Block+1%2C+Investing+USD+166+Million&newsId=8100a579-8902-43e9-bbf9-ae47e223fb20&token=ODEwMGE1NzktODkw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8100a579-8902-43e9-bbf9-ae47e223fb20</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 03:56:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd (BPCL) announced that its subsidiary, Bharat PetroResources Limited (BPRL), discovered oil in Onshore Block 1, Abu Dhabi, through a 50:50 Special Purpose Vehicle, Urja Bharat Pte Limited (UBPL). The discovery follows the award of the exploration concession in March 2019 and a successful exploration phase with a total investment of nearly USD 166 million. The concession agreement covers 6,162 square kilometers, granting UBPL 100% concession rights. The first oil discovery was made in the XN-76 well, confirming the presence of unconventional oil resources in the Shilaif formation. BPRL is optimistic about the well results and looking forward to establishing the economic deliverability of wells during the appraisal phase. Additionally, oil was discovered in the exploration well XN-79 02S in the Habshan reservoir. These discoveries will contribute to BPRL&apos;s efforts towards India&apos;s energy security.</p><ul><li>Bharat Petroleum Corporation Ltd&apos;s subsidiary, Bharat PetroResources Limited (BPRL), discovers oil in Onshore Block 1, Abu Dhabi.</li><li>The discovery follows the award of the exploration concession in March 2019 and a successful exploration phase with a total investment of nearly USD 166 million.</li><li>The concession agreement covers 6,162 square kilometers, granting UBPL 100% concession rights.</li><li>The first oil discovery was made in the XN-76 well, confirming the presence of unconventional oil resources in the Shilaif formation.</li><li>BPRL is optimistic about the well results and looking forward to establishing the economic deliverability of wells during the appraisal phase.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/85ead94e-3850-484b-87c1-a690c5d28a43.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BHARAT PETROLEUM CORPORATION LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[OSWALPUMPS] Oswal Pumps Secures ₹ 119.92 Crore Solar Pump Order under PM-KUSUM B Scheme</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Oswal+Pumps+Ltd&title=Oswal+Pumps+Secures+%E2%82%B9+119.92+Crore+Solar+Pump+Order+under+PM-KUSUM+B+Scheme&newsId=d15a517e-9052-4770-a94a-ce1a167ac3d4&token=ZDE1YTUxN2UtOTA1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d15a517e-9052-4770-a94a-ce1a167ac3d4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 03:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Oswal Pumps Ltd has received a Letter of Award from Karnataka Renewable Energy Development Limited for 214 Surface Solar Agriculture Pumps Set and 3049 Submersible Solar Agriculture Pump Sets for the entire state of Karnataka under Component-B of PM-KUSUM scheme. The total value of the pumps is approximately ₹ 119.92 Crore (inclusive of GST). The order includes design, manufacture, supply, transport, installation, testing, and commissioning of Surface Solar Agriculture Pumps Set and Submersible Solar Agriculture Pump Sets of 3HP, 5 HP, 7.5 HP &amp; 10 HP at identified farmers&apos; site in the state of Karnataka, including complete system warranty and its repair and maintenance and Remote Monitoring System (‘RMS’) for 5 years. The installation and commissioning along with RMS integration and submission of Invoices and documents, shall be carried out as per the MNRE stipulated time i.e. on or before March 31, 2026. The contract period is up to five years from the date of installation &amp; commissioning of last pump under this DWA.</p><ul><li>Oswal Pumps has secured an order worth ₹ 119.92 Crore from Karnataka Renewable Energy Development Limited under PM-KUSUM B Scheme.</li><li>The order includes the supply and installation of 3,263 Off-Grid DC Solar Photovoltaic Water Pumping Systems.</li><li>The systems will be installed at identified farmers’ locations across the state of Karnataka, supporting sustainable irrigation and promoting the adoption of renewable energy in the agricultural sector.</li><li>This Order further strengthens Oswal Pumps Limited’s position as a leading player in the solar pumping solutions segment.</li><li>The project is expected to be completed by March 31, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/725f35bb-39c5-4cee-a51b-91f72dfa43ab.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Oswal Pumps Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PURVA] Puravankara Expands Portfolio with Rs 13,900 Cr GDV in Acquisitions in Q3FY26 &amp; 9MFY26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Puravankara+Ltd&title=Puravankara+Expands+Portfolio+with+Rs+13%2C900+Cr+GDV+in+Acquisitions+in+Q3FY26+%26+9MFY26&newsId=38cc95bf-50ce-4b3a-852c-decffe91618c&token=MzhjYzk1YmYtNTBj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">38cc95bf-50ce-4b3a-852c-decffe91618c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 03:47:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Puravankara Limited, one of India’s most trusted real estate developers, reported pre-sales of Rs 1,414 crores in Q3FY26, marking a 17% YoY growth. The average price realisation improved by 12% YoY, while customer collections for the quarter grew by 22% YoY to Rs 1,140 crores. During the quarter, Puravankara handed over 1.23 msft, delivering 1,116 homes, bringing the cumulative handover for 9MFY26 to 2.58 msft (2,446 homes). The company has a total land bank of ~32 msft and ongoing projects total ~34 msft.</p><ul><li>Puravankara reported pre-sales of Rs 1,414 crores in Q3FY26, marking a 17% YoY growth.</li><li>Customer collections for the quarter grew by 22% YoY to Rs 1,140 crores.</li><li>Puravankara handed over 1.23 msft, delivering 1,116 homes, in Q3 FY26.</li><li>The company made significant progress in expanding its portfolio, adding over 12.76 msft of potential developable area with an estimated GDV of approximately Rs 13,900 crores in 9MFY26.</li><li>Puravankara has a total land bank of ~32 msft and ongoing projects total ~34 msft.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/80c37076-b471-427f-80fd-6d3d09dc8a3e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Puravankara Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GARMNTMNTR] Garment Mantra Lifestyle Ltd Achieves ~100 Crore Export Sales in Current Financial Year</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Garment+Mantra+Lifestyle+Ltd&title=Garment+Mantra+Lifestyle+Ltd+Achieves+~100+Crore+Export+Sales+in+Current+Financial+Year&newsId=aeed6c57-5921-43dc-9b54-4ae2a47405cb&token=YWVlZDZjNTctNTky</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aeed6c57-5921-43dc-9b54-4ae2a47405cb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 03:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Garment Mantra Lifestyle Limited has achieved a historic milestone by reaching ~100 Crore in export sales in the current financial year. This achievement marks the largest and most significant milestone in the Company’s history, reflecting its strong execution capabilities, growing acceptance of its products in international markets, and its focused strategy on export-led growth. The Company&apos;s state-of-the-art manufacturing infrastructure, skilled workforce, and efficient supply chain capabilities have enabled it to scale operations while maintaining stringent quality and compliance standards. The Company&apos;s export business has not been materially impacted by recent American tariff developments.</p><ul><li>Garment Mantra Lifestyle Limited has achieved export sales of ~100 Crore in the current financial year.</li><li>This is the highest-ever export performance since the Company’s inception.</li><li>The achievement is a result of consistent focus on quality manufacturing, product innovation, timely execution, and strong customer relationships.</li><li>The Company’s state-of-the-art manufacturing infrastructure, skilled workforce, and efficient supply chain capabilities have enabled it to scale operations while maintaining stringent quality and compliance standards.</li><li>Garment Mantra Lifestyle Limited&apos;s export business has not been materially impacted by recent American tariff developments.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3656e1e1-5a33-41be-a4af-f1178e908b6c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Garment Mantra Lifestyle Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AIIL] Authum Investment &amp; Infrastructure Ltd Announces 4:1 Bonus Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Authum+Investment+%26+Infrastructure+Ltd&title=Authum+Investment+%26+Infrastructure+Ltd+Announces+4%3A1+Bonus+Shares&newsId=ef5ed5bb-4235-4707-80d8-ce5f3c69c8ad&token=ZWY1ZWQ1YmItNDIz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef5ed5bb-4235-4707-80d8-ce5f3c69c8ad</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 03:35:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Bonus</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Authum Investment &amp; Infrastructure Ltd has approved the allotment of 67,93,80,400 fully paid-up Bonus Equity Shares of face value Rs. 1/- each in the proportion of 4:1. The Bonus Shares will be credited to the eligible Shareholders in their demat account. The Record Date for this purpose is January 13, 2026. The Paid-up Share Capital of the Company will increase from Rs. 16,98,45,100 to Rs. 84,92,25,500 post bonus issue.</p><ul><li>Authum Investment &amp; Infrastructure Ltd announces 4:1 Bonus Shares</li><li>67,93,80,400 Bonus Equity Shares of face value Rs. 1/- each to be allotted</li><li>Record Date set as January 13, 2026</li><li>Paid-up Share Capital to increase from Rs. 16,98,45,100 to Rs. 84,92,25,500 post bonus issue</li><li>Bonus Shares to be credited to eligible Shareholders&apos; demat accounts</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cb7cbfcc-2a3d-464a-b275-2d742c8ea53a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Authum Investment & Infrastructure Ltd | Category: Bonus</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MINID] Mini Diamonds Secures INR 14 Crores Domestic Order for Lab Grown Polished Diamonds</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MINI+DIAMONDS+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Mini+Diamonds+Secures+INR+14+Crores+Domestic+Order+for+Lab+Grown+Polished+Diamonds&newsId=3803c266-703e-4a44-be8d-48a96b318d6b&token=MzgwM2MyNjYtNzAz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3803c266-703e-4a44-be8d-48a96b318d6b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 03:29:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Mini Diamonds India Ltd has secured a significant domestic order of INR 14.00 Crores from a Mumbai based client for the supply of lab-grown diamonds. This order supports the company&apos;s focus on scaling volumes in the domestic market and reflects the growing acceptance of its lab-grown polished diamonds. The company will execute the order through its established procurement, manufacturing, and dispatch framework in line with internal controls and quality benchmarks. The timely fulfillment is expected to strengthen the company’s domestic position in the lab-grown polished diamond segment and support repeat business and deeper channel relationships.</p><ul><li>Mini Diamonds secures INR 14 Crores domestic order for lab-grown diamonds</li><li>Order from a Mumbai-based client</li><li>Supports the company’s focus on scaling volumes in the domestic market</li><li>Reflects growing acceptance of the Company’s lab-grown polished diamonds</li><li>Order to strengthen the company’s domestic position in the lab-grown polished diamond segment</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fa25ba8d-882f-47fc-8105-33c4f50bfeef.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MINI DIAMONDS (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IOC] Indian Oil Corporation Makes Significant Oil Discoveries in Abu Dhabi&apos;s Onshore Block 1</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDIAN+OIL+CORPORATION+LTD.&title=Indian+Oil+Corporation+Makes+Significant+Oil+Discoveries+in+Abu+Dhabi%27s+Onshore+Block+1&newsId=89a73cca-29a9-40d3-871d-93b8b8ff4999&token=ODlhNzNjY2EtMjlh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">89a73cca-29a9-40d3-871d-93b8b8ff4999</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 03:24:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Indian Oil Corporation Limited (IOCL) and Bharat PetroResources Limited, through their Special Purpose Vehicle Urja Bharat Pte Limited (UBPL), have made significant oil discoveries in the Onshore Block 1 Exploration Concession in Abu Dhabi. The first discovery was made in the Unconventional Shilaif play in XN-76 exploratory well, which flowed light crude oil at surface from the Shilaif formation after successful hydrofracking operations. The second discovery was made in the Habshan reservoir in the exploratory well XN- 79 02S. Both companies are positive about these discoveries and are looking forward to appraising and potentially developing these finds. This is a significant achievement for both parent companies as international operators.</p><ul><li>Indian Oil Corporation and Bharat PetroResources Limited make first oil discovery in the Unconventional Shilaif play in XN-76 exploratory well</li><li>Successful hydrofracking operations lead to flow of light crude oil at surface from the Shilaif formation</li><li>Second oil discovery made in the Habshan reservoir in the exploratory well XN- 79 02S</li><li>Companies looking forward to appraising and potentially developing these discoveries</li><li>Positive achievement for both parent companies as international operators</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4a9d5e0f-9043-4bd0-af53-889ee443eb31.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDIAN OIL CORPORATION LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>