<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:28:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[CHOICEIN] Choice International Ltd to Consider and Approve Un-Audited Financial Result on Feb 3, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CHOICE+INTERNATIONAL+LTD.&title=Choice+International+Ltd+to+Consider+and+Approve+Un-Audited+Financial+Result+on+Feb+3%2C+2026&newsId=9dff73ec-71fb-4f96-b73e-b87b2194b0c7&token=OWRmZjczZWMtNzFm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9dff73ec-71fb-4f96-b73e-b87b2194b0c7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:24:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Choice International Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 3, 2026, to consider and approve the Un-Audited Financial Result for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will also note the Limited Review Report. The trading window for dealing in the company&apos;s securities was closed from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results, as required under the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations 2015.</p><ul><li>Choice International Ltd&apos;s Board of Directors to meet on February 3, 2026, to consider and approve Un-Audited Financial Result for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The meeting will also note the Limited Review Report.</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the company&apos;s securities was closed from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/52bfa248-fe88-4496-9a69-8e6602a7b071.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CHOICE INTERNATIONAL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GPTINFRA] GPT Infraprojects Reports 2.0% Revenue Growth in Q3 FY26; Orders Inflow at Rs 1,074 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GPT+INFRAPROJECTS+LTD.&title=GPT+Infraprojects+Reports+2.0%25+Revenue+Growth+in+Q3+FY26%3B+Orders+Inflow+at+Rs+1%2C074+Crores&newsId=78f49a4a-5ef5-4579-a87d-8ca1d18fc561&token=NzhmNDlhNGEtNWVm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78f49a4a-5ef5-4579-a87d-8ca1d18fc561</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:22:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>GPT Infraprojects Limited reported its financial results for the third quarter (Q3) and nine months (9M) ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s consolidated revenue from operations stood at Rs 890.7 crore, a 9.6% YoY increase. The consolidated EBITDA stood at Rs 130.3 crore, a 27.2% YoY increase, with an EBITDA margin of 14.9%. The consolidated PAT after minorities stood at Rs 65.7 crore, a 17.7% YoY increase, with a PAT margin of 7.5%. The standalone revenue stood at Rs 866.5 crore, a growth of 8.2%. The standalone EBITDA stood at Rs 123.6 crore, a growth of 12.1% YoY, with an EBITDA margin of 14.5%. The standalone PAT stood at Rs 63.2 crore, a growth of 3.4% YoY. The company announced a interim dividend of Re 0.75 per share. The order backlog stands healthy at Rs 4,415 crore, with order inflow of Rs 1,770 crore during the year including incremental orders from existing contracts.</p><ul><li>Consolidated revenue from operations stood at Rs 890.7 crore, a 9.6% YoY increase.</li><li>Consolidated EBITDA stood at Rs 130.3 crore, a 27.2% YoY increase, with an EBITDA margin of 14.9%.</li><li>Consolidated PAT after minorities stood at Rs 65.7 crore, a 17.7% YoY increase, with a PAT margin of 7.5%.</li><li>Standalone revenue stood at Rs 866.5 crore, a growth of 8.2%.</li><li>Order backlog stands healthy at Rs 4,415 crore, with order inflow of Rs 1,770 crore during the year including incremental orders from existing contracts.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2715f87b-422d-45cc-991d-1c7955b7c269.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GPT INFRAPROJECTS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RAMCOSYS] Ramco Systems posts Q3 revenue of USD 20.18m with EBITDA of 26%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RAMCO+SYSTEMS+LTD.&title=Ramco+Systems+posts+Q3+revenue+of+USD+20.18m+with+EBITDA+of+26%25&newsId=1ae1318f-c0e2-4772-b82d-49fe67eefe35&token=MWFlMTMxOGYtYzBl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1ae1318f-c0e2-4772-b82d-49fe67eefe35</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:22:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Ramco Systems, a global enterprise software company, announced its Q3 results for the financial year 2025-26. The global consolidated income stood at USD 20.35m with an EBITDA of USD 5.24m at 26%. Considering a one-time exceptional item, the net profit after tax stood at USD 0.36m. The quarter saw steady order bookings, stable recurring revenue, and a strong cash balance. Key customers were added across various sectors and regions, and Ramco Payce was certified as a Workday Global Payroll Connect partner.</p><ul><li>Global consolidated income of USD 20.35m</li><li>EBITDA of 26% at USD 5.24m</li><li>Steady quarterly order bookings of USD 10.62m</li><li>Stable recurring revenue of USD 11.29m</li><li>Certification of Ramco Payce as a Workday Global Payroll Connect partner</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/33888ef1-bce9-4c1f-b1a5-af74e6acf8f5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RAMCO SYSTEMS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[COCHINSHIP] Cochin Shipyard Ltd Fined for Non-Compliance with SEBI LODR Regulations; Awaits Government Appointment of Independent Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Cochin+Shipyard+Ltd&title=Cochin+Shipyard+Ltd+Fined+for+Non-Compliance+with+SEBI+LODR+Regulations%3B+Awaits+Government+Appointment+of+Independent+Directors&newsId=6940a572-29cf-4b4c-b17b-ac1f8e4ee2ed&token=Njk0MGE1NzItMjlj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6940a572-29cf-4b4c-b17b-ac1f8e4ee2ed</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:21:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cochin Shipyard Ltd has been fined by BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange of India Limited for non-compliance with Regulation 17(1), 18, and 19 of the SEBI LODR Regulations. The non-compliance pertains to the absence of sufficient number of Independent Directors and non-compliance with the constitution of Audit Committee and Nomination and Remuneration Committee. The total fine imposed is Rs. 9,77,040 each, including GST @ 18%. The matter was placed before the Board of Directors, who acknowledged the fact that the power to appoint Directors on the Board of the Company vests with the Government of India. The appointment of the remaining five independent directors is awaited. The Audit Committee and the Nomination and Remuneration Committee could be re-constituted in line with the SEBI LODR Regulations only after sufficient number of independent directors are appointed. The company has been advised to continue following up the matter with the Administrative Ministry and to file appropriate waiver requests with the Stock Exchanges once compliance is achieved.</p><ul><li>Cochin Shipyard Ltd fined for non-compliance with SEBI LODR Regulations</li><li>Fine imposed by BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange of India Limited</li><li>Awaiting government appointment of five independent directors</li><li>Board advised to continue following up the matter with the Administrative Ministry</li><li>Company to file waiver requests with the Stock Exchanges once compliance is achieved</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cb0379a3-a44f-43a3-90a1-c0cc2eef09bb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Cochin Shipyard Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VERTEX] Vertex Securities Ltd. Approves Rights Issue of Equity Shares Up to Rs. 15 Crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VERTEX+SECURITIES+LTD.&title=Vertex+Securities+Ltd.+Approves+Rights+Issue+of+Equity+Shares+Up+to+Rs.+15+Crore&newsId=bd861311-cb42-41cf-af64-eccd4dce6b8f&token=YmQ4NjEzMTEtY2I0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd861311-cb42-41cf-af64-eccd4dce6b8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:21:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vertex Securities Ltd. announced the outcome of its Board Meeting held on January 28, 2026. The Board approved the offer and issuance of equity shares for an amount not exceeding Rs. 15 Crore through a Rights Issue to eligible equity shareholders. The Company will constitute a Rights Issue Committee and file a draft Letter of Offer with the BSE Limited. The meeting commenced at 03:00 PM IST and concluded at 06:37 PM IST.</p><ul><li>Vertex Securities Ltd. to raise funds up to Rs. 15 Crore through Rights Issue.</li><li>The Rights Issue is open to eligible equity shareholders of the Company.</li><li>The Company will constitute a Rights Issue Committee for the purpose.</li><li>A draft Letter of Offer will be filed with the BSE Limited.</li><li>The decision was made at the Board Meeting held on January 28, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/34be4dd3-bc1f-4a94-94a9-644e39142c6c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VERTEX SECURITIES LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KPITTECH] KPIT Technologies Grants 21,000 Stock Options Under RSU Plan 2022</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KPIT+Technologies+Ltd&title=KPIT+Technologies+Grants+21%2C000+Stock+Options+Under+RSU+Plan+2022&newsId=116291b8-ccb8-4600-b019-6ef1a649c09b&token=MTE2MjkxYjgtY2Ni</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">116291b8-ccb8-4600-b019-6ef1a649c09b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>ESOP</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>KPIT Technologies Ltd has granted 21,000 options to eligible employees under the KPIT Technologies Limited - Restricted Stock Unit Plan (&apos;RSU Plan 2022) in accordance with the Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The Nomination and Remuneration (HR) Committee of the Board of Directors approved the grant in a meeting held on January 28, 2026. The options, which were approved by shareholders in the Annual General Meeting held on August 24, 2022, will have an exercise price of Rs 10/- per option, the face value of the share as on the date of grant.</p><ul><li>Grant of 21,000 options to eligible employees under RSU Plan 2022</li><li>Exercise price set at Rs 10/- per option</li><li>Options to vest after a minimum of 1 year but not later than 4 years from the date of grant</li><li>Options yet to be exercised</li><li>Approval given by shareholders in the Annual General Meeting held on August 24, 2022</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5decae0b-f808-48e6-a57c-f5e0a560f9c3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KPIT Technologies Ltd | Category: ESOP</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HEROMOTOCO] Hero MotoCorp May Declare Interim Dividend for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HERO+MOTOCORP+LTD.&title=Hero+MotoCorp+May+Declare+Interim+Dividend+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=bf26f01b-aaa6-4697-81c6-23ffeba41da5&token=YmYyNmYwMWItYWFh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf26f01b-aaa6-4697-81c6-23ffeba41da5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:21:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hero Motocorp Ltd has informed the BSE that the company&apos;s Board of Directors will meet on February 5, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months period ended December 31, 2025. The Board may also consider declaring an interim dividend for the financial year 2025-26.</p><ul><li>Hero MotoCorp&apos;s Board of Directors to meet on February 5, 2026</li><li>Consideration and approval of unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Possible declaration of interim dividend for the financial year 2025-26</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/71d52ab4-fbfc-4c73-acb6-1a1825be1bdb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HERO MOTOCORP LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TRABI] Transgene Biotek Ltd to Approve Q4 Results for 2025 in Board Meeting on 13th February</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TRANSGENE+BIOTEK+LTD.&title=Transgene+Biotek+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+Results+for+2025+in+Board+Meeting+on+13th+February&newsId=2ae0cbf3-10de-49ab-8d0d-daa7f7b2b6d7&token=MmFlMGNiZjMtMTBk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ae0cbf3-10de-49ab-8d0d-daa7f7b2b6d7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Transgene Biotek Ltd has informed the BSE about a scheduled Board of Directors meeting on 13th February 2026. The meeting will consider and approve the Un-Audited Financial Results (Standalone &amp; Consolidated) for the quarter ended 31st December 2025, along with the Limited Review Report (Standalone &amp; Consolidated) for the same quarter. The meeting will also transact other necessary business. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the company was closed from 1st January 2026 till 48 hours after the financial results become generally available information, in accordance with the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) (Amendment) Regulations, 2018.</p><ul><li>Transgene Biotek Ltd to approve Q4 results for 2025 in Board meeting on 13th February</li><li>Un-Audited Financial Results (Standalone &amp; Consolidated) for Q4 2025 to be considered and approved</li><li>Limited Review Report (Standalone &amp; Consolidated) for Q4 2025 to be considered and approved</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities of the company was closed from 1st January 2026 as per SEBI regulations</li><li>Other business as required will be transacted in the meeting</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/53bca3a1-11d3-45e5-abe9-0d90b6d45c48.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TRANSGENE BIOTEK LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDUSINDBK] Indusind Bank Ltd Announces Changes in Senior Management Personnel</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDUSIND+BANK+LTD.&title=Indusind+Bank+Ltd+Announces+Changes+in+Senior+Management+Personnel&newsId=4cc5bf05-548c-4de4-be52-a1d9e161eae0&token=NGNjNWJmMDUtNTQ4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4cc5bf05-548c-4de4-be52-a1d9e161eae0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indusind Bank Ltd has announced changes in its Senior Management Personnel. Niraj Piyush Shah has ceased to be a Senior Management Personnel due to a change in reporting hierarchy. Manikantan Iyer and Shruti Kumar have been added to the list of Senior Management Personnel. The changes are in compliance with the Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Niraj Piyush Shah ceases to be a Senior Management Personnel</li><li>Manikantan Iyer and Shruti Kumar appointed as Senior Management Personnel</li><li>Changes in reporting hierarchy</li><li>Compliance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI Listing Regulations</li><li>Disclosure of information pursuant to Regulation 30 of the SEBI Listing Regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6c164cdd-3692-405c-8f45-6573a3fe458d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDUSIND BANK LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IRONWOOD] Ironwood Education Ltd Enters Joint Development Agreement with AVA Lifespaces LLP for SRA Project in Mumbai</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ironwood+Education+Ltd&title=Ironwood+Education+Ltd+Enters+Joint+Development+Agreement+with+AVA+Lifespaces+LLP+for+SRA+Project+in+Mumbai&newsId=c7b3646b-5a5d-40a9-86a9-47264f161563&token=YzdiMzY0NmItNWE1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7b3646b-5a5d-40a9-86a9-47264f161563</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:12:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Ironwood Education Ltd has entered into a Joint Development Agreement with AVA Lifespaces LLP for the joint development of a Slum Rehabilitation Authority (SRA) Project situated at Hanuman Nagar, Vadar Pada, C.T.S. No. 163 A (pt), plot area 1,752.53 Sq.m (village Akurli, Kandivali (East), Mumbai — 400101, R/S Ward, “Naytarun CHS (Prop)”. The Company will pay a refundable Security Deposit of INR 5.50 crore to AVA. Upon completion of the Project and settlement of Project Costs, Net Profits shall be distributed as 70% to IRONWOOD and 30% to AVA. The transaction is at arm&apos;s length and promoter/promoter group/group companies are not interested in the transaction, except for a few related party details.</p><ul><li>Ironwood Education Ltd and AVA Lifespaces LLP entered into a Joint Development Agreement on January 28, 2026</li><li>The agreement is for the joint development of an SRA Project in Mumbai</li><li>The Company will pay a refundable Security Deposit of INR 5.50 crore to AVA</li><li>Upon completion of the Project, Net Profits shall be distributed as 70% to IRONWOOD and 30% to AVA</li><li>The transaction is at arm&apos;s length</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cac8ee3d-84b7-40c4-ad86-093a8ab3cb2b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ironwood Education Ltd | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>