<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:54:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[PTCIL] PTC Industries Reports Strong Q3 &amp; 9M FY26 Results with 114.6% YoY Revenue Growth and 28.9% YoY PAT Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PTC+Industries+Ltd&title=PTC+Industries+Reports+Strong+Q3+%26+9M+FY26+Results+with+114.6%25+YoY+Revenue+Growth+and+28.9%25+YoY+PAT+Growth&newsId=5ea7dbc7-4e3c-4985-b994-2c541c3bd52e&token=NWVhN2RiYzctNGUz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ea7dbc7-4e3c-4985-b994-2c541c3bd52e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>PTC Industries, a leading Indian manufacturer of high-performance materials and precision-engineered components for critical aerospace and defence applications, has announced financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company reported a robust growth of 114.6% YoY in total income for Q3FY26, and a growth of 28.9% YoY in profit after tax for the same period. The aerospace division secured a development and supply order from Blue Origin for large, high-integrity Superalloy investment castings for the BE-4 engines, and signed a long-term agreement with Honeywell Aerospace for the supply of Titanium and Superalloy precision investment castings. PTC received an order from ISRO’s Vikram Sarabhai Space Centre (VSSC) involving conversion of 40 tonnes of Grade 1 Titanium sponge into Ti-6Al-4V Titanium alloy ingots using a Double Vacuum Arc Remelting (Double VAR) process. The company also signed MoUs with the Ministry of Steel under PLI Scheme 1.2 for Specialty Steel, covering Titanium Alloys and Super Alloys.</p><ul><li>PTC Industries reported a 114.6% YoY growth in revenue for Q3FY26.</li><li>Profit after tax for Q3FY26 grew by 28.9% YoY.</li><li>Secured a development and supply order from Blue Origin for large, high-integrity Superalloy investment castings for the BE-4 engines.</li><li>Signed a long-term agreement with Honeywell Aerospace for the supply of Titanium and Superalloy precision investment castings.</li><li>Received an order from ISRO’s Vikram Sarabhai Space Centre (VSSC) involving conversion of 40 tonnes of Grade 1 Titanium sponge into Ti-6Al-4V Titanium alloy ingots using a Double Vacuum Arc Remelting (Double VAR) process.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/83cd73c7-5ada-49f1-84c1-5c52e9979099.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PTC Industries Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DEVX] Dev Accelerator Ltd Completes Sale of 38% Equity Investment in Scaleax Advisory Private Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Dev+Accelerator+Ltd&title=Dev+Accelerator+Ltd+Completes+Sale+of+38%25+Equity+Investment+in+Scaleax+Advisory+Private+Limited&newsId=dad0a623-c43d-48a2-ae3d-df5a457090ee&token=ZGFkMGE2MjMtYzQz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dad0a623-c43d-48a2-ae3d-df5a457090ee</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Dev Accelerator Ltd has completed the sale of its 38% equity investment in its associate company, Scaleax Advisory Private Limited, to Dev Information Technology Limited and Mr. Aaryan Jaxay Shah. The total consideration for the sale is Rs. 3,80,000/- (Rupees Three Lakh Eighty Thousand Only). This transaction marks the end of Scaleax&apos;s status as an associate company of Dev Accelerator Ltd.</p><ul><li>Dev Accelerator Ltd has sold its 38% equity investment in Scaleax Advisory Private Limited</li><li>The sale was made to Dev Information Technology Limited and Mr. Aaryan Jaxay Shah</li><li>The total consideration for the sale is Rs. 3,80,000/- (Rupees Three Lakh Eighty Thousand Only)</li><li>This transaction marks the end of Scaleax&apos;s status as an associate company of Dev Accelerator Ltd</li><li>The sale was completed in accordance with Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ed723e2d-2d72-4b6a-98e6-f48586b14b02.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Dev Accelerator Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AVI] AVI Polymers Ltd. Extends Rights Issue Dates to March 16, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AVI+Polymers+Ltd&title=AVI+Polymers+Ltd.+Extends+Rights+Issue+Dates+to+March+16%2C+2026&newsId=152c044c-6883-4bea-9a6f-76c1594f645c&token=MTUyYzA0NGMtNjg4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">152c044c-6883-4bea-9a6f-76c1594f645c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Right Issue</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>AVI Polymers Ltd. has announced an extension of the Rights Issue dates. The issue, originally scheduled to open on February 20, 2026, and close on March 11, 2026, will now open on February 23, 2026, and close on March 16, 2026. This extension is to provide shareholders with an opportunity to exercise their rights in the Rights Issue. The finalization of the allotment will be done on March 23, 2026, with the credit of shares expected on March 30, 2026, and listing on March 31, 2026.</p><ul><li>AVI Polymers Ltd. extends the Rights Issue dates</li><li>Original opening date was February 20, 2026, now it&apos;s February 23, 2026</li><li>Original closing date was March 11, 2026, now it&apos;s March 16, 2026</li><li>Finalization of allotment on March 23, 2026</li><li>Expected credit of shares on March 30, 2026, and listing on March 31, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fa75dde4-14b5-4fb8-853b-a8c8396b4f93.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AVI Polymers Ltd | Category: Right Issue</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NUCLEUS] Nucleus Software Exports Ltd Incorporates Wholly Owned Subsidiary in Vietnam</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NUCLEUS+SOFTWARE+EXPORTS+LTD.&title=Nucleus+Software+Exports+Ltd+Incorporates+Wholly+Owned+Subsidiary+in+Vietnam&newsId=9db15b57-e2e1-4056-8133-163b9c8dd9d6&token=OWRiMTViNTctZTJl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9db15b57-e2e1-4056-8133-163b9c8dd9d6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:44:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Nucleus Software Exports Ltd has incorporated a wholly owned subsidiary, NUCLEUS SOFTWARE VIETNAM COMPANY LIMITED, in Vietnam. The new company will serve as a Business Development and Sales hub, and also provide software development services to local customers. NUCLEUS SOFTWARE VIETNAM COMPANY LIMITED is incorporated in Vietnam and is yet to commence its business operations.</p><ul><li>Nucleus Software Exports Ltd has incorporated a wholly owned subsidiary, NUCLEUS SOFTWARE VIETNAM COMPANY LIMITED, in Vietnam</li><li>The new company will serve as a Business Development and Sales hub</li><li>NUCLEUS SOFTWARE VIETNAM COMPANY LIMITED will also provide software development services to local customers</li><li>The subsidiary is incorporated in Vietnam and is yet to commence its business operations</li><li>This expansion is expected to strengthen Nucleus Software&apos;s global presence and business operations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5cb390ec-49d3-44c4-995e-fd199bc660ad.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NUCLEUS SOFTWARE EXPORTS LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZYDUSLIFE] Zydus Lifesciences receives final USFDA approval for Bosentan tablets for oral suspension, 32 mg</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Zydus+Lifesciences+Ltd&title=Zydus+Lifesciences+receives+final+USFDA+approval+for+Bosentan+tablets+for+oral+suspension%2C+32+mg&newsId=2fc7a012-2c85-46f6-84ee-330563bf6d1e&token=MmZjN2EwMTItMmM4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2fc7a012-2c85-46f6-84ee-330563bf6d1e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:41:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>USFDA</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Zydus Lifesciences Limited has received final approval from the USFDA for Bosentan tablets, oral suspension, 32 mg (USRLD: Tracleer® Tablets for Oral Suspension, 32 mg). The approval is for the treatment of Pulmonary Arterial Hypertension (PAH) in children aged 3 years and older. The drug is a dual endothelin receptor antagonist that lowers high blood pressure in the lungs, typically administered based on body weight. The group&apos;s formulation manufacturing facility at SEZ, Ahmedabad will manufacture the Bosentan 32 mg tablets. The drug had annual sales of USD 9.3 mn in the United States (IQVIA MAT December 2025). Zydus now has 432 approvals and has so far filed 505 ANDAs since the commencement of the filing process in FY 2003-04.</p><ul><li>Zydus Lifesciences receives final approval from USFDA for Bosentan tablets for oral suspension, 32 mg</li><li>Indicated for the treatment of Pulmonary Arterial Hypertension (PAH) in children aged 3 years and older</li><li>Dual endothelin receptor antagonist that lowers high blood pressure in the lungs</li><li>Manufacturing to start at the group’s formulation manufacturing facility at SEZ, Ahmedabad</li><li>Bosentan 32 mg tablets had annual sales of USD 9.3 mn in the United States (IQVIA MAT December 2025)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/babb1a1c-1324-44bc-a460-ca5668ee199f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Zydus Lifesciences Ltd | Category: USFDA</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VRUDDHI] Vruddhi Engineering Works Ltd. Announces Reappointment of Managing Director and Whole-time Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vruddhi+Engineering+Works+Ltd&title=Vruddhi+Engineering+Works+Ltd.+Announces+Reappointment+of+Managing+Director+and+Whole-time+Directors&newsId=c08c7553-31a5-4664-9fcf-14fe164bcb43&token=YzA4Yzc1NTMtMzFh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c08c7553-31a5-4664-9fcf-14fe164bcb43</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:34:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vruddhi Engineering Works Ltd. announced the reappointment of Mrs. Bindi Kunal Mehta as Managing Director and Mr. Vedant Mukesh Mehta and Mrs. Varsha Mukesh Mehta as Whole-time Directors for a further period of three years. The reappointments were approved in the Board Meeting held on February 18, 2026. The company also approved the Notice of Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) to be held on March 12, 2026.</p><ul><li>Reappointment of Mrs. Bindi Kunal Mehta as Managing Director for three years.</li><li>Reappointment of Mr. Vedant Mukesh Mehta as Whole-time Director for three years.</li><li>Reappointment of Mrs. Varsha Mukesh Mehta as Whole-time Director for three years.</li><li>Approval of Notice of Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) to be held on March 12, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8141940d-8783-4603-ac97-322f7c791a4e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vruddhi Engineering Works Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KAJARIACER] Kajaria Ceramics Acquires 25% Stake in Kajaria Adhesive, Making it a Wholly-Owned Subsidiary</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KAJARIA+CERAMICS+LTD.&title=Kajaria+Ceramics+Acquires+25%25+Stake+in+Kajaria+Adhesive%2C+Making+it+a+Wholly-Owned+Subsidiary&newsId=2a1bcbe0-9724-4d63-9320-57bdf9d4d88e&token=MmExYmNiZTAtOTcy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a1bcbe0-9724-4d63-9320-57bdf9d4d88e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Kajaria Ceramics Ltd has acquired 2,500 (i.e. 25%) equity shares of Kajaria Adhesive Private Limited (KAPL), making KAPL a wholly-owned subsidiary of the company. The acquisition was made on February 18, 2026, from Mr. Kartik Kajaria, a member of the Promoter Group. KAPL is under process to set up a manufacturing facility in Erode (Tamil Nadu) to commence manufacturing of adhesives for tiles.</p><ul><li>Kajaria Ceramics acquires 25% stake in Kajaria Adhesive Private Limited</li><li>Kajaria Adhesive Private Limited becomes a wholly-owned subsidiary of Kajaria Ceramics</li><li>The acquisition was made from Mr. Kartik Kajaria, a member of the Promoter Group</li><li>Kajaria Adhesive is setting up a manufacturing facility in Erode, Tamil Nadu</li><li>The acquisition was made at an arm&apos;s length basis</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3ee63547-6de4-4d61-9567-b2bc8b551de9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KAJARIA CERAMICS LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BHARTIHEXA] Bharti Hexacom Ltd: Priyanka Jain Appointed as Circle Head — Commercial, North East Circle</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Bharti+Hexacom+Ltd&title=Bharti+Hexacom+Ltd%3A+Priyanka+Jain+Appointed+as+Circle+Head+%E2%80%94+Commercial%2C+North+East+Circle&newsId=9b3dd5ed-1510-4add-9bac-e0f1bfd82bc1&token=OWIzZGQ1ZWQtMTUx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b3dd5ed-1510-4add-9bac-e0f1bfd82bc1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bharti Hexacom Ltd has announced the appointment of Priyanka Jain as Circle Head — Commercial, North East Circle (NESA) with effect from March 13, 2026. Priyanka Jain, a Chartered Accountant, has been with the Bharti Group since 2015 and has progressed through various roles including Deputy Manager in BPA support, DSS Head, Material Planner, Cost Analyst, USOF Project Management, Fiber Planning, and Own Site Planning. She has been instrumental in delivering Opex targets, achieving circle-wide compliance, winning the &apos;Most Improved Compliance Circle&apos; award, and playing a significant role in securing the Chairman&apos;s Award for the circle.</p><ul><li>Priyanka Jain appointed as Circle Head — Commercial, North East Circle (NESA)</li><li>Jain has been with Bharti Group since 2015 and has progressed through various roles</li><li>She has been instrumental in delivering Opex targets and achieving circle-wide compliance</li><li>Jain played a pivotal role in securing the Chairman&apos;s Award for the circle</li><li>Appointment effective from March 13, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ae5cbdbb-7371-4baf-b2cf-733e339cd968.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Bharti Hexacom Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PRESTIGE] Prestige Estates Projects Acquires 100% Partnership Interest in Aspire Spaces Tellapur LLP</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PRESTIGE+ESTATES+PROJECTS+LTD.&title=Prestige+Estates+Projects+Acquires+100%25+Partnership+Interest+in+Aspire+Spaces+Tellapur+LLP&newsId=57e73142-b656-4f41-9587-06eaabd04ded&token=NTdlNzMxNDItYjY1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57e73142-b656-4f41-9587-06eaabd04ded</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Prestige Estates Projects Ltd has acquired 100% partnership interest in Aspire Spaces Tellapur LLP, a Limited Liability Partnership incorporated on July 26, 2024. The LLP is into the business of real estate development and has now become a wholly owned step-down subsidiary of the Company. The acquisition was completed on February 18, 2026, for a cash consideration of Rs. 1 Million. The LLP has a total saleable area of 10 million square feet for a residential project in Tellapur, Hyderabad.</p><ul><li>Prestige Estates Projects Ltd acquires 100% partnership interest in Aspire Spaces Tellapur LLP</li><li>Aspire Spaces Tellapur LLP is a Limited Liability Partnership incorporated on July 26, 2024, and is into the business of real estate development</li><li>The acquisition was completed on February 18, 2026, for a cash consideration of Rs. 1 Million</li><li>The LLP has a total saleable area of 10 million square feet for a residential project in Tellapur, Hyderabad</li><li>Aspire Spaces Tellapur LLP is now a wholly owned step-down subsidiary of Prestige Estates Projects Ltd</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ad80326a-644e-4da4-85ef-081b27db9b67.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PRESTIGE ESTATES PROJECTS LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TEJASNET] Tejas Networks Receives Rs. 69.9658 Crore from Ministry of Communications</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Tejas+Networks+Ltd&title=Tejas+Networks+Receives+Rs.+69.9658+Crore+from+Ministry+of+Communications&newsId=003b1584-aa82-4a81-a40f-e1c3c2920974&token=MDAzYjE1ODQtYWE4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">003b1584-aa82-4a81-a40f-e1c3c2920974</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 12:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Tejas Networks Limited has received an amount of Rs. 69.9658 Crore from the Ministry of Communications, Department of Telecommunications, New Delhi. This amount is towards the balance 15% of the eligible incentive for FY 2024 — 2025, under the Production Linked Incentive Scheme Guidelines.</p><ul><li>Tejas Networks Limited has received an investment of Rs. 69.9658 Crore from the Ministry of Communications.</li><li>The investment is towards the balance 15% of the eligible incentive for FY 2024 — 2025 under the Production Linked Incentive Scheme Guidelines.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/295ae4ab-cb7d-47b8-8af6-820a64b0449c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Tejas Networks Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>