<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:17:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[NETRIPPLES] Netripples Software Ltd. Reports No Related Party Transactions for Q1 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Netripples+Software+Ltd&title=Netripples+Software+Ltd.+Reports+No+Related+Party+Transactions+for+Q1+2021&newsId=97977b72-1a4e-441d-86bc-d0160b12d741&token=OTc5NzdiNzItMWE0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97977b72-1a4e-441d-86bc-d0160b12d741</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:31:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In accordance with Regulation 23(9) of the Listing Regulations, Netripples Software Ltd. has reported no related party transactions for the quarter ended 31st March 2021. This disclosure is of prominence as per the regulation and has been uploaded on the company&apos;s website for information and record keeping purposes. The managing director of Netripples Software Ltg. is the authorized signatory for this report.</p><ul><li>Netripples Software Ltd. reported no related party transactions for Q1 2021</li><li>This disclosure is in accordance with Regulation 23(9) of the Listing Regulations</li><li>The report has been uploaded on the company&apos;s website for record keeping</li><li>The managing director is the authorized signatory for the report</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c062fe20-638a-41ad-a878-0c35800ef17c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Netripples Software Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NETRIPPLES] Netripples Software Ltd Submits Updated RPT Report for Q3 2020 with No Related Party Transactions</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Netripples+Software+Ltd&title=Netripples+Software+Ltd+Submits+Updated+RPT+Report+for+Q3+2020+with+No+Related+Party+Transactions&newsId=eb172cd8-096b-473f-a36d-aa602f0d3848&token=ZWIxNzJjZDgtMDk2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eb172cd8-096b-473f-a36d-aa602f0d3848</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Netripples Software Ltd has added an updated RPT (Related Party Transactions) report in the Dashboard for the quarter ending September 2020. The report has been submitted in accordance with the Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. As per Regulation 23(9), the company has disclosed that there were no related party transactions for the quarter ended 30th September 2020. This disclosure is of prominence as per the regulation. The same letter has been uploaded on the company&apos;s website for reference.</p><ul><li>Netripples Software Ltd has submitted an updated RPT report for Q3 2020.</li><li>The report has been submitted in accordance with the Exchange Board of India regulations.</li><li>There were no related party transactions for the quarter ended 30th September 2020.</li><li>The disclosure is of prominence as per the regulation.</li><li>The letter has been uploaded on the company&apos;s website for reference.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cd14784d-26bb-43de-8f23-52db4e2ffcfc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Netripples Software Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAATVIKGL] Saatvik Green Energy&apos;s Subsidiary Secures INR 13.80 Crores Order for Solar PV Modules</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Saatvik+Green+Energy+Ltd&title=Saatvik+Green+Energy%27s+Subsidiary+Secures+INR+13.80+Crores+Order+for+Solar+PV+Modules&newsId=4f82a93a-487f-4d5c-95a6-c26b57c0b20a&token=NGY4MmE5M2EtNDg3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4f82a93a-487f-4d5c-95a6-c26b57c0b20a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Saatvik Green Energy Ltd announced that its material subsidiary, Saatvik Solar Industries Private Limited, has received and accepted an order worth INR 13.80 Crores from one renowned Independent Power producers/EPC Players for the supply of solar PV modules. The order will be executed by February 2026.</p><ul><li>Saatvik Solar Industries Private Limited received an order for INR 13.80 Crores from Independent Power producers/EPC Players</li><li>The order is for the supply of solar PV modules</li><li>The order will be executed by February 2026</li><li>The order is worth approximately USD 1.8 million as of February 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1ee2d89e-21e4-4776-a6f4-cc381cbbdd9a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Saatvik Green Energy Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NETRIPPLES] Netripples Software Ltd. Records No Related Party Transactions in Q3 2021</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Netripples+Software+Ltd&title=Netripples+Software+Ltd.+Records+No+Related+Party+Transactions+in+Q3+2021&newsId=edc768c2-5740-477b-8993-97da5b2812a9&token=ZWRjNzY4YzItNTc0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">edc768c2-5740-477b-8993-97da5b2812a9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In accordance with the Listing Regulations 2015, Netripples Software Ltd. has updated its 23(9) RPT report for the quarter ending September 2021. The report, uploaded on the company&apos;s website, indicates no related party transactions for the quarter period ended 30th September 2021. This information is shared for record and compliance purposes.</p><ul><li>Netripples Software Ltd. reports no related party transactions for Q3 2021</li><li>The report was updated in accordance with Listing Regulations 2015</li><li>The updated report is available on the company&apos;s website</li><li>The update is for record and compliance purposes</li><li>The report was updated on time as per the regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/74b26c57-37e9-49b7-816a-3cda4d6d89f6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Netripples Software Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PPARIVAH] Paradeep Parivahan Ltd Announces EGM for Issuing Convertible Warrants</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Paradeep+Parivahan+Ltd&title=Paradeep+Parivahan+Ltd+Announces+EGM+for+Issuing+Convertible+Warrants&newsId=ba06b3c3-a8af-467a-9f75-7bb5921e6c17&token=YmEwNmIzYzMtYThh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba06b3c3-a8af-467a-9f75-7bb5921e6c17</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:04:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Paradeep Parivahan Ltd has called for an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) on January 31, 2026, to consider the issuance of up to 12,00,000 (Twelve Lakhs only) convertible warrants on a preferential basis. The warrants, priced at Rs. 156.17 each, will allow the holders to subscribe for one equity share of the company at a premium of Rs. 146.17 within 18 months from the date of allotment. The decision is subject to approval from the members, regulatory authorities, and applicable laws.</p><ul><li>Paradeep Parivahan Ltd announces EGM for issuing convertible warrants.</li><li>Up to 12,00,000 warrants to be issued at a price of Rs. 156.17 each.</li><li>Warrant holders can subscribe for one equity share at a premium of Rs. 146.17 within 18 months from the date of allotment.</li><li>The decision is subject to approval from members, regulatory authorities, and applicable laws.</li><li>The warrants will be issued to promoter and non-promoter allottees.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a272f6b6-8bc4-4097-8217-f4154812d9e6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Paradeep Parivahan Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RPOWER] Reliance Power Ltd: No Transfer Requests Received During Special Window</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RELIANCE+POWER+LTD.&title=Reliance+Power+Ltd%3A+No+Transfer+Requests+Received+During+Special+Window&newsId=d1754d8e-2501-42aa-8cbb-faf78498f013&token=ZDE3NTRkOGUtMjUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d1754d8e-2501-42aa-8cbb-faf78498f013</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Reliance Power Ltd has reported that no transfer requests were received from shareholders for re-lodgement of transfer transactions during the special window from December 01, 2025 to January 06, 2026. The company has undertaken various awareness initiatives to inform shareholders about the special window, including newspaper notices, stock exchange disclosures, social media outreach, and website disclosures.</p><ul><li>No transfer requests received during the special window</li><li>Company has undertaken various awareness initiatives</li><li>Public Notices published in Financial Express and Navshakti</li><li>Notices filed with BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange of India Limited</li><li>Posts shared on LinkedIn, Facebook, and X (formerly Twitter)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b11233b8-7d46-4230-88ae-14b6c4e7c2a3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RELIANCE POWER LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SOLARIUM] Solarium Green Energy Ltd Approves Appointment of M/s Anil Bohra &amp; Associates as Internal Auditor for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Solarium+Green+Energy+Ltd&title=Solarium+Green+Energy+Ltd+Approves+Appointment+of+M%2Fs+Anil+Bohra+%26+Associates+as+Internal+Auditor+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=8295ccb4-d973-413f-93f9-5fc5c1e2cee0&token=ODI5NWNjYjQtZDk3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8295ccb4-d973-413f-93f9-5fc5c1e2cee0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Solarium Green Energy Ltd announced the approval of the appointment of M/s Anil Bohra &amp; Associates as the Internal Auditor for the Financial Year 2025-26. The decision was made during a Board Meeting held on January 09, 2026. The meeting also saw the appointment of M/s. SCS and CO LLP as Secretarial Auditor for the same financial year. Furthermore, the designation of Mr. Himanshu Garg, the Chief Financial Officer, was changed to President — Growth and International Business, along with Business Finance. Mr. Rohit Jindal was appointed as the new Chief Financial Officer and Key Managerial Personnel.</p><ul><li>Solarium Green Energy Ltd approved the appointment of M/s Anil Bohra &amp; Associates as Internal Auditor for FY 2025-26</li><li>M/s. SCS and CO LLP appointed as Secretarial Auditor for FY 2025-26</li><li>Mr. Himanshu Garg&apos;s designation changed to President — Growth and International Business</li><li>Mr. Rohit Jindal appointed as new Chief Financial Officer and Key Managerial Personnel</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7c80ad0a-86d9-4534-a4b9-bb5c376f0eb7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Solarium Green Energy Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RAJTUBE] Rajasthan Tube Manufacturing Company Ltd. Postpones Board Meeting to Tuesday, January 13, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RAJASTHAN+TUBE+MANUFACTURING+CO.LTD.&title=Rajasthan+Tube+Manufacturing+Company+Ltd.+Postpones+Board+Meeting+to+Tuesday%2C+January+13%2C+2026&newsId=e07df360-ab42-4b98-aade-ce41b1229feb&token=ZTA3ZGYzNjAtYWI0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e07df360-ab42-4b98-aade-ce41b1229feb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:51:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rajasthan Tube Manufacturing Company Ltd. has postponed its scheduled Board of Directors meeting, originally set for Friday, January 09, 2026. The new date for the meeting is Tuesday, January 13, 2026. This change is due to unavoidable circumstances. Additionally, the company&apos;s trading window will remain closed until 48 hours after the outcome of the Board meeting is declared.</p><ul><li>Rajasthan Tube Manufacturing Company Ltd. postpones Board of Directors meeting to Tuesday, January 13, 2026.</li><li>The original meeting date was Friday, January 09, 2026.</li><li>The postponement is due to unavoidable circumstances.</li><li>The company&apos;s trading window will remain closed until 48 hours after the Board meeting outcome is declared.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/44256146-51b8-485e-b54b-3bb318d668aa.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RAJASTHAN TUBE MANUFACTURING CO.LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SOLARIUM] Solarium Green Energy Ltd Appoints M/s SCS and CO LLP as Secretarial Auditor and M/s Anil Bohra and Associates as Internal Auditor for F.Y -2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Solarium+Green+Energy+Ltd&title=Solarium+Green+Energy+Ltd+Appoints+M%2Fs+SCS+and+CO+LLP+as+Secretarial+Auditor+and+M%2Fs+Anil+Bohra+and+Associates+as+Internal+Auditor+for+F.Y+-2025-26&newsId=86a7ce3a-ff79-4dbf-89a8-fa537fa4bb8e&token=ODZhN2NlM2EtZmY3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86a7ce3a-ff79-4dbf-89a8-fa537fa4bb8e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:41:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Solarium Green Energy Ltd has approved the appointment of M/s SCS and CO LLP, Practicing Company Secretaries, as a Secretarial Auditor and M/s Anil Bohra and Associates (Chartered Accountants) as an Internal Auditor for the Financial Year 2025-26. The company also announced a change in the designation of Mr. Himanshu Garg and appointed Mr. Rohit Jindal as the new Chief Financial Officer.</p><ul><li>Solarium Green Energy Ltd has appointed M/s SCS and CO LLP as the Secretarial Auditor for the Financial Year 2025-26.</li><li>M/s Anil Bohra and Associates has been appointed as the Internal Auditor for the Financial Year 2025-26.</li><li>Mr. Himanshu Garg&apos;s designation has been changed to President — Growth and International Business, along with Business Finance.</li><li>Mr. Rohit Jindal has been appointed as the new Chief Financial Officer and Key Managerial Personnel.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ac3987ad-aef6-41e3-8ee1-55a7eabfaa12.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Solarium Green Energy Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SOLARIUM] Solarium Green Energy Ltd Appoints Mr. Rohit Jindal as New CFO</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Solarium+Green+Energy+Ltd&title=Solarium+Green+Energy+Ltd+Appoints+Mr.+Rohit+Jindal+as+New+CFO&newsId=3c82f514-0dea-43b0-8824-9798151f35c9&token=M2M4MmY1MTQtMGRl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3c82f514-0dea-43b0-8824-9798151f35c9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 16:34:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Solarium Green Energy Ltd has appointed Mr. Rohit Jindal as the new Chief Financial Officer (CFO) and Key Managerial Personnel. The appointment was made during the Board Meeting held on January 09, 2026. Mr. Jindal&apos;s appointment is expected to strengthen the company&apos;s financial management and governance framework in line with its growing business operations.</p><ul><li>Solarium Green Energy Ltd has appointed a new Chief Financial Officer (CFO)</li><li>Mr. Rohit Jindal is the new CFO</li><li>Appointment made during the Board Meeting held on January 09, 2026</li><li>Mr. Jindal&apos;s appointment is expected to strengthen the company&apos;s financial management and governance framework</li><li>His experience and leadership are expected to support the Company’s financial functions and long-term growth strategy</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0bda946e-d4ee-4585-93a3-3b977ccbec58.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Solarium Green Energy Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>