<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 09:17:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[KPITTECH] KPIT Technologies Ltd Receives Request for Reclassification from Promoters Ajay Bhagwat &amp; Ashwini Bhagwat</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KPIT+Technologies+Ltd&title=KPIT+Technologies+Ltd+Receives+Request+for+Reclassification+from+Promoters+Ajay+Bhagwat+%26+Ashwini+Bhagwat&newsId=d60388a0-921e-48a3-9c7a-7f66a81c0e85&token=ZDYwMzg4YTAtOTIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d60388a0-921e-48a3-9c7a-7f66a81c0e85</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 08:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>KPIT Technologies Ltd has received request letters for reclassification from promoters, Mr. Ajay Bhagwat &amp; Ms. Ashwini Bhagwat. The two early founders of the company have not been associated with the day-to-day operations for the past two decades and have been pursuing their own independent business interests through Renu Electronics. Their shareholding is now purely financial in nature, with no managerial, strategic, or decision-making role in the Company. The reclassification from &apos;Promoter&apos; to &apos;Public&apos; category requires approval from the Board of Directors and both stock exchanges, BSE Limited &amp; National Stock Exchange of India Limited.</p><ul><li>KPIT Technologies Ltd received reclassification request from promoters Ajay Bhagwat &amp; Ashwini Bhagwat.</li><li>Ajay Bhagwat &amp; Ashwini Bhagwat were early founders but not involved in day-to-day operations for 20 years.</li><li>They have been focusing on their own business through Renu Electronics.</li><li>Their shareholding is purely financial with no managerial, strategic, or decision-making role.</li><li>Reclassification from &apos;Promoter&apos; to &apos;Public&apos; category is subject to Board and stock exchange approvals.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/db1cb18d-c6e3-48f4-88a2-bbb75af87600.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KPIT Technologies Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUCROSA] Super Crop Safe Ltd. Corrigendum: Changes in Relevant Dates for Extra-Ordinary General Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SUPER+CROP+SAFE+LTD.&title=Super+Crop+Safe+Ltd.+Corrigendum%3A+Changes+in+Relevant+Dates+for+Extra-Ordinary+General+Meeting&newsId=de87600a-ca61-474c-a965-2fe8fa812b99&token=ZGU4NzYwMGEtY2E2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de87600a-ca61-474c-a965-2fe8fa812b99</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 07:01:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Super Crop Safe Ltd. has issued a corrigendum to the notice of its Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) scheduled for January 19, 2026. The corrigendum includes amendments to the relevant dates for determining the minimum issue price and floor price of equity shares, and the date for calculating the trading days for the company&apos;s shares. The changes are in accordance with the ICDR Regulations and SEBI(ICDR) Regulations.</p><ul><li>Amendments to the relevant date for determining the minimum issue price of equity shares</li><li>Changes in the relevant date for calculating the floor price for the issue of equity shares</li><li>Revision in the relevant date for the purpose of calculating the trading days for the company&apos;s shares</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a9c55487-6968-4c56-ab86-22782403e450.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SUPER CROP SAFE LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SEAMECLTD] Seamec Ltd&apos;s Vessel &apos;SEAMEC PALADIN&apos; Sails to Dubai for Statutory Drydocking</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SEAMEC+LTD.&title=Seamec+Ltd%27s+Vessel+%27SEAMEC+PALADIN%27+Sails+to+Dubai+for+Statutory+Drydocking&newsId=86542403-86ce-4eb5-ab66-1df6f0e40bad&token=ODY1NDI0MDMtODZj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86542403-86ce-4eb5-ab66-1df6f0e40bad</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 07:01:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Seamec Ltd has informed that their vessel, &apos;SEAMEC PALADIN&apos;, has sailed to Dubai on 17th January 2026 at 22:05 hours for undertaking Statutory Drydocking. Upon completion of the drydock, the vessel will return to India to continue its Long Term Charter with ONGC. The event was reported at 22:50 hours on 17th January 2026.</p><ul><li>Seamec Ltd&apos;s vessel &apos;SEAMEC PALADIN&apos; has sailed to Dubai for Statutory Drydocking.</li><li>The drydocking is expected to be completed in due course.</li><li>Upon completion, the vessel will return to India to continue its Long Term Charter with ONGC.</li><li>The event was reported on 17th January 2026 at 22:50 hours.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1bf77337-e26f-4cff-a180-7c86647c0fec.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SEAMEC LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HPAL] Fire Incident at HP Adhesives Ltd Manufacturing Unit</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HP+Adhesives+Ltd&title=Fire+Incident+at+HP+Adhesives+Ltd+Manufacturing+Unit&newsId=ea4afca3-f409-44d5-b371-3d69827b55df&token=ZWE0YWZjYTMtZjQw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ea4afca3-f409-44d5-b371-3d69827b55df</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 07:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Incident</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>A fire incident occurred at HP Adhesives Ltd&apos;&apos;s manufacturing unit in Raigad, Maharashtra on Saturday, 17th January 2026. The cause of the fire is currently under investigation. There were no casualties or injuries. The company is assessing the damage and loss, and has adequate insurance coverage to cover the costs. They are taking necessary steps to restore normal operations at the plant.</p><ul><li>Fire incident at HP Adhesives Ltd manufacturing unit</li><li>No casualties or injuries reported</li><li>Company assessing damage and loss</li><li>Adequate insurance coverage in place</li><li>Company taking steps to restore normal operations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/193f1b0a-76a6-4e3e-beb2-33b873c0ddf4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HP Adhesives Ltd | Category: Incident</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUVENPHAR] Cohance Lifesciences Grants 3,89,668 Stock Options Under ESOP 2023</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Suven+Pharmaceuticals+Ltd&title=Cohance+Lifesciences+Grants+3%2C89%2C668+Stock+Options+Under+ESOP+2023&newsId=37604cba-5601-482d-a7e3-ec0671a65f95&token=Mzc2MDRjYmEtNTYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37604cba-5601-482d-a7e3-ec0671a65f95</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 22:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cohance Lifesciences Ltd has approved the grant of 3,89,668 stock options to eligible employees under the Employee Stock Option Plan 2023 (ESOP 2023). This includes 2,18,077 stock options granted pursuant to the Scheme of Amalgamation between Cohance Lifesciences Limited and erstwhile Cohance Lifesciences Limited. The options have a vesting period of not earlier than 1 year and not later than 10 years from the date of grant. The exercise period is up to 3 years from the date of vesting.</p><ul><li>Grant of 3,89,668 stock options to eligible employees under ESOP 2023</li><li>Includes 2,18,077 stock options granted pursuant to Scheme of Amalgamation</li><li>Vesting period of not earlier than 1 year and not later than 10 years from the date of grant</li><li>Exercise period is up to 3 years from the date of vesting</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/69f63bdc-1bd5-40b7-89e3-b572ce2a8e47.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Suven Pharmaceuticals Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FMNL] Future Market Networks Ltd Announces Merger Application with Metawear Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=FUTURE+MARKET+NETWORKS+LTD.&title=Future+Market+Networks+Ltd+Announces+Merger+Application+with+Metawear+Limited&newsId=da6ce433-8f8d-4ea8-ae92-9af75a06b22b&token=ZGE2Y2U0MzMtOGY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">da6ce433-8f8d-4ea8-ae92-9af75a06b22b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 22:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Merger</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Future Market Networks Ltd has filed an application for approval of merger between Metawear Limited and itself with the National Company Law Tribunal, Mumbai Bench. The merger application was submitted on 17th January, 2025, following in-principle approval from stock exchanges BSE and NSE. The company will keep stock exchanges updated on further developments regarding the scheme.</p><ul><li>Future Market Networks Ltd and Metawear Limited have applied for merger under section 230 to section 232 and other applicable provisions of the Companies Act, 2013.</li><li>The merger application has been submitted to the National Company Law Tribunal, Mumbai Bench on 17th January, 2025.</li><li>In-principle approval has been received from stock exchanges BSE and NSE.</li><li>Future Market Networks Ltd will keep stock exchanges updated on further developments regarding the merger scheme.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8d3f744a-255b-4a1f-8e4f-9821daba43ca.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: FUTURE MARKET NETWORKS LTD. | Category: Merger</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAMHI] Samhi Hotels Ltd Incorporates Wholly-Owned Subsidiary SAMHI Skyline Private Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Samhi+Hotels+Ltd&title=Samhi+Hotels+Ltd+Incorporates+Wholly-Owned+Subsidiary+SAMHI+Skyline+Private+Limited&newsId=e445e377-5032-4235-ad8f-e0e4e2bdd3cc&token=ZTQ0NWUzNzctNTAz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e445e377-5032-4235-ad8f-e0e4e2bdd3cc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:51:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Samhi Hotels Ltd has incorporated a wholly-owned subsidiary company named SAMHI Skyline Private Limited on 16th January 2026. The new subsidiary has been registered with an authorized share capital of INR 10,00,000 (Indian Rupees Ten Lakhs Only) and will carry on the business to purchase, manage, own, acquire, lease, promote, takeover or lease and to operate and run hotels, holiday resorts, motels, cottages, and accommodations of all description in India or abroad. The entire Paid-up Share Capital of INR 1,00,000 (Indian Rupees One Lakh Only) will be held by SAMHI Hotels Limited, the Holding Company.</p><ul><li>Samhi Hotels Ltd incorporates a wholly-owned subsidiary, SAMHI Skyline Private Limited</li><li>New subsidiary registered with an authorized share capital of INR 10,00,000</li><li>SAMHI Skyline to operate in the Hotel business with all facilities in India or abroad</li><li>The entire Paid-up Share Capital of INR 1,00,000 held by SAMHI Hotels Limited, the Holding Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c15d827f-69eb-427d-af63-e128997a0a36.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Samhi Hotels Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WELCORP] Welspun Corp Ltd Acquires 2.57% Stake in Welspun Mauritius Holdings for USD 5.962 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Welspun+Corp+Limited&title=Welspun+Corp+Ltd+Acquires+2.57%25+Stake+in+Welspun+Mauritius+Holdings+for+USD+5.962+Million&newsId=f200901a-b37e-47f5-abdd-d93847485558&token=ZjIwMDkwMWEtYjM3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f200901a-b37e-47f5-abdd-d93847485558</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Welspun Corp Ltd has approved the acquisition of a 2.57% equity stake in Welspun Mauritius Holdings Limited (WMHL) from Welspun Pipes Inc., USA, a wholly-owned subsidiary of the Company. The transaction is valued at not more than USD 5.962 million and is expected to streamline the Company’s overseas holding structure. The transaction does not have any material impact on the operations, financial position, or profitability of the Company.</p><ul><li>Welspun Corp Ltd to acquire a 2.57% equity stake in Welspun Mauritius Holdings Limited</li><li>Transaction valued at not more than USD 5.962 million</li><li>Objective is to streamline the Company’s overseas holding structure</li><li>No material impact on the operations, financial position, or profitability of the Company</li><li>Transaction to be completed by FY 2025-2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f3274b19-324d-45b4-9b6f-3e60a7a7e04b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Welspun Corp Limited | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WELCORP] Welspun Corp Ltd Acquires 2.57% Equity Stake in Welspun Mauritius Holdings Limited for USD 5.962 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Welspun+Corp+Limited&title=Welspun+Corp+Ltd+Acquires+2.57%25+Equity+Stake+in+Welspun+Mauritius+Holdings+Limited+for+USD+5.962+Million&newsId=d16d68be-5e3c-4889-b079-2e99f6e83c5e&token=ZDE2ZDY4YmUtNWUz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d16d68be-5e3c-4889-b079-2e99f6e83c5e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:11:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Welspun Corp Ltd has approved the acquisition of a 2.57% equity stake in Welspun Mauritius Holdings Limited from Welspun Pipes Inc., USA, a wholly-owned subsidiary of the Company. The transaction is valued at not exceeding USD 5.962 million, subject to regulatory compliances. Upon completion, Welspun Mauritius Holdings Limited will become a direct wholly-owned subsidiary of the Company. The objective of the proposed acquisition is to streamline the Company’s overseas holding structure.</p><ul><li>Welspun Corp Ltd to acquire 2.57% equity stake in Welspun Mauritius Holdings Limited</li><li>Transaction valued at not exceeding USD 5.962 million</li><li>Welspun Mauritius Holdings Limited to become direct wholly-owned subsidiary of the Company</li><li>Acquisition aimed at streamlining the Company’s overseas holding structure</li><li>No impact on the Consolidated Financials</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/204e5916-4599-4808-a823-ec22f10581ee.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Welspun Corp Limited | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[THYROCARE] Thyrocare Technologies Ltd: Statutory Auditor M S K A &amp; Associates Converts to LLP</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Thyrocare+Technologies+Ltd&title=Thyrocare+Technologies+Ltd%3A+Statutory+Auditor+M+S+K+A+%26+Associates+Converts+to+LLP&newsId=2a8b53e6-520b-400d-8575-d4dc9a4e8842&token=MmE4YjUzZTYtNTIw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a8b53e6-520b-400d-8575-d4dc9a4e8842</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 16:11:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Auditor Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Thyrocare Technologies Ltd has been informed about the conversion of its Statutory Auditor, M S K A &amp; Associates, into a Limited Liability Partnership (LLP) under the Limited Liability Partnership Act, 2008. The new name of the auditor is MSKA&amp; Associates LLP (LLPIN: ACT-3789), with ICAI Firm Registration Number 105047W (Old) / W101187 (New). This conversion does not result in a change of audit responsibilities, resignation, or appointment of a new auditor; the audit engagement continues uninterrupted.</p><ul><li>Thyrocare Technologies Ltd&apos;s Statutory Auditor, M S K A &amp; Associates, has converted into a Limited Liability Partnership (LLP) named MSKA&amp; Associates LLP.</li><li>The conversion does not lead to any changes in audit responsibilities, resignation, or appointment of a new auditor.</li><li>The audit engagement continues uninterrupted.</li><li>MSKA&amp; Associates LLP has ICAI Firm Registration Number 105047W (Old) / W101187 (New).</li><li>The conversion is in compliance with Regulation 30 and Schedule III of the SEBI Listing Regulations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c393293d-02b4-432b-8537-0a2ab3f6c3d3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Thyrocare Technologies Ltd | Category: Auditor Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>