<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:57:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[MASTEK] Mastek UK Ltd Recognised by EcoVadis for Sustainability Excellence</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MASTEK+LTD.&title=Mastek+UK+Ltd+Recognised+by+EcoVadis+for+Sustainability+Excellence&newsId=953ea40d-7bd6-4283-abdd-db1edef0f3af&token=OTUzZWE0MGQtN2Jk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">953ea40d-7bd6-4283-abdd-db1edef0f3af</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mastek (UK) Ltd, a wholly owned subsidiary of Mastek, has been awarded a Silver Medal in the EcoVadis Sustainability Assessment. The assessment evaluates companies across four core pillars: Environment, Labour &amp; Human Rights, Ethics, and Sustainable Procurement. Mastek UK Ltd ranked in the Top 7% overall among IT companies and achieved an exceptional Top 2% ranking in the Environment category. This recognition reinforces Mastek&apos;s belief in responsible growth and long-term success.</p><ul><li>Mastek (UK) Ltd awarded a Silver Medal in the EcoVadis Sustainability Assessment</li><li>Ranked in the Top 7% overall among IT companies and Top 2% in the Environment category</li><li>Recognition reinforces Mastek&apos;s commitment to sustainability and responsible growth</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/37d53f8f-eeeb-4756-a981-dc020f4c9c89.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MASTEK LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HCLTECH] HCLTech Recognized as a Leader in 2025 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Service Integration and Management</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HCL+TECHNOLOGIES+LTD.&title=HCLTech+Recognized+as+a+Leader+in+2025+Gartner+Magic+Quadrant+for+Service+Integration+and+Management&newsId=35965726-c3b2-4c63-9a21-67d8367aa863&token=MzU5NjU3MjYtYzNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">35965726-c3b2-4c63-9a21-67d8367aa863</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:57:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>HCL Technologies Ltd, a leading global technology company, has been recognized as a Leader in the 2025 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Service Integration and Management (SIAM). The company has over 13 years of expertise in the SIAM market and delivers innovative solutions across key verticals such as manufacturing, retail, and healthcare. HCLTech&apos;s Al Force aims to advance SIAM across the enterprise to govern multiple functions, teams, and AI Agents, enabling faster decisions, responsible AI adoption, and sustained value creation.</p><ul><li>HCLTech recognized as a Leader in 2025 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Service Integration and Management</li><li>13 years of expertise in the SIAM market</li><li>Delivering innovative solutions across manufacturing, retail, and healthcare verticals</li><li>HCLTech&apos;s Al Force advances SIAM across the enterprise</li><li>Enabling faster decisions, responsible AI adoption, and sustained value creation</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a8392e75-cf14-4939-982f-7e8c78770784.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HCL TECHNOLOGIES LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ETT] Laddu Gopal Online Services Ltd. Announces Rights Issue of Equity Shares Worth Rs. 30 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ETT+Ltd&title=Laddu+Gopal+Online+Services+Ltd.+Announces+Rights+Issue+of+Equity+Shares+Worth+Rs.+30+Crores&newsId=637f8167-8199-40ea-90ce-78635697ed2c&token=NjM3ZjgxNjctODE5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">637f8167-8199-40ea-90ce-78635697ed2c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:53:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Laddu Gopal Online Services Ltd. has informed the BSE that the Board of Directors will meet on 02/03/2026 to consider and approve the Intimation of Rights. This follows the approval of a Rights Issue by the Board on 23rd February 2026, where fully paid-up equity shares of the company worth Rs. 30,00,00,000/- will be offered to eligible shareholders. The Rights Issue Committee will meet on the same day to discuss various matters related to the Rights Issue, including the Rights Issue price, entitlement ratio, record date, timing, and other terms and conditions. The Trading Window for dealing in the securities of the company by the designated persons and their immediate relatives has been closed from 25th February 2026 and will remain closed till 48 hours after the Rights Issue Committee Meeting.</p><ul><li>Laddu Gopal Online Services Ltd. to conduct a Rights Issue of equity shares worth Rs. 30 Crores</li><li>The Rights Issue is approved by the Board of Directors and will be offered to eligible shareholders</li><li>A Rights Issue Committee meeting is scheduled on 02/03/2026 to discuss various matters related to the Rights Issue</li><li>The Trading Window for dealing in the securities of the company is closed from 25th February 2026</li><li>The Trading Window will remain closed till 48 hours after the Rights Issue Committee Meeting</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/eb28aae9-343e-4332-85e9-8982f13b50bb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ETT Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IMCAP] Fedders Electric and Engineering Delisted from Bombay Stock Exchange &amp; National Stock Exchange</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IM%2B+Capitals+Limited&title=Fedders+Electric+and+Engineering+Delisted+from+Bombay+Stock+Exchange+%26+National+Stock+Exchange&newsId=a2b9beea-a054-4404-b091-149fc45271d4&token=YTJiOWJlZWEtYTA1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2b9beea-a054-4404-b091-149fc45271d4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:49:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Fedders Holding Ltd has informed that its material subsidiary, Fedders Electric and Engineering Limited, has received an order dated 23.02.2026 from Bombay Stock Exchange &amp; National Stock Exchange approving the delisting of equity shares of Fedders Electric and Engineering Limited. The delisting will be effective from March 02, 2026. This decision comes in view of the order of Hon’ble NCLT Allahabad Bench, Prayagraj dated 16.10.2025. Fedders Holding Ltd does not anticipate any material impact on its consolidated financial statements.</p><ul><li>Fedders Electric and Engineering Limited has received an order for delisting from Bombay Stock Exchange &amp; National Stock Exchange</li><li>The delisting is effective from March 02, 2026</li><li>The decision is in view of the order of Hon’ble NCLT Allahabad Bench, Prayagraj dated 16.10.2025</li><li>Fedders Holding Ltd does not anticipate any material impact on its consolidated financial statements</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/50aef018-ed0f-4605-a141-4fb4857ba305.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IM+ Capitals Limited | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BARBEQUE] United Foodbrands Ltd Incorporates a Step-Down Subsidiary in Qatar</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Barbeque-Nation+Hospitality+Ltd&title=United+Foodbrands+Ltd+Incorporates+a+Step-Down+Subsidiary+in+Qatar&newsId=c6e4f785-9ad8-40a9-ab92-5bd298892d47&token=YzZlNGY3ODUtOWFk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c6e4f785-9ad8-40a9-ab92-5bd298892d47</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:49:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>United Foodbrands Ltd has incorporated a new Step-Down Subsidiary, Barbeque Nation Restaurant W.L.L, in Doha, Qatar. The new subsidiary, with a share capital of QAR 200,000 divided into 100 shares of QAR 2,000 each, is a food services/restaurant business. The incorporation was approved on February 24, 2026, and Barbeque Nation MENA Holding Limited, a Wholly Owned Subsidiary of the Company, has subscribed to 60 shares, acquiring 60% shareholding. None of the promoters or members of the Promoters Group or Directors of the Company are interested, financially or otherwise, in Barbeque Nation Restaurant W.L.L. The new subsidiary is in line with the business of the Company.</p><ul><li>United Foodbrands Ltd incorporates a new Step-Down Subsidiary, Barbeque Nation Restaurant W.L.L, in Qatar</li><li>The new subsidiary is a food services/restaurant business</li><li>Barbeque Nation MENA Holding Limited, a Wholly Owned Subsidiary of the Company, has subscribed to 60 shares, acquiring 60% shareholding</li><li>The new subsidiary is in line with the business of the Company</li><li>None of the promoters or members of the Promoters Group or Directors of the Company are interested in Barbeque Nation Restaurant W.L.L</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/18af39ff-52ad-425c-ac60-8d878adfff8c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Barbeque-Nation Hospitality Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UNIECOM] Kama Ayurveda Partners with Unicommerce for Streamlined Online Operations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Unicommerce+Esolutions+Ltd&title=Kama+Ayurveda+Partners+with+Unicommerce+for+Streamlined+Online+Operations&newsId=3491586e-fc96-41b2-a78a-97b68979100a&token=MzQ5MTU4NmUtZmM5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3491586e-fc96-41b2-a78a-97b68979100a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:46:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Partnership</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Kama Ayurveda, one of India’s leading wellness and natural beauty brands, has partnered with Unicommerce to streamline its online operations. The partnership aims to ensure faster and more efficient deliveries by leveraging Unicommerce’s flagship platform, Uniware, and its logistics tech platform Shipway. This will help Kama Ayurveda manage orders, inventory, warehouse operations, and shipments from a single platform, enabling it to serve customers more quickly and accurately.</p><ul><li>Kama Ayurveda partners with Unicommerce to streamline online operations</li><li>Unicommerce’s Uniware to manage orders and warehouses more efficiently</li><li>Integration with Unicommerce’s Shipway to optimise deliveries and reduce transit times</li><li>Centralised inventory management, faster order processing, and accurate reporting</li><li>Unicommerce’s technology to provide detailed sales insights and simplify accounting</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1363d750-f5ca-4f1f-a543-3b03b147d55e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Unicommerce Esolutions Ltd | Category: Partnership</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDUSINDBK] IndusInd Bank Goes Live with Next-Gen UPI Processing Platform, Offers Faster Transaction Speed and Seamless Disaster Recovery</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDUSIND+BANK+LTD.&title=IndusInd+Bank+Goes+Live+with+Next-Gen+UPI+Processing+Platform%2C+Offers+Faster+Transaction+Speed+and+Seamless+Disaster+Recovery&newsId=daf43afb-175d-46f9-a74f-45d303e755dd&token=ZGFmNDNhZmItMTc1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">daf43afb-175d-46f9-a74f-45d303e755dd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:43:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>IndusInd Bank has announced that its digital banking channels are now live on the Next-gen UPI processing platform, UPI 6.0, built by Mindgate Solutions. This 6th generation upgrade is a transformative leap in India’s real-time payments ecosystem, offering an uninterrupted, high-performance payment experience for millions of customers and merchants across the country. The platform delivers sub-second response times, near-zero technical declines, and seamless disaster recovery within minutes, ensuring superior transaction reliability and operational continuity.</p><ul><li>IndusInd Bank is the first private bank to go live on the Next-gen UPI processing platform for both Issuer and Acquirer services on the cloud.</li><li>The platform offers a state-of-the-art real-time payments stack, delivering 30% faster recovery time (RTO) and providing up to 75% higher scalability headroom with the current infrastructure.</li><li>The launch aligns with IndusInd Bank’s Digital 2.0 strategy, focusing on creating a seamless, secure, and intuitive banking ecosystem.</li><li>The platform is designed to deliver sub-second response times, near-zero technical declines, and seamless disaster recovery within minutes.</li><li>IndusInd Bank serves around 42 million customers through 3,120 branches/banking outlets and 3,063 ATMs, reaching 1.62 lac villages across India.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0651f4d9-1d8b-453d-84eb-1f77b84ed5f4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDUSIND BANK LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NATPEROX] Naperol Investments Declares Interim Dividend of 30% for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NATIONAL+PEROXIDE+LTD.&title=Naperol+Investments+Declares+Interim+Dividend+of+30%25+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=ce14fa49-4cef-444d-a4fa-44f73ee632aa&token=Y2UxNGZhNDktNGNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce14fa49-4cef-444d-a4fa-44f73ee632aa</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:39:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Naperol Investments Ltd has announced an interim dividend for the financial year 2025-26 of Rs. 3.00/- per equity share, which is 30% of the face value of Rs.10/- per equity share. The record date to determine the eligibility of shareholders to receive this interim dividend is fixed as Wednesday, 4th March 2026. The dividend is subject to deduction/withholding of applicable taxes and will be paid within the stipulated timelines as prescribed under law.</p><ul><li>Naperol Investments has declared an interim dividend of 30% for FY 2025-26.</li><li>The interim dividend is Rs. 3.00/- per equity share.</li><li>The record date to determine the eligibility of shareholders is 4th March 2026.</li><li>The dividend is subject to deduction/withholding of applicable taxes.</li><li>The dividend will be paid within the stipulated timelines as prescribed under law.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bda059c6-48f0-4b53-bc24-55710970d8ec.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NATIONAL PEROXIDE LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HCLTECH] HCLTech Named as a Leader in IDC MarketScape: Canadian Al Services 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HCL+TECHNOLOGIES+LTD.&title=HCLTech+Named+as+a+Leader+in+IDC+MarketScape%3A+Canadian+Al+Services+2025&newsId=523d88cd-a0bc-48c4-8dc5-89d539491ebc&token=NTIzZDg4Y2QtYTBi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">523d88cd-a0bc-48c4-8dc5-89d539491ebc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:37:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Al Services</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>HCL Technologies Ltd, a leading global technology company, has been recognized as a Leader in the IDC MarketScape: Canadian Al Services 2025 Vendor Assessment. The company stands out with its client centricity and tailored engagement models. HCLTech&apos;s Al capabilities have been praised by clients for its ability to codevelop Al use cases, range of Al services, domain and technical expertise, and innovation. The company has been operating in Canada for over 16 years, supporting Al initiatives across various sectors. HCLTech&apos;s Al-led engagements in the region help organizations build competitive advantage, advance sustainability goals, and unlock growth through data-driven transformation and business model innovation.</p><ul><li>HCLTech named a Leader in IDC MarketScape: Canadian Al Services 2025</li><li>Recognized for client centricity and tailored engagement models</li><li>Praised for ability to codevelop Al use cases and range of Al services</li><li>16 years of operation in Canada, supporting Al initiatives across various sectors</li><li>Al-led engagements help organizations build competitive advantage and unlock growth</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a36ca0b7-0b08-4974-9c9e-7cc083862ebe.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HCL TECHNOLOGIES LTD. | Category: Al Services</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NATPEROX] Naperol Investments Ltd Declares Interim Dividend of 30% for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NATIONAL+PEROXIDE+LTD.&title=Naperol+Investments+Ltd+Declares+Interim+Dividend+of+30%25+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=23f2d012-bf87-4855-b714-e1cd90084d22&token=MjNmMmQwMTItYmY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23f2d012-bf87-4855-b714-e1cd90084d22</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 06:37:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Naperol Investments Ltd has announced an interim dividend for the financial year 2025-26 of Rs. 3.00/- per equity share, which is 30% of the face value of Rs.10/- per equity share. The record date to determine the eligibility of shareholders to receive the dividend is fixed as Wednesday, 4th March 2026. The dividend is subject to applicable taxes and will be paid within the stipulated timelines as prescribed under law.</p><ul><li>Naperol Investments Ltd has declared an interim dividend of Rs. 3.00/- per equity share for FY 2025-26.</li><li>The dividend represents 30% of the face value of Rs.10/- per equity share.</li><li>The record date to determine the eligibility of shareholders is fixed as Wednesday, 4th March 2026.</li><li>The dividend is subject to deduction/withholding of applicable taxes.</li><li>The dividend will be paid within the stipulated timelines as prescribed under law.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e6ef014d-32fc-47a0-8dce-f4154fd25540.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NATIONAL PEROXIDE LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>