<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:45:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SNIM] Svarnim Trade Udyog Ltd Appoints Mr. Rahul Sharma as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Svarnim+Trade+Udyog+Ltd&title=Svarnim+Trade+Udyog+Ltd+Appoints+Mr.+Rahul+Sharma+as+Company+Secretary+and+Compliance+Officer&newsId=93756064-fd95-414d-9a99-b095dd7381d4&token=OTM3NTYwNjQtZmQ5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93756064-fd95-414d-9a99-b095dd7381d4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:44:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Expansion</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Svarnim Trade Udyog Ltd, a company based in Kolkata, has appointed Mr. Rahul Sharma as its Company Secretary and Compliance Officer. Mr. Sharma, with membership number A79711, is an Associate Company Secretary (ACS) and has completed 21 months of Management Training with a practicing firm. He has been recognized for his strong analytical skills and professional excellence. The appointment was approved in a Board of Directors meeting held on 2nd March, 2026.</p><ul><li>Svarnim Trade Udyog Ltd has appointed Mr. Rahul Sharma as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer</li><li>Mr. Rahul Sharma is an Associate Company Secretary (ACS) with comprehensive exposure to corporate laws and secretarial compliance</li><li>Mr. Sharma has been recognized for his strong analytical skills and professional excellence</li><li>The appointment was approved in a Board of Directors meeting held on 2nd March, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4fb7e36c-2d8e-4728-9fa4-1dd2259b217d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Svarnim Trade Udyog Ltd | Category: Expansion</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RRECL] RDB Real Estate Constructions Ltd: Independent Director Mr. Samprati Kamdar Resigns Due to Pre-Occupation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RDB+Real+Estate+Constructions+Ltd&title=RDB+Real+Estate+Constructions+Ltd%3A+Independent+Director+Mr.+Samprati+Kamdar+Resigns+Due+to+Pre-Occupation&newsId=11da6ef0-5c8e-4892-91f3-4fdeb52114d8&token=MTFkYTZlZjAtNWM4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11da6ef0-5c8e-4892-91f3-4fdeb52114d8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:42:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>RDB Real Estate Constructions Ltd announced the resignation of its Independent Director, Mr. Samprati Kamdar, due to his pre-occupation and other personal commitments. The resignation is effective from the close of business hours on 027 March, 2026. Mr. Kamdar will also cease to be a member of the Audit Committee and Committee of Directors of the Board. The Board has reconstituted these Committees in accordance with applicable regulatory requirements. Mr. Kamdar confirmed that there are no other material reasons for his resignation other than those mentioned in his resignation letter. Mr. Kamdar served as the Chairman of the Audit, Nomination &amp; Remuneration Committee and Stakeholders Relationship Committee at BFM Industries Limited and as an Independent Director at NTC Industries Limited.</p><ul><li>Independent Director Mr. Samprati Kamdar resigns from RDB Real Estate Constructions Ltd.</li><li>Resignation effective from the close of business hours on 027 March, 2026.</li><li>Mr. Kamdar to cease membership in Audit Committee and Committee of Directors.</li><li>Board reconstitutes Committees in accordance with regulatory requirements.</li><li>Mr. Kamdar confirms no other material reasons for resignation.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e99fda5d-77a8-424c-a6b0-7f1b8d37fb09.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RDB Real Estate Constructions Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ACSTECH] ACS Technologies Ltd Revises Corporate Guarantee for Subsidiary Iotiq Innovations Private Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ACS+Technologies+Ltd&title=ACS+Technologies+Ltd+Revises+Corporate+Guarantee+for+Subsidiary+Iotiq+Innovations+Private+Limited&newsId=d25647e2-1b34-4b8a-886c-f8d312ff0b61&token=ZDI1NjQ3ZTItMWIz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d25647e2-1b34-4b8a-886c-f8d312ff0b61</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>ACS Technologies Ltd, formerly known as LN Industries India Limited, has revised its corporate guarantee for its subsidiary, Iotiq Innovations Private Limited. The Board of Directors approved an enhancement of the existing corporate guarantee from Rs. 2,50,00,000 to Rs. 4,50,00,000 in favor of State Bank of India. This enhancement is in compliance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The revised guarantee is provided on an arm&apos;s length basis and there is no impact on the Company other than disclosure in the Financial Statements.</p><ul><li>ACS Technologies Ltd enhances corporate guarantee for subsidiary</li><li>Guarantee increased from Rs. 2,50,00,000 to Rs. 4,50,00,000</li><li>Guarantee given in favor of State Bank of India</li><li>Transaction done on an arm&apos;s length basis</li><li>No impact on the Company other than disclosure in Financial Statements</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3d1fbd0b-c4f9-403d-a3fd-0ac7778b886f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ACS Technologies Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SANINFRA] Sanmit Infra Secures 250,000 SQMT Micro Surfacing Work Order from Anand Constructions</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sanmit+Infra+Limited&title=Sanmit+Infra+Secures+250%2C000+SQMT+Micro+Surfacing+Work+Order+from+Anand+Constructions&newsId=1ad8dfd3-c45e-45be-8595-b3d66f41419a&token=MWFkOGRmZDMtYzQ1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1ad8dfd3-c45e-45be-8595-b3d66f41419a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:42:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Sanmit Infra Ltd has secured a significant work order of 250000 SQMT Micro Surfacing Work at Nagothane Road Project for M/s. Anand Constructions. The contract is priced at Rs. 3,51,05,000/- (including GST 18%). The work is expected to commence on 15-03-2026 and end on 31-05-2026. The contract includes all machinery, manpower, materials, fuel, QC/QA, supervision, and execution. The scope of work also includes the basic requirement of laboratory equipment provision.</p><ul><li>Secured a work order of 250000 SQMT Micro Surfacing Work at Nagothane Road Project for M/s. Anand Constructions</li><li>Contract price is Rs. 3,51,05,000/- (including GST 18%)</li><li>Work commencement date is 15-03-2026 and end date is 31-05-2026</li><li>Includes all machinery, manpower, materials, fuel, QC/QA, supervision, and execution</li><li>The scope of work also includes the basic requirement of laboratory equipment provision</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c60bce6c-f1c0-4464-a0b2-4ecb47b854fa.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sanmit Infra Limited | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DSFCL] DCM Shriram Fine Chemicals Appoints Alok Bansidhar Shriram and Sunil Behari Mathur as Additional Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DCM+Shriram+Fine+Chemicals+Ltd&title=DCM+Shriram+Fine+Chemicals+Appoints+Alok+Bansidhar+Shriram+and+Sunil+Behari+Mathur+as+Additional+Directors&newsId=aa49c83f-aa70-4271-bf89-9cf97f26aaf2&token=YWE0OWM4M2YtYWE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa49c83f-aa70-4271-bf89-9cf97f26aaf2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:42:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>DCM Shriram Fine Chemicals Limited has appointed Mr. Alok Bansidhar Shriram and Mr. Sunil Behari Mathur as Additional Directors (Non Executive, Non Independent). The appointments are subject to approval of Shareholders. Both directors have confirmed that they are not debarred under the Companies Act, 2013 and SEBI LODR Regulations to hold an office of director. The composition of the Board of Directors of the Company will continue to be in compliance with the requirements prescribed under the Companies Act, 2013 and SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>DCM Shriram Fine Chemicals Limited has appointed two new Additional Directors.</li><li>The appointments are subject to approval of Shareholders.</li><li>Both directors have confirmed that they are not debarred under the Companies Act, 2013 and SEBI LODR Regulations to hold an office of director.</li><li>The composition of the Board of Directors of the Company will continue to be in compliance with the requirements prescribed under the Companies Act, 2013 and SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2a3bf19a-15af-4865-94da-0e53c1f4f0f7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DCM Shriram Fine Chemicals Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BHARATCOAL] Bharat Coking Coal Ltd Announces Changes in Key Managerial Personnel</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Bharat+Coking+Coal+Ltd&title=Bharat+Coking+Coal+Ltd+Announces+Changes+in+Key+Managerial+Personnel&newsId=d4bb597d-5a0e-47e9-8121-b1eb6b12bbb6&token=ZDRiYjU5N2QtNWEw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4bb597d-5a0e-47e9-8121-b1eb6b12bbb6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bharat Coking Coal Ltd (BCCL) has announced changes in its key managerial personnel. The Board of Directors, in a meeting held on 28 February 2026, approved the appointment of Shri Rajesh Kumar as the Chief Financial Officer (CFO) with immediate effect. He replaces Shri M.S. Raju, who was earlier designated as CFO. The Board also approved the appointment of Shri Debanuj Debnath as the Company Secretary and Compliance Officer, effective 1 March 2026, following the superannuation of Shri Bani Kumar Parui on 28 February 2026. The changes were made to ensure continuity and efficiency in the company&apos;s financial and compliance operations.</p><ul><li>Shri Rajesh Kumar appointed as CFO of BCCL</li><li>Shri M.S. Raju ceases to be CFO of BCCL</li><li>Shri Debanuj Debnath appointed as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer of BCCL</li><li>Shri Bani Kumar Parui superannuates from BCCL on 28 February 2026</li><li>Changes made to ensure continuity and efficiency in BCCL&apos;s financial and compliance operations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/81ca7bc7-5ef0-467e-af28-3fcd613ed0a7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Bharat Coking Coal Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RGF] RGF Capital Markets Ltd Closes Trading Window for Fund Raising Determination</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RGF+Capital+Markets+Ltd&title=RGF+Capital+Markets+Ltd+Closes+Trading+Window+for+Fund+Raising+Determination&newsId=b9dd9a1a-f010-4426-a358-483665632119&token=YjlkZDlhMWEtZjAx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b9dd9a1a-f010-4426-a358-483665632119</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:41:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>RGF Capital Markets Ltd has announced the closure of its trading window for all designated persons from March 01, 2026. This closure is in connection with the Board Meeting scheduled on March 06, 2026, which will determine the proposal for fund raising through rights issue, preferential issue, or any other permissible mode. The trading window will reopen 48 hours after the conclusion of the meeting.</p><ul><li>RGF Capital Markets Ltd closes trading window for all designated persons from March 01, 2026.</li><li>The closure is in connection with the Board Meeting on March 06, 2026, for fund raising determination.</li><li>The trading window will reopen 48 hours after the Board Meeting.</li><li>Designated persons are advised not to buy, sell, pledge, or deal in the securities of the Company during this period.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a16ca4fd-81c5-4967-94f4-93143bf08232.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RGF Capital Markets Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RRECL] RDB Real Estate Constructions Ltd Amends Code of Practice and Procedures for Fair Disclosure of UPSI</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RDB+Real+Estate+Constructions+Ltd&title=RDB+Real+Estate+Constructions+Ltd+Amends+Code+of+Practice+and+Procedures+for+Fair+Disclosure+of+UPSI&newsId=1c685a8f-8066-4973-b2ca-31835c318d9c&token=MWM2ODVhOGYtODA2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c685a8f-8066-4973-b2ca-31835c318d9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:38:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Code of Practice and Procedures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>RDB Real Estate Constructions Ltd has amended its &apos;Code of Practices and Procedures for Fair Disclosure of Unpublished Price Sensitive Information&apos; in compliance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015. The amended Code aims to maintain uniformity, transparency, and fairness in dealing with all stakeholders, enabling equal access to relevant information for all investors.</p><ul><li>RDB Real Estate Constructions Ltd amends its Code of Practice and Procedures for Fair Disclosure of Unpublished Price Sensitive Information</li><li>The amendment ensures compliance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015</li><li>The updated Code aims to maintain uniformity, transparency, and fairness in dealing with all stakeholders</li><li>Equal access to relevant information for all investors is supported</li><li>The amended Code is available on the company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/972c09d6-35bc-43a3-a569-704b3d365100.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RDB Real Estate Constructions Ltd | Category: Code of Practice and Procedures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDSWFTLAB] Ind-Swift Laboratories Ltd Receives EcoVadis Silver Medal for Sustainability and Ethics</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IND-SWIFT+LABORATORIES+LTD.&title=Ind-Swift+Laboratories+Ltd+Receives+EcoVadis+Silver+Medal+for+Sustainability+and+Ethics&newsId=f26ec2d8-df5b-4a2f-a8ac-8bc80a2a4bc9&token=ZjI2ZWMyZDgtZGY1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f26ec2d8-df5b-4a2f-a8ac-8bc80a2a4bc9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:38:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Award</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ind-Swift Laboratories Ltd, a pharmaceutical company, has been awarded the EcoVadis Silver Medal for its Global Business Unit (GBU), a 100% Export Oriented Unit located at Village Jawaharpur, Derabassi (Punjab). The Silver Medal is awarded to companies that rank within the top 15% of all organizations assessed globally by EcoVadis during the evaluation period. This recognition strengthens the Company’s positioning in global supply chains where ESG ratings are increasingly a prerequisite for partnerships, especially with multinational pharmaceutical companies and regulated market customers.</p><ul><li>Ind-Swift Laboratories Ltd received the EcoVadis Silver Medal for its GBU, placing it among the top 15% of organizations globally assessed.</li><li>The Silver Medal reflects strong performance in sustainability, ethics, environment, labour &amp; human rights, and responsible procurement.</li><li>The recognition enhances investor confidence, global market access, risk governance, and brand &amp; reputation capital.</li><li>Ind-Swift Laboratories Ltd maintains multiple internationally recognized certifications, forming a robust governance and compliance backbone.</li><li>The Company is committed to continuous improvement in ESG performance and sustainable value creation.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/18412d92-97f8-4c47-b839-05b455fdfa22.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IND-SWIFT LABORATORIES LTD. | Category: Award</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GSBFIN] GSB Finance Ltd Amends &apos;Code of Fair Disclosure&apos; to Enhance Transparency</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GSB+FINANCE+LTD.&title=GSB+Finance+Ltd+Amends+%27Code+of+Fair+Disclosure%27+to+Enhance+Transparency&newsId=179944c2-88a9-4013-98f7-24e22f1e004e&token=MTc5OTQ0YzItODhh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">179944c2-88a9-4013-98f7-24e22f1e004e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:35:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>GSB Finance Ltd has amended its &apos;Code of practices and procedures for fair disclosure of UPSI&apos; to strengthen its framework and policy for fair disclosure of events and occurrences that could impact price discovery in the market for the securities of the Company. The amended Code intends to promote transparency amongst the investors and formulate a framework for fair disclosure of Unpublished Price Sensitive Information (UPSI). The amended Code is applicable to all the persons of the Company who could possess UPSI relating to the Company.</p><ul><li>GSB Finance Ltd amends its &apos;Code of practices and procedures for fair disclosure of UPSI&apos;</li><li>Strengthens framework and policy for fair disclosure of events and occurrences that could impact price discovery</li><li>Promotes transparency amongst the investors</li><li>Formulates a framework for fair disclosure of Unpublished Price Sensitive Information (UPSI)</li><li>Applicable to all the persons of the Company who could possess UPSI relating to the Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ebb44cad-ec13-43ad-9416-4ebf65a80784.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GSB FINANCE LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>