<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 21:22:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[CIPLA] Cipla Ltd. Concludes GST Department Inspection with No Material Impact</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CIPLA+LTD.&title=Cipla+Ltd.+Concludes+GST+Department+Inspection+with+No+Material+Impact&newsId=e0586e77-a705-4325-957c-35f9a0a095c2&token=ZTA1ODZlNzctYTcw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0586e77-a705-4325-957c-35f9a0a095c2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 20:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cipla Ltd. has notified the conclusion of an Inspection/Search by the Goods &amp; Service Tax Department, Maharashtra on 7th February, 2026. The company has provided all necessary documents, clarifications and details as requested. There is no material impact on the company&apos;s financials, operations, or other activities due to the inspection/search.</p><ul><li>Cipla Ltd. has concluded an Inspection/Search by the Goods &amp; Service Tax Department, Maharashtra on 7th February, 2026.</li><li>The company has provided all necessary documents, clarifications, and details as requested.</li><li>There is no material impact on the company&apos;s financials, operations, or other activities due to the inspection/search.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2e2d7405-f32d-48be-921c-cb43f85e3a8d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CIPLA LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHRIKRISH] Shri Krishna Devcon Ltd to Approve Q4 Results on Feb 14, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHRI+KRISHNA+DEVCON+LTD.&title=Shri+Krishna+Devcon+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+Results+on+Feb+14%2C+2026&newsId=ed43a865-1e26-4198-9e43-68088f0a8bbe&token=ZWQ0M2E4NjUtMWUy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed43a865-1e26-4198-9e43-68088f0a8bbe</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 20:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shri Krishna Devcon Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 14, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025. The meeting will also address routine businesses. In accordance with Regulation 29 of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015, the trading window for all designated persons, including promoters, directors, key managerial personnel, designated employees, fiduciaries, their immediate relatives, and all connected persons, will be closed until the expiry of 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results to the stock exchange.</p><ul><li>Shri Krishna Devcon Ltd to consider and approve Q4 results on Feb 14, 2026</li><li>Trading window to remain closed till 48 hours after result declaration</li><li>Meeting to address routine businesses along with result approval</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/37b5bdea-0ace-4175-b996-ecb128617c70.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHRI KRISHNA DEVCON LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RLFL] Ramchandra Leasing &amp; Finance Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025 in February 2026 Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ramchandra+Leasing+%26+Finance+Ltd&title=Ramchandra+Leasing+%26+Finance+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025+in+February+2026+Board+Meeting&newsId=266262c9-83e6-4028-bb48-6c49b3cd6484&token=MjY2MjYyYzktODNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">266262c9-83e6-4028-bb48-6c49b3cd6484</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 20:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ramchandra Leasing &amp; Finance Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 14, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will also take note of the Limited Review Report for the same period. Additionally, the Board will discuss the resignation or appointment of Directors and other relevant matters.</p><ul><li>Ramchandra Leasing &amp; Finance Ltd to approve Q3 and nine months results for 2025</li><li>The meeting is scheduled for February 14, 2026</li><li>The Board will consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>The Board will take note of the Limited Review Report for the same period</li><li>The resignation or appointment of Directors will be discussed</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ecf56b5a-1603-4818-a527-c9fb87fc710f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ramchandra Leasing & Finance Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NNTL] N2N Technologies Ltd to Consider and Approve Unaudited Financial Results on Feb 14, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=N2N+Technologies+Limited&title=N2N+Technologies+Ltd+to+Consider+and+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+on+Feb+14%2C+2026&newsId=fd1e7c2a-427c-4f38-9d6d-80f96ff1bc97&token=ZmQxZTdjMmEtNDI3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd1e7c2a-427c-4f38-9d6d-80f96ff1bc97</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 20:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>N2N Technologies Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 14, 2026 to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will also approve the limited review report.</p><ul><li>N2N Technologies Ltd to consider and approve unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The meeting will be held on February 14, 2026.</li><li>The approval of the limited review report will also be on the agenda.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/729e2176-5c14-4e25-bf57-b1bb032f2380.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: N2N Technologies Limited | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IISL] Ishaan Infrastructures to Consider and Approve Un-audited Financial Results on Feb 11, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ishaan+Infrastructures+and+Shelters+Ltd&title=Ishaan+Infrastructures+to+Consider+and+Approve+Un-audited+Financial+Results+on+Feb+11%2C+2026&newsId=32258413-1b9a-4e20-a0c0-8ba600504325&token=MzIyNTg0MTMtMWI5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32258413-1b9a-4e20-a0c0-8ba600504325</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ishaan Infrastructures And Shelters Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 11, 2026, to consider and approve the Un-audited Standalone Financial Results for the third quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The meeting will take place at 507-B, Titanium City Centre, near Sachin Towers, 100 Feet Road, Anandnagar, Satellite, Jodhpur Char Rasta, Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India, 380015. The agenda also includes the review of any other business with the permission of the Chair.</p><ul><li>Ishaan Infrastructures Board of Directors to meet on February 11, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve Un-audited Standalone Financial Results for Q3 and nine months of 2025</li><li>The meeting will take place at Titanium City Centre, Ahmedabad, Gujarat</li><li>The agenda includes the review of any other business with the permission of the Chair</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a5b9a12f-0040-462e-a9ba-b08803b726dd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ishaan Infrastructures and Shelters Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GODREJAGRO] Godrej Agrovet Launches New Insecticide &apos;TAKAI&apos; for Rice Crops</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Godrej+Agrovet+Ltd&title=Godrej+Agrovet+Launches+New+Insecticide+%27TAKAI%27+for+Rice+Crops&newsId=71b420ba-69c3-4742-9f47-6969e2d03b5e&token=NzFiNDIwYmEtNjlj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71b420ba-69c3-4742-9f47-6969e2d03b5e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 16:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Godrej Agrovet Limited has launched a new insecticide TAKAI, developed for rice crops. Powered by Cyclapryn™ technology developed by ISK Japan, TAKAI is effective against key rice pests, Stem Borer and Leaf Folder. The insecticide provides extensive protection when applied at 15-30 Days After Transplant (DAT) and again at 40-60 DAT. The company is in process of getting label approval in Maize, Chilli, Cabbage, Soybean, Chickpea and Sugarcane crops too for TAKAI.</p><ul><li>Launch of new insecticide &apos;TAKAI&apos; for rice crops</li><li>Powered by Cyclapryn™ technology developed by ISK Japan</li><li>Effective against key rice pests Stem Borer and Leaf Folder</li><li>Provides extensive protection when applied at 15-30 DAT and 40-60 DAT</li><li>Label approval sought for use in Maize, Chilli, Cabbage, Soybean, Chickpea and Sugarcane crops</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7901afb5-3c16-4350-a169-8589b84408a3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Godrej Agrovet Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAKUMA] Sakuma Exports Ltd to Approve Q4 Results on Feb 14, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SAKUMA+EXPORTS+LTD.&title=Sakuma+Exports+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+Results+on+Feb+14%2C+2026&newsId=06b94ae9-bacf-49b9-b9fb-22856d6603c5&token=MDZiOTRhZTktYmFj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06b94ae9-bacf-49b9-b9fb-22856d6603c5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 14:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sakuma Exports Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 14, 2026, to consider and approve the Un-Audited Financial Results (Standalone and Consolidated) for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The meeting will also consider and approve the Limited Review Report (Standalone and Consolidated) by the statutory Auditor of the Company. The trading window for dealing in securities of the Company will remain closed from 1st January, 2026, and will open 48 hours after the declaration of the said Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Sakuma Exports Ltd to consider and approve Q4 results for the year 2025 on Feb 14, 2026</li><li>The meeting will also approve the Limited Review Report by the statutory Auditor</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities of the Company will remain closed from 1st January, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0fad0449-833f-4235-9b54-2770898db985.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SAKUMA EXPORTS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASHAPURMIN] Independent Director, Mr. Pundarik Sanyal, Completes His Second Term at Ashapura Minechem Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ASHAPURA+MINECHEM+LTD.&title=Independent+Director%2C+Mr.+Pundarik+Sanyal%2C+Completes+His+Second+Term+at+Ashapura+Minechem+Ltd&newsId=fc4d6a1a-0ce6-4a26-96ee-7c672c1f108f&token=ZmM0ZDZhMWEtMGNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc4d6a1a-0ce6-4a26-96ee-7c672c1f108f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ashapura Minechem Ltd announces the completion of the second term of Mr. Pundarik Sanyal as an Independent Director. He ceased to be the Independent Director from the close of business hours on 08th February, 2026. The Board of Directors acknowledges his valuable contributions and guidance during his tenure.</p><ul><li>Mr. Pundarik Sanyal completes his second term as an Independent Director at Ashapura Minechem Ltd.</li><li>He ceased to be the Independent Director from the close of business hours on 08th February, 2026.</li><li>The Board of Directors acknowledges his valuable contributions and guidance during his tenure.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/16208b60-963a-4226-8a24-0d6338b1a874.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ASHAPURA MINECHEM LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[URAVI] Uravi Defence and Technology Ltd. Announces EGM for Shareholder Approval on Key Decisions</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Uravi+T+And+Wedge+Lamps+Ltd&title=Uravi+Defence+and+Technology+Ltd.+Announces+EGM+for+Shareholder+Approval+on+Key+Decisions&newsId=91fb808e-7256-43f2-b4da-6d7146606a05&token=OTFmYjgwOGUtNzI1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">91fb808e-7256-43f2-b4da-6d7146606a05</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Uravi Defence and Technology Ltd., formerly known as Uravi T &amp; Wedge Lamps Limited, has announced an Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) to be held on March 02, 2026, at 4.00 P.M. The meeting will be conducted through video conferencing in accordance with MCA and SEBI guidelines. The agenda includes the appointment of M/S Viren Gandhi &amp; Co as the new Statutory Auditors, consideration of a proposal for disinvestment in SKL India Private Limited, and approval of a material related party transaction for disinvestment of 50.01% shareholding in SKL. The remote e-voting will commence on February 27, 2026, and end on March 01, 2026.</p><ul><li>Appointment of M/S Viren Gandhi &amp; Co as Statutory Auditors.</li><li>Consideration of a proposal for disinvestment in SKL India Private Limited.</li><li>Approval of a material related party transaction for disinvestment of 50.01% shareholding in SKL.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7e7284a8-f566-4779-a529-eb9b6361a476.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Uravi T And Wedge Lamps Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HCG] HealthCare Global Enterprises Ltd. to Consider Fund Raise by Rights Issue on Feb 17, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HealthCare+Global+Enterprises+Ltd&title=HealthCare+Global+Enterprises+Ltd.+to+Consider+Fund+Raise+by+Rights+Issue+on+Feb+17%2C+2026&newsId=a8a17a43-54f9-47c5-9651-7ca96b44665b&token=YThhMTdhNDMtNTRm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8a17a43-54f9-47c5-9651-7ca96b44665b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>HealthCare Global Enterprises Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 17, 2026, to consider and approve a proposal for a fund raise through a rights issue. The company&apos;s trading window for dealing in securities will be closed for all designated persons from February 9, 2026, to February 26, 2026, in accordance with the Company&apos;s Code of Conduct for Prevention of Insider Trading.</p><ul><li>HealthCare Global Enterprises Ltd. to consider a fund raise by rights issue on Feb 17, 2026</li><li>The company&apos;s trading window for dealing in securities will be closed for all designated persons from Feb 9, 2026, to Feb 26, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f6471e06-c9e9-4a00-833a-8b17c3f51bf7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HealthCare Global Enterprises Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>