<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 18:29:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[TVSMOTOR] TVS Motor Strengthens its presence in Egypt with TVS RONIN and TVS NTORQ RACE EDITION Launch</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TVS+MOTOR+COMPANY+LTD.&title=TVS+Motor+Strengthens+its+presence+in+Egypt+with+TVS+RONIN+and+TVS+NTORQ+RACE+EDITION+Launch&newsId=68020361-2da8-4825-b22a-6cab2743a2ac&token=NjgwMjAzNjEtMmRh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68020361-2da8-4825-b22a-6cab2743a2ac</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>TVS Motor Company, a global leader in two and three-wheeler manufacturing, unveiled two new products, the TVS Ronin Top and TVS Ntorg RE, in Egypt. The launch ceremony was attended by key stakeholders, dealers, influencers, and senior representatives from TVS Motor Company and Ezz LCV, TVS’s authorized distributor in Egypt. This step marks a significant move in TVS Motor Company’s long-term strategic focus to deepen its presence in Egypt. The TVS Ronin Top, available in Nimbus Grey and Midnight Blue, offers a unique modern-retro design philosophy, cutting-edge engineering, optimized performance, and everyday versatility. The TVS Ntorg RE, available in Marine Blue and Red, enhances the brand’s presence in the performance scooter category with its sporty design, responsive acceleration, and advanced features. This launch strengthens TVS Motor Company’s commitment to delivering well-engineered products and expanding its global portfolio.</p><ul><li>TVS Motor Company launched two new products, the TVS Ronin Top and TVS Ntorg RE, in Egypt.</li><li>The launch was attended by key stakeholders, dealers, influencers, and senior representatives from TVS Motor Company and Ezz LCV.</li><li>The TVS Ronin Top offers a unique modern-retro design philosophy, cutting-edge engineering, optimized performance, and everyday versatility.</li><li>The TVS Ntorg RE enhances the brand’s presence in the performance scooter category with its sporty design, responsive acceleration, and advanced features.</li><li>This launch marks a significant step in TVS Motor Company’s long-term strategic focus to deepen its presence in Egypt.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/43fc5f3e-d50f-4587-8cab-8dfa4c5eff28.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TVS MOTOR COMPANY LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ACMESOLAR] ACME Solar Subsidiary Commissions 4 MW of 100 MW Wind Power Project in Gujarat</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ACME+Solar+Holdings+Ltd&title=ACME+Solar+Subsidiary+Commissions+4+MW+of+100+MW+Wind+Power+Project+in+Gujarat&newsId=5f2fe746-8a94-4726-815d-24226670121f&token=NWYyZmU3NDYtOGE5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f2fe746-8a94-4726-815d-24226670121f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:51:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>ACME Solar Holdings Limited has announced that its subsidiary, ACME Eco Clean Energy Private Limited, has successfully commissioned an additional 4 MW out of the 100 MW wind power project located at Village: Titoda, Taluka: Sayla, Dist: Surendaranagar, Gujarat. This achievement brings the total commissioned capacity to 76 MW out of 100 MW. The commissioning has been confirmed by officials from Gujarat Energy Development Agency (GEDA) and Paschim Gujarat Vij Company Limited (PGVCL), with formal certificates expected to be issued shortly.</p><ul><li>ACME Solar&apos;s subsidiary commissions 4 MW of a 100 MW wind power project in Gujarat</li><li>Total commissioned capacity now stands at 76 MW out of 100 MW</li><li>Commissioning confirmed by GEDA and PGVCL officials</li><li>Formal certificates awaited</li><li>Location: Village: Titoda, Taluka: Sayla, Dist: Surendaranagar, Gujarat</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ca569d14-d26b-44d4-88a2-2aa2bef82487.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ACME Solar Holdings Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BEML] BEML Ltd Approves Rs 1500 Crores Investment for Greenfield Rail Manufacturing Facility - BRAHMA</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BEML+LTD.&title=BEML+Ltd+Approves+Rs+1500+Crores+Investment+for+Greenfield+Rail+Manufacturing+Facility+-+BRAHMA&newsId=ff262570-7423-451f-b8bc-4a92aa5574a4&token=ZmYyNjI1NzAtNzQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff262570-7423-451f-b8bc-4a92aa5574a4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:51:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>BEML Ltd board has approved an estimated investment of approximately Rs 1500 crores for a greenfield rail manufacturing facility named BRAHMA. The facility will be set up at Umariya, near Bhopal, Madhya Pradesh. The project is expected to be completed in a phase-wise manner over five years. The investment is aimed at enhancing the Company’s manufacturing capabilities.</p><ul><li>BEML Ltd has approved an estimated investment of approximately Rs 1500 crores for a greenfield rail manufacturing facility named BRAHMA.</li><li>The facility will be located at Umariya, near Bhopal, Madhya Pradesh.</li><li>The project is expected to be completed in a phase-wise manner over five years.</li><li>The investment is aimed at enhancing the Company’s manufacturing capabilities.</li><li>The mode of financing for the project is long-term debt.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/60b99224-198e-4509-942f-db7489d0cfd4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BEML LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JKIPL] Jinkushal Industries Ltd. Approves Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jinkushal+Industries+Ltd&title=Jinkushal+Industries+Ltd.+Approves+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+2025&newsId=63ed7c38-186c-4662-b2ee-d1e5582d8915&token=NjNlZDdjMzgtMTg2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63ed7c38-186c-4662-b2ee-d1e5582d8915</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:42:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jinkushal Industries Ltd. has considered and approved the unaudited financial results (standalone and consolidated) for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The board of directors approved the results in a meeting held on 7th February 2026, based on the recommendations of the audit committee. The limited review report on the un-audited financial results was also taken on record. The results will be published in newspapers and uploaded on the company&apos;s website as per Regulation 47 of the Listing Regulations.</p><ul><li>Jinkushal Industries Ltd. approved unaudited financial results for Q3 2025</li><li>Results were considered in a board meeting on 7th February 2026</li><li>Approval was based on the recommendations of the audit committee</li><li>Limited review report on the un-audited financial results was taken on record</li><li>Results to be published in newspapers and uploaded on the company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/360ce7bd-29ee-4a89-8918-8c23554af6be.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jinkushal Industries Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JKIPL] Jinkushal Industries Ltd. Approves Un-Audited Financial Results for Q3 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jinkushal+Industries+Ltd&title=Jinkushal+Industries+Ltd.+Approves+Un-Audited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+2025&newsId=142dff44-61ac-47dd-bfbe-00d426eeab38&token=MTQyZGZmNDQtNjFh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">142dff44-61ac-47dd-bfbe-00d426eeab38</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jinkushal Industries Ltd. has considered and approved the Un-Audited Financial Results (Standalone and Consolidated) for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The Board of Directors approved the results in a meeting held on 07th February 2026. The Limited Review Report on the Un-Audited Financial Results was also taken on record. The results will be uploaded on the company&apos;s website and published in newspapers as per Regulation 47 of the Listing Regulations.</p><ul><li>Jinkushal Industries Ltd. approved the Un-Audited Financial Results for Q3 2025</li><li>The results were approved by the Board of Directors in a meeting held on 07th February 2026</li><li>The Limited Review Report on the Un-Audited Financial Results was also taken on record</li><li>The results will be uploaded on the company&apos;s website and published in newspapers as per Regulation 47 of the Listing Regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/085a27be-9874-4d30-9b04-b97a34acb057.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jinkushal Industries Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HARIGOV] Hari Govind International Ltd Appoints New Company Secretary and CFO</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HARI+GOVIND+INTERNATIONAL+LTD.&title=Hari+Govind+International+Ltd+Appoints+New+Company+Secretary+and+CFO&newsId=5ca5c49b-c0b2-4e18-bd16-2d2f07533619&token=NWNhNWM0OWItYzBi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ca5c49b-c0b2-4e18-bd16-2d2f07533619</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hari Govind International Ltd has appointed Ms. Divya P. S as the Company Secretary and Compliance Officer, and Mr. Abhilash Thekkumpurath as the Chief Financial Officer. Ms. Divya, an Associate Member of the Institute of Company Secretaries of India, brings six years of post-qualification experience in corporate compliance and governance. Mr. Abhilash, with the designation of key managerial personnel, will assume his role as CFO from February 7, 2026.</p><ul><li>Ms. Divya P. S appointed as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer</li><li>Mr. Abhilash Thekkumpurath appointed as Chief Financial Officer</li><li>Ms. Divya has six years of post-qualification experience in corporate compliance and governance</li><li>Mr. Abhilash to assume CFO role from February 7, 2026</li><li>Appointments aim to comply with Companies Act, 2013 and SEBI (LODR) Regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/78d5287e-138d-40d4-bda5-22973d540bd9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HARI GOVIND INTERNATIONAL LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RITCO] Ritco Logistics Secures ~X%82 Crore in New Contracts in January 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ritco+Logistics+Ltd&title=Ritco+Logistics+Secures+~X%2582+Crore+in+New+Contracts+in+January+2026&newsId=85ad4230-4c8b-4d9c-9157-422233226fba&token=ODVhZDQyMzAtNGM4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85ad4230-4c8b-4d9c-9157-422233226fba</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Ritco Logistics Ltd., a leading integrated logistics and multimodal transport solutions provider, commenced calendar year 2026 on a positive note by securing new transportation contracts worth approximately %82 crore in January 2026. These wins reflect Ritco’s continued strength in core industrial sectors and its ability to secure long-term, repeat business through consistent service delivery and operational excellence.</p><ul><li>Secured new transportation contracts worth approximately %82 crore in January 2026</li><li>Multiple long-term contracts in the steel and metals segment worth 233 Crores</li><li>One-year logistics contracts with ITC Ltd involving multi-origin and multi-destination movements across India</li><li>New annual contracts with ITC and Roquette involving regional and pan-India movements worth 11 Cr</li><li>TrucksUp marked a significant business milestone with the launch of its FASTag service</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2f0a13f3-34f6-4cf6-b143-cfe4978cc69e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ritco Logistics Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RITCO] Ritco Logistics Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q4 Results and Amend Employee Stock Option Plan</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ritco+Logistics+Ltd&title=Ritco+Logistics+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q4+Results+and+Amend+Employee+Stock+Option+Plan&newsId=d17fc977-c686-4028-bec9-c2f97d39746a&token=ZDE3ZmM5NzctYzY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d17fc977-c686-4028-bec9-c2f97d39746a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:34:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ritco Logistics Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 11 February 2026 to consider and approve various agendas. The meeting will review and consider the unaudited Consolidated and Standalone financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The Company will also consider amending its Employee Stock Option Plan to provide vesting flexibility to the Compensation Committee. Additionally, the Board will approve the notice of Postal Ballot seeking approval of the Shareholders on various matters and appoint a Scrutinizer to conduct the Postal Ballot process. The Record Date for the purpose of voting through postal ballot will also be fixed.</p><ul><li>Ritco Logistics Ltd to review and approve Q4 results for 2025</li><li>Company to consider amendment of Employee Stock Option Plan</li><li>Notice of Postal Ballot to be approved</li><li>Scrutinizer to be appointed for Postal Ballot process</li><li>Record Date for postal ballot voting to be fixed</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/83debeef-e9b2-47fe-9b53-1675cfb75f48.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ritco Logistics Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EMCURE] Emcure Pharmaceuticals&apos; Manufacturing Plant Disrupted by Fire for 5-7 Days</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Emcure+Pharmaceuticals+Ltd&title=Emcure+Pharmaceuticals%27+Manufacturing+Plant+Disrupted+by+Fire+for+5-7+Days&newsId=f4d73b91-93fc-44b7-bd61-cf8cee2e46bd&token=ZjRkNzNiOTEtOTNm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4d73b91-93fc-44b7-bd61-cf8cee2e46bd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Emcure Pharmaceuticals Ltd. has reported a fire incident at the utility block of its manufacturing plant (Plant I) located at Hinjawadi, Pune, Maharashtra on February 07, 2026. The fire has caused a temporary disruption in the plant&apos;s operations for an estimated period of 5 to 7 days. There are no human injuries or casualties reported. The company is taking necessary measures to restore operations and has adequate insurance coverage for the plant.</p><ul><li>Fire at Emcure Pharmaceuticals&apos; manufacturing plant in Pune, Maharashtra</li><li>Operations temporarily disrupted for 5-7 days</li><li>No human injuries or casualties reported</li><li>Company taking measures to restore operations</li><li>Adequate insurance coverage for the plant</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7250217b-a086-4767-b7fa-00c72362e065.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Emcure Pharmaceuticals Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FILATEX] Filatex India Ltd. Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025, Reports Increased Revenue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=FILATEX+INDIA+LTD.-%24&title=Filatex+India+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Reports+Increased+Revenue&newsId=371523fb-f4e6-40ed-ab7c-284fd47f3725&token=MzcxNTIzZmItZjRl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">371523fb-f4e6-40ed-ab7c-284fd47f3725</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Filatex India Ltd. has announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations has increased to 1,04,970 lakhs for the quarter and 3,17,503 lakhs for the nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The Board of Directors approved these results in their meeting held on 7th February, 2026. The company has also made further investments of 2,000 lakhs in its wholly owned subsidiary, Texfil Private Limited. The Government of India&apos;s notification of four Labour Codes has resulted in an incremental impact of 116.34 lakhs on the company&apos;s gratuity and long-term compensated absences.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for Q3 2025 is 1,04,970 lakhs</li><li>Revenue from operations for nine months ended 31st December, 2025 is 3,17,503 lakhs</li><li>Board of Directors approved the results in their meeting held on 7th February, 2026</li><li>Further investments of 2,000 lakhs made in Texfil Private Limited</li><li>Incremental impact of 116.34 lakhs due to the Government of India&apos;s Labour Codes notification</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/41f6b0e2-d9ad-47de-aa89-5498250d3752.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: FILATEX INDIA LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>