<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 20:17:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[PNGJL] P N Gadgil Jewellers Ltd Opens New Store in Khargar, Navi Mumbai</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=P+N+Gadgil+Jewellers+Ltd&title=P+N+Gadgil+Jewellers+Ltd+Opens+New+Store+in+Khargar%2C+Navi+Mumbai&newsId=50a49444-f8b5-4550-90b8-37ce1c715cb5&token=NTBhNDk0NDQtZjhi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50a49444-f8b5-4550-90b8-37ce1c715cb5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 15:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>P N Gadgil Jewellers Ltd has announced the opening of a new store at Shree Krishna Paradise, Kharghar, Navi Mumbai, Maharashtra - 410210. The store was inaugurated on January 04, 2026, at around 05:30 P.M. This brings the total number of stores to 67.</p><ul><li>P N Gadgil Jewellers Ltd has expanded its presence with a new store in Navi Mumbai</li><li>The new store is located at Shree Krishna Paradise, Kharghar</li><li>The store was inaugurated on January 04, 2026</li><li>This brings the total number of stores to 67</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/05dcda66-e29a-421a-98d7-9c68a6f2cb22.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: P N Gadgil Jewellers Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LOKESHMACH] Lokesh Machines Ltd Receives Order Worth Rs. 22 Crores From Ministry of Defence</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LOKESH+MACHINES+LTD.&title=Lokesh+Machines+Ltd+Receives+Order+Worth+Rs.+22+Crores+From+Ministry+of+Defence&newsId=f98b5196-ceb5-4c24-bc54-5279169a853a&token=Zjk4YjUxOTYtY2Vi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f98b5196-ceb5-4c24-bc54-5279169a853a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 15:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Lokesh Machines Ltd has announced that it has received an order worth Rs. 22,00,46,400/- from the Ministry of Defence, Advanced Weapons and Equipment India Limited. The order is for the supply of 9x19mm Machine Pistol Consisting Sub-Assemblies/Components. The order is to be executed on or before March 19, 2026.</p><ul><li>Order worth Rs. 22 crores from the Ministry of Defence</li><li>Supply of 9x19mm Machine Pistol Consisting Sub-Assemblies/Components</li><li>Order to be executed on or before March 19, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/132ae083-0374-4021-a8f1-e18e83828abb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LOKESH MACHINES LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NYKAA] Nykaa Reports Strong Q3 FY2026 Performance with High Twenties Consolidated GMV and NSV Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=FSN+E-Commerce+Ventures+Ltd&title=Nykaa+Reports+Strong+Q3+FY2026+Performance+with+High+Twenties+Consolidated+GMV+and+NSV+Growth&newsId=0f81869b-04df-4dde-9e83-7f91893de755&token=MGY4MTg2OWItMDRk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f81869b-04df-4dde-9e83-7f91893de755</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 14:45:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Nykaa (FSN E-Commerce Ventures Limited along with its subsidiaries) delivered a robust performance in Q3 FY2026 with Consolidated GMV and NSV growth expected to be in late twenties. The Beauty vertical is expected to deliver accelerated NSV growth of late twenties, while the Fashion vertical is expected to continue its revived growth trajectory with NSV growth of mid-twenties. The growth is attributed to the success of House of Nykaa brands, Pink Friday sale, and robust new customer acquisition.</p><ul><li>Consolidated GMV and NSV growth expected to be in late twenties in Q3 FY2026</li><li>Nykaa’s Beauty vertical is expected to deliver accelerated NSV growth of late twenties</li><li>Fashion vertical is expected to continue its revived growth trajectory with NSV growth of mid-twenties</li><li>Outperformance of House of Nykaa brands and robust new customer acquisition contributed to the superior performance</li><li>Beauty vertical’s Net Revenue growth is expected to be in the upper end of mid-twenties</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f42a9b29-1e37-463f-ad0d-5cb608892cac.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: FSN E-Commerce Ventures Ltd | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TFCILTD] Tourism Finance Corporation of India Ltd to Co-Sponsor, Act as Anchor Investor in Two AIFs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TOURISM+FINANCE+CORPORATION+OF+INDIA+LTD.&title=Tourism+Finance+Corporation+of+India+Ltd+to+Co-Sponsor%2C+Act+as+Anchor+Investor+in+Two+AIFs&newsId=fc3ee396-6ab1-4421-bbfe-fa5af446ab50&token=ZmMzZWUzOTYtNmFi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc3ee396-6ab1-4421-bbfe-fa5af446ab50</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 13:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tourism Finance Corporation of India Limited (TFCI) has decided to act as a co-sponsor and an anchor investor of Holystone Hospitality Fund, an equity focussed Category II Alternative Investment Fund (AIF), investing up to 5% of the fund corpus. The application for registration of Holystone Hospitality Fund as an AIF has been filed with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI). TFCI has also decided to act as an anchor investor of Certus Real Estate Fund Category II Alternative Investment Fund, investing up to 10% of the total fund size. The application for its registration has also been filed with SEBI.</p><ul><li>TFCI to co-sponsor and act as an anchor investor in Holystone Hospitality Fund AIF</li><li>Investment up to 5% of the fund corpus in Holystone Hospitality Fund AIF</li><li>Application for registration of Holystone Hospitality Fund as an AIF filed with SEBI</li><li>TFCI to act as an anchor investor in Certus Real Estate Fund Category II AIF</li><li>Investment up to 10% of the total fund size in Certus Real Estate Fund AIF</li><li>Application for registration of Certus Real Estate Fund AIF filed with SEBI</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f366c43d-da3a-4618-90aa-752988f3f628.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TOURISM FINANCE CORPORATION OF INDIA LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EQUITASBNK] Equitas Small Finance Bank Ltd. Reports 10.6% QoQ Growth in Gross Advances for Q3 FY26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Equitas+Small+Finance+Bank+Ltd&title=Equitas+Small+Finance+Bank+Ltd.+Reports+10.6%25+QoQ+Growth+in+Gross+Advances+for+Q3+FY26&newsId=be7bfa1b-d8d9-4457-9547-44604e7a429f&token=YmU3YmZhMWItZDhk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be7bfa1b-d8d9-4457-9547-44604e7a429f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 13:01:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Equitas Small Finance Bank Ltd. has reported a 10.6% QoQ growth in gross advances for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The total deposits stood at Rs. 43,668 crore, showing a 0.97% QoQ decrease. The bank&apos;s Cost of Funds (%) was 7.13%. The bank also completed two transactions involving the sale of non-performing assets (&apos;NPAs&apos;) to Asset Reconstruction Companies (&apos;ARCs&apos;).</p><ul><li>Gross Advances grew by 10.6% QoQ in Dec’25 Quarter</li><li>Total Deposits stood at Rs. 43,668 crore with a 0.97% QoQ decrease</li><li>Cost of Funds (%) was 7.13%</li><li>Bank completed two transactions involving the sale of NPAs to ARCs</li><li>Equitas Small Finance Bank Ltd. is contributing towards a better society</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0b9547d6-e6d2-45bb-a60f-bc333834cd0d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Equitas Small Finance Bank Ltd | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TOYAMSL] Toyam Sports Ltd to Approve Q3 and H1 Results for FY 2025-2026 on Jan 8, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Toyam+Sports+Ltd&title=Toyam+Sports+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+H1+Results+for+FY+2025-2026+on+Jan+8%2C+2026&newsId=b677a578-2322-4a79-a120-3c241fe45cb6&token=YjY3N2E1NzgtMjMy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b677a578-2322-4a79-a120-3c241fe45cb6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 10:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Toyam Sports Ltd has informed BSE that their Board of Directors will meet on January 8, 2026, to consider and approve the Standalone and Consolidated Un-Audited Financial Results for the Quarter and half year ended September 30, 2025, along with the Limited Review Report on the Results. The trading window for dealing in securities/shares of the Company will open 48 hours after the declaration of the Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Toyam Sports Ltd to consider and approve Q3 and H1 results for FY 2025-2026</li><li>The meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on 08/01/2026</li><li>Trading window to open 48 hours after the declaration of the Financial Results</li><li>Financial Results are for the Quarter and half year ended September 30, 2025</li><li>Limited Review Report on the Results to be approved</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/305841a3-e33d-425b-82dd-4f1d1ef2d95f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Toyam Sports Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CUPIDALBV] Cupid Breweries to Acquire Rinpoche Spirits and Crochet Industries for Rs. 348.38 Crores and Rs. 5.86 Crores Respectively</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Cupid+Breweries+And+Distilleries+Ltd&title=Cupid+Breweries+to+Acquire+Rinpoche+Spirits+and+Crochet+Industries+for+Rs.+348.38+Crores+and+Rs.+5.86+Crores+Respectively&newsId=056f6cca-47cc-4e68-b5be-17a239760cf2&token=MDU2ZjZjY2EtNDdj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">056f6cca-47cc-4e68-b5be-17a239760cf2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 09:32:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Cupid Breweries and Distilleries Ltd has approved the acquisition of 100% share capital of Rinpoche Spirits Private Limited (RSPL) and up to 8,75,000 equity shares of Crochet Industries Private Limited (CIPL) through preferential issue of equity shares. The transaction is expected to enhance the company&apos;s national footprint, capacity, and revenue visibility with EBITDA scalability. The total consideration for the RSPL acquisition is Rs. 348.38 Crores and for the CIPL acquisition is Rs. 5.86 Crores. The board has also approved the execution of a Share Purchase Agreement (SPA) for the proposed transaction.</p><ul><li>Acquisition of 100% share capital of Rinpoche Spirits Private Limited for Rs. 348.38 Crores</li><li>Acquisition of up to 8,75,000 equity shares of Crochet Industries Private Limited for Rs. 5.86 Crores</li><li>Expected to enhance company&apos;s national footprint, capacity, and revenue visibility</li><li>Approval of execution of Share Purchase Agreement (SPA) for the proposed transaction</li><li>Amendment to the Articles of Association of the Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bc00d125-8195-4d7f-bbe9-ed7d86870a43.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Cupid Breweries And Distilleries Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CUPIDALBV] Cupid Breweries to Acquire Rinpoche Spirits and Crochet Industries for Rs. 348.38 Crores and Rs. 5.86 Crores Respectively</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Cupid+Breweries+And+Distilleries+Ltd&title=Cupid+Breweries+to+Acquire+Rinpoche+Spirits+and+Crochet+Industries+for+Rs.+348.38+Crores+and+Rs.+5.86+Crores+Respectively&newsId=99bd7c68-b4e1-4811-bb0e-46cbb91d8bc5&token=OTliZDdjNjgtYjRl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">99bd7c68-b4e1-4811-bb0e-46cbb91d8bc5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 09:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Cupid Breweries and Distilleries Ltd has approved the acquisition of 100% share capital of Rinpoche Spirits Private Limited (RSPL) and up to 8,75,000 equity shares of Crochet Industries Private Limited (CIPL) through preferential issue of equity shares. The total consideration for RSPL is Rs. 348.38 Crores and for CIPL is Rs. 5.86 Crores. The acquisition will enhance Cupid Breweries&apos; national footprint, capacity, and revenue visibility with EBITDA scalability. The Board has also approved the execution of a Share Purchase Agreement (SPA) for the proposed transaction.</p><ul><li>Acquisition of 100% share capital of Rinpoche Spirits Private Limited for Rs. 348.38 Crores</li><li>Acquisition of up to 8,75,000 equity shares of Crochet Industries Private Limited for Rs. 5.86 Crores</li><li>Enhancement of national footprint, capacity, and revenue visibility with EBITDA scalability</li><li>Approval of execution of Share Purchase Agreement (SPA) for the proposed transaction</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/26f888b8-fdec-4d04-a73d-d58d2c7a7021.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Cupid Breweries And Distilleries Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PCJEWELLER] PC Jeweller Ltd Achieves 37% YoY Revenue Growth in Q3FY2026, Secures Approval for 1,000 Franchisee Units in Uttar Pradesh</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PC+JEWELLER+LTD.&title=PC+Jeweller+Ltd+Achieves+37%25+YoY+Revenue+Growth+in+Q3FY2026%2C+Secures+Approval+for+1%2C000+Franchisee+Units+in+Uttar+Pradesh&newsId=da0a1a56-df0f-4891-9e4c-424dde2391bc&token=ZGEwYTFhNTYtZGYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">da0a1a56-df0f-4891-9e4c-424dde2391bc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 09:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>PC Jeweller Limited, a leading player in the jewellery industry, concluded Q3FY2026 with a robust performance, achieving standalone revenue growth of approximately 37% YoY. The strong performance was driven by robust consumer demand during the ongoing festival and wedding season. The Company had submitted a proposal to The Directorate of Industries and Enterprises Promotion, Government of Uttar Pradesh, under their campaign CHIEF MINISTER — YUVA UDYAMI VIKAS ABHIYAN for on-boarding as a Franchise Brand on the CM-YUVA Portal. The proposal received the approval and the Company has also entered into a Memorandum of Understanding with CM YUVA Mission under Department of MSME and Export Promotion, Government of Uttar Pradesh for the same. This initiative will enhance the Company’s visibility, scalability and retail network, foster an entrepreneurial ecosystem, improve youth employability, promote self-employment and contribute to the economic development of Uttar Pradesh through innovation and enterprise creation. The Company remains committed to achieving a debt-free status in the near future and has already reduced its outstanding debt by approximately 68% since the execution of Settlement Agreement with the Banks on 30th September 2024. The financial details provided above are provisional and subject to Limited Review by Statutory Auditor.</p><ul><li>PC Jeweller Ltd achieves 37% YoY revenue growth in Q3FY2026</li><li>Robust consumer demand during the ongoing festival and wedding season</li><li>Approval received for on-boarding as a Franchise Brand on the CM-YUVA Portal</li><li>1,000 jewellery retail franchisee units to be established in rural/semi-urban areas of Uttar Pradesh</li><li>Significant progress towards debt-free status with 68% reduction in outstanding debt since September 2024</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/34bee256-f40a-4bde-9d29-55eda3778bac.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PC JEWELLER LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CUPIDALBV] Cupid Breweries and Distilleries Ltd. Approves Acquisition of Rinpoche Spirits and Crochet Industries Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Cupid+Breweries+And+Distilleries+Ltd&title=Cupid+Breweries+and+Distilleries+Ltd.+Approves+Acquisition+of+Rinpoche+Spirits+and+Crochet+Industries+Shares&newsId=a5192afa-9f83-4235-af80-a6980a6775b3&token=YTUxOTJhZmEtOWY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5192afa-9f83-4235-af80-a6980a6775b3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 09:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cupid Breweries and Distilleries Ltd. has approved the acquisition of up to 100% of the share capital of Rinpoche Spirits Private Limited (RSPL) and up to 8,75,000 equity shares of Crochet Industries Private Limited (CIPL). The acquisition of RSPL shares will be through a preferential issue by way of share swap, while the acquisition of CIPL shares will be through a preferential issue for consideration other than cash. The transactions are expected to enhance the company&apos;s national footprint, capacity, and revenue visibility with EBITDA scalability. The board has also approved the execution of necessary documents for the proposed transactions.</p><ul><li>Acquisition of up to 100% of the share capital of Rinpoche Spirits Private Limited (RSPL) for consideration other than cash through a preferential issue by way of share swap.</li><li>Acquisition of up to 8,75,000 equity shares of Crochet Industries Private Limited (CIPL) for consideration other than cash through a preferential issue.</li><li>The transactions are expected to enhance the company&apos;s national footprint, capacity, and revenue visibility with EBITDA scalability.</li><li>The board has approved the execution of necessary documents for the proposed transactions.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0ca6dbce-2cf4-4c0c-9150-6490ad550879.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Cupid Breweries And Distilleries Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>