<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:59:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SHARDFI] Vinod Kumar Tripathi Acquires Shares in Eco Hotels and Resorts Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHARAD+FIBRES+%26+YARN+PROCESSORS+LTD.&title=Vinod+Kumar+Tripathi+Acquires+Shares+in+Eco+Hotels+and+Resorts+Ltd&newsId=e3cfa146-6791-4ecd-b5f8-bd1c9551b64b&token=ZTNjZmExNDYtNjc5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3cfa146-6791-4ecd-b5f8-bd1c9551b64b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:56:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>According to a disclosure made under Regulation 29(1) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011, Vinod Kumar Tripathi, a Whole-time Director at Eco Hotels and Resorts Limited, has acquired shares in the company. The acquisition details are as follows: Before the acquisition, the acquirer along with PACs held 4.83% shares and 0.19% voting rights otherwise than by equity shares. Post-acquisition, the acquirer&apos;s holding increased to 5.02% shares and 0.19% voting rights otherwise than by equity shares. The acquisition was made through the open market. The total diluted share/voting capital of the company remains unchanged at 51,507,235 after the acquisition.</p><ul><li>Vinod Kumar Tripathi, a Whole-time Director at Eco Hotels and Resorts Limited, has acquired shares in the company</li><li>The acquisition details are as per the disclosure made under Regulation 29(1) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011</li><li>Before the acquisition, the acquirer along with PACs held 4.83% shares and 0.19% voting rights otherwise than by equity shares</li><li>Post-acquisition, the acquirer&apos;s holding increased to 5.02% shares and 0.19% voting rights otherwise than by equity shares</li><li>The acquisition was made through the open market</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/03658145_B2B4_49D0_950F_00CD8C25D36C_102132.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHARAD FIBRES & YARN PROCESSORS LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IITL] Nimbus India Acquires 1.03% Shares in Industrial Investment Trust Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDUSTRIAL+INVESTMENT+TRUST+LTD.&title=Nimbus+India+Acquires+1.03%25+Shares+in+Industrial+Investment+Trust+Ltd&newsId=fcbe25ce-2c8b-475e-8383-d80151cde58e&token=ZmNiZTI1Y2UtMmM4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fcbe25ce-2c8b-475e-8383-d80151cde58e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:51:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Nimbus India Limited, a Promoter/Promoter group of Industrial Investment Trust Limited, has acquired 2,01,000 Equity Shares of the company on February 09, 2026. This acquisition was made through Nimbus (India) Limited, which now holds 1.03% of the total voting rights in the company. The total share capital of the company after the acquisition stands at Rs. 19,60,87,800/-.</p><ul><li>Nimbus India Limited acquires 2,01,000 Equity Shares of Industrial Investment Trust Limited</li><li>The acquisition represents 1.03% of the total voting rights in the company</li><li>The total share capital of the company after the acquisition stands at Rs. 19,60,87,800/-</li><li>The acquisition was made through Nimbus (India) Limited</li><li>Nimbus India Limited is a Promoter/Promoter group of Industrial Investment Trust Limited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2C0D55B6_771C_49C8_A0E1_79A2D256989C_101646.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDUSTRIAL INVESTMENT TRUST LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KAPILCO] Skybiotech Healthcare Ltd to Approve Q3 FY2025-2026 Financial Results on Feb 14, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KAPIL+COTEX+LTD.&title=Skybiotech+Healthcare+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+FY2025-2026+Financial+Results+on+Feb+14%2C+2026&newsId=c5d44f4a-ed6c-46c1-8e39-cc7d0614118b&token=YzVkNDRmNGEtZWQ2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5d44f4a-ed6c-46c1-8e39-cc7d0614118b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Skybiotech Healthcare Ltd has announced a Board of Directors meeting on February 14, 2026. The agenda includes the approval of the unaudited financial results and limited review report for the quarter ending on December 31, 2025. This is in accordance with the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015, Regulation 29(1) (a).</p><ul><li>Skybiotech Healthcare Ltd scheduled a Board of Directors meeting on February 14, 2026</li><li>The meeting aims to approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ending on December 31, 2025</li><li>The approval also includes the limited review report of the Company for the same quarter</li><li>The announcement is in compliance with the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015, Regulation 29(1) (a)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3b859950-fa8e-43ca-bb53-3a5788c12b88.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KAPIL COTEX LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IGIL] International Gemmological Institute India Ltd: Board Approves Second Interim Dividend, Name Change, and Alteration to MOA &amp; AOA</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=International+Gemmological+Institute+India+Ltd&title=International+Gemmological+Institute+India+Ltd%3A+Board+Approves+Second+Interim+Dividend%2C+Name+Change%2C+and+Alteration+to+MOA+%26+AOA&newsId=892a99cb-f282-40f2-afc7-17190feb001e&token=ODkyYTk5Y2ItZjI4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">892a99cb-f282-40f2-afc7-17190feb001e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:49:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of International Gemmological Institute India Ltd has approved the payment of the Second Interim Dividend of Rs. 2.50 per equity share for the financial year 2025-26. The company has also approved a change in its name to &apos;International Gemological Institute Limited&apos; and the consequent alteration to the MOA and AOA. A postal ballot notice will be sent to the shareholders for their approval.</p><ul><li>Payment of Second Interim Dividend of Rs. 2.50 per equity share for the financial year 2025-26</li><li>Approval of change in the name of the company to &apos;International Gemological Institute Limited&apos;</li><li>Consequent alteration to the MOA and AOA of the company</li><li>Approval of a postal ballot notice to be sent to the shareholders for their approval</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/09197251-ff55-400b-ab1c-a116e795c9e3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: International Gemmological Institute India Ltd | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SILVERLINE] Silverline Technologies Ltd. Receives Non-Binding LOI for Potential 20% Stake Sale to UAE-Based Trueledger Technologies FZE</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SILVERLINE+TECHNOLOGIES+LTD.&title=Silverline+Technologies+Ltd.+Receives+Non-Binding+LOI+for+Potential+20%25+Stake+Sale+to+UAE-Based+Trueledger+Technologies+FZE&newsId=75a082d0-a940-4d54-9ec1-340f3fc41e62&token=NzVhMDgyZDAtYTk0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75a082d0-a940-4d54-9ec1-340f3fc41e62</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:44:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Silverline Technologies Limited has received a non-binding Letter of Intent (LOI) from Trueledger Technologies FZE, a UAE-based technology research and holding company, expressing preliminary interest in exploring a potential strategic investment of up to 20% stake in Silverline Technologies. The proposed investment aims to provide strategic exposure to the Company’s artificial intelligence-led initiatives. The final transaction structure, including the mode of investment, valuation, and rights (if any), will be determined in compliance with applicable regulations and after due consideration by the Company’s Board of Directors. The LOI is non-binding, and there is no certainty that the discussions will result in a concluded transaction. The Company will evaluate the proposal in accordance with applicable laws and make appropriate disclosures to the Exchange(s), as and when required.</p><ul><li>Silverline Technologies Ltd. received a non-binding LOI from Trueledger Technologies FZE for potential strategic investment</li><li>Trueledger Technologies FZE expressed preliminary interest in exploring a potential 20% stake acquisition</li><li>The proposed investment aims to provide strategic exposure to the Company’s artificial intelligence-led initiatives</li><li>The final transaction structure, valuation, and rights will be determined in compliance with applicable regulations</li><li>No binding agreement, consideration, or valuation has been finalized; there is no certainty of a concluded transaction</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e0b32597-5564-4744-a0e9-1ac9b3d76d0f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SILVERLINE TECHNOLOGIES LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IGIL] International Gemmological Institute India Ltd Declares Second Interim Dividend of Rs. 2.50 and Approves Name Change</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=International+Gemmological+Institute+India+Ltd&title=International+Gemmological+Institute+India+Ltd+Declares+Second+Interim+Dividend+of+Rs.+2.50+and+Approves+Name+Change&newsId=7486b0c8-a4d6-4e22-80c0-a9de5f5bf3eb&token=NzQ4NmIwYzgtYTRk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7486b0c8-a4d6-4e22-80c0-a9de5f5bf3eb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:44:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>International Gemmological Institute India Ltd has declared and approved the payment of the Second Interim Dividend of Rs. 2.50 per equity share for the financial year 2025-26. The company has also approved a change in its name to &apos;International Gemological Institute Limited&apos;, subject to the approval of shareholders and other statutory authorities. The dividend will be paid on or before March 13, 2026, to those members whose names appear in the record on February 17, 2026.</p><ul><li>International Gemmological Institute India Ltd has declared a second interim dividend of Rs. 2.50 per equity share for the financial year 2025-26.</li><li>The company has approved a change in its name to &apos;International Gemological Institute Limited&apos;, subject to necessary approvals.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/64019331-8e2e-41cb-ac0e-dd32b4ef1223.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: International Gemmological Institute India Ltd | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IGIL] International Gemmological Institute India Ltd Declares Second Interim Dividend &amp; Approves Name Change</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=International+Gemmological+Institute+India+Ltd&title=International+Gemmological+Institute+India+Ltd+Declares+Second+Interim+Dividend+%26+Approves+Name+Change&newsId=f9aee950-ad71-4526-97b8-ca952ea81523&token=ZjlhZWU5NTAtYWQ3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9aee950-ad71-4526-97b8-ca952ea81523</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:39:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>International Gemmological Institute India Ltd has declared a second interim dividend of Rs. 2.50 per equity share for the financial year 2025-26. The record date for this dividend is February 17, 2026. The company has also approved a change in its name to International Gemological Institute Limited, subject to shareholder and regulatory approval. The name change will require consequential alterations to the Memorandum of Association and Articles of Association.</p><ul><li>International Gemmological Institute India Ltd has declared a second interim dividend of Rs. 2.50 per equity share.</li><li>The record date for the dividend is February 17, 2026.</li><li>The company has approved a change in its name to International Gemological Institute Limited.</li><li>The name change is subject to shareholder and regulatory approval.</li><li>The name change will require consequential alterations to the Memorandum of Association and Articles of Association.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/940a9456-8b8c-4475-8850-00c3d0f27970.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: International Gemmological Institute India Ltd | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MRO-TEK] Umiya Holding Pvt Ltd Acquires Shares in Umiya Buildcon Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MRO-TEK+Realty+Ltd&title=Umiya+Holding+Pvt+Ltd+Acquires+Shares+in+Umiya+Buildcon+Ltd&newsId=9c8a0cfc-140e-4261-965a-cf094919b86a&token=OWM4YTBjZmMtMTQw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c8a0cfc-140e-4261-965a-cf094919b86a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Umiya Holding Pvt Ltd has made a disclosure under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011 for Umiya Buildcon Limited (Formerly MRO-TEK Realty Limited). The acquisition details are as follows: Before the acquisition, Umiya Holding Pvt Ltd held 38.01% shares and voting rights. Post-acquisition, the holding increased to 38.01% shares and voting rights. The acquisition was made through the open market. The securities acquired have a redemption date of 10-02-2026. The equity share capital and total voting capital of Umiya Buildcon Limited remained the same before and after the acquisition.</p><ul><li>Umiya Holding Pvt Ltd acquires shares in Umiya Buildcon Ltd</li><li>Acquisition made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011</li><li>Acquisition details: 0.005% shares and voting rights</li><li>Acquisition made through open market</li><li>Securities have a redemption date of 10-02-2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/47FFAE2D_7D52_4F42_8BA4_AB069ECD70C6_100316.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MRO-TEK Realty Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GREENPLY] Greenply Industries: Karuna Investment Pvt Ltd Acquires Shares; Promoter Group&apos;s Holding Increases to 51.85%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GREENPLY+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Greenply+Industries%3A+Karuna+Investment+Pvt+Ltd+Acquires+Shares%3B+Promoter+Group%27s+Holding+Increases+to+51.85%25&newsId=24f82edc-1d6d-43d1-a05b-57c9db5d28b0&token=MjRmODJlZGMtMWQ2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24f82edc-1d6d-43d1-a05b-57c9db5d28b0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Greenply Industries Ltd. has received a disclosure under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011 from Karuna Investment Pvt Ltd. The disclosure pertains to the change in shareholding of equity shares and voting rights of the Promoters Promoter Group of Greenply Industries Limited. Karuna Investment Pvt Ltd., along with its Person Acting in Concert (PACs), has acquired shares, leading to an increase in the Promoter Group&apos;s holding to 51.85%. The acquisition took place on the open market on 09.02.2026.</p><ul><li>Karuna Investment Pvt Ltd. acquires shares in Greenply Industries Ltd.</li><li>Promoter Group&apos;s holding increases to 51.85% post acquisition.</li><li>Acquisition took place on the open market on 09.02.2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/614F8EFF_7686_4E4C_A8A5_532891EE720D_100009.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GREENPLY INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IGIL] International Gemmological Institute India Ltd Declares Second Interim Dividend and Approves Name Change</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=International+Gemmological+Institute+India+Ltd&title=International+Gemmological+Institute+India+Ltd+Declares+Second+Interim+Dividend+and+Approves+Name+Change&newsId=dce92f58-9f76-44f1-bf8b-e14c2d488b47&token=ZGNlOTJmNTgtOWY3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dce92f58-9f76-44f1-bf8b-e14c2d488b47</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 04:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>International Gemmological Institute India Ltd (IGI) announced the declaration of a Second Interim Dividend of Rs. 2.50 per equity share for the financial year 2025-26. The company also approved a change in its name to &apos;International Gemological Institute Limited&apos; from &apos;International Gemmological Institute (India) Limited&apos;, subject to shareholder and regulatory approval. The Board Meeting was held on February 11, 2026.</p><ul><li>Declaration of Second Interim Dividend of Rs. 2.50 per equity share</li><li>Change in the name of the Company to &apos;International Gemological Institute Limited&apos;</li><li>Subject to Shareholders&apos; and regulatory approval</li><li>Consequential alteration to the Memorandum of Association and Articles of Association</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3b126347-b9dd-42c2-beba-099808285903.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: International Gemmological Institute India Ltd | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>