<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:21:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[REDTAPE] Redtape Ltd Clarifies on Stake Sale Rumors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Redtape+Ltd&title=Redtape+Ltd+Clarifies+on+Stake+Sale+Rumors&newsId=e07e029c-4fa5-4966-afd3-308a74f59318&token=ZTA3ZTAyOWMtNGZh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e07e029c-4fa5-4966-afd3-308a74f59318</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Redtape Ltd, in response to BSE&apos;s query, clarified that while they do explore strategic opportunities for growth and expansion, no event has occurred that warrants a disclosure under Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015 at this stage. They also stated that they are not aware of any information that has not been announced to the Exchanges, which could explain the movement in the trading. They confirmed that they will keep the Exchanges informed of any material events as required under Regulation 30 of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Redtape Ltd explores strategic opportunities for growth and expansion</li><li>No event has occurred that warrants a disclosure under Regulation 30 of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Redtape Ltd is not aware of any unannounced information that could explain the movement in the trading</li><li>Redtape Ltd will keep the Exchanges informed of any material events as required under Regulation 30 of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0346bc4a-8879-42c8-bb9e-f0c3655081d5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Redtape Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INTERARCH] Interarch Building Solutions Secures Undisclosed Order Worth Approximately Rs. 130 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Interarch+Building+Products+Ltd&title=Interarch+Building+Solutions+Secures+Undisclosed+Order+Worth+Approximately+Rs.+130+Crores&newsId=62566202-e38f-4c85-823c-11ca41e02295&token=NjI1NjYyMDItZTM4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62566202-e38f-4c85-823c-11ca41e02295</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:20:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Interarch Building Solutions Ltd. has received a Letter of Intent (LOI) from a customer for an order. The customer&apos;s name cannot be disclosed due to confidentiality and commercial considerations. The order, worth approximately Rs. 130 Crores, includes complete design, engineering, manufacturing, and supply &amp; erection of Pre-Engineered Steel Building System. The order is expected to be completed in 17 months with a 10% advance payment along with the order.</p><ul><li>Interarch Building Solutions secures a new order from an undisclosed customer</li><li>The order is worth approximately Rs. 130 Crores</li><li>The order includes complete design, engineering, manufacturing, and supply &amp; erection of Pre-Engineered Steel Building System</li><li>The order is expected to be completed in 17 months</li><li>The order was awarded with a 10% advance payment along with the order</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9207f710-59f1-4e5f-9cb8-027843510d22.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Interarch Building Products Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[THELEELA] Leela Palaces Hotels &amp; Resorts Ltd Receives Four Appellate Orders from Joint Commissioner of Commercial Taxes (Appeals-5), Bengaluru</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Leela+Palaces+Hotels+%26+Resorts+Ltd&title=Leela+Palaces+Hotels+%26+Resorts+Ltd+Receives+Four+Appellate+Orders+from+Joint+Commissioner+of+Commercial+Taxes+%28Appeals-5%29%2C+Bengaluru&newsId=fd19c896-b0ae-4025-ad1e-7c63b97a2f65&token=ZmQxOWM4OTYtYjBh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd19c896-b0ae-4025-ad1e-7c63b97a2f65</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Leela Palaces Hotels &amp; Resorts Ltd has received four appellate orders from Joint Commissioner of Commercial Taxes (Appeals-5), Bengaluru. The company is evaluating further appellate remedies, if any. The orders do not have any material impact on the financial, operation, or other activities of the company. The company is committed to complying with all relevant laws and regulations.</p><ul><li>Leela Palaces Hotels &amp; Resorts Ltd has received four appellate orders from Joint Commissioner of Commercial Taxes (Appeals-5), Bengaluru.</li><li>The company is evaluating further appellate remedies, if any.</li><li>The orders do not have any material impact on the company&apos;s financial, operation, or other activities.</li><li>The company is committed to complying with all relevant laws and regulations.</li><li>The required information is enclosed as Annexure — A and will be available on the company&apos;s website.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/652abb5f-b4b4-41d3-8eaa-51870f76a775.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Leela Palaces Hotels & Resorts Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DEVLAB] Sad Demise of Mrs. Jamnaben Lavjibhai Donda from Dev Labtech Venture Ltd Promoter Group</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Dev+Labtech+Venture+Ltd&title=Sad+Demise+of+Mrs.+Jamnaben+Lavjibhai+Donda+from+Dev+Labtech+Venture+Ltd+Promoter+Group&newsId=be6d06c5-b698-4a4d-891c-abd6296a3b59&token=YmU2ZDA2YzUtYjY5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be6d06c5-b698-4a4d-891c-abd6296a3b59</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dev Labtech Venture Ltd has informed about the demise of Mrs. Jamnaben Lavjibhai Donda, who was a part of the Promoter Group of the Company. She held no shares in the Company and will cease to be part of the Promoter Group in accordance with Regulation 31A(6)(c) of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015. The Company has requested for the update of this information in the records.</p><ul><li>Mrs. Jamnaben Lavjibhai Donda, a member of the Promoter Group of Dev Labtech Venture Ltd, has passed away.</li><li>She did not hold any shares in the Company.</li><li>Mrs. Donda will be removed from the Promoter Group as per Regulation 31A(6)(c) of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</li><li>The Company has requested for the update of this information in the records.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/062988c6-b8b1-4584-9f57-3c42c2170475.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Dev Labtech Venture Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TOKYOPLAST] Tokyo Plast International Ltd. Announces Q3 and Full Year Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TOKYO+PLAST+INTERNATIONAL+LTD.&title=Tokyo+Plast+International+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+Full+Year+Results+for+2025&newsId=8bee5cc6-881e-4ae7-8118-565bc0418597&token=OGJlZTVjYzYtODgx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8bee5cc6-881e-4ae7-8118-565bc0418597</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tokyo Plast International Ltd. has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s standalone financial results were prepared in accordance with Ind AS 34, Interim Financial Reporting, and other applicable accounting standards. The review report, conducted by UB G &amp; Company Chartered Accountants, confirmed that the financial statements were free of material misstatements and disclosed all required information as per the SEBI regulations.</p><ul><li>Tokyo Plast International Ltd. announced its unaudited standalone financial results for Q3 and full year 2025.</li><li>The results were prepared in accordance with Ind AS 34, Interim Financial Reporting, and other applicable accounting standards.</li><li>UB G &amp; Company Chartered Accountants conducted a review report and found no material misstatements in the financial statements.</li><li>The financial statements disclosed all required information as per the SEBI regulations.</li><li>The company&apos;s financial results can be accessed on the company&apos;s website and the Stock Exchange website.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/27c53f6c-7bd4-43a1-a011-a09316495ba8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TOKYO PLAST INTERNATIONAL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VELHO] Velan Hotels Ltd Enters Asset Sale Agreement with JP Associates Asia Pacific for Hotel Properties</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VELAN+HOTELS+LTD.&title=Velan+Hotels+Ltd+Enters+Asset+Sale+Agreement+with+JP+Associates+Asia+Pacific+for+Hotel+Properties&newsId=4ef9fd85-c0c7-4414-b347-d4feb5d34f0b&token=NGVmOWZkODUtYzBj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4ef9fd85-c0c7-4414-b347-d4feb5d34f0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:01:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Velan Hotels Ltd has entered into an Asset Sale Agreement with JP Associates Asia Pacific Private Ltd, Coimbatore, for the sale of its hotel properties. The agreement was made on 13th January 2026, with an expected completion date before 31st March 2026. The Company has received Rs. 5 Crores as an advance for the sale. The buyer is not related to the promoter/promoter group. The sale is not a part of any scheme of arrangement and the Company is in the process of obtaining shareholder’s approval for the proposed sale.</p><ul><li>Velan Hotels Ltd enters Asset Sale Agreement with JP Associates Asia Pacific</li><li>Agreement for sale of Company’s Hotel properties</li><li>Expected completion date before 31st March 2026</li><li>Rs. 5 Crores received as advance for the sale</li><li>Company in process of obtaining shareholder’s approval for the proposed sale</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d2f9c064-4d36-42ea-b027-df696dbdd7c2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VELAN HOTELS LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[REGAAL] Regaal Resources Ltd: DGGI Conducts Search Operation, Company Makes Voluntary Payment of Rs. 88,72,228</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Regaal+Resources+Ltd&title=Regaal+Resources+Ltd%3A+DGGI+Conducts+Search+Operation%2C+Company+Makes+Voluntary+Payment+of+Rs.+88%2C72%2C228&newsId=f48275aa-47e5-4294-a78f-ae9352ab9bab&token=ZjQ4Mjc1YWEtNDdl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f48275aa-47e5-4294-a78f-ae9352ab9bab</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:01:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Regaal Resources Ltd has informed that officers of the Directorate General of GST Intelligence (DGGI), Patna Zonal Unit conducted a search operation under the Central Goods and Services Tax Act, 2017. The search was conducted at the Principal Place of Business of the Company from 10th January 2026 to 12th January 2026. The officers checked the relevant documents, registers, and other records available and seized some registers and records related to GST for further verification. The Company, in a voluntary move, has paid Rs. 88,72,228 (including tax payment of Rs. 77,14,980 and penalty of Rs. 11,57,248) under Section 74(5) of the CGST Act, 2017. The Company is currently evaluating the matter and will take appropriate actions in due course, in accordance with applicable laws and Regulations.</p><ul><li>DGGI conducted a search operation at Regaal Resources Ltd&apos;s Principal Place of Business.</li><li>The search was conducted from 10th January 2026 to 12th January 2026.</li><li>Officers checked relevant documents, registers, and other records.</li><li>Some registers and records related to GST were seized for further verification.</li><li>Regaal Resources Ltd made a voluntary payment of Rs. 88,72,228 under Section 74(5) of the CGST Act, 2017.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/accc6630-294a-4fb3-b654-0422ce1a07d6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Regaal Resources Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASIANHOTNR] Asian Hotels (North) Ltd to Raise Funds via INR 300 Crores NCDs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Asian+Hotels+%28North%29+Limited&title=Asian+Hotels+%28North%29+Ltd+to+Raise+Funds+via+INR+300+Crores+NCDs&newsId=86777924-d8ad-4439-aa4d-1e8c1ae4246d&token=ODY3Nzc5MjQtZDhh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86777924-d8ad-4439-aa4d-1e8c1ae4246d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:01:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Asian Hotels (North) Ltd has announced a Board Meeting on January 16, 2026, to consider the proposal for raising funds by way of issuance of 3,000 unlisted, senior, secured, redeemable non-convertible debentures (NCDs) of face value INR 10,00,000 each, amounting to a nominal value of up to INR 300,00,00,000 on a private placement basis. The company has also informed the closure of the trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company from January 01, 2026, as per the Company&apos;s Code of Conduct under the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Asian Hotels (North) Ltd to raise funds through INR 300 Crores NCDs</li><li>The company scheduled a Board Meeting on January 16, 2026, to consider the proposal</li><li>3,000 unlisted, senior, secured, redeemable non-convertible debentures (NCDs) will be issued</li><li>NCDs will have a face value of INR 10,00,000 each</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company closed from January 01, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/858e6450-49a5-4aa8-8058-d6abbab3126c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Asian Hotels (North) Limited | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SYSTMTXC] Systematix Corporate Services Ltd to Approve Q3 and 9M Un-Audited Financial Results on Jan 21, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SYSTEMATIX+CORPORATE+SERVICES+LTD.&title=Systematix+Corporate+Services+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+9M+Un-Audited+Financial+Results+on+Jan+21%2C+2026&newsId=21c8272e-fcdf-4e4d-87bb-e6adb30aa8e7&token=MjFjODI3MmUtZmNk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21c8272e-fcdf-4e4d-87bb-e6adb30aa8e7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:01:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Systematix Corporate Services Ltd has announced a Board Meeting on January 21, 2026, to consider and approve the standalone &amp; consolidated un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company will be closed from January 01, 2026, and will open 48 hours after the announcement of the un-audited financial results. The PAN of Directors, Promoters, Designated Persons, and their immediate relatives has been freezed by depositories from January 01, 2026, till the completion of the Closure of Trading Window Period, in accordance with the SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/ISD/ISD-PoD- 2/P/CIR/2023/124 dated July 19, 2023.</p><ul><li>Systematix Corporate Services Ltd to consider and approve un-audited financial results for Q3 and 9M 2025</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities to be closed from January 01, 2026</li><li>Trading window to open 48 hours after the announcement of un-audited financial results</li><li>PAN of Directors, Promoters, Designated Persons, and their immediate relatives frozen by depositories</li><li>Freeze to last till the completion of the Closure of Trading Window Period</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d21401de-8d4f-4ee2-87a1-c1de0cd15caf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SYSTEMATIX CORPORATE SERVICES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PAYTM*] Paytm Completes Acquisition of Fincollect Services, Incorporates New Subsidiary in Luxembourg</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=One+97+Communications+Ltd&title=Paytm+Completes+Acquisition+of+Fincollect+Services%2C+Incorporates+New+Subsidiary+in+Luxembourg&newsId=bc01a52c-dd29-4b18-bffa-933907da93aa&token=YmMwMWE1MmMtZGQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc01a52c-dd29-4b18-bffa-933907da93aa</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>One 97 Communications Ltd, the parent company of Paytm, has completed the acquisition of 100% stake in Fincollect Services Private Limited from Urja Money Private Limited. This acquisition was previously announced on October 15, 2025, and Fincollect Services has now become a direct wholly owned subsidiary of the Company as of January 13, 2026. In addition, Paytm Cloud Technologies Limited (PCTL), a wholly owned subsidiary of One 97 Communications Ltd, has incorporated a new wholly owned subsidiary (WOS) named &apos;Paytm Europe Payments S.A.&apos; in Luxembourg on January 12, 2026, by subscribing to 30,000 equity shares of EURO 1 (One Only) each.</p><ul><li>Paytm&apos;s parent company, One 97 Communications Ltd, has completed the acquisition of Fincollect Services Private Limited.</li><li>Fincollect Services has become a direct wholly owned subsidiary of One 97 Communications Ltd.</li><li>Paytm Cloud Technologies Limited (PCTL) has incorporated a new wholly owned subsidiary (WOS) named &apos;Paytm Europe Payments S.A.&apos; in Luxembourg.</li><li>The new subsidiary was incorporated on January 12, 2026, by subscribing to 30,000 equity shares of EURO 1 (One Only) each.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/124f601f-87de-47a9-b575-0b561437d625.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: One 97 Communications Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>