<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:40:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ROSELABS] Roselabs Finance Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025 with Net Loss of ₹ 29.17 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ROSELABS+FINANCE+LTD.&title=Roselabs+Finance+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025+with+Net+Loss+of+%E2%82%B9+29.17+Crores&newsId=52b0d62e-bfdf-43ab-bb90-822bac966ab5&token=NTJiMGQ2MmUtYmZk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">52b0d62e-bfdf-43ab-bb90-822bac966ab5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:35:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Roselabs Finance Ltd has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a net loss of ₹ 29.17 Crores for the year ended December 31, 2025. The loss for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, was ₹ 3.47 Crores. The company&apos;s revenue from operations for the quarter was ₹ 120.75 Crores, a decrease from the ₹ 122.59 Crores in the same quarter of the previous year. The total comprehensive income for the quarter was ₹ (3.67) Crores. The company operates in the real estate development sector and is in the process of merging with Lodha Developers Limited.</p><ul><li>Net loss of ₹ 29.17 Crores for the year ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter was ₹ 120.75 Crores.</li><li>Total comprehensive income for the quarter was ₹ (3.67) Crores.</li><li>In the process of merging with Lodha Developers Limited.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/18cbbbcf-243c-4ac4-a586-e53ba6874afd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ROSELABS FINANCE LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AUBANK] AU Small Finance Bank: Appointment of New Independent Director, Strategic Organizational Changes, and Q3 2025 Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AU+Small+Finance+Bank+Ltd&title=AU+Small+Finance+Bank%3A+Appointment+of+New+Independent+Director%2C+Strategic+Organizational+Changes%2C+and+Q3+2025+Financial+Results&newsId=3e174380-2853-4696-81ff-5fd7a5e2b9b4&token=M2UxNzQzODAtMjg1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e174380-2853-4696-81ff-5fd7a5e2b9b4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:34:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>AU Small Finance Bank has announced strategic organizational changes, the appointment of a new Independent Director, and the approval of the Q3 2025 financial results. The bank has approved the appointment of Mr. Vivek Tripathi as Whole-Time Director (Executive Director) for a term of 3 years, subject to necessary approvals. Mr. Uttam Tibrewal will conclude his current term as Whole-Time Director but continue as Deputy CEO. The bank has also reported an increase in total income for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Vivek Tripathi as Whole-Time Director (Executive Director)</li><li>Mr. Uttam Tibrewal to conclude his term as Whole-Time Director but continue as Deputy CEO</li><li>Increase in total income for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025</li><li>Strategic organizational changes in leadership structure</li><li>Q3 2025 financial results approved</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/eae3976d-d9d0-424d-8f78-6de325f76b80.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AU Small Finance Bank Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHRIDINE] Shri Dinesh Mills Ltd. to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results on Feb 3, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHRI+DINESH+MILLS+LTD.-%24&title=Shri+Dinesh+Mills+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+on+Feb+3%2C+2026&newsId=d35f4cfb-896b-4e49-9778-b99891670d9e&token=ZDM1ZjRjZmItODk2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d35f4cfb-896b-4e49-9778-b99891670d9e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:34:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shri Dinesh Mills Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 3, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The trading window for directors, officers, and designated employees of the company will be closed from January 18, 2026, to February 5, 2026 (both days inclusive) in accordance with the SEBI regulations.</p><ul><li>Shri Dinesh Mills Ltd. to consider and approve unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December 2025</li><li>Board Meeting scheduled on 3rd February 2026</li><li>Trading window closed for Directors, Officers and designated employees from 18th January 2026 to 5th February 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b7f5eb45-e822-447b-a3f3-28802a18182f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHRI DINESH MILLS LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DCMSHRIRAM] DCM Shriram Ltd Declares 2nd Interim Dividend of Rs. 3.60 per Share for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DCM+Shriram+Limited&title=DCM+Shriram+Ltd+Declares+2nd+Interim+Dividend+of+Rs.+3.60+per+Share+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=4888f9b2-b1a5-4db3-95d0-3e07b2bee8ea&token=NDg4OGY5YjItYjFh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4888f9b2-b1a5-4db3-95d0-3e07b2bee8ea</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:33:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>DCM Shriram Ltd has declared a 2nd interim dividend of Rs. 3.60 per equity share of face value of Rs. 2/- each for the Financial Year 2025-26. The Record Date for the purpose of the said Interim Dividend is 24th January 2026. The company has also reported its Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025.</p><ul><li>DCM Shriram Ltd declares 2nd interim dividend of Rs. 3.60 per share for FY 2025-26</li><li>Record Date for the purpose of the said Interim Dividend is 24th January 2026</li><li>Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025 reported</li><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter ended 31st December 2025 is Rs. 3,834.26 crores</li><li>Profit after tax for the quarter ended 31st December 2025 is Rs. 201.36 crores</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d388e969-8b00-41f5-aec6-15f4ac586fa0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DCM Shriram Limited | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KRYSTAL] Krystal Integrated Services Ltd Incorporates Wholly Owned Subsidiary Krystal Waste Work Prabhag G Private Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Krystal+Integrated+Services+Ltd&title=Krystal+Integrated+Services+Ltd+Incorporates+Wholly+Owned+Subsidiary+Krystal+Waste+Work+Prabhag+G+Private+Limited&newsId=a570f11f-8f39-4441-9604-2c7f94b3ef5c&token=YTU3MGYxMWYtOGYz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a570f11f-8f39-4441-9604-2c7f94b3ef5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Krystal Integrated Services Ltd has incorporated a wholly owned subsidiary named Krystal Waste Work Prabhag G Private Limited on January 20, 2026. The subsidiary has been incorporated under the Companies Act, 2013, with a CIN of U37003MH2026PTC466214 and a registered office in Maharashtra. The subsidiary is planned to carry on the business of collection, segregation, transportation, processing, treatment, recycling, reuse, disposal, and management of all types of waste. Krystal Integrated Services Ltd will subscribe to 10,000 equity shares of face value of Rs.10/- each aggregating to Rs. 1,00,000/- in cash through its authorized representative and nominee, acquiring 100% shareholding and control.</p><ul><li>Krystal Integrated Services Ltd has incorporated a wholly owned subsidiary named Krystal Waste Work Prabhag G Private Limited.</li><li>The subsidiary has been incorporated under the Companies Act, 2013, with a CIN of U37003MH2026PTC466214 and a registered office in Maharashtra.</li><li>The subsidiary is planned to carry on the business of collection, segregation, transportation, processing, treatment, recycling, reuse, disposal, and management of all types of waste.</li><li>Krystal Integrated Services Ltd will subscribe to 10,000 equity shares of face value of Rs.10/- each aggregating to Rs. 1,00,000/- in cash through its authorized representative and nominee, acquiring 100% shareholding and control.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8c5db6f8-2e85-4858-b731-7fc38f7ef579.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Krystal Integrated Services Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHOPERSTOP] Shoppers Stop Ltd. Announces Q3 Results for FY2025-2026, Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results Approved in Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHOPPERS+STOP+LTD.&title=Shoppers+Stop+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+Results+for+FY2025-2026%2C+Unaudited+Standalone+and+Consolidated+Financial+Results+Approved+in+Board+Meeting&newsId=750282ba-5abe-4009-becf-55220450904b&token=NzUwMjgyYmEtNWFi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">750282ba-5abe-4009-becf-55220450904b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shoppers Stop Ltd. has announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The announcement was made following the Board of Directors&apos; meeting held on January 20, 2026. The company&apos;s financial results were reviewed by SRBC&amp;COLLP, a Limited Liability Partnership, and found to be in compliance with the recognition and measurement principles laid down in Indian Accounting Standard 34 and other accounting principles generally accepted in India. The results are also in compliance with Regulation 33 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, as amended. The review did not reveal any material misstatements or non-disclosures as per the Listing Regulations.</p><ul><li>Shoppers Stop Ltd. announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 FY2025-2026.</li><li>The results were reviewed by SRBC&amp;COLLP, a Limited Liability Partnership, and found to be in compliance with relevant accounting standards and regulations.</li><li>The company&apos;s financial results were approved in a Board meeting that commenced at 3.45 p.m. and concluded at 5.40 p.m.</li><li>The results are available on the company&apos;s corporate website i.e. https://[corporate.shoppersstop.com/investors/.</li><li>The review did not reveal any material misstatements or non-disclosures as per the Listing Regulations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/24d4efd2-5cb4-4723-ae97-4d687967d03a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHOPPERS STOP LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PHOTON] Photon Capital Advisors Ltd. Announces Increase in Authorised Share Capital and Preferential Issue of Equity Shares and Warrants</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PHOTON+CAPITAL+ADVISORS+LTD.&title=Photon+Capital+Advisors+Ltd.+Announces+Increase+in+Authorised+Share+Capital+and+Preferential+Issue+of+Equity+Shares+and+Warrants&newsId=21794cd0-6d75-4bac-88b5-d17a1ef47082&token=MjE3OTRjZDAtNmQ3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21794cd0-6d75-4bac-88b5-d17a1ef47082</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:32:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Photon Capital Advisors Ltd. announced that its Board of Directors approved an increase in the company&apos;s authorised share capital and the issuance of equity shares and warrants on a preferential basis. The company will increase its authorised share capital from Rs. 4,00,00,000 to Rs. 6,00,00,000, divided into 60,00,000 equity shares of Rs. 10/- each. The board also approved alterations to the object clause of the Memorandum of Association. Additionally, the company will issue up to 12,07,000 equity shares and 19,90,000 share warrants on a preferential basis to persons under the proposed Promoter and Non-Promoter Category. The record date for voting is February 12, 2026.</p><ul><li>Approval to increase authorised share capital to Rs. 6,00,00,000</li><li>Alteration of the object clause of the Memorandum of Association</li><li>Issuance of up to 12,07,000 equity shares on a preferential basis</li><li>Issuance of up to 19,90,000 share warrants on a preferential basis</li><li>Convening of Extra-Ordinary General Meeting on February 19, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5b3676ab-9c91-4e9e-91e6-e0753870db54.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PHOTON CAPITAL ADVISORS LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SARVESHWAR] Sarveshwar Foods Ltd and JKHPMC Sign MoA for Basmati Rice Clusters Development in Jammu Region</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sarveshwar+Foods+Ltd&title=Sarveshwar+Foods+Ltd+and+JKHPMC+Sign+MoA+for+Basmati+Rice+Clusters+Development+in+Jammu+Region&newsId=e5884cb7-4e55-4884-89cb-49042cea2672&token=ZTU4ODRjYjctNGU1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5884cb7-4e55-4884-89cb-49042cea2672</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>MoU</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>In a significant initiative, Sarveshwar Foods Ltd and JKHPMC have signed a Memorandum of Agreement (MoA) for the development of Basmati Rice Clusters in the districts of Jammu, Samba, and Kathua. The project, amounting to 197.29 crores, aims to transform the basmati value chain in Jammu and Kashmir, and is expected to benefit approximately 7,500 farmers, improving productivity, quality, and market access for Basmati rice growers.</p><ul><li>Sarveshwar Foods Ltd and JKHPMC sign MoA for Basmati Rice Clusters development in Jammu region.</li><li>Project aims to transform basmati value chain in Jammu and Kashmir.</li><li>Expected to benefit approximately 7,500 farmers and cover nearly 12,000 hectares of agricultural land.</li><li>Farmers to be equipped and trained in modern agricultural technologies and scientific farming practices.</li><li>Sarveshwar Foods Limited is an ISO 22000:2018, USFDA, BRC, Kosher, NPPO USA &amp; CHINA, and NOP- USDA Organic certified Company.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8328e513-0fb6-429d-a5fb-295fa04219cf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sarveshwar Foods Ltd | Category: MoU</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SARVESHWAR] JKHPMC Signs MoA with Sarveshwar Foods Ltd for Development of Basmati Rice Clusters in Jammu Region Under HADP Project amounting to 197.29 crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sarveshwar+Foods+Ltd&title=JKHPMC+Signs+MoA+with+Sarveshwar+Foods+Ltd+for+Development+of+Basmati+Rice+Clusters+in+Jammu+Region+Under+HADP+Project+amounting+to+197.29+crores&newsId=695f86ca-ead1-45f6-b9a8-366a362870f4&token=Njk1Zjg2Y2EtZWFk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">695f86ca-ead1-45f6-b9a8-366a362870f4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:32:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>MoU</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>In a major initiative aimed at strengthening the Basmati rice value chain and enhancing farmers’ income, the Jammu and Kashmir Horticulture Produce Marketing Corporation (JKHPMC), functioning as the Cluster Development Agency (CDA), signed a Memorandum of Agreement (MoA) with Sarveshwar Foods Ltd for the development of Basmati Rice Clusters in the districts of Jammu, Samba, and Kathua. The project will be implemented through a wholly owned subsidiary of Sarveshwar Foods Limited, Himalayan Ancient Foods Private Limited, to ensure focused execution, efficient governance, and effective monitoring of cluster development activities. The agreement was formally signed by Mohammad Farooq Dar, Managing Director of JKHPMC, and Dr. Gayatri Tandon, Project Head, Sarveshwar Foods Ltd. The project is expected to benefit approximately 7,500 farmers and will cover nearly 12,000 hectares of agricultural land across the three districts. The initiative aims to improve productivity, quality, and market access for Basmati rice growers while ensuring better price realization and income enhancement. As part of the project, farmers will be equipped and trained in modern agricultural technologies, scientific farming practices, and improved crop management techniques to enhance efficiency, yield, and profitability.</p><ul><li>JKHPMC and Sarveshwar Foods Ltd sign MoA for development of Basmati Rice Clusters in Jammu Region under HADP Project</li><li>Project to be implemented by Himalayan Ancient Foods Private Limited, a subsidiary of Sarveshwar Foods Limited</li><li>Aimed at strengthening Basmati rice value chain and enhancing farmers’ income</li><li>Expected to benefit approximately 7,500 farmers and cover nearly 12,000 hectares of agricultural land</li><li>Farmers to be equipped and trained in modern agricultural technologies and scientific farming practices</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/aa782071-b705-4428-af81-78437c3ea4a0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sarveshwar Foods Ltd | Category: MoU</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HILINFRA] Highway Infrastructure Accelerates Order Momentum with Rs. 64.68 Crores Toll Contract from NHAI</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Highway+Infrastructure+Ltd&title=Highway+Infrastructure+Accelerates+Order+Momentum+with+Rs.+64.68+Crores+Toll+Contract+from+NHAI&newsId=ab3b4bb5-5a1c-45d0-8bfd-8bd9d513d92c&token=YWIzYjRiYjUtNWEx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab3b4bb5-5a1c-45d0-8bfd-8bd9d513d92c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 12:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Toll Contract</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Highway Infrastructure, an integrated infrastructure development and management company, has received a Letter of Award (LOA) from the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) for engagement as the user-fee agency at the Mundka Fee Plaza. The project, valued at Rs. 64.68 Crores, covers the operation and collection of user fees at the Mundka Toll Plaza located at km 22+750 on NH-344M and NH-344N. This award adds to a series of recent wins, significantly strengthening HIL’s order book and future revenue visibility. The company’s sustained momentum in securing national highway tolling projects positions it well for scaled bidding in larger, higher-yield opportunities.</p><ul><li>Receipt of Letter of Award (LOA) from NHAI for Mundka Fee Plaza toll contract worth Rs. 64.68 Crores.</li><li>Project covers operation and collection of user fees at Mundka Toll Plaza with associated facilities maintenance.</li><li>Multiple recent wins strengthening HIL’s order book and future revenue visibility.</li><li>Company positioned for scaled bidding in larger, higher-yield opportunities.</li><li>Highway Infrastructure continues to adopt technology-driven tolling systems for efficient operations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2af7258e-f5a6-44d5-a490-a76aa3eaf182.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Highway Infrastructure Ltd | Category: Toll Contract</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>