<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:29:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ASHOKA] Ashoka Buildcon Ltd Secures $45.3 Million EPC Project in Liberia</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ASHOKA+BUILDCON+LTD.&title=Ashoka+Buildcon+Ltd+Secures+%2445.3+Million+EPC+Project+in+Liberia&newsId=7a09b7ed-a2f4-440b-80b9-a8ddd0c515e4&token=N2EwOWI3ZWQtYTJm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7a09b7ed-a2f4-440b-80b9-a8ddd0c515e4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:01:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Ashoka Buildcon Ltd has been awarded a Letter of Award (LOA) by the Ministry of Public Works, Liberia for the &apos;Upgrading of the Road from Nrowkia (Sasstown Jn) to Barclayville and Nrowkia (Sasstown Jn) to Sasstown and Part of Nrowkia (Sasstown Jn) to Nipleppo road Project in Republic of Liberia&apos;. The project is an Engineering, Procurement and Construction (EPC) contract with a value of USD 45,276,621.07 and is expected to be completed within 24 months.</p><ul><li>Ashoka Buildcon Ltd has been awarded a $45.3 million EPC project in Liberia.</li><li>The project involves upgrading of the road from Nrowkia (Sasstown Jn) to Barclayville and Nrowkia (Sasstown Jn) to Sasstown and Part of Nrowkia (Sasstown Jn) to Nipleppo road in Republic of Liberia.</li><li>The project is expected to be completed within 24 months.</li><li>The trading window for the concerned Designated Persons of the Company and their immediate relatives will remain closed till 48 hours after the disclosure.</li><li>The details of the project are provided in Annexure I as per the Master Circular No. SEBI/HO/CFD/PoD2/CIR/P/0155 dated November 11, 2024.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f8d38d35-7406-4464-99dd-7283426300e5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ASHOKA BUILDCON LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NATCOPHARM] NATCO Pharma Ltd Receives Approval for Semaglutide Injection in India</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NATCO+PHARMA+LTD.&title=NATCO+Pharma+Ltd+Receives+Approval+for+Semaglutide+Injection+in+India&newsId=9084c269-9bcd-401e-b6dd-32d4db42ed55&token=OTA4NGMyNjktOWJj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9084c269-9bcd-401e-b6dd-32d4db42ed55</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 04:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>NATCO Pharma Limited has received approval from the Central Drugs Standard Control Organisation (CDSCO) to manufacture and market generic Semaglutide Injection in India. The product is indicated for the treatment of adults with insufficiently controlled type 2 diabetes mellitus as an adjunct to diet and exercise. NATCO is a R&amp;D oriented, and a science driven leading Oncology player in the targeted therapies of the domestic market, focusing on limited competition molecule in the US. The company has 9 manufacturing sites and 2 R&amp;D facilities in India, approved by several leading regulatory authorities like U.S. FDA, Brazil ANVISA, Health Canada, WHO and others, catering to 50+ global markets.</p><ul><li>NATCO Pharma Ltd received approval from CDSCO for Semaglutide in India</li><li>Semaglutide is indicated for the treatment of adults with insufficiently controlled type 2 diabetes mellitus</li><li>NATCO will launch the product in the India market in March’26</li><li>NATCO is a R&amp;D oriented, and a science driven leading Oncology player in the domestic market</li><li>NATCO has 9 manufacturing sites and 2 R&amp;D facilities in India, approved by several leading regulatory authorities</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b6c90a85-70f8-463c-9d7e-ac74e6aeb477.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NATCO PHARMA LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ORTINLAABS] Ortin Global Ltd. Open Offer for Acquisition of 21,14,162 Equity Shares by Parveen Ram Sarup Satija</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ortin+Laboratories+Ltd&title=Ortin+Global+Ltd.+Open+Offer+for+Acquisition+of+21%2C14%2C162+Equity+Shares+by+Parveen+Ram+Sarup+Satija&newsId=01d137cf-fd7d-4d7d-83dd-12633fbef7a9&token=MDFkMTM3Y2YtZmQ3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01d137cf-fd7d-4d7d-83dd-12633fbef7a9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 02:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Open Offer</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rarever Financial Advisors Pvt. Ltd., as the Manager to the Offer, has submitted a Corrigendum to the Public Announcement for Ortin Global Limited’s open offer. The offer aims to acquire 21,14,162 fully paid-up equity shares, representing 26.00% of the voting share capital, at an offer price of X14.65/- per equity share. The Corrigendum includes certain modifications to the Public Announcement, which should be read in continuation and in conjunction with the original Public Announcement.</p><ul><li>Ortin Global Ltd. open offer for acquisition of 21,14,162 equity shares</li><li>Offer price of X14.65/- per equity share</li><li>Corrigendum issued by Rarever Financial Advisors Pvt. Ltd.</li><li>Modifications to the Public Announcement</li><li>26.00% of the voting share capital acquisition</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5608E7E4-DD0D-4641-AB2F-52B025E56899-074141.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ortin Laboratories Ltd | Category: Open Offer</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TEJASSVI] Saffron Capital Advisors to Acquire up to 70,00,000 Equity Shares of Tejassvi Aaharam Ltd for ~ 7,00,00,000/-</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Tejassvi+Aaharam+Ltd&title=Saffron+Capital+Advisors+to+Acquire+up+to+70%2C00%2C000+Equity+Shares+of+Tejassvi+Aaharam+Ltd+for+~+7%2C00%2C00%2C000%2F-&newsId=da152166-a464-4268-a8bf-8e81439ad562&token=ZGExNTIxNjYtYTQ2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">da152166-a464-4268-a8bf-8e81439ad562</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 02:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Saffron Capital Advisors Pvt. Ltd., along with other acquirers and a Person Acting in Concert (PAC), have submitted a Public Announcement to acquire up to 70,00,000 Equity Shares of Tejassvi Aaharam Ltd for ~ 7,00,00,000/-. The open offer is being made pursuant to the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011, as amended. The open offer is for at least 26% of the Emerging Voting Share Capital of the Target Company, as on the 10th working day from the closure of the tendering period. The public shareholding of the Target Company comprises 12.04% of the Emerging Voting Share Capital, after excluding the Other Shareholders of the Transferor Company who are proposed allottees in the preferential issue and are considered as Deemed Persons Acting in Concert with the Acquirers and the PAC for the purposes of this open offer.</p><ul><li>Saffron Capital Advisors Pvt. Ltd. and other acquirers plan to acquire up to 70,00,000 Equity Shares of Tejassvi Aaharam Ltd.</li><li>The total value of the acquisition is ~ 7,00,00,000/-.</li><li>The open offer is being made pursuant to the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011, as amended.</li><li>The open offer is for at least 26% of the Emerging Voting Share Capital of the Target Company.</li><li>The public shareholding of the Target Company comprises 12.04% of the Emerging Voting Share Capital, after excluding the Other Shareholders of the Transferor Company who are proposed allottees in the preferential issue and are considered as Deemed Persons Acting in Concert with the Acquirers and the PAC for the purposes of this open offer.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7455E0F0-DEA7-443E-BE96-558F598893C8-074557.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Tejassvi Aaharam Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JINDALPOLY] Jindal Poly Films Ltd Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JINDAL+POLY+FILMS+LTD.&title=Jindal+Poly+Films+Ltd+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025&newsId=4df1ffa9-a689-4b1b-99d3-241348aacb81&token=NGRmMWZmYTktYTY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4df1ffa9-a689-4b1b-99d3-241348aacb81</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 02:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jindal Poly Films Ltd has announced the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The Board of Directors approved the results in a meeting that commenced on February 13, 2026, and concluded on February 14, 2026. The results are available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025 approved</li><li>Meeting of the Board of Directors commenced on February 13, 2026, and concluded on February 14, 2026</li><li>Results available on the company&apos;s website: https://www.jindalpoly.com</li><li>Fire occurred in a subsidiary Company’s plant located in Nashik, Maharashtra in the quarter ended June 30, 2025, resulting in damage. Necessary adjustments will be recognized in the subsequent periods after the completion of assessment.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d4d150e6-140a-47f9-ba00-130a8b61e080.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JINDAL POLY FILMS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JINDALPOLY] Jindal Poly Films Ltd Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JINDAL+POLY+FILMS+LTD.&title=Jindal+Poly+Films+Ltd+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025&newsId=84f7afa8-d0da-4268-8a4e-aa86b195a269&token=ODRmN2FmYTgtZDBk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">84f7afa8-d0da-4268-8a4e-aa86b195a269</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 02:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jindal Poly Films Ltd has announced the financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The Board of Directors approved the unaudited Standalone and Consolidated financial results in a meeting that commenced on February 13, 2026 and concluded on February 14, 2026. The company reported a profit before tax and after exceptional items for the continuing operations of INR 51,151.40 lakhs and a net profit after tax for the period from continuing operations of INR 37,107.82 lakhs.</p><ul><li>Profit before tax and after exceptional items for the continuing operations of INR 51,151.40 lakhs</li><li>Net profit after tax for the period from continuing operations of INR 37,107.82 lakhs</li><li>Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated financial results approved by the Board of Directors</li><li>Meeting of the Board of Directors commenced on February 13, 2026 and concluded on February 14, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dd355806-719e-4380-825e-de1a8865cfde.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JINDAL POLY FILMS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VIKRAN] Vikran Engineering Ltd Approves Rs. 300 Crores Term Loan, Reports Q3 Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vikran+Engineering+Ltd&title=Vikran+Engineering+Ltd+Approves+Rs.+300+Crores+Term+Loan%2C+Reports+Q3+Results&newsId=a2454a99-7a0b-4fe4-b977-85b54f9c4fb2&token=YTI0NTRhOTktN2Ew</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2454a99-7a0b-4fe4-b977-85b54f9c4fb2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:07:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vikran Engineering Ltd has approved the availing of a term loan or issuance of unlisted, secured, rated, redeemable non-convertible debentures for an aggregate amount of up to approximately Rs. 300 Crores. The company&apos;s Board has also delegated the powers to the Corporate Affairs Committee for finalization of terms &amp; conditions. The company reported its un-audited financial results for the quarter ended December 2025, with a profit before tax of INR 17,629 lakhs. The company also noted an ongoing litigation with a customer on recoverability of balance amounting to INR 2,929 lakhs.</p><ul><li>Approval of term loan or issuance of non-convertible debentures up to Rs. 300 Crores</li><li>Delegation of powers to Corporate Affairs Committee for finalization of terms &amp; conditions</li><li>Reported profit before tax of INR 17,629 lakhs for Q3 2025</li><li>Ongoing litigation with a customer on recoverability of balance amounting to INR 2,929 lakhs</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/30e4397a-4b82-4136-85b8-ca12ce4b90e3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vikran Engineering Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SICALLOG] Sical Logistics Approves Rights Issue of Equity Shares and Quarterly Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SICAL+LOGISTICS+LTD.&title=Sical+Logistics+Approves+Rights+Issue+of+Equity+Shares+and+Quarterly+Financial+Results&newsId=06692a4d-47b4-4d75-9c3b-466664dc7c64&token=MDY2OTJhNGQtNDdi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06692a4d-47b4-4d75-9c3b-466664dc7c64</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sical Logistics Limited has informed the exchange about the approval of the rights issue of equity shares and the quarterly financial results. The rights issue of equity shares will be offered to the public shareholders of the Company as on the record date, with a rights entitlement ratio of 11 (eleven) rights equity shares for every 5 (five) equity shares held. The quarterly financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, have been considered and approved by the Board.</p><ul><li>Sical Logistics approved a rights issue of equity shares for an aggregate amount not exceeding Rs. 93,02,90,560/-</li><li>The rights issue is offered to public shareholders as on the record date with a rights entitlement ratio of 11:5</li><li>The Board considered and approved the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4d700500-781b-4566-90b7-3181b8819a12.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SICAL LOGISTICS LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EMAINDIA] EMA India Ltd. Reports Q3 and Nine Months Results for FY 2025-26, Announces Director Appointments and Resignation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=EMA+INDIA+LTD.&title=EMA+India+Ltd.+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+FY+2025-26%2C+Announces+Director+Appointments+and+Resignation&newsId=a87c2553-75ad-40cf-bf66-d0956f517409&token=YTg3YzI1NTMtNzVh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a87c2553-75ad-40cf-bf66-d0956f517409</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>EMA India Ltd. announced the revised outcome of its board meeting held on February 13, 2026. The company reported the Un-audited Standalone Financial Results for the Quarter and nine months ended 31% December, 2025, along with the Limited Review Report of the Auditors on Standalone Financial Results. The board appointed Mr. Apurva Shivaji Adhalrao as an Additional Director (Executive, Non-Independent) and Mr. Rajendra Senapati as an Additional Director (Non-Executive, Independent). The board also accepted the resignation of Ms. Honey Bhatia as a Non-Executive Independent Director due to personal reasons. The Audit Committee and Nomination &amp; Remuneration Committee have been reconstituted following Ms. Bhatia&apos;s resignation.</p><ul><li>EMA India Ltd. reported Q3 and nine months results for FY 2025-26</li><li>Un-audited Standalone Financial Results and Limited Review Report of the Auditors on Standalone Financial Results were approved</li><li>Mr. Apurva Shivaji Adhalrao and Mr. Rajendra Senapati appointed as Additional Directors</li><li>Ms. Honey Bhatia resigned as a Non-Executive Independent Director</li><li>Audit Committee and Nomination &amp; Remuneration Committee reconstituted</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8162e292-a1d4-48aa-a1a4-b9f62e53f5cf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: EMA INDIA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SICALLOG] Sical Logistics Ltd. Approves Quarterly Financial Results and Rights Issue Terms</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SICAL+LOGISTICS+LTD.&title=Sical+Logistics+Ltd.+Approves+Quarterly+Financial+Results+and+Rights+Issue+Terms&newsId=fffa353a-7961-4e6a-9f30-6290e1aa8094&token=ZmZmYTM1M2EtNzk2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fffa353a-7961-4e6a-9f30-6290e1aa8094</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sical Logistics Limited has approved its quarterly financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s board of directors also approved certain clarificatory updates to the terms of the proposed rights issue of equity shares. The rights issue will offer 11 (eleven) rights equity shares for every 5 (five) equity shares held by public shareholders on the record date. The issue size is 1,45,35,790 (one crore forty-five lakh thirty-five thousand seven hundred ninety) fully paid-up equity shares, for an aggregate amount not exceeding Rs. 93,02,90,560/- (ninety-three crore two lakh ninety thousand five hundred sixty only). The rights issue price remains unchanged at Rs. 64 per rights equity share.</p><ul><li>Approval of Quarterly Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Clarificatory updates to the terms of the proposed rights issue of equity shares</li><li>Rights issue offers 11 (eleven) rights equity shares for every 5 (five) equity shares held by public shareholders</li><li>Issue size is 1,45,35,790 (one crore forty-five lakh thirty-five thousand seven hundred ninety) fully paid-up equity shares</li><li>Rights issue price remains unchanged at Rs. 64 per rights equity share</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d830f961-3875-4012-8023-04a14dbafeee.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SICAL LOGISTICS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>