<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:31:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[MAJESAUT] Majestic Auto Ltd Receives Order Modifying GST Demand from ₹ 9,56,04,387 to ₹ 3,39,238</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MAJESTIC+AUTO+LTD.-%24&title=Majestic+Auto+Ltd+Receives+Order+Modifying+GST+Demand+from+%E2%82%B9+9%2C56%2C04%2C387+to+%E2%82%B9+3%2C39%2C238&newsId=81d7ad19-d132-4561-a8e2-b2dbbddf9222&token=ODFkN2FkMTktZDEz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">81d7ad19-d132-4561-a8e2-b2dbbddf9222</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Majestic Auto Ltd has received an order from the Additional Commissioner Grade-II Appeal, GST Appellate Authority, Gautam Budha Nagar, Uttar Pradesh, modifying the earlier GST demand of ₹ 9,56,04,387 to ₹ 3,39,238. The order was passed pursuant to an appeal filed by the company on December 30, 2023, against an order of Deputy Commissioner (GST) that raised a demand of ₹ 956.04 Lakhs on the company in December 2023 for the financial year 2017-18. The appeal has been accepted by the Appellate Authority, and the demand has been modified to ₹ 3,39,238. The contingent liability appearing in the Notes to Accounts of the company on this account will stand extinguished. The other expenses will increase by ₹ 3,39,238, and the Profit before tax &amp; Profit after tax will reduce by the same amount during the current financial year 2025-26. No finding of deliberate violation has been recorded by the Appellate Authority.</p><ul><li>Majestic Auto Ltd receives order modifying GST demand from ₹ 9,56,04,387 to ₹ 3,39,238</li><li>Order passed pursuant to an appeal filed by the company on December 30, 2023</li><li>No finding of deliberate violation recorded by the Appellate Authority</li><li>Contingent liability appearing in the Notes to Accounts of the company to be extinguished</li><li>Other expenses to increase by ₹ 3,39,238 and Profit before tax &amp; Profit after tax to reduce by the same amount during the current financial year 2025-26</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3946677e-43e8-4def-a9cc-fd33c470676e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MAJESTIC AUTO LTD.-$ | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUNPHARMA] Sun Pharma Announces the Availability of UNLOXCYT™ (cosibelimab-ipdl) for Advanced Cutaneous Squamous Cell Carcinoma (aCSCC)</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SUN+PHARMACEUTICAL+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Sun+Pharma+Announces+the+Availability+of+UNLOXCYT%E2%84%A2+%28cosibelimab-ipdl%29+for+Advanced+Cutaneous+Squamous+Cell+Carcinoma+%28aCSCC%29&newsId=ba86a9eb-cb40-4d88-af07-066b4fac5430&token=YmE4NmE5ZWItY2I0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba86a9eb-cb40-4d88-af07-066b4fac5430</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 17:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Limited has announced the availability of UNLOXCYT™ (cosibelimab-ipdl) for the treatment of adults in the U.S. with metastatic cutaneous squamous cell carcinoma (mCSCC) or locally advanced CSCC (laCSCC) who are not candidates for curative surgery or curative radiation. UNLOXCYT offers a balanced treatment approach with long-term data confirming durable efficacy and a proven tolerability profile. It has a multifaceted mechanism of action that helps restore the adaptive immune response and engages the innate immune system while preserving PD-L2 signaling.</p><ul><li>Sun Pharma announces the availability of UNLOXCYT™ (cosibelimab-ipdl) for the treatment of adults with metastatic cutaneous squamous cell carcinoma (mCSCC) or locally advanced CSCC (laCSCC) who are not candidates for curative surgery or curative radiation.</li><li>UNLOXCYT offers a balanced treatment approach with long-term data confirming durable efficacy and a proven tolerability profile.</li><li>UNLOXCYT has a multifaceted mechanism of action that helps restore the adaptive immune response and engages the innate immune system while preserving PD-L2 signaling.</li><li>UNLOXCYT is now available in the U.S. for healthcare professionals to prescribe.</li><li>Sun Pharma is committed to ensuring access from day one with the UNLOXCYT SUPPORT™ patient access and affordability program.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/08817f40-0386-46c4-8c55-9556e2e44513.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SUN PHARMACEUTICAL INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[URBANCO] Urban Company Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on Jan 23, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Urban+Company+Ltd&title=Urban+Company+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+Jan+23%2C+2026&newsId=dfcea8b9-8233-4ba5-bc12-3a5515a5671f&token=ZGZjZWE4YjktODIz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dfcea8b9-8233-4ba5-bc12-3a5515a5671f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:11:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Urban Company Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 23, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company will also host an earnings conference call for investors and analysts on the same day from 06:30 p.m. to 07:30 p.m. (IST) to discuss the financial results. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company will re-open 48 hours after the declaration of the aforesaid financial results.</p><ul><li>Urban Company Ltd to consider and approve Q3 and nine months financial results on Jan 23, 2026</li><li>The company will host an earnings conference call for investors and analysts on Jan 23, 2026</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company to re-open 48 hours after the financial results declaration</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/09ba268a-b8df-4824-9c50-16cfef21716b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Urban Company Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PRIMIND] Prime Industries Ltd Approves Regularization and Appointment of Rama Nand Gupta as Whole Time Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PRIME+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Prime+Industries+Ltd+Approves+Regularization+and+Appointment+of+Rama+Nand+Gupta+as+Whole+Time+Director&newsId=0c87ddb8-3c72-4949-81c8-11e29294ab88&token=MGM4N2RkYjgtM2M3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c87ddb8-3c72-4949-81c8-11e29294ab88</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Prime Industries Ltd held a Board Meeting on 15th January, 2026, where they approved the regularization of Rama Nand Gupta as Director and his appointment as Whole Time Director, subject to shareholder approval in the ensuing General Meeting. The company also increased its authorized share capital and announced an Extraordinary General Meeting.</p><ul><li>Regularization of Rama Nand Gupta as Director</li><li>Appointment of Rama Nand Gupta as Whole Time Director</li><li>Increase in authorized share capital</li><li>Announcement of Extraordinary General Meeting</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f6975df0-1fe0-474d-af94-9cc5994d2d9e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PRIME INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INERTIAST] Banganga Paper Industries Ltd Approves Increase in Authorised Share Capital and Shifting of Registered Office</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INERTIA+STEEL+LTD.&title=Banganga+Paper+Industries+Ltd+Approves+Increase+in+Authorised+Share+Capital+and+Shifting+of+Registered+Office&newsId=be58dabc-9170-4f58-997a-c27f252958ec&token=YmU1OGRhYmMtOTE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be58dabc-9170-4f58-997a-c27f252958ec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:51:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Capital Increase and Office Relocation</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Banganga Paper Industries Ltd, formerly known as Inertia Steel Limited, has announced significant changes during their Extra Ordinary General Meeting held on Wednesday, January 14, 2026. The shareholders have approved an increase in the company&apos;s authorized share capital from Rs. 12,00,00,000 to Rs. 36,00,00,000 by creating additional equity shares of Re. 1/- each, which will rank pari passu with the existing equity shares. Furthermore, the company plans to shift its registered office from the State of Maharashtra to the State of Meghalaya, subject to the approval of the Central Government and/or any prescribed authority.</p><ul><li>Authorized share capital increase from Rs. 12,00,00,000 to Rs. 36,00,00,000</li><li>Creation of additional 24,00,00,000 equity shares of Re. 1/- each</li><li>Shifting of registered office from Maharashtra to Meghalaya</li><li>Subject to approval from Central Government and/or prescribed authority</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8f97b948-9669-4824-bae9-0817a5146e1e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INERTIA STEEL LTD. | Category: Capital Increase and Office Relocation</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DELTACORP] Delta Corp Ltd Announces Business and Project Update: New Cruise Vessel, Placed Dhargal Land Parcel Development on Hold, Proposed Demerger of Businesses, and More</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DELTA+CORP+LTD.&title=Delta+Corp+Ltd+Announces+Business+and+Project+Update%3A+New+Cruise+Vessel%2C+Placed+Dhargal+Land+Parcel+Development+on+Hold%2C+Proposed+Demerger+of+Businesses%2C+and+More&newsId=9ccbb0b3-747b-4a13-81b5-4dcab4401aff&token=OWNjYmIwYjMtNzQ3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ccbb0b3-747b-4a13-81b5-4dcab4401aff</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:51:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Delta Corp Ltd has provided an update on key business, operational, and corporate developments. The company is in the advanced stages of completing a new casino vessel for the Mandovi River in Goa, expected to commence operations in April 2026. The development of an integrated resort on the Dhargal land parcel has been put on hold, with the company evaluating options for monetization. Delta Corp has filed an application with the NCLT for the demerger of its businesses into two separate entities. The company is also investing in a real estate platform, acquiring land parcels, and developing hotels and casinos in various locations. Additionally, Delta Corp is awaiting final judgments in matters related to GST rate increase and Daman casino license.</p><ul><li>Delta Corp is completing a new casino vessel for Goa&apos;s Mandovi River</li><li>The company has decided to hold the development of an integrated resort on the Dhargal land parcel</li><li>Delta Corp has filed for demerger of its gaming and hospitality businesses</li><li>The company is investing in a real estate platform and developing hotels and casinos</li><li>Delta Corp is awaiting final judgments in matters related to GST rate increase and Daman casino license</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9e3d1d5f-9b27-4096-9d6c-68cf60fb93e3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DELTA CORP LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KRSNAA] Krsnaa Diagnostics Ltd CFO Pawan Daga Resigns</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Krsnaa+Diagnostics+Ltd&title=Krsnaa+Diagnostics+Ltd+CFO+Pawan+Daga+Resigns&newsId=afdc1a3e-f50b-4d2f-91fe-03a1938d27e3&token=YWZkYzFhM2UtZjUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">afdc1a3e-f50b-4d2f-91fe-03a1938d27e3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Auditor</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Krsnaa Diagnostics Ltd announced the resignation of its Chief Financial Officer, Mr. Pawan Daga. His last working day with the Company will be till the close of business hours on January 19, 2026. The Company expressed gratitude for his services and contributions during his five-year tenure.</p><ul><li>Mr. Pawan Daga resigns from the position of Chief Financial Officer of Krsnaa Diagnostics Ltd.</li><li>His last working day will be on January 19, 2026.</li><li>The Company expressed appreciation for his services and contributions during his tenure.</li><li>The resignation is due to personal and professional priorities.</li><li>The finance function is said to be well-positioned for continued success.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ccdd0072-35ff-48dd-9406-ad529a2e323e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Krsnaa Diagnostics Ltd | Category: Auditor</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LUMAXTECH] Lumax Auto Technologies Ltd: National Company Law Tribunal Sanctions Scheme of Arrangement for Amalgamation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LUMAX+AUTO+TECHNOLOGIES+LTD.&title=Lumax+Auto+Technologies+Ltd%3A+National+Company+Law+Tribunal+Sanctions+Scheme+of+Arrangement+for+Amalgamation&newsId=2e29ac04-f3d0-4e48-9a53-3778008307f4&token=MmUyOWFjMDQtZjNk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e29ac04-f3d0-4e48-9a53-3778008307f4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:11:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Lumax Auto Technologies Ltd has announced that the Hon&apos;ble National Company Law Tribunal, Chandigarh Bench has pronounced an order sanctioning the Scheme of Arrangement for Amalgamation between Greenfuel Energy Solutions Private Limited and Lumax Resources Private Limited, both subsidiaries of the company. The order, however, contains certain factual errors which the company is taking necessary steps to rectify. Upon receipt of the rectified order, the company will intimate and file the requisite disclosure with the Stock Exchanges.</p><ul><li>National Company Law Tribunal sanctions Scheme of Arrangement for Amalgamation between Lumax Auto Technologies subsidiaries</li><li>Scheme involves Greenfuel Energy Solutions Private Limited and Lumax Resources Private Limited</li><li>Company to rectify certain factual errors in the order</li><li>Rectified order to be intimated and filed with Stock Exchanges upon receipt</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/10945b06-2555-415b-a25d-c671362b11a6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LUMAX AUTO TECHNOLOGIES LTD. | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RBA] Restaurant Brands Asia Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Discuss Fund Raising</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Restaurant+Brands+Asia+Ltd&title=Restaurant+Brands+Asia+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Discuss+Fund+Raising&newsId=88e7b900-cbaf-45f9-b102-60c0f53e19fc&token=ODhlN2I5MDAtY2Jh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88e7b900-cbaf-45f9-b102-60c0f53e19fc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 15:11:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Restaurant Brands Asia Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 20, 2026, to consider and approve a proposal for fund raising. The company may consider various methods for fund raising, including a preferential issue on a private placement basis, rights issue, qualified institutional placement, or any other methods as appropriate. The company will also consider convening an extraordinary general meeting to seek approval from members for the fund raising proposal. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the company by designated persons and their immediate relatives will remain closed from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the conclusion of the Board Meeting.</p><ul><li>Restaurant Brands Asia Ltd to consider fund raising proposal on January 20, 2026</li><li>Company may consider various methods for fund raising</li><li>Extraordinary general meeting to be considered for member approval</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities to remain closed</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/911dfc62-cfbe-41a1-ba54-c4b2dc049712.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Restaurant Brands Asia Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HSCL] Himadri Speciality Chemical Ltd. Reports on Re-lodgement of Transfer Requests of Physical Shares for December 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Himadri+Speciality+Chemical+Ltd&title=Himadri+Speciality+Chemical+Ltd.+Reports+on+Re-lodgement+of+Transfer+Requests+of+Physical+Shares+for+December+2025&newsId=5f80f623-6f02-466d-8846-1388c8527f75&token=NWY4MGY2MjMtNmYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f80f623-6f02-466d-8846-1388c8527f75</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:47:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Himadri Speciality Chemical Ltd. has released a report on the re-lodgement of transfer requests of physical shares for the month of December 2025. The report, provided by the Registrar and Share Transfer Agent (RTA) M/s. S. K. Infosolutions Private Limited, confirms the status of requests received from shareholders for the re-lodgment of transfer requests for physical shares under the special window provided by the SEBI Circular dated 2nd July 2025. The report includes the number of requests received, processed, approved, and rejected during the month, with an average processing time.</p><ul><li>Himadri Speciality Chemical Ltd. releases report on re-lodgement of transfer requests of physical shares for December 2025.</li><li>Report provided by Registrar and Share Transfer Agent (RTA) M/s. S. K. Infosolutions Private Limited.</li><li>Includes number of requests received, processed, approved, and rejected during the month.</li><li>Includes average processing time for requests.</li><li>Confirms compliance with SEBI circular no. SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97dated 2nd July, 2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ecaf4917-e66c-49a3-bcb8-a7eabc3408e3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Himadri Speciality Chemical Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>