<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:24:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[JRELTD] Eraaya Lifespaces Secures Judicial Protection against False Claims by Mr. Robin Raina</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Justride+Enterprises+Ltd&title=Eraaya+Lifespaces+Secures+Judicial+Protection+against+False+Claims+by+Mr.+Robin+Raina&newsId=74ccfe05-7a45-4d6e-ad1e-b2f6b3ed644c&token=NzRjY2ZlMDUtN2E0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74ccfe05-7a45-4d6e-ad1e-b2f6b3ed644c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:21:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Eraaya Lifespaces Limited has secured comprehensive judicial protection against false claims and frivolous pleas filed by Mr. Robin Raina based on a forged document. The Hon’ble District Judge (Commercial Court), Delhi, has passed an order rejecting the Arbitration Plea filed by Mr. Raina and granting several interim reliefs in favor of the Company and its global subsidiaries operating under Ebix Inc. The litigation between the Company and Mr. Raina emanates from a disputed document, which the Company has consistently maintained to be forged and fabricated. The Hon’ble Court has restrained and injuncted Mr. Raina from seeking or pursuing any reliefs, remedies, or proceedings of any nature founded upon or arising out of the disputed document.</p><ul><li>Eraaya Lifespaces Limited secures comprehensive judicial protection against false claims and frivolous pleas filed by Mr. Robin Raina based on a forged document.</li><li>The Hon’ble District Judge (Commercial Court), Delhi, has passed an order rejecting the Arbitration Plea filed by Mr. Raina and granting several interim reliefs in favor of the Company and its global subsidiaries operating under Ebix Inc.</li><li>The disputed document, which the Company has consistently maintained to be forged and fabricated, is the basis of the litigation between the Company and Mr. Raina.</li><li>The Hon’ble Court has restrained and injuncted Mr. Raina from seeking or pursuing any reliefs, remedies, or proceedings of any nature founded upon or arising out of the disputed document.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b6c73f96-026e-48c8-88ca-ddda04e959c1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Justride Enterprises Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SANPA] Sangal Papers Ltd Confirms Status of Re-lodgement Requests for Physical Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SANGAL+PAPERS+LTD.&title=Sangal+Papers+Ltd+Confirms+Status+of+Re-lodgement+Requests+for+Physical+Shares&newsId=5e9ab1e2-6999-4824-84db-815a8e997345&token=NWU5YWIxZTItNjk5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5e9ab1e2-6999-4824-84db-815a8e997345</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:11:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sangal Papers Ltd has confirmed the status of re-lodgement requests for physical shares. The company received a report from their Registrar and Transfer Agent, MAS Services Limited, on re-lodgement of transfer requests of physical shares, dated 07/01/2026, which was received on 09/01/2026. The confirmation is for the period from December 1, 2025, to December 31, 2025. The company has processed a certain number of requests during this period.</p><ul><li>Sangal Papers Ltd confirms the status of re-lodgement requests for physical shares.</li><li>Report received from Registrar and Transfer Agent MAS Services Limited on re-lodgement of transfer requests.</li><li>Period for re-lodgement requests confirmation: December 1, 2025, to December 31, 2025.</li><li>Number of requests received and processed during the mentioned period.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4769f41e-331d-4912-953d-29c9420f65ee.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SANGAL PAPERS LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZYDUSWELL] Zydus Wellness Ltd. Granted Ad-Interim Relief in GST Demand Case by Gujarat High Court</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ZYDUS+WELLNESS+LTD.-%24&title=Zydus+Wellness+Ltd.+Granted+Ad-Interim+Relief+in+GST+Demand+Case+by+Gujarat+High+Court&newsId=c456537b-7847-40e8-9ec8-ada1f417086a&token=YzQ1NjUzN2ItNzg0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c456537b-7847-40e8-9ec8-ada1f417086a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Zydus Wellness Ltd. has received an ad-interim relief from the Gujarat High Court in a writ petition filed by its subsidiary, Zydus Wellness Products Limited (ZWPL), against a GST demand of ₹ 56.33 crores. The demand was raised by The Directorate General of Goods and Services Tax Intelligence, Surat Zonal Unit (DGGI) under section 74(5) of the Central Goods and Services Tax Act, 2017. The period covered by the order relates to a pre-acquisition period prior to January 30, 2019, and hence the liability stands fully indemnified by Heinz Italia S.P.A. The matter was listed for hearing on January 9, 2026, and the court has granted ad-interim relief to ZWPL, restraining further proceedings in relation to the said order.</p><ul><li>Zydus Wellness Ltd. subsidiary, Zydus Wellness Products Limited (ZWPL), received an ad-interim relief from the Gujarat High Court in a writ petition.</li><li>The petition was filed against a GST demand of ₹ 56.33 crores raised by The Directorate General of Goods and Services Tax Intelligence, Surat Zonal Unit (DGGI).</li><li>The demand was raised under section 74(5) of the Central Goods and Services Tax Act, 2017 for the pre-acquisition period prior to January 30, 2019.</li><li>The liability stands fully indemnified by Heinz Italia S.P.A.</li><li>The Gujarat High Court restrained further proceedings in relation to the said order.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/055a1755-3d53-4901-bc21-0a488aa9708d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ZYDUS WELLNESS LTD.-$ | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AMANTA] Amanta Healthcare Ltd Appoints GoIndia Advisors LLP as Investor Relations Agency</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Amanta+Healthcare+Ltd&title=Amanta+Healthcare+Ltd+Appoints+GoIndia+Advisors+LLP+as+Investor+Relations+Agency&newsId=0676b0f9-4762-4869-b383-818ac632d8a9&token=MDY3NmIwZjktNDc2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0676b0f9-4762-4869-b383-818ac632d8a9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Amanta Healthcare Limited has appointed M/s. GolIndia Advisors LLP, Mumbai, as its Investor Relationship Agency. The agency will provide Investor Relations Advisory Services to the Company. The contact details of the IR agency are as follows: GoIndia Advisors LLP, 7th floor, Godrej BKC, Plot no. C-68, Avenue 3, G Block BKC, Bandra Kurla Complex, Bandra East, Mumbai, Maharashtra 400051. The email ID is rakesh@goindiaadvisors.com and the contact number is 02262640831.</p><ul><li>Amanta Healthcare Ltd has appointed GolIndia Advisors LLP as its Investor Relations Agency.</li><li>The agency will provide Investor Relations Advisory Services to the Company.</li><li>The contact details of the IR agency are provided in the announcement.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/20cad383-8f4e-458c-b147-3628df0e8a5d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Amanta Healthcare Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HIGHENE] High Energy Batteries India Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on 31st January, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HIGH+ENERGY+BATTERIES+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=High+Energy+Batteries+India+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+31st+January%2C+2026&newsId=9befdeac-7076-4023-b281-49628debddc5&token=OWJlZmRlYWMtNzA3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9befdeac-7076-4023-b281-49628debddc5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 05:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>High Energy Batteries India Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 31st January, 2026 to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. This is in accordance with Regulation 29 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>High Energy Batteries India Ltd to consider and approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December, 2025.</li><li>Meeting of the Board of Directors scheduled on 31st January, 2026.</li><li>Compliance with Regulation 29 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3f2647a6-e50f-4ec4-81cb-f7afa7ffaf07.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HIGH ENERGY BATTERIES (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KERNEX] Kernex Microsystems&apos; Request for Extension of CLW Order Delivery Period Rejected</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KERNEX+MICROSYSTEMS+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Kernex+Microsystems%27+Request+for+Extension+of+CLW+Order+Delivery+Period+Rejected&newsId=7be14a41-3acf-4669-8af4-6c25ed0498c0&token=N2JlMTRhNDEtM2Fj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7be14a41-3acf-4669-8af4-6c25ed0498c0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 05:51:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Kernex Microsystems India Ltd. updates on the CLW Order Obligations and Disclosure Requirements, 2015, regarding a 2024 order for the Supply, Installation, Testing, and Commissioning of On-Board KAVACH equipment for 2,500 Locomotives. The company faced delays in the certification process and submitted a formal request for an extension, which was not considered by CLW. The non-consideration does not impact the company&apos;s financials, technical credentials, or eligibility for future tenders. Indian Railways recently floated additional locomotive tenders, and Kernex Microsystems plans to utilize existing inventory for execution of upcoming requirements, ongoing projects, and future opportunities.</p><ul><li>Kernex Microsystems India Ltd. provides an update on the CLW Order Obligations and Disclosure Requirements, 2015</li><li>Company faced delays in the certification process for a 2024 order of On-Board KAVACH equipment for 2,500 Locomotives</li><li>Formal request for extension of delivery period was submitted but not considered by CLW</li><li>Non-consideration of extension request does not adversely impact company&apos;s financials, technical credentials, or eligibility</li><li>Kernex Microsystems to utilize existing inventory for execution of upcoming CLW &amp; BLW requirements, ongoing projects, and future opportunities</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/652653ae-df32-4a8c-aa87-c392a2ee40fc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KERNEX MICROSYSTEMS (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GHUSHINE] Ghushine Fintrade Ocean Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Appoint Company Secretary and Compliance Officer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ghushine+Fintrrade+Ocean+Ltd&title=Ghushine+Fintrade+Ocean+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Appoint+Company+Secretary+and+Compliance+Officer&newsId=2fed9410-d12a-4ca1-a6e2-895b696609c1&token=MmZlZDk0MTAtZDEy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2fed9410-d12a-4ca1-a6e2-895b696609c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 05:41:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ghushine Fintrade Ocean Ltd has informed the BSE that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on 14/01/2026. The agenda includes the consideration and approval of the appointment of a Company Secretary and Compliance Officer. The meeting will also discuss other necessary matters with the permission of the Chairperson.</p><ul><li>Ghushine Fintrade Ocean Ltd scheduled a Board Meeting on 14th January 2026</li><li>The meeting aims to consider and approve the appointment of a Company Secretary and Compliance Officer</li><li>Other necessary matters will be discussed with the permission of the Chairperson</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2dc97f71-96eb-4b81-8b0a-2f4ae7541901.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ghushine Fintrrade Ocean Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NIBE] NIBE Subsidiary Granted License for Firearms Manufacturing and Proof Testing</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NIBE+Ltd&title=NIBE+Subsidiary+Granted+License+for+Firearms+Manufacturing+and+Proof+Testing&newsId=bf5856ec-3b0c-4ab2-8dbf-32ef2f707ee1&token=YmY1ODU2ZWMtM2Iw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf5856ec-3b0c-4ab2-8dbf-32ef2f707ee1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 05:40:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Nibe Defence and Aerospace Limited (NDAL), a subsidiary of NIBE Ltd, has been granted a license for manufacturing and proof testing of firearms by the Ministry of Home Affairs, Government of India. The license, granted under the provisions of the Arms Act, 1959, Arms Rules, 2016, and Notifications, allows NDAL to manufacture and proof-test firearms/ammunition and associated systems. This marks a significant strategic milestone for the company, representing its formal entry into the manufacturing and proof-testing of firearms and ammunition.</p><ul><li>Nibe Defence and Aerospace Limited (NDAL) granted license for manufacturing and proof testing of firearms by Ministry of Home Affairs, Government of India</li><li>License allows NDAL to manufacture and proof-test firearms/ammunition and associated systems</li><li>Significant strategic milestone for the company</li><li>Formal entry into the manufacturing and proof-testing of firearms and ammunition</li><li>License valid for 7 years from the date of grant</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/edec3cb0-2872-4f5a-bfd6-00310c9d7afc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NIBE Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JUSTO] Promoter Puspamitra Das Acquires 2,000 Shares of Justo Realfintech Ltd via Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Justo+Realfintech+Ltd&title=Promoter+Puspamitra+Das+Acquires+2%2C000+Shares+of+Justo+Realfintech+Ltd+via+Open+Market&newsId=637be00f-d752-42e1-b2b8-8167cb347353&token=NjM3YmUwMGYtZDc1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">637be00f-d752-42e1-b2b8-8167cb347353</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 05:24:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Puspamitra Das, a promoter of Justo Realfintech Ltd, has acquired 2,000 equity shares of the company through the open market. This acquisition increases Das&apos; holding to 38.22% of the company&apos;s total share and voting capital. The acquisition was made on 9th January 2026, and the total equity share capital of the company stands at INR 18,79,81,420 consisting of 1,87,98,142 Equity Shares of Rs. 10 each.</p><ul><li>Puspamitra Das, a promoter of Justo Realfintech Ltd, has acquired 2,000 equity shares of the company.</li><li>The acquisition was made through the open market.</li><li>This acquisition increases Das&apos; holding to 38.22% of the company&apos;s total share and voting capital.</li><li>The total equity share capital of the company stands at INR 18,79,81,420 consisting of 1,87,98,142 Equity Shares of Rs. 10 each.</li><li>The acquisition was made on 9th January 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/207A52CB_B550_4169_AFC8_B07EA5803ED2_104647.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Justo Realfintech Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GENESIS] Ms. V Varalakshmi Acquires 7,36,500 Equity Shares of Genesis Ibrc India Ltd Through SPA</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Genesis+Ibrc+India+Ltd&title=Ms.+V+Varalakshmi+Acquires+7%2C36%2C500+Equity+Shares+of+Genesis+Ibrc+India+Ltd+Through+SPA&newsId=3f0baf2e-8511-45ce-9018-de1410976cc9&token=M2YwYmFmMmUtODUx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3f0baf2e-8511-45ce-9018-de1410976cc9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 05:20:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Exchange has received a disclosure under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011 from Ms. V Varalakshmi. The disclosure pertains to the acquisition of 7,36,500 Equity Shares of GENESIS IBRC INDIA LIMITED through a SPA (Off-Market). The total paid-up share capital of the company before the acquisition was Rs 13,00,00,000, comprising of 1,30,00,000 fully paid equity shares of Rs 10 each. Post-acquisition, the paid-up share capital remains the same.</p><ul><li>Ms. V Varalakshmi acquires 7,36,500 Equity Shares of GENESIS IBRC INDIA LIMITED through a SPA.</li><li>The total paid-up share capital of the company before the acquisition was Rs 13,00,00,000, comprising of 1,30,00,000 fully paid equity shares of Rs 10 each.</li><li>Post-acquisition, the paid-up share capital remains the same.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/42A39DFA_A8F6_42D9_95EF_8F3CDD933D71_103814.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Genesis Ibrc India Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>