<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 18:56:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SUMUKAAG] Sumuka Agro Industries Fixes Record Date for Gujjubhai Foods Merger</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sumuka+Agro+Industries+Ltd&title=Sumuka+Agro+Industries+Fixes+Record+Date+for+Gujjubhai+Foods+Merger&newsId=181d45db-1cac-4a62-8445-ab8b84299a11&token=MTgxZDQ1ZGItMWNh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">181d45db-1cac-4a62-8445-ab8b84299a11</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:51:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Merger</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Sumuka Agro Industries Ltd. has fixed Monday, March 9, 2026, as the record date for determining the shareholders of Gujjubhai Foods Private Limited who shall be entitled to receive fully paid-up equity shares of Sumuka Agro Industries as per the share exchange ratio set out in the Scheme of Merger. This follows the sanction of the merger by the National Company Law Tribunal, Mumbai Bench. The share exchange ratio is 7 (Seven) fully paid up equity shares of Sumuka Agro Industries for every 4 (Four) fully paid equity shares held by the shareholders of Gujjubhai Foods.</p><ul><li>Sumuka Agro Industries has fixed March 9, 2026, as the record date for the merger with Gujjubhai Foods</li><li>The merger is based on a share exchange ratio of 7:4</li><li>The merger has been sanctioned by the National Company Law Tribunal, Mumbai Bench</li><li>The record date is set for determining the shareholders of Gujjubhai Foods who shall be entitled to receive Sumuka Agro Industries shares</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/83e1f9ee-d168-48b4-b98c-747d2c76caec.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sumuka Agro Industries Ltd | Category: Merger</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUMUKAAG] Sumuka Agro Industries Ltd Announces Effective Date of Gujjubhai Foods Private Limited Merger</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sumuka+Agro+Industries+Ltd&title=Sumuka+Agro+Industries+Ltd+Announces+Effective+Date+of+Gujjubhai+Foods+Private+Limited+Merger&newsId=60e5d9b2-17bb-4cc7-8591-e7569d241146&token=NjBlNWQ5YjItMTdi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60e5d9b2-17bb-4cc7-8591-e7569d241146</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:37:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Merger</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Sumuka Agro Industries Ltd has announced the effective date of the scheme of merger by absorption of Gujjubhai Foods Private Limited. The merger, sanctioned by the National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT) on February 4, 2026, has been completed after fulfilling all conditions and filing the certified copy of the order with the Ministry of Corporate Affairs. The scheme has become effective from February 23, 2026, as per Regulation 30 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Sumuka Agro Industries Ltd announces the effective date of the merger with Gujjubhai Foods Private Limited.</li><li>The merger was sanctioned by the NCLT on February 4, 2026.</li><li>All conditions of the merger have been fulfilled and the certified copy of the order has been filed with the Ministry of Corporate Affairs.</li><li>The scheme of merger has become effective from February 23, 2026.</li><li>The announcement is in compliance with Regulation 30 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5e61f4f3-fee9-4204-869a-90e55a2a3c66.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sumuka Agro Industries Ltd | Category: Merger</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MOTHERSON] Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd Incorporates New Subsidiary - Motherson Energy Systems Naarangwadi Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Samvardhana+Motherson+International+Ltd&title=Samvardhana+Motherson+International+Ltd+Incorporates+New+Subsidiary+-+Motherson+Energy+Systems+Naarangwadi+Limited&newsId=a5efaa64-c445-4eb8-8266-ad63882943be&token=YTVlZmFhNjQtYzQ0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5efaa64-c445-4eb8-8266-ad63882943be</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Samvardhana Motherson International Limited has informed the exchange about the incorporation of its new indirect wholly owned subsidiary, Motherson Energy Systems Naarangwadi Limited (MESNL). MESNL, a wholly owned subsidiary of Motherson New Energy Limited (MNEL), was incorporated on February 24, 2026. MESNL will be engaged in the business of designing, developing, owning, and operating power, energy, and infrastructure projects primarily based on renewable sources for captive use by Motherson Group entities.</p><ul><li>Samvardhana Motherson International Limited has incorporated a new indirect wholly owned subsidiary, Motherson Energy Systems Naarangwadi Limited.</li><li>Motherson Energy Systems Naarangwadi Limited is a wholly owned subsidiary of Motherson New Energy Limited.</li><li>MESNL will be engaged in the business of designing, developing, owning, and operating power, energy, and infrastructure projects primarily based on renewable sources for captive use by Motherson Group entities.</li><li>The initial authorized share capital of MESNL is divided into 50,000 equity shares of Face Value of Rs. 10/- per share.</li><li>The entire share capital of MESNL is held by Motherson New Energy Limited and its nominees.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5a2167c7-2571-4361-a78c-b1f8f4b27616.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MOTHERSON] Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd Incorporates New Subsidiary - Motherson Energy Systems Bhend Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Samvardhana+Motherson+International+Ltd&title=Samvardhana+Motherson+International+Ltd+Incorporates+New+Subsidiary+-+Motherson+Energy+Systems+Bhend+Limited&newsId=247b1630-b874-4d35-9ede-d0a3615900d0&token=MjQ3YjE2MzAtYjg3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">247b1630-b874-4d35-9ede-d0a3615900d0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:21:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Samvardhana Motherson International Limited has informed the exchange about the incorporation of its indirect wholly owned subsidiary, Motherson Energy Systems Bhend Limited (MESBL). MESBL, incorporated on February 24, 2026, will be engaged in the business of designing, developing, owning, and operating power, energy, and infrastructure projects based on renewable sources for captive use by Motherson Group at Bhendwade, Maharashtra.</p><ul><li>Samvardhana Motherson International Limited has incorporated a new wholly owned subsidiary, Motherson Energy Systems Bhend Limited.</li><li>MESBL will be engaged in the business of renewable energy projects for captive use by Motherson Group.</li><li>The new subsidiary is incorporated in Bhendwade, Maharashtra.</li><li>The initial authorized share capital of MESBL is divided into 50,000 equity shares of Face Value of Rs. 10/- per share.</li><li>Motherson New Energy Limited, a wholly owned subsidiary of Samvardhana Motherson International Limited, holds the entire share capital of MESBL.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ea562d2b-365b-4d8e-a766-425d06a4b73b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Samvardhana Motherson International Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ENBETRD] Enbee Trade &amp; Finance Receives Approval for Rights Issue of Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ENBEE+TRADE+%26+FINANCE+LTD.&title=Enbee+Trade+%26+Finance+Receives+Approval+for+Rights+Issue+of+Equity+Shares&newsId=7d16d550-b7d1-4c14-aed5-49931cf4fc81&token=N2QxNmQ1NTAtYjdk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7d16d550-b7d1-4c14-aed5-49931cf4fc81</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Enbee Trade &amp; Finance Ltd has received in-principle approval from BSE Limited for the proposed Rights Issue of equity shares. The company had earlier informed about the approval process in October 2025. The Board of Directors will meet on 25th February 2026 to consider and approve the Issue Price, Rights Entitlement Ratio, Record Date, and other terms and conditions of the Rights Issue.</p><ul><li>Enbee Trade &amp; Finance Ltd has received in-principle approval from BSE Limited for the proposed Rights Issue of equity shares.</li><li>The company had earlier informed about the approval process in October 2025.</li><li>The Board of Directors will meet on 25th February 2026 to consider and approve the Issue Price, Rights Entitlement Ratio, Record Date, and other terms and conditions of the Rights Issue.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/83312584-edfc-406e-8067-8de0eb163c1b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ENBEE TRADE & FINANCE LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VIPIND] VIP Industries Ltd: Inspection/Search Proceedings Initiated by Maharashtra State Tax Authority</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=V.I.P.INDUSTRIES+LTD.-%24&title=VIP+Industries+Ltd%3A+Inspection%2FSearch+Proceedings+Initiated+by+Maharashtra+State+Tax+Authority&newsId=839cce79-92fa-4166-8da0-050aab85cfd6&token=ODM5Y2NlNzktOTJm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">839cce79-92fa-4166-8da0-050aab85cfd6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>VIP Industries Ltd. has notified that the Assistant Commissioner of State Tax, Maharashtra initiated inspection/search proceedings at the Company’s registered office and manufacturing unit situated in Nashik, Maharashtra on February 24, 2026. The company is cooperating fully with the authority. At present, there is no material impact on the financials, business operations or any other activities of the Company due to the aforesaid Inspection / Search proceedings. The company will make necessary disclosures in accordance with regulatory provisions if there is any material update.</p><ul><li>Inspection/search proceedings initiated by the Assistant Commissioner of State Tax, Maharashtra</li><li>VIP Industries Ltd. is fully cooperating with the authority</li><li>No material impact on the company&apos;s financials, business operations or any other activities as of now</li><li>Company will make necessary disclosures as required by regulations in case of any material updates</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7727a6d9-44dc-4546-a3cc-57de7c6449e5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: V.I.P.INDUSTRIES LTD.-$ | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[POWERGRID] CCEA Approves Enhanced Delegation to POWERGRID for Increased Equity Investment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=POWER+GRID+CORPORATION+OF+INDIA+LTD.&title=CCEA+Approves+Enhanced+Delegation+to+POWERGRID+for+Increased+Equity+Investment&newsId=8ed99127-7204-49e9-af1b-5fc433ba2bfa&token=OGVkOTkxMjctNzIw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ed99127-7204-49e9-af1b-5fc433ba2bfa</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:02:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>The Cabinet Committee on Economic Affairs (CCEA) has approved the enhanced delegation to POWERGRID under the extant guidelines of DPE on delegation of powers to Maharatna CPSEs. This approval enhances the permissible equity investment limit of POWERGRID from the current threshold of Rs. 5,000 Crore per subsidiary to Rs. 7,500 Crore per subsidiary, while retaining the existing cap of 15% of the Company’s net worth. This move will enable POWERGRID to expand its investment in its core business and support the evacuation of renewable energy capacity, helping achieve the target of 500 GW from non-fossil-based sources.</p><ul><li>CCEA approves enhanced delegation to POWERGRID under DPE guidelines</li><li>Equity investment limit increased from Rs. 5,000 Crore to Rs. 7,500 Crore per subsidiary</li><li>15% cap of the Company’s net worth remains unchanged</li><li>Approval will support the evacuation of renewable energy capacity</li><li>Will help achieve the target of 500 GW from non-fossil-based sources</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4f81056b-9355-4a55-80b9-e52d368e7211.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: POWER GRID CORPORATION OF INDIA LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[OLPCL] Olympic Cards Ltd Defaults on Rs. 15.17 Cr Term Loan from HDFC Bank</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=OLYMPIC+CARDS+LTD.&title=Olympic+Cards+Ltd+Defaults+on+Rs.+15.17+Cr+Term+Loan+from+HDFC+Bank&newsId=1ef29153-0698-4d4c-b23e-2d5c116e8573&token=MWVmMjkxNTMtMDY5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1ef29153-0698-4d4c-b23e-2d5c116e8573</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:54:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Olympic Cards Ltd, script code 334190, has defaulted on a Rs. 15.17 Cr term loan from HDFC Bank. The default occurred on 27th January 2026. The outstanding loan amount from HDFC Bank is Rs. 4.22 Cr. The company&apos;s total financial indebtedness, including short-term and long-term debt, stands at Rs. 12.23 Cr as of 30th September 2025.</p><ul><li>Olympic Cards Ltd has defaulted on a term loan from HDFC Bank.</li><li>The default amount is Rs. 15.17 Cr, with Rs. 12.04 Cr as principal and Rs. 3.13 Cr as interest.</li><li>The outstanding loan amount from HDFC Bank is Rs. 4.22 Cr.</li><li>The company&apos;s total financial indebtedness stands at Rs. 12.23 Cr as of 30th September 2025.</li><li>The default occurred on 27th January 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/95a4d101-b3ef-4e2e-9d24-4a802126f1b3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: OLYMPIC CARDS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[5PAISA] 5paisa Capital Ltd. to Raise Funds Through Rights Issue of Up to INR 4,750 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=5paisa+Capital+Ltd&title=5paisa+Capital+Ltd.+to+Raise+Funds+Through+Rights+Issue+of+Up+to+INR+4%2C750+Million&newsId=6cbc5232-bbbb-432b-a02d-fcdf4e878ee1&token=NmNiYzUyMzItYmJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6cbc5232-bbbb-432b-a02d-fcdf4e878ee1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:47:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>5paisa Capital Ltd. has announced a meeting of its Board of Directors on February 28, 2026, to consider and approve various matters related to raising funds through a rights issue. The company had previously approved the issuance of fully paid-up equity shares with a face value of INR 10 each, for an amount not exceeding INR 4,750.00 million (Rupees Four Thousand Seven Hundred and Fifty Million only). The meeting will discuss the specific terms of the issue, including the issue price, rights entitlement ratio, record date, timing of the issue, and other incidental matters.</p><ul><li>5paisa Capital Ltd. to raise funds through rights issue</li><li>Issue amount not exceeding INR 4,750.00 million</li><li>Board meeting scheduled on February 28, 2026, to discuss the issue terms</li><li>Compliance with SEBI Listing Regulations and Companies Act, 2013</li><li>Fully paid-up equity shares with a face value of INR 10 each</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f8dd01b3-a27a-4089-9d91-145c0ea6af71.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: 5paisa Capital Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GODREJAGRO] Godrej Agrovet Ltd Receives Notice from Income Tax Department Under Section 226(3) of Income Tax Act, 1961</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Godrej+Agrovet+Ltd&title=Godrej+Agrovet+Ltd+Receives+Notice+from+Income+Tax+Department+Under+Section+226%283%29+of+Income+Tax+Act%2C+1961&newsId=41a1b4b9-f603-44e2-b71a-de10ee71d4b1&token=NDFhMWI0YjktZjYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41a1b4b9-f603-44e2-b71a-de10ee71d4b1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 16:41:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Godrej Agrovet Limited has received a notice from the Income Tax Department under Section 226(3) of the Income Tax Act, 1961. The notice has been issued to HDFC Bank Limited for payment of Rs. 41,36,010/- on account of late payment interest, late filing levy and interest under Section 220(2) of the Income Tax Act, 1961. The Company has stated that there is no material impact on its financial operations or other activities due to the demand made via the notice. The Company is in the process of filing a correction statement with the Income Tax Authority.</p><ul><li>Godrej Agrovet Ltd. received a notice from the Income Tax Department under Section 226(3) of the Income Tax Act, 1961.</li><li>The notice has been issued to HDFC Bank Limited for payment of Rs. 41,36,010/- on account of late payment interest, late filing levy and interest under Section 220(2) of the Income Tax Act, 1961.</li><li>The Company has stated that there is no material impact on its financial operations or other activities due to the demand made via the notice.</li><li>The Company is in the process of filing a correction statement with the Income Tax Authority.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a6544706-d82f-42df-8753-132959939f13.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Godrej Agrovet Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>