<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 21:25:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[PTIL] Prabhat Technologies Board Meeting Rescheduled for Financial Results Approval</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Prabhat+Technologies+%28India%29+Ltd&title=Prabhat+Technologies+Board+Meeting+Rescheduled+for+Financial+Results+Approval&newsId=ff52fb38-dd45-4663-b010-959f76308963&token=ZmY1MmZiMzgtZGQ0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff52fb38-dd45-4663-b010-959f76308963</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 16:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Prabhat Technologies (India) Ltd has informed the BSE that the meeting of the Board of Directors, originally scheduled for February 16, 2026, has been rescheduled to February 18, 2026, due to unavoidable reasons. The meeting will consider and approve the Un-audited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in shares of the company will remain closed till 48 hours after the announcement of the Un-audited Financial Results, in accordance with the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015 and the Company&apos;s Code of Conduct for Prevention of Insider Trading.</p><ul><li>Prabhat Technologies Board Meeting rescheduled to February 18, 2026</li><li>Board to consider and approve Un-audited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Trading window to remain closed till 48 hours after the announcement of Un-audited Financial Results</li><li>Compliance with SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Adherence to the Company&apos;s Code of Conduct for Prevention of Insider Trading</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d0e1aaa9-a148-42b5-b327-40a3fc983791.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Prabhat Technologies (India) Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MAYUKH] Sattva Sukun Lifecare Reschedules Board Meeting to Approve Q3 Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Mayukh+Dealtrade+Ltd&title=Sattva+Sukun+Lifecare+Reschedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+Results&newsId=e6faca5b-7b31-4e8e-9bec-7a9587505b5c&token=ZTZmYWNhNWItN2Iz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e6faca5b-7b31-4e8e-9bec-7a9587505b5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 16:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sattva Sukun Lifecare Ltd. has rescheduled its Board Meeting to February 19, 2026, to consider and approve the Un-Audited Financial Results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The meeting was previously scheduled for February 16, 2026, but was rescheduled to enable the Company to finalize certain pending information and documents. The &apos;Trading Window&apos; for dealing in the shares of the Company will remain closed up to the expiry of 48 hours post the date of declaration of the Unaudited Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Sattva Sukun Lifecare reschedules Board Meeting to February 19, 2026</li><li>Rescheduling aimed at finalizing pending information and documents for Q3 results</li><li>Un-Audited Financial Results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, to be considered and approved</li><li>Trading Window for dealing in the shares of the Company to remain closed up to 48 hours post Q3 results declaration</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d97016c1-744a-4a82-812b-1416c49a1d30.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Mayukh Dealtrade Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADANIPORTS] Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone Ltd Incorporates 12 Subsidiaries in Singapore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADANI+PORTS+AND+SPECIAL+ECONOMIC+ZONE+LTD.&title=Adani+Ports+and+Special+Economic+Zone+Ltd+Incorporates+12+Subsidiaries+in+Singapore&newsId=a9007701-28cd-4036-bb30-f1f72a320742&token=YTkwMDc3MDEtMjhj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a9007701-28cd-4036-bb30-f1f72a320742</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 16:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone Ltd, a leading port infrastructure company, has announced the incorporation of 12 new subsidiaries in Singapore by its step-down subsidiary, The Adani Harbour International DMCC. The new subsidiaries, named B316 Pte. Ltd., TP16 Pte. Ltd., TP27 Pte. Ltd., TP28 Pte. Ltd., TP29 Pte. Ltd., TP30 Pte. Ltd., TP31 Pte. Ltd., TP32 Pte. Ltd., TP33 Pte. Ltd., TP34 Pte. Ltd., TP35 Pte. Ltd., and TP36 Pte. Ltd., were incorporated on 16th February, 2026. Each subsidiary has an authorized and paid-up share capital of 50,000 shares of SGD 1 each and a turnover of nil, as they are yet to commence business operations. The acquisition does not fall under related party transactions and the subsidiaries operate in the Marine / Harbour sector. Astro Worldwide Investment Limited, BVI, a wholly owned subsidiary of Sunrise Worldwide Enterprise Limited, BVI, holds 100% shares of each subsidiary.</p><ul><li>Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone Ltd incorporates 12 new subsidiaries in Singapore</li><li>Subsidiaries incorporated by The Adani Harbour International DMCC, a step-down subsidiary of the company</li><li>Each subsidiary has an authorized and paid-up share capital of 50,000 shares of SGD 1 each</li><li>Subsidiaries operate in the Marine / Harbour sector</li><li>Astro Worldwide Investment Limited, BVI holds 100% shares of each subsidiary</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/31bb46f8-0474-454b-aba3-c45263e5f234.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADANI PORTS AND SPECIAL ECONOMIC ZONE LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BLAL] Re-appointment of Shri Anil Jerath as Non-Executive Director on BEML Land Assets Ltd Board</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BEML+Land+Assets+Ltd&title=Re-appointment+of+Shri+Anil+Jerath+as+Non-Executive+Director+on+BEML+Land+Assets+Ltd+Board&newsId=e9a0bf5b-3c26-424d-a9a1-1f6061d1339c&token=ZTlhMGJmNWItM2My</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9a0bf5b-3c26-424d-a9a1-1f6061d1339c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 16:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>BEML Land Assets Ltd (BLAL) has announced the re-appointment of Shri Anil Jerath as a Non-Executive Director on its Board. The President of India (Ministry of Defence) has extended Jerath&apos;s tenure from 01.02.2026 to 31.08.2026, i.e., up to the date of his superannuation from the services of BEML Ltd. Jerath is a Cost &amp; Management Accountant from the Institute of Cost Accountants of India with 35 years of experience in Government, Public &amp; Private Sectors. He has been appointed as a Director on the Board of the Company w.e.f. 01.02.2024 and is also a Director (Finance) on the Board of M/s BEML LIMITED. He does not have any inter-se relationship among the Directors of the Company.</p><ul><li>Re-appointment of Shri Anil Jerath as Non-Executive Director on BEML Land Assets Ltd Board</li><li>Tenure extension from 01.02.2026 to 31.08.2026</li><li>Jerath is a Cost &amp; Management Accountant with 35 years of experience</li><li>Also a Director (Finance) on the Board of M/s BEML LIMITED</li><li>No inter-se relationship among the Directors of the Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b7b018d3-3582-4abc-bb72-de283abdde18.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BEML Land Assets Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WMINIMT] Western Ministil Ltd Allots 40 Lakhs Equity Shares &amp; 63.74 Lakhs Convertible Warrants</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=WESTERN+MINISTIL+LTD.&title=Western+Ministil+Ltd+Allots+40+Lakhs+Equity+Shares+%26+63.74+Lakhs+Convertible+Warrants&newsId=b378361b-6a84-43af-83b9-427832fc20b9&token=YjM3ODM2MWItNmE4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b378361b-6a84-43af-83b9-427832fc20b9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 16:20:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>On Monday, February 16, 2026, the Board of Directors of Western Ministil Limited held a meeting at the registered office and approved the allotment of 40,00,000 Equity Shares of face value =10/- each at an issue price of =10/- per Equity Share and 63,74,252 Convertible Warrants on a preferential basis. The allottees include Kalpesh Naginbhai Patel, Vandana Patel, Abhishek Kumar Upadhyay, Bansraj Gond, Mrityunjay Kumar Rai, Brand Avenue Media Private Limited, Himanshu Shah, Vijay Valjibhai Thakkar, Sheetal Jethaji Solanki, Vreha Nehal Choksi, Jash Vijay Thakkar, and Dinesh Muddu Kotian. The meeting commenced at 07.00 pm and concluded at 08.00 pm.</p><ul><li>Western Ministil Ltd allotted 40,00,000 Equity Shares and 63,74,252 Convertible Warrants on a preferential basis.</li><li>The allottees include Kalpesh Naginbhai Patel, Vandana Patel, Abhishek Kumar Upadhyay, Bansraj Gond, Mrityunjay Kumar Rai, Brand Avenue Media Private Limited, Himanshu Shah, Vijay Valjibhai Thakkar, Sheetal Jethaji Solanki, Vreha Nehal Choksi, Jash Vijay Thakkar, and Dinesh Muddu Kotian.</li><li>The preferential allotment was approved at the Board of Directors meeting held on February 16, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8fb8c6a7-a3eb-4170-8bae-103b707e5d13.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: WESTERN MINISTIL LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CANDOUR] Candour Techtex Ltd Approves Preferential Allotment of Equity Shares and Warrants</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Candour+Techtex+Ltd&title=Candour+Techtex+Ltd+Approves+Preferential+Allotment+of+Equity+Shares+and+Warrants&newsId=74336860-8f86-40f3-99fa-65090c50426f&token=NzQzMzY4NjAtOGY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74336860-8f86-40f3-99fa-65090c50426f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 16:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Candour Techtex Ltd has approved the allotment of 52,54,700 equity shares and 79,72,600 warrants on a preferential basis. The equity shares are priced at Rs. 125/- each (including a premium of Rs. 115/-) and the warrants are convertible into equity shares at the same price within 18 months from the date of allotment. However, the issuance of 12,60,000 equity shares and 10,99,400 warrants has been cancelled due to non-receipt of allotment money.</p><ul><li>Candour Techtex Ltd approves preferential allotment of equity shares and warrants.</li><li>52,54,700 equity shares priced at Rs. 125/- each (including a premium of Rs. 115/-) allotted.</li><li>79,72,600 warrants convertible into equity shares at Rs. 125/- each allotted.</li><li>12,60,000 equity shares and 10,99,400 warrants issuance cancelled due to non-receipt of allotment money.</li><li>The company has received 25% of the warrant issue price from the allottee.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ae3c5b3d-3134-4241-88f0-88ff4e93aeaf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Candour Techtex Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WMINIMT] Western Ministil Ltd Allots 40 Lakhs Equity Shares and 63.74 Lakhs Convertible Warrants on Preferential Basis</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=WESTERN+MINISTIL+LTD.&title=Western+Ministil+Ltd+Allots+40+Lakhs+Equity+Shares+and+63.74+Lakhs+Convertible+Warrants+on+Preferential+Basis&newsId=83231aab-f066-48c2-bae1-5e7a39fc9499&token=ODMyMzFhYWItZjA2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">83231aab-f066-48c2-bae1-5e7a39fc9499</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 16:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>On Monday, February 16, 2026, the Board of Directors of Western Ministil Limited held a meeting at the registered office of the company. During the meeting, the board considered and approved the allotment of 40,00,000 (Forty Lakhs) Equity Shares of face value of =10/- each at an issue price of =10/- (Rupees Ten Only) per Equity Share and 63,74,252 (Sixty Three Lakhs Seventy Four Thousand Two Hundred Fifty Two) Convertible Warrants on a preferential basis. This decision was made in accordance with a special resolution passed by the Members of the Company at their Extra-ordinary General Meeting held on December 24, 2025 and In-Principle Approval received from BSE Ltd on February 02, 2026. The list of allottees includes Kalpesh Naginbhai Patel, Vandana Patel, Abhishek Kumar Upadhyay, Bansraj Gond, Mrityunjay Kumar Rai, Brand Avenue Media Private Limited, Himanshu Shah, Vijay Valjibhai Thakkar, Sheetal Jethaji Solanki, Vreha Nehal Choksi, Jash Vijay Thakkar, and Dinesh Muddu Kotian.</p><ul><li>Western Ministil Ltd board approves allotment of 40 Lakhs Equity Shares and 63.74 Lakhs Convertible Warrants on a preferential basis.</li><li>The allotment is in accordance with a special resolution passed by the Members of the Company and In-Principle Approval from BSE Ltd.</li><li>Kalpesh Naginbhai Patel is allotted the highest number of Equity Shares and Convertible Warrants.</li><li>Brand Avenue Media Private Limited is one of the allottees.</li><li>The list of allottees also includes Himanshu Shah and Vijay Valjibhai Thakkar.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e4eda873-3e5b-45c2-83d4-4e5f54a4b641.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: WESTERN MINISTIL LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SURJIND] Suraj Industries&apos; Shareholding in Shri Gang Industries Increases to 19.31%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SURAJ+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Suraj+Industries%27+Shareholding+in+Shri+Gang+Industries+Increases+to+19.31%25&newsId=54c327b1-c58c-4228-874a-37fed479f61a&token=NTRjMzI3YjEtYzU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54c327b1-c58c-4228-874a-37fed479f61a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 16:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pursuant to the conversion of 7,00,000 (Seven Lakh) 0.01% Compulsorily Convertible Preference Shares (CCPS) of face value =10/- each at a conversion price of Rs.99/- per equity share, Suraj Industries Limited&apos;s shareholding in Shri Gang Industries and Allied Products Limited has increased to 19.31% of the increased paid-up equity share capital of Shri Gang. The paid-up equity share capital of Shri Gang stands increased to Rs.19,73,00,000/- (Rupees Nineteen Crore Seventy-Three Lakh only), comprising 1,97,30,000 (One Crore Ninety-Seven Lakh Thirty Thousand) Equity Shares of face value =10/- each.</p><ul><li>Suraj Industries&apos; shareholding in Shri Gang Industries has increased to 19.31%</li><li>Shri Gang Industries has allotted 7,00,000 (Seven Lakh) Equity Shares of face value =10/- each</li><li>The conversion was done at a price of Rs.99/- per equity share</li><li>Shri Gang Industries&apos; paid-up equity share capital stands increased to Rs.19,73,00,000/-</li><li>The increase in paid-up equity share capital comprises 1,97,30,000 (One Crore Ninety-Seven Lakh Thirty Thousand) Equity Shares of face value =10/- each</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/801ecac5-1bcb-42d7-90df-f2e65486330d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SURAJ INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CINERAD] GTT Data Solutions Ltd EGM Held on 12 February 2026: Key Resolutions Passed</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CINERAD+COMMUNICATIONS+LTD.&title=GTT+Data+Solutions+Ltd+EGM+Held+on+12+February+2026%3A+Key+Resolutions+Passed&newsId=88d298fa-ccde-4899-a80f-d90fdf58c06e&token=ODhkMjk4ZmEtY2Nk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88d298fa-ccde-4899-a80f-d90fdf58c06e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 16:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>GTT Data Solutions Ltd held its Extraordinary General Meeting (EGM) on 12 February 2026. The meeting was conducted from 09:00 AM to 09:35 AM. The Scrutinizer for the meeting was MIHEN HALANI from M/s. Mihen Halani &amp; Associates. There were a total of 5294 shareholders on the record date. The meeting was attended by 48 shareholders, including 6 promoters and 42 public shareholders. 8 resolutions were passed during the meeting. The key resolution passed was to increase the Authorised Share Capital of the Company and make consequent alteration in Clause V of the Memorandum of Association. The promoters and promoter group held 26,000,949 shares, and they voted 100.0001% in favour of the resolution. The public shareholders held 15,768,294 shares and they voted 100.0001% in favour of the resolution. The resolution was passed with 99.9999% of the votes in favour.</p><ul><li>GTT Data Solutions Ltd held its EGM on 12 February 2026</li><li>The meeting was conducted from 09:00 AM to 09:35 AM</li><li>8 resolutions were passed during the meeting</li><li>Key resolution passed: Increase in Authorised Share Capital and alteration in Clause V of the Memorandum of Association</li><li>Promoters and promoter group voted 100.0001% in favour of the resolution</li><li>Public shareholders voted 100.0001% in favour of the resolution</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1ccc8a69-1fcb-4bb7-b1a0-792aab5f200c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CINERAD COMMUNICATIONS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SKP] Shri Krishna Prasadam Ltd Announces Financial Results for Quarter and Nine Months Ended December 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shri+Krishna+Prasadam+Ltd&title=Shri+Krishna+Prasadam+Ltd+Announces+Financial+Results+for+Quarter+and+Nine+Months+Ended+December+2025&newsId=a310be3d-da82-44e5-bea4-e2b80f8a9d68&token=YTMxMGJlM2QtZGE4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a310be3d-da82-44e5-bea4-e2b80f8a9d68</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:55:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shri Krishna Prasadam Ltd has announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The results were reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors. The Statutory Auditors have conducted a limited review on these results. The company operates under one segment and has incorporated a wholly-owned subsidiary named &apos;Avro Recycling Limited&apos; during the nine months ended December 31, 2025.</p><ul><li>Financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025 announced</li><li>Results reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors</li><li>Limited review conducted by the Statutory Auditors</li><li>Company operates under one segment</li><li>Incorporated a wholly-owned subsidiary named &apos;Avro Recycling Limited&apos;</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b71dab5b-d456-4e9f-9473-84207fc5c07c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shri Krishna Prasadam Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>