<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:50:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[NBCC] NBCC (India) Ltd Secures Rs. 76.27 Cr. Contract for Dharanidhar University Infrastructure Development</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NBCC+%28India%29+Ltd&title=NBCC+%28India%29+Ltd+Secures+Rs.+76.27+Cr.+Contract+for+Dharanidhar+University+Infrastructure+Development&newsId=931ddb6b-f715-4ae1-acdc-54bcb2dae631&token=OTMxZGRiNmItZjcx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">931ddb6b-f715-4ae1-acdc-54bcb2dae631</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:47:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>NBCC (India) Limited has been awarded a contract worth approximately Rs. 76.27 Crores for the construction of academic and hostel buildings, as well as other infrastructure facilities, including external development works for Dharanidhar University in Keonjhar, Odisha. The contract is part of the company&apos;s normal course of business and is not a related party transaction.</p><ul><li>NBCC (India) Ltd has been awarded a contract worth approximately Rs. 76.27 Crores for Dharanidhar University infrastructure development.</li><li>The project includes the construction of academic and hostel buildings, as well as other infrastructure facilities and external development works.</li><li>The contract is part of the company&apos;s normal course of business and is not a related party transaction.</li><li>The project is located in Keonjhar, Odisha.</li><li>The contract value is approximately Rs. 76.27 Crores.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/04c6a774-3cf7-48ae-94b2-802707dbf8fb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NBCC (India) Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CONCOR] CONCOR Signs MoU with Vizhinjam International Seaport Ltd to Develop Strategic Logistics Collaboration</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CONTAINER+CORPORATION+OF+INDIA+LTD.&title=CONCOR+Signs+MoU+with+Vizhinjam+International+Seaport+Ltd+to+Develop+Strategic+Logistics+Collaboration&newsId=f0f19034-f789-4c3f-8e91-31bdad379dd5&token=ZjBmMTkwMzQtZjc4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0f19034-f789-4c3f-8e91-31bdad379dd5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>MoU</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Container Corporation of India Ltd. (CONCOR) and Vizhinjam International Seaport Ltd. (VISL), a Government of Kerala undertaking, have signed a non-binding and non-exclusive Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) on 23 February 2026 at Thiruvananthapuram. The MoU is for the development of a Container Freight Station (CFS) in the vicinity of Vizhinjam International Seaport, Thiruvananthapuram, Kerala. The CFS is expected to have facilities such as Customs-bonded area, warehouse, Container handling and storage yards, Import-export cargo handling facilities, Weighbridges and other related facilities for seamless end-to-end services to the customers. This strategic collaboration is expected to support the development of an integrated logistics ecosystem contributing to regional and national economic growth.</p><ul><li>CONCOR and VISL sign a non-binding and non-exclusive MoU for the development of a Container Freight Station (CFS)</li><li>The CFS is expected to have facilities such as Customs-bonded area, warehouse, Container handling and storage yards, Import-export cargo handling facilities, Weighbridges and other related facilities</li><li>The collaboration is expected to support the development of an integrated logistics ecosystem contributing to regional and national economic growth</li><li>The partnership is envisioned as a gateway for global maritime trade</li><li>The MoU signing reflects CONCOR’s commitment to providing seamless, rail-led multimodal logistics solutions and expanding logistics infrastructure</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2212b822-5e74-42ab-80f5-c5cfe9e9595d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CONTAINER CORPORATION OF INDIA LTD. | Category: MoU</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WAAREEENER] Waaree and ZFI Sign Electrolyzer as a Service Agreement for 2.5 MW Electrolyzer for ZFI’s GH2 Expansion Project in Uttar Pradesh</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Waaree+Energies+Ltd&title=Waaree+and+ZFI+Sign+Electrolyzer+as+a+Service+Agreement+for+2.5+MW+Electrolyzer+for+ZFI%E2%80%99s+GH2+Expansion+Project+in+Uttar+Pradesh&newsId=c5ad2255-ef34-4a71-99f4-145ae376b92f&token=YzVhZDIyNTUtZWYz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5ad2255-ef34-4a71-99f4-145ae376b92f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:40:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Zero Footprint Industries Ltd (ZFI) and Waaree Clean Energy Solutions Private Limited, a wholly owned subsidiary of Waaree Energies Limited, have signed an Electrolyzer as a Service (EAAS) Agreement for a 2.5 MW Alkaline Electrolyzer for ZFI’s planned capacity addition for Green Hydrogen in Uttar Pradesh. The agreement also includes a Strategic MoU to supply 50 MW of electrolyzers through EAAS route for ZFI’s multiple decentralised small green hydrogen projects across Northern India. The project aims to produce ~41 lac Nm3 of green hydrogen and ~20 lac Nm3 of green oxygen annually, primarily for ZFI’s existing customers across mentha oil, chemical, steel and pharma industries. The project is supported by Uttar Pradesh New &amp; Renewable Development Agency (UPNEDA) under its Green Hydrogen Policy 2024 and aligns with 5 MMTPA GH2 production target as envisaged under India’s National Green Hydrogen Mission.</p><ul><li>Signing of EAAS Agreement for 2.5 MW Alkaline Electrolyzer for ZFI’s GH2 Expansion Project in Uttar Pradesh</li><li>Strategic MoU to supply 50 MW of electrolyzers through EAAS route for ZFI’s multiple decentralised small green hydrogen projects across Northern India</li><li>Production of ~41 lac Nm3 of green hydrogen and ~20 lac Nm3 of green oxygen annually</li><li>Supported by Uttar Pradesh New &amp; Renewable Development Agency (UPNEDA) under its Green Hydrogen Policy 2024</li><li>Alignment with 5 MMTPA GH2 production target as envisaged under India’s National Green Hydrogen Mission</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ac6e1cd0-51e7-44f5-8931-8116298d39ea.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Waaree Energies Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASHAPURMIN] Chetan Navnitlal Shah Acquires 85,000 Shares in Ashapura Minechem Ltd via Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ASHAPURA+MINECHEM+LTD.&title=Chetan+Navnitlal+Shah+Acquires+85%2C000+Shares+in+Ashapura+Minechem+Ltd+via+Open+Market&newsId=90db1a0e-52b8-4f2b-b7ab-b62d249ff5ea&token=OTBkYjFhMGUtNTJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90db1a0e-52b8-4f2b-b7ab-b62d249ff5ea</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>According to a disclosure made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011, Chetan Navnitlal Shah has acquired 85,000 equity shares in Ashapura Minechem Ltd. The acquisition took place in the open market on 20th February, 2026. Before the acquisition, Chetan Navnitlal Shah held 14.37% shares in the company. Post-acquisition, his holding increased to 14.46%.</p><ul><li>Chetan Navnitlal Shah acquires 85,000 shares in Ashapura Minechem Ltd</li><li>The acquisition took place in the open market</li><li>The shares were acquired on 20th February, 2026</li><li>Pre-acquisition, Chetan Navnitlal Shah held 14.37% shares in the company</li><li>Post-acquisition, his holding increased to 14.46%</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7982BCEF_87DD_4F6F_B870_C056362D8161_145109.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ASHAPURA MINECHEM LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ROSSELLIND] Promoter Harsh Mohan Gupta Transfers Shares to Daughter Samara Gupta via Off-market Inter-se Transfer in Rossell India Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ROSSELL+INDIA+LTD.&title=Promoter+Harsh+Mohan+Gupta+Transfers+Shares+to+Daughter+Samara+Gupta+via+Off-market+Inter-se+Transfer+in+Rossell+India+Ltd&newsId=b713a825-3775-4d00-bf53-18c721be1072&token=YjcxM2E4MjUtMzc3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b713a825-3775-4d00-bf53-18c721be1072</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:28:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Harsh Mohan Gupta, a promoter of Rossell India Limited, has transferred 35,79,170 equity shares of the company to his daughter, Ms. Samara Gupta, through an off-market inter-se transfer by way of gift on 20th February 2026. This transfer represents 9.49% of the total voting capital of the company. The shares were transferred from Harsh Mohan Gupta&apos;s holding to Samara Gupta&apos;s holding, diluting the total voting capital of the company to 30.00%. The equity share capital and total voting capital of the company remain unchanged at Rs.7,53,92,950 (3,76,96,475 shares of Rs. 2 each) before and after the transfer.</p><ul><li>Harsh Mohan Gupta, a promoter of Rossell India Ltd, transfers shares to his daughter, Ms. Samara Gupta.</li><li>The transfer represents 9.49% of the total voting capital of the company.</li><li>The transfer took place through an off-market inter-se transfer by way of gift.</li><li>The transfer diluted the total voting capital of the company to 30.00%.</li><li>The equity share capital and total voting capital of the company remain unchanged.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3095B8D1_C198_4443_A9F5_A99DBE5C6A7D_144456.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ROSSELL INDIA LTD. | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ESABINDIA] Nippon India Mutual Fund Acquires 2.67% Stake in Esab India Ltd Through Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ESAB+INDIA+LTD.&title=Nippon+India+Mutual+Fund+Acquires+2.67%25+Stake+in+Esab+India+Ltd+Through+Open+Market&newsId=7113bedd-0f6d-4761-a33e-91537719ba85&token=NzExM2JlZGQtMGY2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7113bedd-0f6d-4761-a33e-91537719ba85</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:27:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Nippon India Mutual Fund has acquired 2.67% stake in Esab India Ltd through the open market. The acquisition was made between October 16, 2020 and February 19, 2026. The total equity share capital and total voting capital of the company remains the same at Rs 15,39,30,200/- before and after the acquisition. The shares were acquired on behalf of Nippon India Mutual Fund through Nippon Life India Trustee Limited A/c. The disclosure was made under Regulation 29(1) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</p><ul><li>Nippon India Mutual Fund acquires 2.67% stake in Esab India Ltd</li><li>Acquisition made through open market</li><li>Acquisition period: From October 16, 2020 to February 19, 2026</li><li>Esab India Ltd&apos;s equity share capital and total voting capital remains the same at Rs 15,39,30,200/-</li><li>Disclosure made under Regulation 29(1) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/92500C17_0633_49A5_89FC_097965AFB23E_145605.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ESAB INDIA LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PATINTLOG] Asgar Patel &amp; Others Acquire 20,000 Shares in Patel Integrated Logistics Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PATEL+INTEGRATED+LOGISTICS+LTD.-%24&title=Asgar+Patel+%26+Others+Acquire+20%2C000+Shares+in+Patel+Integrated+Logistics+Limited&newsId=14f2e40a-ac24-4aa8-b46d-7a0d23c89ba9&token=MTRmMmU0MGEtYWMy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">14f2e40a-ac24-4aa8-b46d-7a0d23c89ba9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:24:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>According to a disclosure received under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeover) Regulations, 2011, Mr. Asgar Shakoor Patel, along with other promoters and promoter groups of Patel Integrated Logistics Limited, have acquired 20,000 equity shares of the company. This acquisition is part of a larger holding of 2,50,17,880 equity shares, which represents 35.95% of the total share and voting capital of the company.</p><ul><li>Asgar Patel and others acquire 20,000 shares in Patel Integrated Logistics Limited</li><li>This acquisition is part of a larger holding of 2,50,17,880 equity shares, representing 35.95% of the total share and voting capital of the company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/DF5F5638_0577_4427_9B76_C9CC7A239C2A_145231.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PATEL INTEGRATED LOGISTICS LTD.-$ | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BINNYMILLS] Binny Mills Ltd. to Consider Allotment of ISIN and Admission in NSDL at Board Meeting on Feb 24, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BINNY+MILLS+LTD.&title=Binny+Mills+Ltd.+to+Consider+Allotment+of+ISIN+and+Admission+in+NSDL+at+Board+Meeting+on+Feb+24%2C+2026&newsId=fd4d199c-3fc9-4aa3-bfac-e6611f4d15b5&token=ZmQ0ZDE5OWMtM2Zj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd4d199c-3fc9-4aa3-bfac-e6611f4d15b5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:22:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Binny Mills Ltd. has informed the BSE about a scheduled Board Meeting on 24/02/2026. The meeting, to be held through video conferencing, will consider and approve the allotment of ISIN and admission of the company&apos;s securities in the National Securities Depository Limited (NSDL) with the appointment of a Registrar and Transfer Agent (RTA) for Dematerialization. Other agenda items are also planned for the meeting.</p><ul><li>Binny Mills Ltd. scheduled Board Meeting on 24/02/2026</li><li>Meeting to consider and approve allotment of ISIN and admission in NSDL</li><li>Appointment of RTA for Dematerialization</li><li>Meeting to be held through video conferencing</li><li>Other agenda items planned for the meeting</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5369db1e-2b59-46fe-a103-962aca6ccb1b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BINNY MILLS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ROSSELLIND] Promoter Samara Gupta Acquires 9.54% Stake in Rossell India Ltd Through Gift from Father</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ROSSELL+INDIA+LTD.&title=Promoter+Samara+Gupta+Acquires+9.54%25+Stake+in+Rossell+India+Ltd+Through+Gift+from+Father&newsId=3ea64656-4c33-4383-9ac4-da4798dce3b8&token=M2VhNjQ2NTYtNGMz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ea64656-4c33-4383-9ac4-da4798dce3b8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Samara Gupta, a promoter of Rossell India Ltd, has acquired 35,79,170 equity shares of the company through an off-market inter-se transfer by way of gift from her father, Mr. Harsh Mohan Gupta, who is also a promoter of the company. The transaction took place on 20th February, 2026. This acquisition results in Samara Gupta holding 9.54% of the diluted share capital of Rossell India Ltd.</p><ul><li>Samara Gupta, a promoter of Rossell India Ltd, acquires 9.54% stake in the company.</li><li>The acquisition was made through an off-market inter-se transfer by way of gift from her father, Mr. Harsh Mohan Gupta.</li><li>The transaction took place on 20th February, 2026.</li><li>Mr. Harsh Mohan Gupta is also a promoter of Rossell India Ltd.</li><li>The acquisition results in Samara Gupta holding 9.54% of the diluted share capital of Rossell India Ltd.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1DCAF2CF_1D7B_49F9_8E58_62AD52782523_144920.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ROSSELL INDIA LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JASH] Rahul Patel Acquires 10,000 Shares of Jash Engineering Ltd via Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jash+Engineering+Ltd&title=Rahul+Patel+Acquires+10%2C000+Shares+of+Jash+Engineering+Ltd+via+Open+Market&newsId=ac8b7d74-28bc-4a2c-8799-ffe5dfcc8b5a&token=YWM4YjdkNzQtMjhi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac8b7d74-28bc-4a2c-8799-ffe5dfcc8b5a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 09:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rahul Patel, a member of the Promoter Group of Jash Engineering Limited, has disclosed the acquisition of 10,000 equity shares of the company under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. The acquisition was made via the open market. Before the acquisition, Rahul Patel held 3,57,08 shares, and after the acquisition, his holding increased to 3,67,08 shares, which is 0.58% of the total voting capital of the company.</p><ul><li>Rahul Patel, a member of the Promoter Group, acquires 10,000 shares of Jash Engineering Ltd</li><li>The acquisition was made via the open market</li><li>Before the acquisition, Rahul Patel held 3,57,08 shares</li><li>After the acquisition, his holding increased to 3,67,08 shares, which is 0.58% of the total voting capital of the company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3059C06A_62B1_42F4_9B6A_ACA5D4E4E0C7_144555.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jash Engineering Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>