<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 01:17:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[NIITMTS] NIIT Subsidiary Acquires 100% Stake in SweetRush Inc. for Up to USD 26 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NIIT+Learning+Systems+Ltd&title=NIIT+Subsidiary+Acquires+100%25+Stake+in+SweetRush+Inc.+for+Up+to+USD+26+Million&newsId=cc48a3e6-3290-45b0-93eb-b2d024daa32c&token=Y2M0OGEzZTYtMzI5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cc48a3e6-3290-45b0-93eb-b2d024daa32c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>NIIT Learning Systems Limited announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, NIIT (USA) Inc., has acquired 100% equity stake in SweetRush Inc., a leader in strategic training interventions and high-end custom learning solutions. The acquisition, completed for up to USD 26 million including earnout amount payable over the next five years, is part of NIIT&apos;s growth strategy to build new capabilities, expand geographically, and penetrate attractive customer segments. SweetRush, founded in 2001 and headquartered in San Francisco, USA, has an estimated consolidated turnover of USD 22.4 million for the financial year ended December 31, 2025. The acquisition brings together SweetRush&apos;s custom, AI-enabled, human-centered learning experience design with NIIT&apos;s global managed learning scale, offering an expanded services portfolio and the opportunity to convert project-based relationships into longer-duration managed learning engagements.</p><ul><li>NIIT (USA) Inc. acquires 100% equity stake in SweetRush Inc.</li><li>Transaction value up to USD 26 million including earnout amount.</li><li>Acquisition supports NIIT&apos;s growth strategy through building new capabilities and geographic expansion.</li><li>SweetRush is a leader in strategic training interventions and high-end custom learning solutions.</li><li>Estimated consolidated turnover of SweetRush for FY 2023-2025 is USD 22.4 million.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9dabf2db-ea33-405e-b8c6-5f5812b2c352.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NIIT Learning Systems Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LEMONTREE] Lemon Tree Hotels Announces Composite Scheme of Arrangement Involving Amalgamation and Demerger</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Lemon+Tree+Hotels+Ltd&title=Lemon+Tree+Hotels+Announces+Composite+Scheme+of+Arrangement+Involving+Amalgamation+and+Demerger&newsId=3edad060-b29b-44e7-9f87-c7b8554dcf03&token=M2VkYWQwNjAtYjI5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3edad060-b29b-44e7-9f87-c7b8554dcf03</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Lemon Tree Hotels Limited has approved a Composite Scheme of Arrangement involving the amalgamation of five wholly owned subsidiaries into the company and Fleur Hotels Limited, and the demerger of its hotel ownership and development undertaking to Fleur Hotels Limited. The scheme is subject to various approvals and conditions.</p><ul><li>Lemon Tree Hotels to amalgamate five wholly owned subsidiaries into the company and Fleur Hotels Limited.</li><li>The company&apos;s hotel ownership and development undertaking will be demerged to Fleur Hotels Limited.</li><li>The scheme is subject to various approvals and conditions.</li><li>The transactions are done at an arm&apos;s length basis.</li><li>Lemon Tree Hotels presently holds 58.91% of the equity share capital of the Transferee Company.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e58fd895-3bcb-40d6-bb4a-0ce4e90324c1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Lemon Tree Hotels Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LEMONTREE] Lemon Tree Hotels Announces Strategic Reorganization and INR 960 Crore Investment from Warburg Pincus in Fleur Hotels</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Lemon+Tree+Hotels+Ltd&title=Lemon+Tree+Hotels+Announces+Strategic+Reorganization+and+INR+960+Crore+Investment+from+Warburg+Pincus+in+Fleur+Hotels&newsId=e1dd39ef-bf42-4ff4-8b59-df8d938f6247&token=ZTFkZDM5ZWYtYmY0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e1dd39ef-bf42-4ff4-8b59-df8d938f6247</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:02:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Lemon Tree Hotels Limited and Fleur Hotels Limited have approved a Composite Scheme of Arrangement to simplify the group structure, enhance strategic focus, and unlock long-term value for shareholders. The reorganization will create two distinct platforms: Lemon Tree Hotels Limited as a pure-play, asset-light hotel management and brand platform, and Fleur Hotels Limited as a large-scale growth-oriented hotel ownership platform. Warburg Pincus will acquire APG’s entire 41.09% stake in Fleur and commit to invest up to INR 960 crore to support Fleur’s growth. The transaction is subject to customary regulatory and shareholder approvals.</p><ul><li>Lemon Tree Hotels and Fleur Hotels approve a Composite Scheme of Arrangement to reorganize the group structure</li><li>Creation of two distinct platforms: Lemon Tree Hotels as a pure-play, asset-light hotel management platform, and Fleur Hotels as a large-scale growth-oriented hotel ownership platform</li><li>Warburg Pincus to acquire APG’s entire 41.09% stake in Fleur and invest up to INR 960 crore in Fleur</li><li>The transaction is subject to customary regulatory and shareholder approvals</li><li>The reorganization aims to unlock long-term value for shareholders and enhance strategic focus</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2474b946-d56e-4bd0-a6bd-ddf3aa7b78ff.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Lemon Tree Hotels Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NIITMTS] NIIT Learning Systems Ltd acquires SweetRush, Inc. to expand near-shore delivery capability in the Americas for USD 26 million</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NIIT+Learning+Systems+Ltd&title=NIIT+Learning+Systems+Ltd+acquires+SweetRush%2C+Inc.+to+expand+near-shore+delivery+capability+in+the+Americas+for+USD+26+million&newsId=47314d12-356d-4c52-80ae-8df5b8d515b4&token=NDczMTRkMTItMzU2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47314d12-356d-4c52-80ae-8df5b8d515b4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>NIIT Learning Systems Limited (NIIT MTS) has acquired 100% of SweetRush, Inc. for an aggregate consideration of up to USD 26 million. The acquisition includes annual performance-based earnouts over the next five years and is completed through NIIT (USA), Inc., a wholly-owned subsidiary of NIIT MTS. SweetRush, founded in 2001, operates with over 100 team members and an extended pool of industry experts across the United States and Costa Rica. The acquisition aims to expand NIIT&apos;s global managed learning scale and offer an expanded services portfolio, including strategic learning interventions, certification solutions, and talent solutions. The union is expected to drive wallet share expansion across enterprise, association, and not-for-profit client segments and convert project-based relationships into longer-duration, annuity-like managed learning engagements.</p><ul><li>NIIT Learning Systems Limited (NIIT MTS) acquires SweetRush, Inc. for up to USD 26 million</li><li>SweetRush is recognized for award-winning strategic learning interventions and custom learning solutions</li><li>NIIT offers a comprehensive, AI-enabled Managed Learning Services platform serving Global 1000 enterprises</li><li>The acquisition aims to expand NIIT&apos;s global managed learning scale and offer an expanded services portfolio</li><li>NIIT expects to drive wallet share expansion across enterprise, association, and not-for-profit client segments</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8482a9c7-0de9-4fb2-acaf-77ce01e18098.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NIIT Learning Systems Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NIITMTS] NIIT Learning Systems Ltd Subsidiary Acquires SweetRush Inc. for $26 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NIIT+Learning+Systems+Ltd&title=NIIT+Learning+Systems+Ltd+Subsidiary+Acquires+SweetRush+Inc.+for+%2426+Million&newsId=0aa64e3b-05d4-445c-ab2b-1b01d6012849&token=MGFhNjRlM2ItMDVk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0aa64e3b-05d4-445c-ab2b-1b01d6012849</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>NIIT Learning Systems Ltd announced that its subsidiary, NIIT (USA) Inc., has acquired 100% equity stake in SweetRush Inc., a leader in strategic training interventions and high-end custom learning solutions for Fortune 1000 enterprises and professional associations. The acquisition, completed for a total consideration of up to $26 million, is part of NIIT&apos;s growth strategy to build new capabilities, expand geographically, and penetrate attractive customer segments. SweetRush, founded in 2001 and headquartered in San Francisco, USA, reported an estimated consolidated turnover of $22.4 million for the financial year ended December 31, 2025. The acquisition will enable NIIT to offer an expanded services portfolio, including strategic learning interventions, certification solutions, and talent solutions, to drive growth across enterprise, association, and not-for-profit client segments.</p><ul><li>NIIT Learning Systems Ltd subsidiary acquires SweetRush Inc.</li><li>Total consideration of up to $26 million, including earnout amount.</li><li>SweetRush reports estimated consolidated turnover of $22.4 million for FY 2025.</li><li>Acquisition to expand NIIT&apos;s services portfolio and drive growth.</li><li>SweetRush is a leader in strategic training interventions and custom learning solutions.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1bcb65c9-6bbc-4c66-8dd2-f8a7704358ab.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NIIT Learning Systems Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MAXESTATES] Max Estates Ltd Subscribes to Unsecured CCDs of Subsidiary Company for INR 68.1 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Max+Estates+Ltd&title=Max+Estates+Ltd+Subscribes+to+Unsecured+CCDs+of+Subsidiary+Company+for+INR+68.1+Crores&newsId=3f5397c5-8799-4f82-9aaf-d3dfa3bc76a0&token=M2Y1Mzk3YzUtODc5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3f5397c5-8799-4f82-9aaf-d3dfa3bc76a0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Max Estates Ltd (MEL) has subscribed to 6,81,00,000 Series 10% coupon unsecured compulsory convertible debentures (CCDs) of its subsidiary company, Max Estates Noida Private Limited (MENPL), for an aggregate consideration of INR 68,10,00,000. This is in addition to the earlier subscription of 45,03,00,000 CCDs by MEL and New York Life Insurance Company (NYL) for INR 450,30,00,000. NYL has also subscribed to an additional 6,60,00,000 CCDs for INR 66,00,00,000. The event occurred on January 9, 2026, at 20:35 Hours (IST).</p><ul><li>Max Estates Ltd subscribes to 6,81,00,000 Series 10% coupon unsecured compulsory convertible debentures of its subsidiary company.</li><li>New York Life Insurance Company subscribes to an additional 6,60,00,000 Series 10% coupon unsecured compulsory convertible debentures of the subsidiary company.</li><li>The total consideration for the subscription is INR 68,10,00,000 for MEL and INR 66,00,00,000 for NYL.</li><li>The event occurred on January 9, 2026, at 20:35 Hours (IST).</li><li>The information was submitted earlier with the Stock Exchanges vide letter dated March 27, 2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d6ad0b60-7a36-47b2-9725-c10ad951b26d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Max Estates Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NIITMTS] NIIT Learning Systems Limited acquires SweetRush, Inc. for up to USD 26 million</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NIIT+Learning+Systems+Ltd&title=NIIT+Learning+Systems+Limited+acquires+SweetRush%2C+Inc.+for+up+to+USD+26+million&newsId=29725b20-0796-4f3d-8d7f-3d854c103f47&token=Mjk3MjViMjAtMDc5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29725b20-0796-4f3d-8d7f-3d854c103f47</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>NIIT Learning Systems Limited (NIIT MTS), a global leader in Managed Learning Services, has acquired 100% of SweetRush, Inc., a leader in AI-enabled custom learning experience design and strategic training interventions. The acquisition, completed through NIIT MTS’ wholly owned subsidiary, NIIT (USA), Inc., is for an aggregate consideration of up to USD 26 million, including annual performance-based earnouts over the next five years. The union brings together SweetRush’s custom, AI-enabled, human-centered learning experience design with NIIT’s global managed learning scale, expanding NIIT MTS’ services portfolio and providing an opportunity to convert project-based relationships into longer-duration, annuity-like managed learning engagements.</p><ul><li>NIIT Learning Systems Limited (NIIT MTS) acquires SweetRush, Inc. for up to USD 26 million</li><li>SweetRush is a leader in AI-enabled custom learning experience design and strategic training interventions</li><li>The acquisition supports NIIT MTS’ growth strategy by expanding services portfolio and converting project-based relationships into managed learning engagements</li><li>SweetRush operates with over 100 team members and an extended pool of industry experts across the United States and Costa Rica</li><li>NIIT MTS is a global leader in Managed Learning Services</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5402df02-ab09-4fb3-987a-33e8f34a1f45.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NIIT Learning Systems Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ICICIGI] ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Inadvertently Discloses Draft Financial Results on WhatsApp</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ICICI+Lombard+General+Insurance+Company+Ltd&title=ICICI+Lombard+General+Insurance+Company+Inadvertently+Discloses+Draft+Financial+Results+on+WhatsApp&newsId=da9aed59-c956-4b1f-9fe2-4546e180c81f&token=ZGE5YWVkNTktYzk1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">da9aed59-c956-4b1f-9fe2-4546e180c81f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Other</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Ltd. has reported an incident where a designated person inadvertently uploaded an unaudited draft financial result for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, on their personal WhatsApp Status. The company took immediate action upon becoming aware of the incident by deleting the status. Investors are advised not to rely on this information until the audited financial results are approved and disseminated by the company. The company has initiated an internal inquiry as per the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, and will share the outcome of the inquiry with the Stock Exchanges.</p><ul><li>ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company inadvertently disclosed an unaudited draft financial result on WhatsApp.</li><li>The company has advised investors not to rely on this information until the audited financial results are approved and disseminated.</li><li>The company took immediate action upon becoming aware of the incident by deleting the status.</li><li>The company has initiated an internal inquiry as per the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015.</li><li>The outcome of the inquiry will be shared with the Stock Exchanges.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/216cb8a3-8bb9-481e-a2aa-9a15912b8d51.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Ltd | Category: Other</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ROSSARI] Rossari Biotech Ltd to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Rossari+Biotech+Ltd&title=Rossari+Biotech+Ltd+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=b68299d2-37a1-4703-90bd-e7b9d0beb848&token=YjY4Mjk5ZDItMzdh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b68299d2-37a1-4703-90bd-e7b9d0beb848</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rossari Biotech Ltd has announced a Board of Directors meeting on January 17, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results (Standalone and Consolidated) for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting is scheduled in accordance with Regulation 29 and 33 of Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. Additionally, the &apos;Trading Window&apos; for dealing in securities of the Company will be closed for all &apos;Designated Persons and their immediate relatives&apos; covered under the Company’s Code of Conduct for Prevention of Insider Trading from January 01, 2026, till 48 hours after the announcement of the Unaudited Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Rossari Biotech Ltd to approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Board of Directors meeting scheduled on January 17, 2026</li><li>Trading Window to be closed for Designated Persons and their immediate relatives from January 01, 2026, till 48 hours after the announcement of the Unaudited Financial Results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4227b6f1-8668-4036-972e-44eb9bcf5c16.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Rossari Biotech Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LEMONTREE] Lemon Tree Hotels Announces Composite Scheme of Arrangement Involving Subsidiaries</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Lemon+Tree+Hotels+Ltd&title=Lemon+Tree+Hotels+Announces+Composite+Scheme+of+Arrangement+Involving+Subsidiaries&newsId=edcd47cf-cb8e-4f24-8d47-f8db33964519&token=ZWRjZDQ3Y2YtY2I4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">edcd47cf-cb8e-4f24-8d47-f8db33964519</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Lemon Tree Hotels Limited has approved a Composite Scheme of Arrangement involving its subsidiaries Fleur Hotels Limited, Carnation Hotels Private Limited, Hamstede Living Private Limited, Oriole Dr. Fresh Hotels Private Limited, Canary Hotels Private Limited, Sukhsagar Complexes Private Limited, and Manakin Resorts Private Limited. The scheme, which is subject to various approvals, includes the amalgamation of certain subsidiaries into the company and the demerger of a part of the business to Fleur Hotels Limited. The scheme also involves the sale of APG Strategic Real Estate Pool N.V.’s entire shareholding of 41.09% in the Transferee Company to Coastal Cedar Investments B.V.</p><ul><li>Approval of a Composite Scheme of Arrangement involving six subsidiaries</li><li>Amalgamation of certain subsidiaries into Lemon Tree Hotels Limited</li><li>Demerger of a part of the business to Fleur Hotels Limited</li><li>Sale of APG Strategic Real Estate Pool N.V.’s entire shareholding of 41.09% in the Transferee Company to Coastal Cedar Investments B.V.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/781fa348-227c-4480-8588-3b783dc308b5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Lemon Tree Hotels Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>