<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:34:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[JAIPAN] Jaipan Industries Ltd: Mr. Vitthal Shankar Sontakke Resigns as Non-Executive Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JAIPAN+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Jaipan+Industries+Ltd%3A+Mr.+Vitthal+Shankar+Sontakke+Resigns+as+Non-Executive+Independent+Director&newsId=9e2c2157-12c2-450c-85cf-b48f7b3fe113&token=OWUyYzIxNTctMTJj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e2c2157-12c2-450c-85cf-b48f7b3fe113</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 15:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jaipan Industries Ltd has announced the resignation of Mr. Vitthal Shankar Sontakke as a Non-Executive Independent Director, effective from the close of business hours on 20th February 2026. The resignation is due to the completion of his tenure and there are no material reasons for his resignation beyond those mentioned in his resignation letter. Mr. Sontakke will also cease to be a member of all the committees of the board from 30th February 2026.</p><ul><li>Mr. Vitthal Shankar Sontakke has resigned as a Non-Executive Independent Director of Jaipan Industries Ltd.</li><li>His resignation is effective from the close of business hours on 20th February 2026.</li><li>The resignation is due to the completion of his tenure.</li><li>Mr. Sontakke will also cease to be a member of all the committees of the board from 30th February 2026.</li><li>There are no material reasons for his resignation beyond those mentioned in his resignation letter.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1237d8fd-174e-4239-a457-bc6dc88fc0fb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JAIPAN INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RELHOME] Reliance Home Finance Receives 12 Resolution Plans in Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Reliance+Home+Finance+Ltd&title=Reliance+Home+Finance+Receives+12+Resolution+Plans+in+Corporate+Insolvency+Resolution+Process&newsId=c4a8abe8-334b-4f35-94c4-11154678ea24&token=YzRhOGFiZTgtMzM0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4a8abe8-334b-4f35-94c4-11154678ea24</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:45:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pursuant to the initiation of the Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP) for Reliance Home Finance Limited, the Resolution Professional has received 12 Resolution Plans from a pool of 28 prospective Resolution Applicants. This development comes in accordance with Section 25(2)(h) of the Insolvency &amp; Bankruptcy Code, 2016, and Regulation 36A of IBBI (Insolvency Resolution Process for Corporate Persons) Regulations, 2016.</p><ul><li>Reliance Home Finance Limited has received 12 Resolution Plans from prospective Resolution Applicants.</li><li>The Resolution Plans were submitted in response to the Invitation for Expression of Interest (EOI) published by the Resolution Professional on November 15, 2025.</li><li>The last date for submission of the Resolution Plan was as per Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li><li>Out of 28 Prospective Resolution Applicants, 12 have submitted their Resolution Plans.</li><li>Reliance Home Finance Limited is currently under Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP) as per the Insolvency &amp; Bankruptcy Code, 2016.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fabdfcfb-11b4-4a72-a075-ea255da2dacd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Reliance Home Finance Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PREMEXPLQ] AKS Family Trust Acquires 41.33% Stake in Premier Explosives Ltd from Promoters</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PREMIER+EXPLOSIVES+LTD.&title=AKS+Family+Trust+Acquires+41.33%25+Stake+in+Premier+Explosives+Ltd+from+Promoters&newsId=e8854515-e0d0-47a2-8c65-4b7ef848bf93&token=ZTg4NTQ1MTUtZTBk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e8854515-e0d0-47a2-8c65-4b7ef848bf93</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>AKS Family Trust, an irrevocable discretionary private trust settled under the Indian Trusts Act, 1882, has completed the acquisition of 41.33% stake in Premier Explosives Ltd. The acquisition was made from existing promoters Mr. Amarnath Gupta and Mrs. Kailash Gupta on February 18, 2026. Post-acquisition, AKS Family Trust holds 2,22,21,735 equity shares, representing 41.33% of the total voting capital of the company. The aggregate promoter and promoter group shareholding remains unchanged at 41.33%, and there is no change in control or management of the company.</p><ul><li>AKS Family Trust acquires 41.33% stake in Premier Explosives Ltd</li><li>The acquisition was made from existing promoters Mr. Amarnath Gupta and Mrs. Kailash Gupta</li><li>Post-acquisition, AKS Family Trust holds 2,22,21,735 equity shares</li><li>The aggregate promoter and promoter group shareholding remains unchanged at 41.33%</li><li>There is no change in control or management of the company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a77fd278-df55-4e20-be7e-df76e53b544e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PREMIER EXPLOSIVES LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CEINSYSTECH] CS TECH Ai Marks NSE Listing with Bell Ringing Ceremony, Reflects on Decade of Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ceinsys+Tech+Ltd&title=CS+TECH+Ai+Marks+NSE+Listing+with+Bell+Ringing+Ceremony%2C+Reflects+on+Decade+of+Growth&newsId=7e7db354-5e25-4679-95f1-859c6874c8d9&token=N2U3ZGIzNTQtNWUy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7e7db354-5e25-4679-95f1-859c6874c8d9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:42:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>CS TECH Ai, a technology-led engineering and geospatial infrastructure solutions company, marked its listing on the National Stock Exchange of India (NSE) with a bell ringing event. The company, which has been listed on the BSE since 2014, aims to broaden institutional participation, strengthen liquidity, and further reinforce its governance framework. Since FY 2014-15, CS TECH Ai has delivered consistent financial growth, with revenue increasing from 108 crore to 418 crore and EBITDA improving from 20 crore to 98 crore. The company has also consistently awarded its shareholders, declaring aggregate dividends of approximately 215% since FY 2014-15 to FY 2024-25. CS TECH Ai operates across critical infrastructure domains and is deploying AI-led initiatives to enhance infrastructure planning and lifecycle management.</p><ul><li>CS TECH Ai marks NSE listing with bell ringing ceremony</li><li>Company has been listed on BSE since 2014</li><li>Aims to broaden institutional participation, strengthen liquidity, and reinforce governance framework</li><li>Consistent financial growth since FY 2014-15</li><li>Deploying AI-led initiatives to enhance infrastructure planning and lifecycle management</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dca8f2d9-447b-4b68-9aa5-81476d514245.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ceinsys Tech Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[QPOWER] Quality Power Electrical Equipments Ltd Subsidiary Receives Letter of Award for Instrument Transformers Supply Worth INR 18.00 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Quality+Power+Electrical+Equipments+Ltd&title=Quality+Power+Electrical+Equipments+Ltd+Subsidiary+Receives+Letter+of+Award+for+Instrument+Transformers+Supply+Worth+INR+18.00+Crores&newsId=cb3e3376-1b1c-46e2-b469-5ade81a57b6e&token=Y2IzZTMzNzYtMWIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb3e3376-1b1c-46e2-b469-5ade81a57b6e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Quality Power Electrical Equipments Ltd announced that its material subsidiary, Mehru Electrical and Mechanical Engineers Private Limited, has received a Letter of Award for supply of Instrument Transformers. The order, worth approximately INR 18.00 Crores (Excluding taxes), is to be executed in approximately 8 months. The company confirmed that there are no related party transactions involved and no promoter/promoter group companies have any interest in the entity that awarded the order.</p><ul><li>Quality Power Electrical Equipments Ltd subsidiary receives Letter of Award for Instrument Transformers supply</li><li>Order worth approximately INR 18.00 Crores (Excluding taxes)</li><li>To be executed in approximately 8 months</li><li>No related party transactions involved</li><li>No promoter/promoter group companies have any interest in the entity that awarded the order</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/89b77f96-6db9-45f6-b492-86c3c7a13880.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Quality Power Electrical Equipments Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ARUNIS] Arunis Abode Ltd Receives Rs. 14.84 Cr. Order from Dhiaani Rental Company Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Arunis+Abode+Ltd&title=Arunis+Abode+Ltd+Receives+Rs.+14.84+Cr.+Order+from+Dhiaani+Rental+Company+Limited&newsId=5ba09621-0859-4d93-bbdd-6b4a61bbafd4&token=NWJhMDk2MjEtMDg1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ba09621-0859-4d93-bbdd-6b4a61bbafd4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:42:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Arunis Abode Ltd, now known as KALIND LIMITED, has received a purchase order from Dhiaani Rental Company Limited, Water Street, Kono Junction, Sierra Leone. The order, amounting to Rs. 14.84 Cr., is for the hiring of Excavator, Loader and Bulldozer. The initial contract period is 12 months, extendable by mutual written consent. The order does not fall under related party transactions and no promoter/promoter group companies have any interest in the entity that awarded the order.</p><ul><li>Arunis Abode Ltd receives order worth Rs. 14.84 Cr.</li><li>Order from Dhiaani Rental Company Limited, Sierra Leone</li><li>Hiring of Excavator, Loader and Bulldozer</li><li>Initial contract period of 12 months</li><li>No related party transactions involved</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/81e967ce-cc4b-4e59-90cf-72dc48930f63.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Arunis Abode Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UNIONBANK] Union Bank of India Conducts Investors/Analysts Meet with Kuwait Investment Office</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=UNION+BANK+OF+INDIA&title=Union+Bank+of+India+Conducts+Investors%2FAnalysts+Meet+with+Kuwait+Investment+Office&newsId=e804d99c-f3db-48b2-be5c-225ab86ef33e&token=ZTgwNGQ5OWMtZjNk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e804d99c-f3db-48b2-be5c-225ab86ef33e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:27:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>On 20th February 2026, representatives of Union Bank of India conducted an Investors/Analysts Meet with the Kuwait Investment Office in London. The meeting took place from 6:30 PM to 7:30 PM (IST) and followed a one-to-one format. The bank referred to publicly available documents for discussions during the interaction. This information is disclosed in accordance with Regulation 30 &amp; 31 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Union Bank of India conducted an Investors/Analysts Meet with the Kuwait Investment Office.</li><li>The meeting took place in London on 20th February 2026.</li><li>The meeting followed a one-to-one format and lasted for an hour.</li><li>The bank referred to publicly available documents for discussions during the interaction.</li><li>The disclosure is made in accordance with SEBI regulations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/924a9875-f407-4903-801e-db75f41b7f2c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: UNION BANK OF INDIA | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SERIND] SER Industries Ltd: Proceedings of Extra Ordinary General Meeting - Key Highlights</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SER+Industries+Ltd&title=SER+Industries+Ltd%3A+Proceedings+of+Extra+Ordinary+General+Meeting+-+Key+Highlights&newsId=fd6d2b18-dcf4-4652-a024-8c9a17b3453b&token=ZmQ2ZDJiMTgtZGNm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd6d2b18-dcf4-4652-a024-8c9a17b3453b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>The Extra-ordinary General Meeting (EGM) of SER Industries Ltd was held on February 20, 2026. The meeting was conducted through Video Conferencing (VC) / Other Audio-Visual Means (OAVM). The key highlights of the meeting include the appointment of Mr. Sunil Kumar Shahi as Managing Director and Chairman, the regularization of Mr. Ayush Munnalal Sharma&apos;s appointment as an Independent Director, and the authorization of the Board to borrow up to INR 200 Crores. Other significant items on the agenda were the increase in limits for loans, guarantees, and investments, alteration in the main object clause of the Memorandum of Association, adoption of new Articles of Association, and a change in the name of the company to &apos;Desi Farms India Limited&apos;. The EGM also sought approval to shift the Registered Office from the State of Karnataka to the State of Maharashtra and increase the Authorized Share Capital.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Sunil Kumar Shahi as Managing Director and Chairman</li><li>Regularization of Mr. Ayush Munnalal Sharma&apos;s appointment as an Independent Director</li><li>Authorization of the Board to borrow up to INR 200 Crores</li><li>Increase in limits for loans, guarantees, and investments</li><li>Alteration in the main object clause of the Memorandum of Association</li><li>Change in the name of the company to &apos;Desi Farms India Limited&apos;</li><li>Shift of the Registered Office from Karnataka to Maharashtra</li><li>Increase in the Authorized Share Capital</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d150db02-72f7-42fc-abb6-5c9acbbe4b19.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SER Industries Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HAPPSTMNDS] NCLT Approves Dispensation from Meetings in Happiest Minds Technologies&apos; Scheme of Amalgamation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Happiest+Minds+Technologies+Ltd&title=NCLT+Approves+Dispensation+from+Meetings+in+Happiest+Minds+Technologies%27+Scheme+of+Amalgamation&newsId=a44fc6e2-4d02-4d02-a53d-74684e429ab5&token=YTQ0ZmM2ZTItNGQw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a44fc6e2-4d02-4d02-a53d-74684e429ab5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:22:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The National Company Law Tribunal, Bengaluru Bench has approved the dispensation from holding meetings of shareholders and creditors in the scheme of amalgamation of Aureustech Systems Private Limited and Happiest Minds Technologies Limited. The order was passed on February 13, 2026, and the certified true copy of the order was received by the company on February 20, 2026. The scheme involves the amalgamation of Aureustech Systems Private Limited, a wholly owned subsidiary, with Happiest Minds Technologies Limited, the holding company. The respective boards of directors of the applicant companies have already approved the scheme at their meetings held on July 29, 2025.</p><ul><li>NCLT approves dispensation from meetings in Happiest Minds Technologies&apos; scheme of amalgamation</li><li>Involves amalgamation of Aureustech Systems Private Limited with Happiest Minds Technologies Limited</li><li>Aureustech Systems Private Limited is a wholly owned subsidiary of Happiest Minds Technologies Limited</li><li>Respective boards of directors of the applicant companies have approved the scheme</li><li>Certified true copy of the order received by the company on February 20, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/37b3c4a8-38e8-446c-8fac-8da70b586195.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Happiest Minds Technologies Ltd | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AHL] Abans Financial Services Ltd: Re-appointment of Directors for Second Term</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Abans+Holdings+Ltd&title=Abans+Financial+Services+Ltd%3A+Re-appointment+of+Directors+for+Second+Term&newsId=bcf19f34-e11d-40cc-9db7-4f4b31f86d54&token=YmNmMTlmMzQtZTEx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bcf19f34-e11d-40cc-9db7-4f4b31f86d54</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 14:22:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Abans Financial Services Ltd has announced the re-appointment of Mr. Abhishek Bansal as Managing Director and Ms. Ashima Chhatwal as an Independent Director for the second term of 5 consecutive years each. The re-appointments are subject to the approval of the shareholders of the Company in their respective meetings.</p><ul><li>Re-appointment of Mr. Abhishek Bansal as Managing Director for the second term of 5 consecutive years.</li><li>Re-appointment of Ms. Ashima Chhatwal as an Independent Director for the second term of 5 consecutive years.</li><li>Re-appointments are subject to the approval of the shareholders of the Company.</li><li>Mr. Abhishek Bansal is a commerce graduate with 8+ years of experience in the field of merger acquisitions, venture capital private equity transactions, legal matters, corporate commercial transactions, and corporate governance practices.</li><li>Ms. Ashima Chhatwal has 8+ years of experience in the field of law and has worked with HCL Technologies Limited, AZB &amp; Partners, and Trilegal.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7f573f22-ac47-46d1-b765-ed9436f7a3af.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Abans Holdings Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>