<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:58:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[GARWSYN] Garware Synthetics Ltd Board Meeting Approves E-Voting Facility, Regularization of Independent Director, and More</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GARWARE+SYNTHETICS+LTD.&title=Garware+Synthetics+Ltd+Board+Meeting+Approves+E-Voting+Facility%2C+Regularization+of+Independent+Director%2C+and+More&newsId=2a565da5-a028-4a5b-94e9-a87ffd8b54d2&token=MmE1NjVkYTUtYTAy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a565da5-a028-4a5b-94e9-a87ffd8b54d2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:57:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Garware Synthetics Ltd, in a recent Board Meeting held on 02™ February, 2026, has approved several key decisions. The company has approved the notice of Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EOGM) to be held on Saturday, 28\</p><ul><li>Approval of Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EOGM) notice</li><li>Regularization of Mrs. Sheetal Sawant as Independent Director</li><li>Book Closure and Record Date for the purpose of AGM</li><li>Introduction of E-Voting Facility for shareholders</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Suhas Sadanand Ganpule as scrutinizer for EOGM</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/69ee20d5-e7d2-49af-974d-163937a249f1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GARWARE SYNTHETICS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ORIRAIL] Oriental Rail Infrastructure Ltd Appoints Stellar IR Advisors as Exclusive Investor Relations Agency</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Oriental+Rail+Infrastructure+Ltd&title=Oriental+Rail+Infrastructure+Ltd+Appoints+Stellar+IR+Advisors+as+Exclusive+Investor+Relations+Agency&newsId=602ecda9-a971-4b8f-b240-b113a8783861&token=NjAyZWNkYTktYTk3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">602ecda9-a971-4b8f-b240-b113a8783861</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:55:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Oriental Rail Infrastructure Ltd has announced the appointment of Stellar IR Advisors Private Limited as their exclusive Investor Relations Advisory Services provider. The appointment is effective from February 01, 2026. This move is part of the company&apos;s ongoing efforts to enhance its investor relations and communication strategies.</p><ul><li>Oriental Rail Infrastructure Ltd has appointed Stellar IR Advisors Private Limited as their exclusive Investor Relations Advisory Services provider.</li><li>The appointment is effective from February 01, 2026.</li><li>This move is a part of the company&apos;s ongoing efforts to enhance its investor relations and communication strategies.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c0af19ba-78c1-41c5-a428-22dfee71416b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Oriental Rail Infrastructure Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HPBL] HCP Plastene Bulkpack Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results of FY 2025-2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HCP+Plastene+Bulkpack+Ltd&title=HCP+Plastene+Bulkpack+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+of+FY+2025-2026&newsId=a07e7278-e025-4a36-b8a9-3709ab26b945&token=YTA3ZTcyNzgtZTAy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a07e7278-e025-4a36-b8a9-3709ab26b945</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:54:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>HCP Plastene Bulkpack Ltd has informed the BSE that their Board of Directors will meet on 10 February 2026 to consider and approve the standalone and consolidated unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ending on 31st December 2025. The meeting will also consider the appointment of a Company Secretary and Compliance Officer, if required. The trading window for the company&apos;s equity shares, which was closed on 1st October 2025, will remain closed and will reopen 48 hours after the financial results are publicly announced.</p><ul><li>HCP Plastene Bulkpack Ltd schedules Board Meeting on 10 February 2026</li><li>Board Meeting to consider and approve Q3 and nine months results of FY 2025-2026</li><li>Trading window for the company&apos;s equity shares to remain closed until 48 hours after the financial results are publicly announced</li><li>Company may appoint a new Company Secretary and Compliance Officer</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8815d36d-4e55-4cb8-80e8-1eadd0a0307a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HCP Plastene Bulkpack Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MFLINDIA] MFL India Ltd Announces Closure of Trading Window Until February 15, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MFL+INDIA+LTD.&title=MFL+India+Ltd+Announces+Closure+of+Trading+Window+Until+February+15%2C+2026&newsId=ecf83dcf-05fc-415f-8ecc-bc7baed27e15&token=ZWNmODNkY2YtMDVm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ecf83dcf-05fc-415f-8ecc-bc7baed27e15</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:54:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>MFL India Ltd has announced the closure of its trading window from Thursday, 1st January, 2026 till 48 hours after the Financial Results for the quarter ended 31st December, 2025 are made public. The trading window will remain closed until 15th February, 2026 due to a scheduled Board Meeting on 13th February, 2026 to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter ended 31st December, 2025.</p><ul><li>MFL India Ltd announces closure of trading window from 1st January, 2026</li><li>Trading window to remain closed till 48 hours after Financial Results for Q4 2025 are made public</li><li>Trading window to remain closed until 15th February, 2026 due to a Board Meeting</li><li>Board Meeting scheduled on 13th February, 2026 to consider and approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q4 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/aa024ed9-48e0-47df-be7e-0e9d6f9d51f6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MFL INDIA LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASMS] Bartronics India Ltd Announces Q3 &amp; 9M FY2025 Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BARTRONICS+INDIA+LTD.&title=Bartronics+India+Ltd+Announces+Q3+%26+9M+FY2025+Financial+Results&newsId=40fb2546-eced-49e0-9679-c2eaf2721291&token=NDBmYjI1NDYtZWNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40fb2546-eced-49e0-9679-c2eaf2721291</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:52:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bartronics India Ltd has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The total revenue from operations for the quarter is INR 4,834.04 Lakhs, with a net profit of INR 244.50 Lakhs. The company&apos;s business primarily relates to providing Technology Solutions. The financial results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for Q3 FY2025 is INR 4,834.04 Lakhs</li><li>Net profit for Q3 FY2025 is INR 244.50 Lakhs</li><li>The company&apos;s business primarily relates to providing Technology Solutions</li><li>Financial results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors</li><li>The company is in the process of regularizing the compliances related to Foreign Subsidiaries and closure of such subsidiaries under the applicable legal framework in respective jurisdiction</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/986a98b1-2753-48e8-87f3-8c2063d04009.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BARTRONICS INDIA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BEPL] Bhansali Engineering Polymers Ltd. to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results for FY 2025-26 and Consider Interim Dividend Declaration</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BHANSALI+ENGINEERING+POLYMERS+LTD.-%24&title=Bhansali+Engineering+Polymers+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+FY+2025-26+and+Consider+Interim+Dividend+Declaration&newsId=691b68b1-1e28-4e41-b420-826d6231c9cf&token=NjkxYjY4YjEtMWUy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">691b68b1-1e28-4e41-b420-826d6231c9cf</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bhansali Engineering Polymers Ltd. has informed the BSE that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on 14th February 2026 to consider and approve the un-audited financial results (standalone &amp; consolidated) for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company will also consider the declaration of interim dividends for the financial year 2025-26. The trading window for dealing in the company&apos;s equity shares by the designated persons and/or their immediate relatives was closed on 1st January 2026 and will open on 17th February 2026.</p><ul><li>Bhansali Engineering Polymers Ltd. to approve Q3 and nine months results for FY 2025-26</li><li>Consideration of interim dividend declaration for FY 2025-26</li><li>Trading window for dealing in company&apos;s equity shares closed from 1st January 2026 to 17th February 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c3e851ef-11ed-42c1-8d62-32f5577e86aa.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BHANSALI ENGINEERING POLYMERS LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EMBASSY] NovoHealth@EmbassyManyata Marks 100 Weeks of Promoting Workplace Wellness</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Embassy+Office+Parks+REIT&title=NovoHealth%40EmbassyManyata+Marks+100+Weeks+of+Promoting+Workplace+Wellness&newsId=d96db7b5-6de5-486e-9f3c-bc4827eeca05&token=ZDk2ZGI3YjUtNmRl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d96db7b5-6de5-486e-9f3c-bc4827eeca05</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:51:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Wellness Initiative</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Embassy Office Parks REIT and Novo Nordisk Education Foundation&apos;s NovoHealth@EmbassyManyata initiative, a workplace wellness programme, has completed 100 weeks at Embassy Manyata Business Park in Bengaluru. The initiative, which was launched on World Obesity Day in 2024, has grown into a vibrant platform encouraging physical activity and holistic health for over 100,000 employees. The programme, which includes the flagship 5K running initiative &apos;Novo Run&apos;, has been instrumental in fostering active lifestyles and holistic well-being among corporate employees in Bengaluru.</p><ul><li>NovoHealth@EmbassyManyata, a workplace wellness programme by Embassy Office Parks REIT and Novo Nordisk Education Foundation, marks 100 weeks of promoting workplace wellness.</li><li>The initiative has grown into a vibrant platform encouraging physical activity and holistic health for over 100,000 employees.</li><li>The programme includes the flagship 5K running initiative &apos;Novo Run&apos;, which has been instrumental in fostering active lifestyles and holistic well-being among corporate employees.</li><li>The initiative was launched on World Obesity Day in 2024 in response to India&apos;s growing health crisis and the role of workplaces in promoting healthier habits.</li><li>The programme has been effective in improving health outcomes, with 85,500 steps towards better health.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c03c9e02-82f4-4957-a1ee-7d6631c9b574.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Embassy Office Parks REIT | Category: Wellness Initiative</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TIL] TIL Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TIL+LTD.&title=TIL+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=4da0b6f8-5623-417a-b722-f658e723e032&token=NGRhMGI2ZjgtNTYy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4da0b6f8-5623-417a-b722-f658e723e032</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>TIL Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 9th February 2026 to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for the third quarter and nine months period ended on 31st December 2025. This is in accordance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements), 2015.</p><ul><li>TIL Ltd scheduled a Board Meeting on 9th February 2026</li><li>The meeting aims to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for the third quarter and nine months period ended on 31st December 2025</li><li>The announcement is in compliance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements), 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8c95e1d4-8f06-42a5-b18f-78840ced224a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TIL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SIGNATURE] Signatureglobal (India) Ltd Clarifies Increase in Volume of Company’s Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Signatureglobal+%28India%29+Ltd&title=Signatureglobal+%28India%29+Ltd+Clarifies+Increase+in+Volume+of+Company%E2%80%99s+Equity+Shares&newsId=889c3ad3-d6f4-49cc-8ec6-6bb997f5a843&token=ODg5YzNhZDMtZDZm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">889c3ad3-d6f4-49cc-8ec6-6bb997f5a843</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:49:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Signatureglobal (India) Ltd has clarified that the recent increase in volume of the company’s equity shares is purely market driven. The company has made all necessary disclosures and announcements as required by Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. There is no pending announcement or price-sensitive information that may affect the price/volume behavior of the scrip.</p><ul><li>Signatureglobal (India) Ltd clarifies increase in volume of company’s equity shares</li><li>The increase is market driven</li><li>Company has made necessary disclosures as per Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>No pending announcements or price-sensitive information</li><li>Price/volume behavior in the scrip is not affected by any undisclosed information</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/27385a54-7139-43a1-9c8b-af61b875e367.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Signatureglobal (India) Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LLFICL] Leading Leasing Finance And Investment Company Ltd to Approve Q4 Results on Feb 11, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Leading+Leasing+Finance+And+Investment+Company+Ltd&title=Leading+Leasing+Finance+And+Investment+Company+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+Results+on+Feb+11%2C+2026&newsId=618513f8-0597-49bb-8f8b-96d35a83732a&token=NjE4NTEzZjgtMDU5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">618513f8-0597-49bb-8f8b-96d35a83732a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Leading Leasing Finance And Investment Company Ltd has announced a Board meeting on February 11, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for designated persons was closed from January 1, 2026, and will reopen after the expiry of 48 hours from the declaration of the financial results.</p><ul><li>Leading Leasing Finance And Investment Company Ltd to consider and approve Q4 results on Feb 11, 2026</li><li>Trading window for designated persons closed from Jan 1, 2026</li><li>Trading window to reopen after 48 hours from Q4 results declaration</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/765b013b-c740-4c67-b43c-1e257d05fb64.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Leading Leasing Finance And Investment Company Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>