<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:36:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[TIMEX] Timex Group India Ltd. Addresses Signature Mismatch in Share Transfers</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TIMEX+GROUP+INDIA+LTD.-%24&title=Timex+Group+India+Ltd.+Addresses+Signature+Mismatch+in+Share+Transfers&newsId=3f3ec6b8-792c-459d-916d-e2e8f1862bdd&token=M2YzZWM2YjgtNzky</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3f3ec6b8-792c-459d-916d-e2e8f1862bdd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:34:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pursuant to SEBI regulations, Timex Group India Ltd. has reported on the re-lodgement of transfer requests of physical shares received in December. A significant number of requests were marked with a major signature mismatch, leading to the application of the procedure outlined in SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/MIRSD/DOS3/CIR/P/2018 dated November 06, 2018. Once the necessary formalities are completed to rectify the discrepancy, the shares will be transferred to the buyer.</p><ul><li>Timex Group India Ltd. addresses signature mismatch in share transfers</li><li>SEBI regulations prompt report on re-lodgement of transfer requests</li><li>Procedure from SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/MIRSD/DOS3/CIR/P/2018 being followed</li><li>Necessary formalities to resolve discrepancies for share transfer</li><li>Shares to be transferred to the buyer upon completion of formalities</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fd02833d-6b74-468d-8f28-f046e0f698a8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TIMEX GROUP INDIA LTD.-$ | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WINSOME] Winsome Yarns Ltd Concludes Adjourned 35th AGM, Announces Financial Year 2024-25 Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=WINSOME+YARNS+LTD.&title=Winsome+Yarns+Ltd+Concludes+Adjourned+35th+AGM%2C+Announces+Financial+Year+2024-25+Results&newsId=48f04dc2-8627-431f-ba8d-3937a35d1f4c&token=NDhmMDRkYzItODYy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48f04dc2-8627-431f-ba8d-3937a35d1f4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Winsome Yarns Ltd, a textile company, recently conducted and concluded its adjourned 35th Annual General Meeting (AGM) for the financial year 2024-25. The original meeting, scheduled for December 30, 2025, was adjourned due to lack of quorum. The adjourned meeting was held on January 6, 2026, through video conference. The meeting was chaired by Anil Kohli, Designated Partner of M/s ARCK Resolution Professionals LLP, who is the Resolution Professional (RP) in charge due to the ongoing Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP) of the Corporate Debtor. The meeting was attended by members through VC and e-voting facilities. The business transacted included the adoption of annual audited financial statements, appointment of a director, and approval of the appointment of M/s Girish Madan &amp; Associates as Secretarial Auditors.</p><ul><li>Winsome Yarns Ltd conducted its adjourned 35th AGM on January 6, 2026, for the financial year 2024-25.</li><li>The original meeting was adjourned due to lack of quorum.</li><li>The meeting was chaired by Anil Kohli, Designated Partner of M/s ARCK Resolution Professionals LLP, who is the RP.</li><li>Business transacted included adoption of annual audited financial statements, appointment of a director, and approval of Secretarial Auditors.</li><li>The meeting was held through video conference and members participated through e-voting facilities.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/81ea346f-add3-4cc7-bbbe-230b431caa6f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: WINSOME YARNS LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MCLEODRUSS] Mcleod Russel India Ltd Changes Email Address of Registrar and Share Transfer Agent</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MCLEOD+RUSSEL+INDIA+LTD.&title=Mcleod+Russel+India+Ltd+Changes+Email+Address+of+Registrar+and+Share+Transfer+Agent&newsId=3ef00aea-3be7-4c7d-852a-3cced32b5153&token=M2VmMDBhZWEtM2Jl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ef00aea-3be7-4c7d-852a-3cced32b5153</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:29:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mcleod Russel India Ltd has announced an update on the change of email address of its Registrar and Share Transfer Agent (RTA), Maheshwari Datamatics Pvt. Ltd. The new email addresses for the RTA are compliance@mdplcorporate.com and contact@mdplcorporate.com, replacing the previous info@mdplin &amp; mdpldc@yahoo.com. The RTA&apos;s address and other details remain unchanged. Stakeholders are requested to direct all future correspondence to the updated email address, which will also be available on the Company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Mcleod Russel India Ltd has changed the email address of its Registrar and Share Transfer Agent (RTA)</li><li>The new email addresses for the RTA are compliance@mdplcorporate.com and contact@mdplcorporate.com</li><li>The previous email addresses info@mdplin &amp; mdpldc@yahoo.com are no longer in use</li><li>The RTA&apos;s address and other details remain unchanged</li><li>Stakeholders are requested to direct all future correspondence to the updated email address</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f6eea9e4-0250-433b-8030-9b7e002a41bf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MCLEOD RUSSEL INDIA LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[OROSMITHS] Orosil Smiths India Ltd Receives Further Payment of ₹ 1 Crore from Buyer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=OROSIL+SMITHS+INDIA+LTD.-%24&title=Orosil+Smiths+India+Ltd+Receives+Further+Payment+of+%E2%82%B9+1+Crore+from+Buyer&newsId=7f7cd018-b2d2-4d83-a46c-6c96b6105aec&token=N2Y3Y2QwMTgtYjJk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7f7cd018-b2d2-4d83-a46c-6c96b6105aec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:23:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Orosil Smiths India Ltd has received a further payment of ₹ 1 Crore from Mr. Sanidhya Garg, towards the remaining sale consideration for the property located at A-89, Sector-2, Noida — 201301. This is in continuation of the company&apos;s earlier intimations dated April 09, 2025, August 28, 2025, September 08, 2025, and November 19, 2025. The company will keep the stock exchange informed about any further developments regarding this matter.</p><ul><li>Orosil Smiths India Ltd has received a further payment of ₹ 1 Crore from the buyer, Mr. Sanidhya Garg</li><li>The payment is towards the remaining sale consideration for a property located at A-89, Sector-2, Noida — 201301</li><li>This is in continuation of the company&apos;s earlier intimations to the stock exchange</li><li>The company will keep the stock exchange informed about any further developments</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/250ab3d9-667e-4182-b637-64d895864427.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: OROSIL SMITHS INDIA LTD.-$ | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[POWERINDIA] Hitachi Energy India Ltd Receives Higher ESG Rating Score of &apos;72.9&apos; for 2025 from SES ESG Research Pvt. Ltd.</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Hitachi+Energy+India+Ltd&title=Hitachi+Energy+India+Ltd+Receives+Higher+ESG+Rating+Score+of+%2772.9%27+for+2025+from+SES+ESG+Research+Pvt.+Ltd.&newsId=c6c05ec4-9616-4a69-88c0-56ea9de341db&token=YzZjMDVlYzQtOTYx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c6c05ec4-9616-4a69-88c0-56ea9de341db</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:21:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hitachi Energy India Ltd has been assigned an ESG rating score of &apos;72.9&apos; for the year 2025 by SES ESG Research Pvt. Ltd., a SEBI registered Category II - ESG Rating Provider. This is an increase from the earlier rating score of ‘70.1’ assigned for the year 2024. The rating reflects the Company’s performance on Environmental, Social and Governance parameters. Notably, the Company did not engage the Rating Agency for the evaluation or issuance of its ESG Rating, and the report was prepared independently using publicly available information.</p><ul><li>Hitachi Energy India Ltd receives an ESG rating score of &apos;72.9&apos; for 2025 from SES ESG Research Pvt. Ltd.</li><li>This is an increase from the earlier rating score of ‘70.1’ assigned for the year 2024.</li><li>The rating reflects the Company’s performance on Environmental, Social and Governance parameters.</li><li>The Company did not engage the Rating Agency for the evaluation or issuance of its ESG Rating.</li><li>The report was prepared independently using publicly available information.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/efed8d01-3e40-43d2-b210-54bbd2976987.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Hitachi Energy India Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RFSL] Richfield Financial Services Ltd. Approves New Office Address and Proposes Public Issue of NCDs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Richfield+Financial+Services+Ltd&title=Richfield+Financial+Services+Ltd.+Approves+New+Office+Address+and+Proposes+Public+Issue+of+NCDs&newsId=9deedf92-6332-4492-a368-2e6a77027e29&token=OWRlZWRmOTItNjMz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9deedf92-6332-4492-a368-2e6a77027e29</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Richfield Financial Services Ltd. announced the outcome of its Board meeting held on January 6, 2026. The Board approved the new registered office address at Door No: 2/184 in the First Floor of the Settu Chettiyar Building, Avadi Road, EB Office Opposite, Poonamalle, Chennai Pin- 600056. Additionally, the Board proposed a Public Issue of Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs) up to Rs. 50 Crore and appointed Infomerics Valuation and Rating Ltd as the rating agency for the proposed NCDs. The proposal to keep the Books of Account at a place other than the Registered Office of the Company was postponed to a subsequent meeting.</p><ul><li>Approval of new registered office address in Chennai</li><li>Proposal of Public Issue of Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs) up to Rs. 50 Crore</li><li>Appointment of Infomerics Valuation and Rating Ltd as the rating agency for the proposed NCDs</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2f98e6d6-e30a-4c82-807e-9a52b93a19f1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Richfield Financial Services Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GRANDFONRY] Grand Foundry Ltd Announces Board Meeting Approval of Director Appointments and Resignations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GRAND+FOUNDRY+LTD.&title=Grand+Foundry+Ltd+Announces+Board+Meeting+Approval+of+Director+Appointments+and+Resignations&newsId=75f9ff35-b590-4a9e-9c22-cc1c84b7cbde&token=NzVmOWZmMzUtYjU5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75f9ff35-b590-4a9e-9c22-cc1c84b7cbde</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Grand Foundry Ltd has announced the approval of various appointments and resignations in its recent Board meeting. The company has appointed Mr. Gaurav Goyal, Mr. Rakesh Kumar Bansal, Mr. Saurabh Goyal, Dr. Reena Sharma, Ms. Shilpi Soni, and Ms. Aishwarya Singhvi as Additional Directors under different categories. The appointments are subject to the approval of the shareholders of the company. The Board also accepted the resignations of Ms. Shivani Jain as Executive Director &amp; CFO, Mr. Ashish Kumar as Executive Director &amp; CEO, and three Independent Directors, Mr. Rajat Kasliwal, Mr. Rahul Bhardwaj, and Mr. Rahul Sharma due to their pre-occupation elsewhere. The company has also appointed Mr. Nitin Gupta as CFO and Ms. Sonia Arora as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer. The registered office of the company has been shifted to Office 17, 1* Floor, A Wing, Bldg No. 19, Pinna Near Trade Centre BKC Bandra East kalina Pinnacle Corporate Park Mumbai-400098 and the additional place of keeping books of accounts and other relevant papers of the company has been shifted to Office No. DSM-408, 4th Floor, DLF Towers, Shivaji Marg, Moti Nagar, New Delhi—110015.</p><ul><li>Appointment of six Additional Directors</li><li>Resignation of four Directors</li><li>Appointment of new CFO and Company Secretary</li><li>Shift of registered office and additional place of keeping books of accounts</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3d4fd0c2-1691-42d1-914e-2bff9b9ac58c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GRAND FOUNDRY LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CEATLTD] Ceat Ltd to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Period Ended Dec 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CEAT+LTD.&title=Ceat+Ltd+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Period+Ended+Dec+31%2C+2025&newsId=40032103-2d61-4b08-9d9a-edb00357727c&token=NDAwMzIxMDMtMmQ2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40032103-2d61-4b08-9d9a-edb00357727c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ceat Ltd has informed BSE that the Board of Directors of the Company will meet on January 19, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and period ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will also take on record the Limited Review Report. Additionally, due to SEBI regulations, the Trading Window for dealing in securities of the Company is currently closed and will remain so until 48 hours after the declaration of the aforesaid results.</p><ul><li>Ceat Ltd to approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and period ended Dec 31, 2025</li><li>Board Meeting scheduled on January 19, 2026</li><li>Trading Window for dealing in securities of the Company is currently closed</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c3619f0c-6296-432a-9410-51cae07ea595.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CEAT LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHAKTIPUMP] Shakti Pumps Invests Rs. 3 Crores in Wholly Owned Subsidiary Shakti Energy Solutions Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHAKTI+PUMPS+%28INDIA%29+LTD.-%24&title=Shakti+Pumps+Invests+Rs.+3+Crores+in+Wholly+Owned+Subsidiary+Shakti+Energy+Solutions+Limited&newsId=d2ed9e46-29e6-4459-a17d-3ceb6f284a32&token=ZDJlZDllNDYtMjll</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2ed9e46-29e6-4459-a17d-3ceb6f284a32</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:13:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Shakti Pumps (India) Limited has invested Rs. 3,00,00,000/- (Rupees Three Crores Only) in its wholly owned subsidiary i.e. Shakti Energy Solutions Limited (SESL). The investment will be used to establish a greenfield high efficiency Solar DCR cell and Solar PV modules manufacturing plant in Pithampur, Madhya Pradesh, with a production capacity of 2.20 GW. SESL, incorporated on 06% September, 2010, had a turnover of Rs. 216.53 Crores in FY25.</p><ul><li>Shakti Pumps invests Rs. 3 Crores in its wholly owned subsidiary Shakti Energy Solutions Limited</li><li>Investment will be used to establish a Solar DCR cell and Solar PV modules manufacturing plant in Pithampur, Madhya Pradesh</li><li>The plant will have a production capacity of 2.20 GW</li><li>Shakti Energy Solutions Limited had a turnover of Rs. 216.53 Crores in FY25</li><li>The investment does not fall under the Related Party Transaction</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f16a8ed6-4380-4f30-b7b0-a32cd19a907c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHAKTI PUMPS (INDIA) LTD.-$ | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BIOCON] Biocon Biologics to Expand Biosimilar Oncology Portfolio, Outline Strategic Vision at J.P. Morgan Healthcare Conference</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BIOCON+LTD.&title=Biocon+Biologics+to+Expand+Biosimilar+Oncology+Portfolio%2C+Outline+Strategic+Vision+at+J.P.+Morgan+Healthcare+Conference&newsId=0c84a516-a08c-4e3b-9202-1b4f18e873d4&token=MGM4NGE1MTYtYTA4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c84a516-a08c-4e3b-9202-1b4f18e873d4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:12:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Biocon Biologics, a fully integrated global biosimilars company and subsidiary of Biocon Ltd., will introduce three new oncology biosimilars at the 44th Annual J.P. Morgan Healthcare Conference in San Francisco. These new assets are among the largest oncology biologics scheduled to lose exclusivity over the next five years and will join Biocon Biologics’ existing portfolio of 17 oncology medications. The company is also planning to integrate as a wholly owned subsidiary of Biocon Limited, strengthening its global leadership in biosimilar insulins and GLP-1 peptide generics to cover the full spectrum of diabetes care. This integration is expected to be completed no later than March 31, 2026.</p><ul><li>Introduction of three new oncology biosimilars - Trastuzumab/Hyaluronidase (Herceptin® SC/Herceptin HYLECTA™), Nivolumab (Opdivo®), and Pembrolizumab (Keytruda®)</li><li>These new assets represent an over $75 billion opportunity, or approximately 35% of the global oncology pharmaceutical market</li><li>Biocon Biologics is planning to integrate as a wholly owned subsidiary of Biocon Limited</li><li>The integration is expected to be completed no later than March 31, 2026</li><li>The integration will strengthen Biocon’s global position to lead in diabetes, oncology, and immunology - therapeutic areas that together account for nearly 40% of global pharmaceutical revenues</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/da154ef0-6278-409a-ae3c-553285b08154.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BIOCON LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>