<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:45:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[STERTOOLS] Sterling Tools Ltd.: Reappointment of Mr. Atul Aggarwal as Managing Director and Mr. Anil Aggarwal as Chairman &amp; Whole Time Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=STERLING+TOOLS+LTD.-%24&title=Sterling+Tools+Ltd.%3A+Reappointment+of+Mr.+Atul+Aggarwal+as+Managing+Director+and+Mr.+Anil+Aggarwal+as+Chairman+%26+Whole+Time+Director&newsId=03beb436-d039-43ab-aef8-6f2b91820201&token=MDNiZWI0MzYtZDAz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03beb436-d039-43ab-aef8-6f2b91820201</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:43:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Sterling Tools Ltd. has decided to reappoint Mr. Atul Aggarwal as Managing Director and Mr. Anil Aggarwal as Chairman &amp; Whole Time Director for a period of five consecutive years, subject to the approval of the shareholders. The reappointment will be effective from 1st April 2026. The Board also approved the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. Additionally, the Company approved the allotment of 1,60,108 equity shares under ESOP and reconstituted the Corporate Social Responsibility Committee.</p><ul><li>Reappointment of Mr. Atul Aggarwal as Managing Director</li><li>Reappointment of Mr. Anil Aggarwal as Chairman &amp; Whole Time Director</li><li>Approval of Unaudited Financial Results for the third quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025</li><li>Allotment of 1,60,108 equity shares under ESOP</li><li>Reconstitution of the Corporate Social Responsibility Committee</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a54126be-04bb-4824-af0c-308d45958c1b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: STERLING TOOLS LTD.-$ | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BALAJITELE] Balaji Telefilms and Netflix Join Forces for Lock Upp Season 2 on Netflix</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BALAJI+TELEFILMS+LTD.&title=Balaji+Telefilms+and+Netflix+Join+Forces+for+Lock+Upp+Season+2+on+Netflix&newsId=cff857b2-72aa-4e32-b8a3-d5b8b76a82d5&token=Y2ZmODU3YjItNzJh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cff857b2-72aa-4e32-b8a3-d5b8b76a82d5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>In a groundbreaking partnership, Balaji Telefilms is bringing its reality format Lock Upp to Netflix for a bigger, sharper, and reimagined season. The show, created by Ekta Kapoor, became a breakout reality phenomenon for its daring format and intense gameplay. The new season, designed for today’s streaming audiences, is set to launch on Netflix with exclusive first-look footage and a host announcement coming soon.</p><ul><li>Balaji Telefilms and Netflix partnership for Lock Upp Season 2</li><li>Bigger, sharper, and reimagined season designed for streaming audiences</li><li>Lock Upp&apos;s daring format and intense gameplay</li><li>Exclusive first-look footage and host announcement coming soon</li><li>Netflix&apos;s continued investment in high-engagement formats</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d51274db-8099-42fb-bb4c-943b2d00d4ae.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BALAJI TELEFILMS LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RPTECH] Rashi Peripherals Ltd. Announces Formation of Step-down Subsidiary in UAE</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Rashi+Peripherals+Ltd&title=Rashi+Peripherals+Ltd.+Announces+Formation+of+Step-down+Subsidiary+in+UAE&newsId=460ce14e-e48d-4cb6-945c-0a4453c4ccba&token=NDYwY2UxNGUtZTQ4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">460ce14e-e48d-4cb6-945c-0a4453c4ccba</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:42:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rashi Peripherals Ltd. has announced the formation of a step-down subsidiary in UAE, which will be a wholly-owned (100%) subsidiary of the company’s subsidiary, Rashi Peripherals Pte. Ltd. The decision was made at a board meeting held on February 3, 2026. The new subsidiary will be engaged in the Distribution of Information and Communication Technology (ICT) products and services.</p><ul><li>Rashi Peripherals Ltd. to form a step-down subsidiary in UAE</li><li>The new subsidiary will be a wholly-owned (100%) entity of Rashi Peripherals Pte. Ltd.</li><li>The decision was made at a board meeting held on February 3, 2026</li><li>The new subsidiary will be engaged in the Distribution of Information and Communication Technology (ICT) products and services</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/287697c2-789b-4f54-965b-2f8496982baa.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Rashi Peripherals Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADFFOODS] ADF Foods Ltd. Updates Key Managerial Personnel for Materiality Determination</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADF+FOODS+LTD.-%24&title=ADF+Foods+Ltd.+Updates+Key+Managerial+Personnel+for+Materiality+Determination&newsId=420a83ec-30fe-4d90-882e-34819b2a453b&token=NDIwYTgzZWMtMzBm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">420a83ec-30fe-4d90-882e-34819b2a453b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:41:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>ADF Foods Ltd. has updated its list of Key Managerial Personnel authorized to determine the materiality of an event or information. This change comes after the cessation of Mr. Shardul Doshi as the Chief Financial Officer and Key Managerial Personnel on 10th December 2025. The new appointment, Mr. Srinivas Ayyagari, has been included in the list of authorized officials. The updated list includes Mr. Bimal Thakkar, Mr. Arjuun Guuha, Mr. Srinivas Ayyagari, and Ms. Shalaka Ovalekar. The contact details of these personnel will be updated on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>ADF Foods Ltd. updates Key Managerial Personnel</li><li>Mr. Shardul Doshi ceases to be Chief Financial Officer and Key Managerial Personnel</li><li>Mr. Srinivas Ayyagari appointed as new Chief Financial Officer and Key Managerial Personnel</li><li>Updated list of Key Managerial Personnel includes Mr. Bimal Thakkar, Mr. Arjuun Guuha, Mr. Srinivas Ayyagari, and Ms. Shalaka Ovalekar</li><li>Updated contact details to be provided on the company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/74857685-fd2a-452b-8f20-32fa6ca9ccef.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADF FOODS LTD.-$ | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RPTECH] Rashi Peripherals Ltd Announces Q3 and 9M Financial Results for 2025, Appoints New Directors, and Forms Step-down Subsidiary in UAE</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Rashi+Peripherals+Ltd&title=Rashi+Peripherals+Ltd+Announces+Q3+and+9M+Financial+Results+for+2025%2C+Appoints+New+Directors%2C+and+Forms+Step-down+Subsidiary+in+UAE&newsId=7b21d919-f88b-4995-872a-83dfa882cac7&token=N2IyMWQ5MTktZjg4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b21d919-f88b-4995-872a-83dfa882cac7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:41:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rashi Peripherals Ltd has announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations for Q3 and 9M 2025 stood at Rs. 44.76 million and Rs. 572.53 million respectively. The company appointed Mr. Rajesh Goenka as an Additional Director, designated as Whole-Time Director and the Chief Executive Officer (CEO) and Dr. Indumati Gopinathan as an Additional Non-Executive Independent Director. Rashi Peripherals also formed a step-down subsidiary in UAE, which will be a Wholly-owned (100%) Subsidiary of the Company’s Subsidiary, i.e. Rashi Peripherals Pte. Ltd.</p><ul><li>Rashi Peripherals reported a revenue from operations of Rs. 44.76 million for Q3 and Rs. 572.53 million for 9M 2025.</li><li>The company appointed Mr. Rajesh Goenka as an Additional Director, designated as Whole-Time Director and the Chief Executive Officer (CEO).</li><li>Dr. Indumati Gopinathan was appointed as an Additional Non-Executive Independent Director of the company.</li><li>Rashi Peripherals formed a step-down subsidiary in UAE, which will be a Wholly-owned (100%) Subsidiary of the Company’s Subsidiary, i.e. Rashi Peripherals Pte. Ltd.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/12b0300f-738e-46e7-95da-2308cdbd58c1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Rashi Peripherals Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUZLON] Suzlon Energy Ltd: Material Price Movement Without Identifiable Trigger</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SUZLON+ENERGY+LTD.&title=Suzlon+Energy+Ltd%3A+Material+Price+Movement+Without+Identifiable+Trigger&newsId=412ca77e-5db5-4eab-b765-500c7e9075e4&token=NDEyY2E3N2UtNWRi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">412ca77e-5db5-4eab-b765-500c7e9075e4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Suzlon Energy Ltd. has reported a Material Price Movement (MPM) on 3rd February 2026 at 9.15 a.m., which couldn&apos;t be linked to any specific event or information in the mainstream media. This disclosure is made in accordance with Regulation 30(11) of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements), Regulations 2015, for the information of the members and the public at large.</p><ul><li>Suzlon Energy Ltd. reported a Material Price Movement on 3rd February 2026.</li><li>The MPM was noticed at 9.15 a.m., but no specific triggering event or information was found in the mainstream media.</li><li>The disclosure is in accordance with Regulation 30(11) of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements), Regulations 2015.</li><li>This disclosure aims to inform the members and the public at large.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/db1380d5-f9ee-4b0c-a14e-cb2c2692bbdf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SUZLON ENERGY LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MAXESTATES] Max Estates Ltd. to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025 on Feb 6, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Max+Estates+Ltd&title=Max+Estates+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025+on+Feb+6%2C+2026&newsId=f77ab45b-1846-437d-af42-f9b9cbc8707f&token=Zjc3YWI0NWItMTg0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f77ab45b-1846-437d-af42-f9b9cbc8707f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Max Estates Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 6, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results of the company for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. This meeting is in accordance with Regulation 29 and other applicable regulations of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The trading window for dealing in shares of the company will remain closed for all designated persons, including promoters, directors, key managerial personnel, designated employees, and other connected persons till 48 hours after the announcement of the results, i.e., Sunday, February 8, 2026.</p><ul><li>Max Estates Ltd. to consider and approve Q3 and nine months results for 2025</li><li>Board meeting scheduled on February 6, 2026</li><li>Trading window to remain closed till 48 hours after the announcement of results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e3638f7e-24ea-4ca4-a365-e98aa3f07239.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Max Estates Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MAHABANK] Bank of Maharashtra&apos;s Executive Director, Shri Rohit Rishi, Ceases Position for MD Role at IIFCL</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BANK+OF+MAHARASHTRA&title=Bank+of+Maharashtra%27s+Executive+Director%2C+Shri+Rohit+Rishi%2C+Ceases+Position+for+MD+Role+at+IIFCL&newsId=62ee8f03-9865-496c-ac2d-f6571f356572&token=NjJlZThmMDMtOTg2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62ee8f03-9865-496c-ac2d-f6571f356572</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:37:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Bank of Maharashtra has announced that Shri Rohit Rishi has ceased to be the Executive Director of the Bank as of 03.02.2026. This change is due to his appointment as Managing Director at India Infrastructure Finance Company Limited (IIFCL), as per the Department of Financial Services, Ministry of Finance, Government of India notification no. 12/11/2023-BO.| dated 3% February, 2026. Compliance with Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015 is requested.</p><ul><li>Shri Rohit Rishi ceases to be Executive Director of Bank of Maharashtra.</li><li>Appointed as Managing Director at India Infrastructure Finance Company Limited (IIFCL).</li><li>Notification from Department of Financial Services, Ministry of Finance, Government of India.</li><li>Compliance with Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7d34f006-d5ca-4246-ad0b-9341ca65a771.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BANK OF MAHARASHTRA | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LLOYDSME] Lloyds Metals and Energy Ltd Approves Allotment of Equity Shares Upon Conversion of Preferentially Issued Convertible Warrants to Non-Promoters</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LLOYDS+METALS+AND+ENERGY+LTD.&title=Lloyds+Metals+and+Energy+Ltd+Approves+Allotment+of+Equity+Shares+Upon+Conversion+of+Preferentially+Issued+Convertible+Warrants+to+Non-Promoters&newsId=62a8e472-3bfc-4a40-996b-451117b8f13d&token=NjJhOGU0NzItM2Jm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62a8e472-3bfc-4a40-996b-451117b8f13d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:34:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Lloyds Metals and Energy Limited has approved the allotment of equity shares upon conversion of preferentially issued convertible warrants to non-promoters. This decision was made during the Board of Directors meeting held on Tuesday, 03 February, 2026. The company had allotted 3,67,95,000 convertible warrants on preferential allotment basis through resolution passed at the Extraordinary General Meeting of the Company held on 29% July, 2024. Out of these, 8,05,500 warrants were converted into 8,05,500 equity shares of the Company of face value Rs. 1 (Rupees One) each. The new equity shares so allotted shall rank pari passu with the existing equity shares of the Company in all respects.</p><ul><li>Approval of Unaudited Financial Results for the Quarter and Nine Months ended 31‘&apos; December, 2025</li><li>Approval for allotment of Equity Shares upon Conversion of Preferentially Issued Convertible Warrants to Non-Promoters</li><li>Incorporation of a wholly owned subsidiary in Maharashtra, India with an estimate aggregate Capital outlay of over Rs. 252,00,00,000 (Rupees Two Hundred and Fifty-Two Crore Only)</li><li>Approval for Slurry Pipeline Project and its Financing</li><li>Approval for designation of Mr. Ashit Patni, Chief Marketing Officer, as Senior Managerial Personnel of the Company</li><li>Approval to acquire equity stake in an entity in Singapore by Lloyds Global Resources FZCO, wholly owned subsidiary of the Company</li><li>Acquisition of equity stake in an entity in South Africa by Lloyds Global Resources FZCO, wholly owned subsidiary of the Company</li><li>Approval to increase in capacity of Pellet Plants at Konsari</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ef9ea454-2167-4b93-ba15-f6c475a37583.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LLOYDS METALS AND ENERGY LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADFFOODS] ADF Foods Ltd. Approves Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADF+FOODS+LTD.-%24&title=ADF+Foods+Ltd.+Approves+Unaudited+Standalone+and+Consolidated+Financial+Results+for+Q3+2025&newsId=97385ee7-04f1-4928-9de0-3698c56e2d66&token=OTczODVlZTctMDRm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97385ee7-04f1-4928-9de0-3698c56e2d66</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:33:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>ADF Foods Limited announced the approval of their unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025 during a board meeting. The meeting was conducted in accordance with Regulation 30 and 33 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The company enclosed the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results along with a limited review report issued by the statutory auditors, M/s. MSKA &amp; Associates, Chartered Accountants.</p><ul><li>ADF Foods Ltd. approved the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December 2025.</li><li>The board meeting was conducted in accordance with Regulation 30 and 33 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li><li>The company enclosed the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results along with a limited review report issued by the statutory auditors, M/s. MSKA &amp; Associates, Chartered Accountants.</li><li>MSKA &amp; Associates conducted a review of the interim financial information in accordance with the Standard on Review Engagements (SRE) 2410.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7707eacf-e848-4ed0-9e7d-44f3d58ebdc2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADF FOODS LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>