<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:20:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SERIND] SER Industries to Alter MOA, AOA, Change Name to Desi Farms India, and Shift Registered Office</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SER+Industries+Ltd&title=SER+Industries+to+Alter+MOA%2C+AOA%2C+Change+Name+to+Desi+Farms+India%2C+and+Shift+Registered+Office&newsId=a25d90ce-e362-4a7d-83c9-eaba28a41780&token=YTI1ZDkwY2UtZTM2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a25d90ce-e362-4a7d-83c9-eaba28a41780</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:03:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SER Industries Ltd has announced alterations in its Memorandum of Association (MOA) and Articles of Association (AOA). Shareholders have approved the adoption of new MOA and AOA, alteration of the Object Clause, and a change in the company&apos;s name to Desi Farms India Limited. The company also plans to shift its registered office from Karnataka to Maharashtra, increase its authorized capital, and continue its main business of procuring, sourcing, collecting, producing, processing, manufacturing, preserving, pasteurizing, packaging, branding, trading, marketing, selling, distributing, exporting and importing milk and milk products, and allied, related or value-added food products.</p><ul><li>Alteration in Memorandum of Association and Articles of Association</li><li>Change of company name to Desi Farms India Limited</li><li>Shift of registered office from Karnataka to Maharashtra</li><li>Increase in the authorized capital</li><li>Continuation of main business in dairy and food products</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ea30bedc-e553-4be5-b913-675a76743d50.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SER Industries Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NITINCAST] Nitin Castings Ltd. Announces Voluntary Delisting from BSE Following Acquirers&apos; Intent</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Nitin+Castings+Ltd&title=Nitin+Castings+Ltd.+Announces+Voluntary+Delisting+from+BSE+Following+Acquirers%27+Intent&newsId=022d9947-42a3-4ff4-a407-96a5d2443de8&token=MDIyZDk5NDctNDJh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">022d9947-42a3-4ff4-a407-96a5d2443de8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Nitin Castings Ltd. has announced its intention to voluntarily delist its equity shares from BSE. This decision comes after receiving an Initial Public Announcement from Mr. Nirmal Kedia, Mr. Nitin Kedia, and M/s. Citrus Castings Private Limited, expressing their intention to acquire all equity shares of the company held by public shareholders and delist the shares from BSE. The company&apos;s Board has approved the delisting, subject to shareholder approval, and has appointed M/s. Kala Agarwal as the Scrutinizer to conduct the Postal Ballot / e-voting process.</p><ul><li>Nitin Castings Ltd. to voluntarily delist from BSE</li><li>Decision follows Acquirers&apos; intention to acquire and delist shares</li><li>Shareholder approval required for the delisting</li><li>M/s. Kala Agarwal appointed as Scrutinizer for Postal Ballot / e-voting process</li><li>Floor price of the delisting offer determined at ₹273.36 per Equity Share</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b9a8434e-4afb-4b12-972f-925ec5b970b8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Nitin Castings Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SERIND] SER Industries Ltd: Sunil Kumar Shahi Re-Designated as Managing Director and Chairman; Ayush Munnalal Sharma Regularised as Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SER+Industries+Ltd&title=SER+Industries+Ltd%3A+Sunil+Kumar+Shahi+Re-Designated+as+Managing+Director+and+Chairman%3B+Ayush+Munnalal+Sharma+Regularised+as+Independent+Director&newsId=e6345f32-6a7f-4a30-81a8-fe061053b8ef&token=ZTYzNDVmMzItNmE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e6345f32-6a7f-4a30-81a8-fe061053b8ef</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SER Industries Ltd has announced changes in the designation of its directors in a recent meeting. Mr. Sunil Kumar Shahi, who was previously the Managing Director, has been re-designated as the Managing Director and Chairman of the company. His appointment will be effective from January 20, 2026, for a period of five years. Mr. Shahi is a seasoned business leader with over 25 years of experience in various sectors. On the other hand, Mr. Ayush Munnalal Sharma has been regularised as an Independent Director of the company with effect from January 20, 2026, for a term of 5 years. He is a lawyer with over a decade of professional experience and specialises in corporate and commercial laws, criminal law, and civil litigation.</p><ul><li>Sunil Kumar Shahi re-designated as Managing Director and Chairman</li><li>Shahi&apos;s appointment effective from January 20, 2026, for five years</li><li>Shahi has over 25 years of experience in various sectors</li><li>Ayush Munnalal Sharma regularised as Independent Director</li><li>Sharma&apos;s appointment effective from January 20, 2026, for five years</li><li>Sharma is a lawyer with over a decade of experience</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/827b3fa2-109f-4fc1-8629-f1de940a9699.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SER Industries Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AVANTEL] Avantel Ltd Independent Director, Mrs. Mini Ipe, Resigns Due to Preoccupation and Personal Commitments</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AVANTEL+LTD.&title=Avantel+Ltd+Independent+Director%2C+Mrs.+Mini+Ipe%2C+Resigns+Due+to+Preoccupation+and+Personal+Commitments&newsId=3252e3c9-22dc-4b60-9057-656379f8b756&token=MzI1MmUzYzktMjJk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3252e3c9-22dc-4b60-9057-656379f8b756</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 15:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Avantel Ltd announced the resignation of its Independent Director, Mrs. Mini Ipe, with effect from February 21, 2026. Mrs. Ipe cited her preoccupation and unexpected personal commitments as the reasons for her resignation. She confirmed that there are no other material reasons for her resignation and she has no material concerns or issues with the management or affairs of the company. Mrs. Ipe has been a Non-Executive Nominee Director at Axis Bank Limited, Non-Executive Independent Director at PTC India Limited and PTC India Financial Services Limited. She has been a member of various committees in these companies.</p><ul><li>Mrs. Mini Ipe resigns as Independent Director of Avantel Ltd.</li><li>Resignation effective from February 21, 2026.</li><li>Mrs. Ipe cites preoccupation and personal commitments as reasons for resignation.</li><li>Mrs. Ipe confirms no other material reasons or concerns with the company&apos;s management or affairs.</li><li>Mrs. Ipe has held directorships in Axis Bank Limited, PTC India Limited, and PTC India Financial Services Limited.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7222a297-9a04-4c98-902d-ae1e5c4b7397.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AVANTEL LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MEESHO] Meesho Ltd Closes Trading Window for Designated Persons</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Meesho+Ltd&title=Meesho+Ltd+Closes+Trading+Window+for+Designated+Persons&newsId=6b9e8ffd-eab3-4172-aedd-7166959aaea0&token=NmI5ZThmZmQtZWFi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6b9e8ffd-eab3-4172-aedd-7166959aaea0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:41:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Meesho Ltd has announced the closure of its trading window for designated persons and their immediate relatives. This closure is in accordance with the Company’s Code of Conduct to Regulate, Monitor and Report Trading by Designated Persons and their Immediate Relatives and pursuant to SEBI PIT Regulations. The trading window will remain closed from Sunday, February 22, 2026 till the end of 48 hours after the declaration of the Audited Financial Results for the quarter and financial year ending March 31, 2026. The date of the Board Meeting to consider and approve these Financial Results will be intimated in due course.</p><ul><li>Meesho Ltd closes trading window for designated persons and their immediate relatives</li><li>Closure in accordance with the Company’s Code of Conduct and SEBI PIT Regulations</li><li>Trading window to remain closed till the end of 48 hours after the declaration of the Audited Financial Results for the quarter and financial year ending March 31, 2026</li><li>Date of Board Meeting to consider and approve these Financial Results will be intimated later</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6b52dc92-96a8-4587-83a1-68a93da41584.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Meesho Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TRL] Taylormade Renewables Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Discuss Fund Raising Proposal</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Taylormade+Renewables+Ltd&title=Taylormade+Renewables+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Discuss+Fund+Raising+Proposal&newsId=51240eb6-da94-4166-94b2-4447efd0c193&token=NTEyNDBlYjYtZGE5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">51240eb6-da94-4166-94b2-4447efd0c193</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:41:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Taylormade Renewables Ltd has informed the BSE that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on 24/02/2026. The agenda includes considering and approving a proposal for raising funds through various methods, including preferential issue, private placements, rights issue, or any other methods permitted under applicable laws. The fundraising could be through the issuance of equity shares, convertible or non-convertible securities, warrants, or debt securities. The proposal is subject to regulatory/statutory approvals, including the approval of the shareholders of the Company. The trading window for dealing in the securities will be closed for all designated persons, their immediate relatives, and other connected persons from the date of this announcement till February 27, 2026.</p><ul><li>Taylormade Renewables Ltd schedules a Board Meeting on 24/02/2026 to discuss a fund raising proposal</li><li>The proposal includes raising funds through various methods such as preferential issue, private placements, rights issue</li><li>The fundraising could be through the issuance of equity shares, convertible or non-convertible securities, warrants, or debt securities</li><li>The proposal is subject to regulatory/statutory approvals, including the approval of the shareholders of the Company</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the securities will be closed for all designated persons, their immediate relatives, and other connected persons from the date of this announcement till February 27, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7f06c0a5-ed3b-4cd6-9780-5da176f941e3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Taylormade Renewables Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VASWANI] Vaswani Industries Ltd to Approve Q3 FY 2025-26 Financial Results on Feb 28, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VASWANI+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Vaswani+Industries+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+FY+2025-26+Financial+Results+on+Feb+28%2C+2026&newsId=a672736e-965f-423d-9cc7-edca02393164&token=YTY3MjczNmUtOTY1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a672736e-965f-423d-9cc7-edca02393164</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:41:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vaswani Industries Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 28, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited standalone financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025 (Q3 FY 2025-26). The meeting will also approve the Limited Review Report of the Statutory Auditors. The trading window will be closed for 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results.</p><ul><li>Vaswani Industries Ltd to approve Q3 FY 2025-26 financial results on Feb 28, 2026</li><li>The meeting will also approve the Limited Review Report of the Statutory Auditors</li><li>Trading window to be closed for 48 hours after the financial results declaration</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c37d3a81-158a-4b25-a50e-74e3f83f3444.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VASWANI INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ARCHITORG] Archit Organosys Ltd to Purchase Land from Chairman and Whole Time Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ARCHIT+ORGANOSYS+LTD.&title=Archit+Organosys+Ltd+to+Purchase+Land+from+Chairman+and+Whole+Time+Director&newsId=a38cdbc6-5567-4bee-9add-1e1e4c26956a&token=YTM4Y2RiYzYtNTU2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a38cdbc6-5567-4bee-9add-1e1e4c26956a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Property Purchase</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Archit Organosys Ltd has approved the purchase of immovable property, specifically land situated at Bhavnagar, from Shri Kandarp Krishnakant Amin, who is the Chairman and Whole Time Director (Promoter) of the Company. The decision was made at a Board of Directors and Audit Committee meeting held on February 21, 2026. The Conveyance Deed/ Sale Deed will be intimated to the Stock Exchange once executed, as per Regulation 30 of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2025.</p><ul><li>Archit Organosys Ltd to purchase land from its Chairman and Whole Time Director.</li><li>The land is situated at Bhavnagar.</li><li>The decision was approved at a Board of Directors and Audit Committee meeting.</li><li>The Conveyance Deed/ Sale Deed will be intimated to the Stock Exchange once executed.</li><li>The transaction is in compliance with Regulation 30 of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b132c856-5c47-4b18-be84-e4941663b334.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ARCHIT ORGANOSYS LTD. | Category: Property Purchase</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SURAJEST] Suraj Estate Developers Ltd. to Raise INR 45 Crores Through NCDs Issue to IDBI Trusteeship Services Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Suraj+Estate+Developers+Ltd&title=Suraj+Estate+Developers+Ltd.+to+Raise+INR+45+Crores+Through+NCDs+Issue+to+IDBI+Trusteeship+Services+Limited&newsId=2c4683fa-a048-4e0c-815d-213dad886977&token=MmM0NjgzZmEtYTA0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2c4683fa-a048-4e0c-815d-213dad886977</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:22:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Suraj Estate Developers Ltd. has approved the allotment of 4,50,00,000 (Four Crores Fifty Lakhs) Unlisted, Secured, Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs) of face value of INR 10/- each, amounting up to INR 45,00,00,000/- (Indian Rupees Forty-Five Crores Only) to IDBI Trusteeship Services Limited on private placement basis. The NCDs are secured by way of paripassu charge over various properties and first and exclusive charge over certain leasehold plots. The interest rate offered is 17% p.a. accrued on a monthly basis, with the first 24 months&apos; interest payable at 12% p.a. on a monthly basis and the remaining interest payable at 17% p.a. on a monthly basis. The repayment will be in 18 equal monthly installments starting from the 25th month.</p><ul><li>Suraj Estate Developers Ltd. to raise INR 45 Crores through NCDs issue.</li><li>NCDs allotted to IDBI Trusteeship Services Limited on private placement basis.</li><li>NCDs secured by paripassu charge over various properties and first and exclusive charge over certain leasehold plots.</li><li>Interest rate of 17% p.a. accrued on a monthly basis.</li><li>Repayment in 18 equal monthly installments starting from the 25th month.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c4080768-00cc-46f0-a715-f17869f04cd4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Suraj Estate Developers Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PARSHVA] Parshva Enterprises Ltd. Increases Authorised Share Capital by Rs. 4.5 Crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Parshva+Enterprises+Ltd&title=Parshva+Enterprises+Ltd.+Increases+Authorised+Share+Capital+by+Rs.+4.5+Crore&newsId=fb9d771d-24ef-428a-b5cf-c8bbf48bc9ea&token=ZmI5ZDc3MWQtMjRl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fb9d771d-24ef-428a-b5cf-c8bbf48bc9ea</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 14:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Parshva Enterprises Ltd. has approved an increase in its authorized share capital from Rs. 15,00,00,000/- to Rs. 10,50,00,000/-. This decision was made pursuant to a postal ballot on February 21, 2026, where the shareholders agreed to the alteration of the Capital Clause of the Memorandum of Association (MOA). The new capital structure will consist of 1,05,00,000 (One Crore Five Lakh) Equity Shares of Rs. 10/- each. This change is in compliance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Parshva Enterprises Ltd. has increased its authorized share capital by Rs. 4.5 Crore.</li><li>The new authorized share capital is Rs. 10,50,00,000/- divided into 1,05,00,000 Equity Shares of Rs. 10/- each.</li><li>This decision was made pursuant to a postal ballot on February 21, 2026.</li><li>The change is in compliance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li><li>The alteration of the Capital Clause of the MOA has been approved by the shareholders.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2c6df194-9b8c-48f1-8e98-9e8014d3a167.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Parshva Enterprises Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>