<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:45:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[MODAIRY] Krishan Kumar Goyal Acquires Major Stake in Modern Dairies Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MODERN+DAIRIES+LTD.&title=Krishan+Kumar+Goyal+Acquires+Major+Stake+in+Modern+Dairies+Ltd&newsId=2b02958d-7e1e-4cd3-8e81-cf660d507fdc&token=MmIwMjk1OGQtN2Ux</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b02958d-7e1e-4cd3-8e81-cf660d507fdc</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:43:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Krishan Kumar Goyal, the Chairman &amp; Managing Director of Modern Dairies Limited, has acquired a significant stake in the company. This acquisition also involves other parties acting in concert with Goyal. The acquisition details are provided as per the Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</p><ul><li>Krishan Kumar Goyal, the Chairman &amp; Managing Director of Modern Dairies Limited, has acquired a significant stake in the company.</li><li>The acquisition also involves other parties acting in concert with Goyal.</li><li>The acquisition is as per the Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</li><li>The total diluted share/voting capital of the TC after the said acquisition is 31,018,010.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/D74441C9_060F_4C86_9465_3E11E4833A19_101052.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MODERN DAIRIES LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NEOINFRA] Darshik D. Mehta Acquires Shares in Neo Infracon Ltd, Holding Increases to 6.76%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NEO+INFRACON+LTD.&title=Darshik+D.+Mehta+Acquires+Shares+in+Neo+Infracon+Ltd%2C+Holding+Increases+to+6.76%25&newsId=71f492a5-0bff-4730-8024-ee4d342d582e&token=NzFmNDkyYTUtMGJm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71f492a5-0bff-4730-8024-ee4d342d582e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>According to a disclosure made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011, Darshik D. Mehta has acquired shares in Neo Infracon Ltd. The acquisition took place on the open market on 27th February 2026. The total shares carrying voting rights acquired by Darshik D. Mehta are 399, which is 0.008% of the total diluted voting rights of the company. This acquisition has increased Darshik D. Mehta&apos;s holding in Neo Infracon Ltd to 6.76% from the previous 6.75%.</p><ul><li>Darshik D. Mehta acquires shares in Neo Infracon Ltd</li><li>Acquisition took place on the open market</li><li>399 shares carrying voting rights acquired</li><li>0.008% increase in total diluted voting rights</li><li>Holding increases to 6.76% from 6.75%</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/E1847FF2_A170_41DC_BE86_A20F73574410_100928.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NEO INFRACON LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AGIIL] Harbans Kaur Acquires 17.65% Stake in AGI Infra Ltd from Promoter Group Members</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AGI+Infra+Ltd&title=Harbans+Kaur+Acquires+17.65%25+Stake+in+AGI+Infra+Ltd+from+Promoter+Group+Members&newsId=975b9c4e-3b3e-472d-8638-4dc031e62cbd&token=OTc1YjljNGUtM2Iz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">975b9c4e-3b3e-472d-8638-4dc031e62cbd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:39:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Harbans Kaur, a member of the Promoter Group of AGI Infra Limited, has submitted a disclosure under Regulation 10(6) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. The disclosure pertains to the acquisition of 17.65% stake in AGI Infra Limited from other Promoter Group members, Bikramjit Singh and Ranijit Singh. The transaction does not involve any consideration as it is a gift. The total number of shares acquired is 2,15,60,000, which is 17.65% of the voting rights of the Target Company.</p><ul><li>Harbans Kaur, a member of the Promoter Group, acquires 17.65% stake in AGI Infra Limited</li><li>The acquisition is from other Promoter Group members, Bikramjit Singh and Ranijit Singh</li><li>The transaction does not involve any consideration as it is a gift</li><li>The total number of shares acquired is 2,15,60,000, which is 17.65% of the voting rights of the Target Company</li><li>The disclosure was made within the time line specified under the Regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ACA45DC1_0EF9_4384_B400_F621FBB70C7A_095831.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AGI Infra Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LAOPALA] Genesis Exports Pvt Ltd Acquires Shares of La Opala RG Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LA+OPALA+RG+LTD.&title=Genesis+Exports+Pvt+Ltd+Acquires+Shares+of+La+Opala+RG+Ltd&newsId=0c44999a-01e4-45fe-af7d-ab95b8d53bed&token=MGM0NDk5OWEtMDFl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c44999a-01e4-45fe-af7d-ab95b8d53bed</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:36:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Genesis Exports Pvt Ltd, along with Persons Acting in Concert (PACs), has acquired 18,000 Equity Shares of La Opala RG Ltd. The acquisition was made through the open market. The total share capital of La Opala RG Ltd is 111,000,000 Equity Shares of Rs 2/- Each.</p><ul><li>Genesis Exports Pvt Ltd and PACs acquire 18,000 Equity Shares of La Opala RG Ltd</li><li>Acquisition made through the open market</li><li>Total share capital of La Opala RG Ltd is 111,000,000 Equity Shares of Rs 2/- Each</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/F15E46D0_92E7_48E5_A21C_D2EAC729C002_100457.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LA OPALA RG LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LAXMIDENTL] Promoter Sameer Kamlesh Merchant Acquires 15,000 Shares in Laxmi Dental Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Laxmi+Dental+Ltd&title=Promoter+Sameer+Kamlesh+Merchant+Acquires+15%2C000+Shares+in+Laxmi+Dental+Ltd&newsId=6368ea7f-2668-4e3f-9ba4-ecc899b31cdd&token=NjM2OGVhN2YtMjY2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6368ea7f-2668-4e3f-9ba4-ecc899b31cdd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:34:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Sameer Kamlesh Merchant, Promoter, CEO and Managing Director of Laxmi Dental Ltd (Formerly known as Laxmi Dental Export Private Limited), has acquired 15,000 equity shares of the company. This acquisition represents 15.80% of the total diluted capital of the company. The shares were acquired on February 27, 2026. The total equity share capital of the company is 5,49,62,149 Equity Shares of Rs. 2/- each and the total diluted share/voting capital of the TC is 5,53,07,928 Equity Shares of Rs. 2/- each.</p><ul><li>Sameer Kamlesh Merchant, Promoter, CEO and Managing Director of Laxmi Dental Ltd, acquires 15,000 shares</li><li>The acquisition represents 15.80% of the total diluted capital of the company</li><li>The shares were acquired on February 27, 2026</li><li>The total equity share capital of the company is 5,49,62,149 Equity Shares of Rs. 2/- each</li><li>The total diluted share/voting capital of the TC is 5,53,07,928 Equity Shares of Rs. 2/- each</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/687B24A4_51B5_4EDF_8D1E_16BBAE0DF948_100208.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Laxmi Dental Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AGIIL] Harbans Kaur Acquires 2,15,60,000 Shares of AGI Infra Ltd via Inter-se Transfer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AGI+Infra+Ltd&title=Harbans+Kaur+Acquires+2%2C15%2C60%2C000+Shares+of+AGI+Infra+Ltd+via+Inter-se+Transfer&newsId=862513e3-d3b2-411f-801b-0cf3eb3e0bdd&token=ODYyNTEzZTMtZDNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">862513e3-d3b2-411f-801b-0cf3eb3e0bdd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Harbans Kaur, a prominent figure, has acquired 2,15,60,000 shares of AGI Infra Ltd via inter-se transfer on February 27, 2026. This acquisition represents 17.65% of the total share and voting capital of the company, and 17.65% of the total diluted share and voting capital. The acquisition was made through a transfer among the promoter group, which is considered a gift. This development could potentially impact the company&apos;s shareholding pattern and future strategic decisions.</p><ul><li>Harbans Kaur acquires 2,15,60,000 shares of AGI Infra Ltd</li><li>Acquisition represents 17.65% of the total share and voting capital</li><li>Acquisition represents 17.65% of the total diluted share and voting capital</li><li>Transfer among the promoter group (Gift)</li><li>Potential impact on the company&apos;s shareholding pattern</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4D482F3D_E4D1_477B_9CF2_F99FF52BF00B_095624.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AGI Infra Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AGIIL] Promoter Group Sells 17.65% Stake in AGI Infra Ltd via Inter-se Transfer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AGI+Infra+Ltd&title=Promoter+Group+Sells+17.65%25+Stake+in+AGI+Infra+Ltd+via+Inter-se+Transfer&newsId=19e91ff9-f128-4746-838b-3ca49faf819a&token=MTllOTFmZjktZjEy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19e91ff9-f128-4746-838b-3ca49faf819a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:29:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Sale</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bikramijit Singh and Ranjit Singh, part of the Promoter Group of AGI Infra Limited, have disclosed the sale of 2,15,60,000 shares (17.65%) via inter-se transfer on February 27, 2026. The shares were sold off-market among the Promoter Group. Before the sale, the Promoter Group held 17.65% of the total voting capital, which has now been completely sold off.</p><ul><li>Promoter Group sells 17.65% stake in AGI Infra Ltd</li><li>Sale of 2,15,60,000 shares reported</li><li>Transaction valued at approximately 17.65% of the total voting capital</li><li>Sale conducted off-market via inter-se transfer among Promoter Group</li><li>Promoter Group&apos;s stake in AGI Infra Ltd now stands at 0%</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/09C6B7DD_7C61_4E02_90C8_BBF4213EDC57_095045.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AGI Infra Ltd | Category: Sale</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AUROPHARMA] Aurobindo Pharma Director Discharged in Delhi Liquor Scam Case</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AUROBINDO+PHARMA+LTD.&title=Aurobindo+Pharma+Director+Discharged+in+Delhi+Liquor+Scam+Case&newsId=ba6c5838-1179-488c-8f0f-14b86ded9891&token=YmE2YzU4MzgtMTE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba6c5838-1179-488c-8f0f-14b86ded9891</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:26:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Aurobindo Pharma Ltd. announced that its Non-Executive Director, Mr. P. Sarath Chandra Reddy, has been discharged from the Delhi Liquor Scam case by the Court of Sh. Jitendra Singh, Special Judge (PC Act) -23, Rouse Avenue Court Complex, New Delhi. The case, which originated from FIR No. RC0032022A0053 dated 17.08.2022, was lodged by CBI/ACB under various sections of the IPC and the Prevention of Corruption Act, 1988. After a thorough analysis of the allegations and material on record, the Court discharged Mr. P. Sarath Chandra Reddy, stating that there was no material showing his involvement in any conspiracy, influence on any public servant, payment or receipt of illegal gratification, or obtaining of any unlawful benefit in relation to the Delhi Liquor Policy. The Company Secretary of Aurobindo Pharma Ltd., B. Adi Reddy, has requested that this information be taken on record.</p><ul><li>Aurobindo Pharma Director, Mr. P. Sarath Chandra Reddy, discharged in Delhi Liquor Scam case</li><li>CBI case originated from FIR No. RC0032022A0053 dated 17.08.2022</li><li>Mr. P. Sarath Chandra Reddy discharged after court found no material against him</li><li>Court noted Reddy&apos;s absence in conspiracy or illegal benefit in Delhi Liquor Policy</li><li>Aurobindo Pharma requests information be taken on record</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3c3f08b1-1d03-4655-961c-1a50ef63c08e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AUROBINDO PHARMA LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INFOBEAN] Infobeans Technologies Ltd Announces 3:1 Bonus Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Infobeans+Technologies+Ltd&title=Infobeans+Technologies+Ltd+Announces+3%3A1+Bonus+Issue&newsId=31352b6e-20c3-4b2c-927b-1e98ff14dcb1&token=MzEzNTJiNmUtMjBj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">31352b6e-20c3-4b2c-927b-1e98ff14dcb1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Bonus</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Infobeans Technologies Ltd announced the allotment of 7,27,19,580 fully paid-up bonus equity shares in the proportion of 3:1 to eligible shareholders, whose names appeared in the Register of Shareholders or List of Beneficial Owners maintained by the Depositories as on the Record Date of February 27, 2026. This allotment has increased the company&apos;s paid-up equity share capital from INR 24,23,98,600 to INR 969,594,400. The fully paid-up bonus equity shares will rank pari-passu in all respects and carry the same rights as the existing equity shares of the company.</p><ul><li>Infobeans Technologies Ltd announces a 3:1 bonus issue</li><li>7,27,19,580 fully paid-up bonus equity shares allotted to eligible shareholders</li><li>Paid-up equity share capital increased from INR 24,23,98,600 to INR 969,594,400</li><li>Bonus equity shares to rank pari-passu with existing equity shares</li><li>Allotment based on shareholder names in the Register of Shareholders or List of Beneficial Owners maintained by the Depositories as on February 27, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8793f089-e614-4eb9-b902-f0d64d8c5c3a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Infobeans Technologies Ltd | Category: Bonus</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SEPC] SEPC Sees Neutral Financial Impact Amid Independent Audit Order</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SEPC+Ltd&title=SEPC+Sees+Neutral+Financial+Impact+Amid+Independent+Audit+Order&newsId=dc4ddc19-960d-4c2e-9d80-4d6b9a66b2c1&token=ZGM0ZGRjMTktOTYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc4ddc19-960d-4c2e-9d80-4d6b9a66b2c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SEPC Limited acknowledges the interim order from the Hon’ble High Court of Madras issued on February 19, 2026, involving the interim attachment of trade receivables as the court seeks a time-bound resolution to the dispute. The company&apos;s financial exposure is mitigated by a 2015 indemnity agreement with the co-respondent, Twarit Consultancy Services Private Ltd. SEPC continues as a going concern and remains committed to full transparency and strict adherence to SEBI listing guidelines. The dispute dates back to an original agreement executed in 2010 and progressed through a Singapore arbitral tribunal and the Indian court system.</p><ul><li>SEPC acknowledges interim order from the Hon’ble High Court of Madras</li><li>Trade receivables attached as court seeks time-bound resolution</li><li>Financial exposure mitigated by 2015 indemnity agreement with Twarit Consultancy</li><li>SEPC continues as a going concern and remains committed to transparency</li><li>Dispute dates back to 2010 and progressed through Singapore arbitral tribunal and Indian court system</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a525d219-81fb-4aae-931c-634e4c197165.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SEPC Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>