<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:20:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ITCHOTELS] ITC Hotels Ltd to Approve Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results on 20th January, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ITC+Hotels+Ltd&title=ITC+Hotels+Ltd+to+Approve+Unaudited+Standalone+and+Consolidated+Financial+Results+on+20th+January%2C+2026&newsId=a5456444-8201-4d9f-9328-b33680a696fd&token=YTU0NTY0NDQtODIw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5456444-8201-4d9f-9328-b33680a696fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>ITC Hotels Ltd has announced a Board Meeting scheduled on 20th January, 2026. The agenda of the meeting includes the consideration and approval of the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results along with the Segment-wise Revenue, Results, Assets and Liabilities (Consolidated) for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025.</p><ul><li>ITC Hotels Ltd has scheduled a Board Meeting on 20th January, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025</li><li>Segment-wise Revenue, Results, Assets and Liabilities (Consolidated) will also be discussed and approved</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2e4adbf7-ea6b-4ff6-a2f4-66b2faa33e83.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ITC Hotels Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[J&amp;KBANK] Jammu &amp; Kashmir Bank Ltd to Approve Unaudited Financial Results on 20th January, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JAMMU+%26+KASHMIR+BANK+LTD.&title=Jammu+%26+Kashmir+Bank+Ltd+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+on+20th+January%2C+2026&newsId=fbdfe4ba-4aed-4fe2-bf95-b79fe6ce88df&token=ZmJkZmU0YmEtNGFl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fbdfe4ba-4aed-4fe2-bf95-b79fe6ce88df</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jammu &amp; Kashmir Bank Ltd has informed BSE that the meeting of the Board of Directors of the Company is scheduled on 20th January, 2026. The Board will consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results (Consolidated and Standalone) of the Bank for the Quarter and Nine Months ended 31st December, 2025. The Trading Window for Designated Persons of the Bank and their relatives will reopen on January 23, 2026 i.e. after 48 hours of declaration of Financial Results of the Bank for the Quarter ended December, 2025.</p><ul><li>Jammu &amp; Kashmir Bank Ltd to consider and approve Unaudited Financial Results for the Quarter and Nine Months ended 31st December, 2025.</li><li>The meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on 20th January, 2026.</li><li>Trading Window for Designated Persons of the Bank and their relatives to reopen on January 23, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f49cf9cd-66cb-4e14-8986-2d08c3276f1b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JAMMU & KASHMIR BANK LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LAHL] Ladam Affordable Housing Ltd: Un-audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 2025 with Proposed Strike Off of Associate Companies</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ladam+Affordable+Housing+Ltd&title=Ladam+Affordable+Housing+Ltd%3A+Un-audited+Standalone+and+Consolidated+Financial+Results+for+Q3+2025+with+Proposed+Strike+Off+of+Associate+Companies&newsId=4a662295-c379-4473-998f-86b8e9fce814&token=NGE2NjIyOTUtYzM3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a662295-c379-4473-998f-86b8e9fce814</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ladam Affordable Housing Ltd. announced its un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company reported revenues, expenses, and profit before tax. The Board took note of the proposed strike off of the associate companies – Ladam Foods Private Limited and Lacon India Limited – which may impact the company&apos;s net worth. The Board also discussed the impact of the closure of associate companies on the financial position of the company. The trading window will open after 48 hours of the announcement of the results as per SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Un-audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 2025 announced</li><li>Revenues, expenses, and profit before tax reported</li><li>Proposed strike off of associate companies – Ladam Foods Private Limited and Lacon India Limited</li><li>Impact on the company&apos;s net worth due to closure of associate companies</li><li>Trading window to open after 48 hours of the announcement as per SEBI regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7587bb29-102e-49c2-bc37-76739d9775c3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ladam Affordable Housing Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AKZOINDIA] Akzo Nobel India Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on Feb 2, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Akzo+Nobel+India+Limited&title=Akzo+Nobel+India+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+Feb+2%2C+2026&newsId=f43c4a03-a587-4a36-b373-d3ae8dba0119&token=ZjQzYzRhMDMtYTU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f43c4a03-a587-4a36-b373-d3ae8dba0119</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Akzo Nobel India Ltd has announced a Board of Directors meeting on February 2, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31 December 2025. This meeting is in compliance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosures Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Akzo Nobel India Ltd scheduled a Board of Directors meeting on February 2, 2026</li><li>The meeting aims to consider and approve unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 and nine months of 2025</li><li>The decision is in accordance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosures Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9d42c32c-5f93-41ba-8201-758cdbfbf1b5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Akzo Nobel India Limited | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AKCAPIT] AK Capital Services Ltd Seeks No-Objection for Re-classification from &apos;Promoter Group&apos; to &apos;Public&apos; Category</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=A.K.CAPITAL+SERVICES+LTD.&title=AK+Capital+Services+Ltd+Seeks+No-Objection+for+Re-classification+from+%27Promoter+Group%27+to+%27Public%27+Category&newsId=593b1a75-17a9-4777-a134-974d5d6471b3&token=NTkzYjFhNzUtMTdh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">593b1a75-17a9-4777-a134-974d5d6471b3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:14:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>AK Capital Services Ltd has submitted an application with BSE Limited for seeking No-objection from Stock Exchange for the re-classification of the status of a member of &apos;Promoter Group&apos; category to &apos;Public&apos; category. The outgoing member, Mr. Abhinav Kumar Mittal, holds no shares in the company. The company requests to take this on record.</p><ul><li>AK Capital Services Ltd seeks re-classification from &apos;Promoter Group&apos; to &apos;Public&apos; category</li><li>Application submitted to BSE Limited for No-objection</li><li>Outgoing member, Mr. Abhinav Kumar Mittal, holds no shares in the company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5026dd87-7a23-48d2-aaa5-9070858ea2eb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: A.K.CAPITAL SERVICES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AKZOINDIA] Akzo Nobel India Ltd: Appointment of New Independent Director and Changes in Designations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Akzo+Nobel+India+Limited&title=Akzo+Nobel+India+Ltd%3A+Appointment+of+New+Independent+Director+and+Changes+in+Designations&newsId=138df99b-f089-4eb8-8f32-b97202c62759&token=MTM4ZGY5OWItZjA4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">138df99b-f089-4eb8-8f32-b97202c62759</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:11:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Akzo Nobel India Ltd announced the outcome of its board meeting held on 9th January 2026. The board appointed Mr. Shantanu Maharaj Khosla as an Additional Director in the category of an Independent Director for a period of three years till 8th January 2029. Mr. Rajiv Rajgopal was re-designated as &apos;Joint Managing Director &amp; Chief Executive Officer&apos;. Mr. Parth Jindal was appointed as an Additional Director in the category of Non-Executive Director (Non-independent) and designated as the Chairman of the Company.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Shantanu Maharaj Khosla as an Independent Director.</li><li>Re-designation of Mr. Rajiv Rajgopal as &apos;Joint Managing Director &amp; Chief Executive Officer&apos;.</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Parth Jindal as an Additional Director and designation as the Chairman of the Company.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8a1b71a5-721f-40d2-804e-3ba6531fdd78.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Akzo Nobel India Limited | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AKZOINDIA] Akzo Nobel India Ltd Receives Order from West Bengal GST Department for Tax Dispute</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Akzo+Nobel+India+Limited&title=Akzo+Nobel+India+Ltd+Receives+Order+from+West+Bengal+GST+Department+for+Tax+Dispute&newsId=d3778ca2-17c1-4972-90d8-9a70056b95a4&token=ZDM3NzhjYTItMTdj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3778ca2-17c1-4972-90d8-9a70056b95a4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Akzo Nobel India Ltd has received an order from the West Bengal GST Department regarding a show cause notice issued on 23 October 2025. The notice was for disallowance of ISD input tax credit under u/s 73 of CGST/SGST Act, 2017, carrying an aggregate demand amount of Rs. 62,75,220/-. The Company submitted its response along with supporting documents. The Senior Joint Commissioner, Large Taxpayer Unit, Corporate Division, West Bengal GST Department reviewed the reply and issued an Order dated 19&apos; December 2025, increasing the aggregate demand amount to Rs. 67,32,604/-. The Company is currently reviewing the Order for response purposes.</p><ul><li>Akzo Nobel India Ltd received an Order from the West Bengal GST Department</li><li>The Order is in relation to a show cause notice issued on 23 October 2025</li><li>The notice was for disallowance of ISD input tax credit under u/s 73 of CGST/SGST Act, 2017</li><li>The Company submitted its response along with supporting documents</li><li>The aggregate demand amount has been increased to Rs. 67,32,604/-</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/33d92310-9449-4b99-ae2e-c10a015bf963.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Akzo Nobel India Limited | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LAHL] Ladam Affordable Housing Ltd Approves Un-Audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q4 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ladam+Affordable+Housing+Ltd&title=Ladam+Affordable+Housing+Ltd+Approves+Un-Audited+Standalone+and+Consolidated+Financial+Results+for+Q4+2025&newsId=d45ddcbd-b544-4914-aab9-7142d4de1685&token=ZDQ1ZGRjYmQtYjU0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d45ddcbd-b544-4914-aab9-7142d4de1685</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:02:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ladam Affordable Housing Ltd has approved the Un-audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company also noted the intention of its associate companies, Ladam Foods Private Limited and Lacon India Limited, to file strike off applications as per the provisions of Section 248 (2) of the Companies Act, 2013. The Board acknowledged that such closure may impact the company&apos;s net worth. The trading window of the company will open after 48 hours after the announcement of the results.</p><ul><li>Ladam Affordable Housing Ltd approved Un-audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q4 2025.</li><li>The company noted the intention of its associate companies to file strike off applications.</li><li>Such closure may impact the company&apos;s net worth.</li><li>The trading window of the company will open after 48 hours after the announcement of the results.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/08530056-b388-441b-8523-b3c4005c8696.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ladam Affordable Housing Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AKZOINDIA] Akzo Nobel India Ltd Receives Order from Bihar GST Department for Tax Dispute</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Akzo+Nobel+India+Limited&title=Akzo+Nobel+India+Ltd+Receives+Order+from+Bihar+GST+Department+for+Tax+Dispute&newsId=bad5decb-3cb7-4f32-a549-b4c4bbd244fe&token=YmFkNWRlY2ItM2Ni</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bad5decb-3cb7-4f32-a549-b4c4bbd244fe</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Akzo Nobel India Ltd has received an order from the Bihar GST Department regarding a show cause notice issued on 24th September 2025. The notice was in relation to the period from April 2021 to March 2022, disallowing ISD input tax credit under u/s 73 of CGST/SGST Act, 2017, with an aggregate demand amount of Rs. 8,22,423/-. The Company submitted its response along with supporting documents. The Joint Commissioner of State Tax, Patna Special Circle, Bihar GST Department, reviewed the reply and issued an Order dated 26th December 2025, increasing the aggregate demand amount to Rs. 8,29,615/-. The Company is currently reviewing the Order for responding purposes.</p><ul><li>Akzo Nobel India Ltd received an Order from the Bihar GST Department</li><li>The Order is in relation to a show cause notice issued on 24th September 2025</li><li>The notice was regarding a tax dispute for the period from April 2021 to March 2022</li><li>The aggregate demand amount has been increased to Rs. 8,29,615/-</li><li>The Company is currently reviewing the Order for responding purposes</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/857172fb-4d7a-48bc-9df7-320030ffae3a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Akzo Nobel India Limited | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LAHL] Ladam Affordable Housing Ltd. Approves Q3 Results, Notes Strike Off Application by Associate Companies</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ladam+Affordable+Housing+Ltd&title=Ladam+Affordable+Housing+Ltd.+Approves+Q3+Results%2C+Notes+Strike+Off+Application+by+Associate+Companies&newsId=a28c7fc8-36b7-42d8-a757-11aa68a2243f&token=YTI4YzdmYzgtMzZi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a28c7fc8-36b7-42d8-a757-11aa68a2243f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ladam Affordable Housing Ltd. announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations for the quarter was Rs. 690 lakhs. The total expenses for the quarter stood at Rs. 4,920 lakhs, leading to a loss before tax of Rs. 4,230 lakhs. The company also noted that its associate companies, Ladam Foods Private Limited and Lacon India Limited, have applied for strike off as per the provisions of Section 248 (2) of the Companies Act, 2013. This may have an impact on the company&apos;s financial position, including its net worth. The trading window of the company will open after 48 hours of the announcement of the results.</p><ul><li>Ladam Affordable Housing Ltd. announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue from operations for the quarter was Rs. 690 lakhs.</li><li>The total expenses for the quarter stood at Rs. 4,920 lakhs, leading to a loss before tax of Rs. 4,230 lakhs.</li><li>Associate companies, Ladam Foods Private Limited and Lacon India Limited, have applied for strike off as per the provisions of Section 248 (2) of the Companies Act, 2013.</li><li>The closure of associate companies may have an impact on the company&apos;s financial position, including its net worth.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d19d1ada-ee86-4750-b0a5-5c72b79587bb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ladam Affordable Housing Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>