<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 06:28:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[AHLUCONT] Ahluwalia Contracts Secures Central Public Work Department Order for Central Vista Project at Delhi</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AHLUWALIA+CONTRACTS+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Ahluwalia+Contracts+Secures+Central+Public+Work+Department+Order+for+Central+Vista+Project+at+Delhi&newsId=6a11c489-8fa2-4ae7-8bbb-4e283e969fc6&token=NmExMWM0ODktOGZh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a11c489-8fa2-4ae7-8bbb-4e283e969fc6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 06:17:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Award</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Ahluwalia Contracts (India) Ltd has been awarded a significant order by the Central Public Work Department, New Delhi for the Construction of Common Central Secretarial Building. The project is an EPC project located at Plot No. 23 B &amp;C Maulana Azad Road, New Delhi. The total contract value is Rs. 3069.70 Crores (Including GST) and the time period for execution is 21 months. The order does not fall under related party transactions and is done at arms length.</p><ul><li>Ahluwalia Contracts secures order from Central Public Work Department for Central Vista Project at Delhi</li><li>Project value is Rs. 3069.70 Crores (Including GST)</li><li>Execution time period is 21 months</li><li>Project is an EPC project located at Plot No. 23 B &amp;C Maulana Azad Road, New Delhi</li><li>Order is not a related party transaction and is done at arms length</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4da0b4a1-4e56-4f4f-9d95-c96b2901af37.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AHLUWALIA CONTRACTS (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Award</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BLUESTONE] Bluestone Jewellery Board Meeting on Jan 22, 2026, to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Statements</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BlueStone+Jewellery+and+Lifestyle+Ltd&title=Bluestone+Jewellery+Board+Meeting+on+Jan+22%2C+2026%2C+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Statements&newsId=ce1fa326-83fb-437d-b5fb-fb3a822b6b0a&token=Y2UxZmEzMjYtODNm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce1fa326-83fb-437d-b5fb-fb3a822b6b0a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 06:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bluestone Jewellery And Lifestyle Ltd has informed BSE that the meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on 22/01/2026. The board will consider and approve the standalone as well as the consolidated Un-audited financial Statements of the Company for the quarter and the nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company by the Insiders/ Designated Persons is closed from Thursday, January 01, 2026 till 48 hours after declaration of the results.</p><ul><li>Bluestone Jewellery Board Meeting scheduled on January 22, 2026</li><li>Board to consider and approve Un-audited financial Statements for Q3 and nine months ended on December 31, 2025</li><li>Trading window for Insiders/ Designated Persons closed from January 01, 2026 till 48 hours after declaration of results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1895d597-c89b-43a8-9ed5-2eadaa1930df.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BlueStone Jewellery and Lifestyle Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TCI] Transport Corporation of India to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months of FY2025-2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TRANSPORT+CORPORATION+OF+INDIA+LTD.&title=Transport+Corporation+of+India+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+of+FY2025-2026&newsId=057944bd-f544-4c8a-a0cf-8483c8725961&token=MDU3OTQ0YmQtZjU0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">057944bd-f544-4c8a-a0cf-8483c8725961</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 06:16:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Transport Corporation Of India Ltd has informed BSE that the meeting of the Board of Directors of the Company is scheduled on 04/02/2026. The meeting will consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results (Standalone &amp; Consolidated) of the Company for the 3 quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for the purpose of trading in the shares of the Company has been closed from January 01, 2026, and will remain closed till February 06, 2026, in accordance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations.</p><ul><li>Transport Corporation of India to approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months of FY2025-2026</li><li>Trading window for the Company&apos;s shares closed from January 01, 2026, to February 06, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6a90c7c4-0949-4c98-a5f7-63162f5d34f9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TRANSPORT CORPORATION OF INDIA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HOMEFIRST] Home First Finance Company India Ltd to Approve Reviewed Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Home+First+Finance+Company+India+Ltd&title=Home+First+Finance+Company+India+Ltd+to+Approve+Reviewed+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=bb1f6000-6a6c-4569-9a7c-2f72158509b0&token=YmIxZjYwMDAtNmE2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb1f6000-6a6c-4569-9a7c-2f72158509b0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 06:11:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Home First Finance Company India Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 22, 2026, to consider and approve the Reviewed Financial Results of the Company for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting is scheduled in accordance with Regulation 29 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. Additionally, the company has informed that the trading window is closed for all Designated Persons and their immediate relatives from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of the reviewed financial results.</p><ul><li>Home First Finance Company India Ltd to consider and approve the Reviewed Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>The meeting is scheduled in accordance with Regulation 29 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Trading window is closed for all Designated Persons and their immediate relatives from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of the reviewed financial results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7ad4a612-537f-42ea-8751-1c6bd4726d44.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Home First Finance Company India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PALMJEWELS] Palm Jewels Ltd: No Pending Price-Sensitive Information, Price Movement Market-Driven</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Palm+Jewels+Ltd&title=Palm+Jewels+Ltd%3A+No+Pending+Price-Sensitive+Information%2C+Price+Movement+Market-Driven&newsId=60c9af17-eff7-4b2b-9f59-8af82f5355e7&token=NjBjOWFmMTctZWZm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60c9af17-eff7-4b2b-9f59-8af82f5355e7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 06:08:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Palm Jewels Ltd has clarified that there is no pending price-sensitive information that could have led to significant movement in the price behavior of the company&apos;s shares. The company ensures that all required information/announcements will be disclosed to the stock exchange as and when required.</p><ul><li>Palm Jewels Ltd has no pending price-sensitive information</li><li>The price movement of the company&apos;s shares is market-driven</li><li>The company will continue to disclose required information/announcements to the stock exchange</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5cc0b88f-7f85-48a4-93b6-2318f267ab7b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Palm Jewels Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHENTRA] Shentracon Chemicals Ltd: Acquirers Increase Offer Period to January 27, 2026, Due to Trading Holiday</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shentracon+Chemicals+Ltd&title=Shentracon+Chemicals+Ltd%3A+Acquirers+Increase+Offer+Period+to+January+27%2C+2026%2C+Due+to+Trading+Holiday&newsId=e7082fbc-acab-490e-a61e-b2587bb3b3e4&token=ZTcwODJmYmMtYWNh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e7082fbc-acab-490e-a61e-b2587bb3b3e4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 06:06:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Open Offer</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bonanza Portfolio Limited, the Manager to the Offer, has submitted a corrigendum to the Letter of Offer for Shentracon Chemicals Ltd. The acquirers, Mr. Amit Lalit Jain and Mr. Hanissh Kanakraj Jaain, have made an open offer to acquire 11,53,917 equity shares of Shentracon Chemicals Limited at a negotiated price of = 0.50 per share, representing 26.00% of the fully paid-up equity and voting share capital. Due to a trading holiday declared on January 15, 2026, the tendering period for the open offer has been extended, and the open offer will now close on January 27, 2026. The revised schedule of activities has been provided accordingly.</p><ul><li>Acquirers extend the open offer period to January 27, 2026, due to a trading holiday</li><li>Mr. Amit Lalit Jain and Mr. Hanissh Kanakraj Jaain make an open offer for 11,53,917 equity shares at = 0.50 per share</li><li>The open offer represents 26.00% of the fully paid-up equity and voting share capital of Shentracon Chemicals Limited</li><li>Trading holiday declared on January 15, 2026, affects the original closing date of the open offer</li><li>Revised schedule of activities provided for the open offer</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6EF95E25-8C7A-4F65-9E76-6FAA002FA9B6-113406.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shentracon Chemicals Ltd | Category: Open Offer</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GRASIM] Grasim Industries Ltd Appoints Mr. Sachin Sahay as Chief Executive Officer of Birla Opus Paints and as Senior Management Personnel</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GRASIM+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Grasim+Industries+Ltd+Appoints+Mr.+Sachin+Sahay+as+Chief+Executive+Officer+of+Birla+Opus+Paints+and+as+Senior+Management+Personnel&newsId=1d5bada7-f7e2-4581-bf4a-10990e4bd571&token=MWQ1YmFkYTctZjdl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d5bada7-f7e2-4581-bf4a-10990e4bd571</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 06:04:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Grasim Industries Ltd has appointed Mr. Sachin Sahay as the Chief Executive Officer of Birla Opus Paints and as Senior Management Personnel of the company. Mr. Sahay, who joins from ITC, brings over 30 years of leadership experience in Sales &amp; Marketing across various roles and geographies. He has played a pivotal role in ITC’s FMCG transformation journey and has led the launch and growth of multiple brands. The appointment is effective from 16th February 2026.</p><ul><li>Mr. Sachin Sahay appointed as Chief Executive Officer of Birla Opus Paints</li><li>Mr. Sahay also appointed as Senior Management Personnel of Grasim Industries Ltd</li><li>Mr. Sahay brings over 30 years of leadership experience in Sales &amp; Marketing</li><li>He has played a pivotal role in ITC’s FMCG transformation journey</li><li>Appointment is effective from 16th February 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c3d85c9d-e93f-4886-a5c0-403afed7a5d5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GRASIM INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JUBLFOOD] Jubilant Consumer Pvt Ltd Creates Pledge on Equity Shares of Jubilant FoodWorks Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jubilant+FoodWorks+Ltd&title=Jubilant+Consumer+Pvt+Ltd+Creates+Pledge+on+Equity+Shares+of+Jubilant+FoodWorks+Limited&newsId=8ca87de8-fe19-48f1-9a25-323bc05473a8&token=OGNhODdkZTgtZmUx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ca87de8-fe19-48f1-9a25-323bc05473a8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 05:59:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Pledge</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jubilant Consumer Pvt Ltd has created a pledge on equity shares of Jubilant FoodWorks Limited. The pledge was created on January 12, 2026, as per the Disclosure Form received by the Exchange under Regulation 31(1) and 31(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. The pledge is towards the security for the loan availed by Jubilant Enpro Private Limited.</p><ul><li>Jubilant Consumer Pvt Ltd creates a pledge on Jubilant FoodWorks Limited&apos;s equity shares.</li><li>The pledge was created on January 12, 2026.</li><li>The pledge is towards the security for the loan availed by Jubilant Enpro Private Limited.</li><li>The disclosure was made under Regulation 31(1) and 31(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/599D8625_C512_453D_B5F8_460FD26409AC_112807.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jubilant FoodWorks Ltd | Category: Pledge</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHRIRAMFIN] Shriram Finance Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on Jan 23, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shriram+Finance+Ltd&title=Shriram+Finance+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+Jan+23%2C+2026&newsId=a526bc2c-54e7-4199-b628-9145ebd0b840&token=YTUyNmJjMmMtNTRl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a526bc2c-54e7-4199-b628-9145ebd0b840</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 05:52:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shriram Finance Ltd has announced a Board Meeting on January 23, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will also approve a periodical resource mobilisation plan for issuance of debt securities.</p><ul><li>Shriram Finance Ltd to approve Q3 and nine months financial results on January 23, 2026</li><li>The company will consider and approve Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>A periodical resource mobilisation plan for issuance of debt securities will also be approved</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f4de6ceb-2923-4ee7-928a-0a6e26ace399.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shriram Finance Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ICICIBANK] Life Insurance Corporation of India Acquires 6.737% Shares in ICICI Bank Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ICICI+BANK+LTD.&title=Life+Insurance+Corporation+of+India+Acquires+6.737%25+Shares+in+ICICI+Bank+Ltd&newsId=b21e7f59-f620-4719-8844-36baf96b2b45&token=YjIxZTdmNTktZjYy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b21e7f59-f620-4719-8844-36baf96b2b45</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 05:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC) has acquired 6.737% shares in ICICI Bank Ltd. The acquisition includes 465122700 shares carrying voting rights, 0 shares with voting rights otherwise than by shares, and 0 warrants/convertible securities/any other instrument that entitles the acquirer to receive shares carrying voting rights in the Target Company (TC). The total holding before the acquisition was 44,28,74,11,722.00 and after the acquisition, it is 14,28,74,11,722.00. The mode of acquisition is not specified in the document.</p><ul><li>Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC) acquires 6.737% shares in ICICI Bank Ltd</li><li>The acquisition includes 465122700 shares carrying voting rights</li><li>The total holding before the acquisition was 44,28,74,11,722.00</li><li>After the acquisition, the total holding is 14,28,74,11,722.00</li><li>The mode of acquisition is not specified in the document</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/89612754_E536_4647_906C_3714AA4CB177_110544.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ICICI BANK LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>