<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 01:48:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[KRSNAA] Krsnaa Diagnostics Ltd. Re-Appoints Rajendra Khivraj Mutha as Executive Chairman for 5 Years</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Krsnaa+Diagnostics+Ltd&title=Krsnaa+Diagnostics+Ltd.+Re-Appoints+Rajendra+Khivraj+Mutha+as+Executive+Chairman+for+5+Years&newsId=a2adb547-485c-4fb2-8bbe-cae2a08eb028&token=YTJhZGI1NDctNDg1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2adb547-485c-4fb2-8bbe-cae2a08eb028</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 16:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Krsnaa Diagnostics Ltd. has announced the re-appointment of Rajendra Khivraj Mutha as Whole-time Director and Chairman, designated as Executive Chairman, for a term of five (5) consecutive years, with effect from April 26, 2026. Mutha, who brings over two decades of expertise in pharmacy diagnostics, is a certified Pharmacist accredited by the Maharashtra State Pharmacy Council. He is known for his extensive knowledge, strategic vision, and operational excellence. Mutha also leads the Company’s Corporate Social Responsibility (CSR) programmes, championing initiatives that uplift underserved communities and reinforce the Company’s role as a trusted healthcare partner. He is not related to any of the Directors on the Board of the Company and is not debarred from holding the office of Director by any SEBI order or any other such authority.</p><ul><li>Rajendra Khivraj Mutha re-appointed as Whole-time Director and Chairman, designated as Executive Chairman, for a term of five (5) consecutive years.</li><li>Mutha&apos;s re-appointment is subject to the approval of the shareholders’ through postal ballot.</li><li>Mutha is a certified Pharmacist with over two decades of expertise in pharmacy diagnostics.</li><li>Mutha leads the Company’s CSR programmes and outreach initiatives focused on community health, recognition of women, and children.</li><li>Mutha is not related to any of the Directors on the Board of the Company and is not debarred from holding the office of Director by any SEBI order or any other such authority.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6bb541e3-90cf-4c04-996d-96163ad6ab63.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Krsnaa Diagnostics Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AXISBANK] AXIS Bank Denies Bidding for Stake in CreditAccess Grameen</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AXIS+BANK+LTD.&title=AXIS+Bank+Denies+Bidding+for+Stake+in+CreditAccess+Grameen&newsId=dba3bd60-0d1f-4ee4-8493-c84f7267a715&token=ZGJhM2JkNjAtMGQx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dba3bd60-0d1f-4ee4-8493-c84f7267a715</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 15:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In response to recent queries, AXIS Bank has clarified that it has not submitted, nor is planning to submit, a bid for a stake in CreditAccess Grameen Limited. The bank is committed to complying with its disclosure obligations under the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>AXIS Bank has not submitted or planned to submit a bid for CreditAccess Grameen Limited</li><li>The bank is committed to complying with its disclosure obligations under SEBI regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8a59391e-31f7-4ed2-8e82-1dc3ebbf643c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AXIS BANK LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IDFCFIRSTB] IDFC First Bank Ltd Appoints KPMG for Forensic Audit</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IDFC+First+Bank+Ltd&title=IDFC+First+Bank+Ltd+Appoints+KPMG+for+Forensic+Audit&newsId=25b543b2-36b3-44c6-8f44-b2c584dc3f1d&token=MjViNTQzYjItMzZi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">25b543b2-36b3-44c6-8f44-b2c584dc3f1d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 15:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>IDFC First Bank Ltd has appointed KPMG to conduct an independent forensic audit, as part of the process initiated earlier. This decision is in compliance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI Listing Regulations and SEBI Master Circular dated January 30, 2026. The bank had previously disclosed its intention to appoint an external agency for this purpose on February 21, 2026. The disclosure is also being uploaded on the bank’s website.</p><ul><li>IDFC First Bank Ltd appoints KPMG for a forensic audit</li><li>Appointment is in compliance with SEBI Listing Regulations and SEBI Master Circular</li><li>Part of the process initiated earlier</li><li>Disclosure is also being uploaded on the bank’s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cbcae673-72e0-42ff-b047-2393872cb01e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IDFC First Bank Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IDFCFIRSTB] IDFC First Bank Ltd to Host Conference Call on Recent Developments</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IDFC+First+Bank+Ltd&title=IDFC+First+Bank+Ltd+to+Host+Conference+Call+on+Recent+Developments&newsId=d98f965b-6160-46a8-b4fc-581fced34568&token=ZDk4Zjk2NWItNjE2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d98f965b-6160-46a8-b4fc-581fced34568</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 14:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>IDFC First Bank Ltd has announced a conference call scheduled for February 23, 2026, at 08:00 a.m. IST. The call will provide a platform for the bank&apos;s senior management to discuss recent developments. The conference call details are as follows:</p><ul><li>IDFC First Bank Ltd to host a conference call on February 23, 2026</li><li>The conference call will discuss recent developments in the bank</li><li>The call will be held at 08:00 a.m. IST</li><li>Dial-in information is provided in the notification</li><li>Pre-registration link is also shared in the notification</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f7010e68-ff20-488e-b4cc-791e13943181.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IDFC First Bank Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUDARSHAN] SEBI Regulation 30: GST Department Initiates Inspection, Search, and Seizure at Sudarshan Pharma Industries Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sudarshan+Pharma+Industries+Ltd&title=SEBI+Regulation+30%3A+GST+Department+Initiates+Inspection%2C+Search%2C+and+Seizure+at+Sudarshan+Pharma+Industries+Ltd&newsId=670101b2-9d19-4a70-a904-c0db6d037299&token=NjcwMTAxYjItOWQx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">670101b2-9d19-4a70-a904-c0db6d037299</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 12:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sudarshan Pharma Industries Ltd, under SEBI Regulation 30, has confirmed an inspection, search, and seizure operation initiated by the Goods &amp; Service Tax Department, Mumbai Maharashtra, at their registered office. The company is fully cooperating with the GST Department and is in the process of collecting and responding to all queries. Upon conclusion of the event, any material developments will be intimated in due course. The business operations of the company continued as usual during the said event.</p><ul><li>SEBI Regulation 30 confirmation from Sudarshan Pharma Industries Ltd</li><li>GST Department inspection, search, and seizure operation initiated</li><li>Company is fully cooperating with the GST Department</li><li>Material developments to be intimated upon conclusion of the event</li><li>Business operations remained unaffected during the event</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1db1740b-330f-4c04-abed-197ed20121e1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sudarshan Pharma Industries Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STYLEBAAZA] Baazar Style Retail Ltd Opens New Store in Jharkhand, Expanding Retail Footprint to 258 Outlets</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Baazar+Style+Retail+Ltd&title=Baazar+Style+Retail+Ltd+Opens+New+Store+in+Jharkhand%2C+Expanding+Retail+Footprint+to+258+Outlets&newsId=12274189-e7a4-4e64-b88b-19fa354bc204&token=MTIyNzQxODktZTdh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12274189-e7a4-4e64-b88b-19fa354bc204</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 07:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Baazar Style Retail Ltd, formerly known as Baazar Style Retail Pvt. Ltd., has announced the opening of a new Style Baazar store in Morabadi, Jharkhand. This addition expands the company&apos;s total number of stores to 258, as of the date of this announcement. The company is committed to complying with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Baazar Style Retail Ltd has opened a new Style Baazar store in Morabadi, Jharkhand.</li><li>The company now has a total of 258 stores across various locations.</li><li>This announcement is in compliance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6ebce6d0-a861-4edf-ae74-59281ee8ba86.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Baazar Style Retail Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ICICIBANK] ICICI Bank Faces Rs. 50,38 Crore Tax Demand from Maharashtra GST Department</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ICICI+BANK+LTD.&title=ICICI+Bank+Faces+Rs.+50%2C38+Crore+Tax+Demand+from+Maharashtra+GST+Department&newsId=12ff3795-8524-4c38-966a-08791b22005b&token=MTJmZjM3OTUtODUy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12ff3795-8524-4c38-966a-08791b22005b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 06:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>On January 4, 2025, ICICI Bank Ltd received an order in original (OIO) from the Maharashtra Goods and Services Tax (GST) Department for a tax demand of Rs. 50,38,09,792/- and an equivalent amount of penalty and interest. The Bank filed an appeal against the OIO. On February 21, 2026, the Bank received an Order in Appeal (OIA) under Section 107 of the Central Goods and Services Tax Act, 2017 from the Maharashtra GST Department, maintaining the tax demand and penalty. The Bank plans to contest the OIA through a further appeal within prescribed timelines.</p><ul><li>ICICI Bank received an OIO from Maharashtra GST Department for a tax demand of Rs. 50,38 crore</li><li>The Bank filed an appeal against the OIO</li><li>Bank received an OIA under Section 107 of the Central Goods and Services Tax Act, 2017</li><li>OIA maintained the tax demand and penalty</li><li>ICICI Bank to contest the OIA through a further appeal</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9d4e04ee-0f4e-4f41-a2e7-17c86f3a6c45.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ICICI BANK LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[QUADRANT] Quadrant Televentures Ltd Extends Invitation for Expression of Interest</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Quadrant+Televentures+Limited-%24&title=Quadrant+Televentures+Ltd+Extends+Invitation+for+Expression+of+Interest&newsId=f2a9fd97-95e8-4409-b218-bbe59b9fded1&token=ZjJhOWZkOTctOTVl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f2a9fd97-95e8-4409-b218-bbe59b9fded1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 05:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Invitation for Expression of Interest</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Quadrant Televentures Ltd, a telecommunication and broadband services provider in Punjab and adjoining areas, has extended the last date for receipt of Expression of Interest (EOI) to 02.03.2026. The company, which reported a revenue of Rs. 273.97 Crores in FY 2024-2025, has a total of 1222 employees and its equity shares are listed with BSE. The last available financial statements and other relevant details can be obtained from the company&apos;s website or by sending an email to gtl.ibc@gmail.com. The eligibility criteria for resolution applicants are also available at the same location. The last date for submission of objections to the provisional list of prospective resolution applicants is now 17.03.2026.</p><ul><li>Quadrant Televentures Ltd extends last date for EOI to 02.03.2026</li><li>Company reported revenue of Rs. 273.97 Crores in FY 2024-2025</li><li>Total of 1222 employees</li><li>Equity shares listed with BSE</li><li>Last date for submission of objections to provisional list extended to 17.03.2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1461cfb0-3ed5-4ca0-9d67-77d3c441ebe7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Quadrant Televentures Limited-$ | Category: Invitation for Expression of Interest</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MINDSPACE] Mindspace EcoRun 2.0 Returns for Second Year with Over 4200 Runners in Hyderabad</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Mindspace+Business+Parks+REIT&title=Mindspace+EcoRun+2.0+Returns+for+Second+Year+with+Over+4200+Runners+in+Hyderabad&newsId=31f44fb1-0b90-49b4-b8fc-97cea2484487&token=MzFmNDRmYjEtMGI5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">31f44fb1-0b90-49b4-b8fc-97cea2484487</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 04:01:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mindspace Business Parks REIT, in association with Mirchi, successfully hosted the second edition of &apos;Mindspace EcoRun 2.0&apos; on February 22, 2026, at Mindspace Madhapur, Hyderabad. The sustainability-led marathon saw participation from over 4200 runners across different age groups. The event was designed around a planet-friendly experience, featuring eco-conscious race kits and waste management practices. Post-event, the waste collected will be upcycled into functional chairs for school children associated with the NGO partner Nirmaan.</p><ul><li>Mindspace REIT and Mirchi successfully hosted the second edition of Mindspace EcoRun 2.0 with over 4200 runners in Hyderabad.</li><li>The event was designed around a planet-friendly experience, incorporating eco-conscious race kits and waste management practices.</li><li>The waste collected post-event will be upcycled into functional chairs for school children associated with the NGO partner Nirmaan.</li><li>The marathon welcomed participants from different age groups, fostering a strong community turnout across Hyderabad’s workplace and neighbourhood ecosystem.</li><li>The second edition of Mindspace EcoRun reflects Mindspace REIT’s continued commitment to integrating sustainability into every aspect of their developments.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cf5725d1-b608-434a-b077-adcc43851200.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Mindspace Business Parks REIT | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IDFCFIRSTB] IDFC First Bank Ltd Identifies Fraudulent Activities of Approximately INR 590 Crore in a Chandigarh Branch</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IDFC+First+Bank+Ltd&title=IDFC+First+Bank+Ltd+Identifies+Fraudulent+Activities+of+Approximately+INR+590+Crore+in+a+Chandigarh+Branch&newsId=ad13fcdd-347c-45d0-9e72-1905abf28921&token=YWQxM2ZjZGQtMzQ3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad13fcdd-347c-45d0-9e72-1905abf28921</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 04:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>IDFC First Bank Ltd has identified unauthorized and fraudulent activities by certain employees at a particular branch in Chandigarh. The fraud involves accounts held by certain departments of the Government of Haryana and potentially other individuals/entities. The preliminary internal assessment shows an approximate reconciliation amount of INR 590 crore. The bank has taken actions including placing suspected officials under suspension, pursuing strict disciplinary, civil, and criminal actions, and cooperating with investigating agencies. An independent external agency has been appointed to conduct a forensic audit.</p><ul><li>IDFC First Bank Ltd identified fraudulent activities in a Chandigarh branch involving Government of Haryana accounts.</li><li>The preliminary internal assessment shows an approximate reconciliation amount of INR 590 crore.</li><li>Four suspected officials have been placed under suspension pending investigation.</li><li>An independent external agency has been appointed to conduct a forensic audit.</li><li>The bank has filed a complaint with the Police authorities and will extend full cooperation to the investigating agencies.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f52c7126-9362-4f4e-9110-09f1efe0f610.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IDFC First Bank Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>