<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 04:03:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[HDBFS] HDB Financial Services Ltd: Mr. Arijit Basu Resigns as Non-Executive Independent Director and Chairman</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HDB+Financial+Services+Ltd&title=HDB+Financial+Services+Ltd%3A+Mr.+Arijit+Basu+Resigns+as+Non-Executive+Independent+Director+and+Chairman&newsId=d2396437-4e25-4866-85d9-c0ce6136b55d&token=ZDIzOTY0MzctNGUy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2396437-4e25-4866-85d9-c0ce6136b55d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 03:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mr. Arijit Basu has resigned as the Non-Executive Independent Director and Chairman of HDB Financial Services Ltd. with immediate effect. The resignation is due to his consideration for the position of Non-Executive Director and Chairman of a bank in India, which presents a conflict of interest. Mr. Basu has served on the board for almost 5 years and has expressed his gratitude for the support received during his tenure.</p><ul><li>Mr. Arijit Basu has resigned as Non-Executive Independent Director and Chairman of HDB Financial Services Ltd.</li><li>The resignation is due to his consideration for a similar position in another bank, presenting a conflict of interest.</li><li>Mr. Basu has served on the board for almost 5 years.</li><li>He has expressed gratitude for the support received during his tenure.</li><li>The company has appreciated Mr. Basu&apos;s invaluable advice, stellar guidance, and support during his tenure.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0e54b4c4-771a-43aa-9387-dfde1e826234.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HDB Financial Services Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AXISCADES] AXISCADES Announces Strategic Hyperscaler win by its ESAI Division</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Axiscades+Technologies+Ltd&title=AXISCADES+Announces+Strategic+Hyperscaler+win+by+its+ESAI+Division&newsId=7520dece-889c-47fd-a94b-a1090a84825c&token=NzUyMGRlY2UtODg5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7520dece-889c-47fd-a94b-a1090a84825c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 03:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>AXISCADES Technologies Limited, a chip to product company and a pioneer in Aerospace, Defence, Electronics, Semiconductor and Artificial Intelligence applications, announces new wins in ESAI division by its subsidiary Mistral Solutions. This strategic contract pertains to testing of audio products of its Hyperscaler customer in the newly established Acoustic Lab in Aeroland facility, Bengaluru. This pilot order is for multiyear, valued at about $1Mn and is expected to generate more opportunities in innovative audio product development. These small form factor audio products stand out through advanced spatial audio processing, custom silicon for superior noise cancellation, and seamless integration with Al for proactive, ambient Al experiences.</p><ul><li>AXISCADES Technologies Limited announces new wins in ESAI division by its subsidiary Mistral Solutions</li><li>Strategic contract with a Hyperscaler customer for testing of audio products</li><li>Pilot order valued at about $1Mn for multiyear</li><li>Expected to generate more opportunities in innovative audio product development</li><li>Small form factor audio products with advanced spatial audio processing and custom silicon for superior noise cancellation</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/58e7743a-5add-4679-9a72-7c48af861445.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Axiscades Technologies Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AXISCADES] Axiscades&apos; Subsidiary, Mistral Solutions, Secures Multi-Year Contract for Testing Audio Products</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Axiscades+Technologies+Ltd&title=Axiscades%27+Subsidiary%2C+Mistral+Solutions%2C+Secures+Multi-Year+Contract+for+Testing+Audio+Products&newsId=9754742b-beec-42b4-8a4f-8172cee8f9de&token=OTc1NDc0MmItYmVl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9754742b-beec-42b4-8a4f-8172cee8f9de</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 03:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Axiscades Technologies Ltd&apos;s subsidiary, Mistral Solutions Pvt Ltd, has been awarded a multi-year contract worth around $1 Million for testing audio products in the newly established Acoustic Lab in Aeroland facility. The contract was awarded by a hyperscaler customer and does not involve any related party transactions.</p><ul><li>Axiscades&apos; subsidiary, Mistral Solutions, secures a multi-year contract for testing audio products.</li><li>The contract is worth around $1 Million.</li><li>The contract involves testing in the newly established Acoustic Lab in Aeroland facility.</li><li>The customer is a hyperscaler entity.</li><li>The contract does not involve any related party transactions.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3e147f4f-4fc3-4a12-8d47-6f165bf16eb0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Axiscades Technologies Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WHEELS] Wheels India Ltd Board Meeting to Approve Q3 Results &amp; Interim Dividend</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=WHEELS+INDIA+LTD.&title=Wheels+India+Ltd+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+Results+%26+Interim+Dividend&newsId=e190078b-74fb-42cd-9bd1-f9ee42988d17&token=ZTE5MDA3OGItNzRm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e190078b-74fb-42cd-9bd1-f9ee42988d17</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 03:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Wheels India Ltd has announced a board meeting scheduled for January 29, 2026, to consider the approval of unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine-months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will also consider and approve, if any, the interim dividend for the financial year ending March 31, 2026, and fix the record date for this purpose. In accordance with the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, the trading window closure period for designated persons and their immediate relatives has commenced from January 01, 2026, and will continue till 48 hours after the announcement of the unaudited financial results.</p><ul><li>Wheels India Ltd board meeting scheduled for January 29, 2026</li><li>Consideration of approval of unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine-months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Consideration and approval of interim dividend for the financial year ending March 31, 2026</li><li>Trading window closure for designated persons and their immediate relatives from January 01, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8124B46F-EDC1-452A-B6C8-2F8AAA6EF585-083021.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: WHEELS INDIA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUNPHARMA] Sun Pharma Receives DCGI Approval for Generic Semaglutide Injection in India for Chronic Weight Management</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SUN+PHARMACEUTICAL+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Sun+Pharma+Receives+DCGI+Approval+for+Generic+Semaglutide+Injection+in+India+for+Chronic+Weight+Management&newsId=bfa90c1c-25e6-4fdc-9abe-f1b6380116eb&token=YmZhOTBjMWMtMjVl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bfa90c1c-25e6-4fdc-9abe-f1b6380116eb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 02:52:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Limited has received approval from the Drugs Controller General of India (DCGI) to manufacture and market a generic version of semaglutide injection for chronic weight management in adults as an adjunct to a reduced calorie diet and increased physical activity. The product, named Noveltreat, will be launched after the expiry of semaglutide patent in India. The approval follows a review of a Phase III clinical trial conducted in India. Noveltreat will be available in five dose strengths and will be administered via a prefilled pen for convenient and accurate dosing.</p><ul><li>Sun Pharma receives DCGI approval for generic semaglutide injection in India for chronic weight management</li><li>Product to be launched under the brand name Noveltreat after the expiry of semaglutide patent in India</li><li>Received approval following a review of a Phase III clinical trial conducted in India</li><li>Product to be available in five dose strengths with a maintenance dose of 2.4 mg once weekly</li><li>Product to be administered via an easy-to-use prefilled pen for convenient and accurate dosing</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/35fc63fc-6317-425f-9194-c3cd3863254c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SUN PHARMACEUTICAL INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RNAVAL] Swan Defence And Heavy Industries Ltd Wins India&apos;s First Chemical Tanker Order; Largest Commercial Shipbuilding Deal for the Nation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Reliance+Naval+and+Engineering+Ltd&title=Swan+Defence+And+Heavy+Industries+Ltd+Wins+India%27s+First+Chemical+Tanker+Order%3B+Largest+Commercial+Shipbuilding+Deal+for+the+Nation&newsId=5821d5d3-72b0-4003-b14a-dc1c70308bff&token=NTgyMWQ1ZDMtNzJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5821d5d3-72b0-4003-b14a-dc1c70308bff</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 02:36:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Swan Defence And Heavy Industries Ltd (SDHI) has secured a contract valued at USD 227 million for six 18,000 DWT IMO Type II chemical tankers from Rederiet Stenersen AS. This is one of India&apos;s largest single commercial shipbuilding orders and the first chemical tanker order placed with an Indian shipyard. The contract also includes an option for six additional vessels. The first vessel is scheduled for delivery within 33 months. This order is a significant achievement for SDHI and a strong endorsement of India&apos;s growing commercial shipbuilding ecosystem.</p><ul><li>SDHI has won a contract worth USD 227 million for six 18,000 DWT IMO Type II chemical tankers from Rederiet Stenersen AS.</li><li>This is one of India&apos;s largest single commercial shipbuilding orders and the first chemical tanker order placed with an Indian shipyard.</li><li>The contract includes an option for six additional vessels.</li><li>The first vessel is scheduled for delivery within 33 months.</li><li>This order is a significant achievement for SDHI and a strong endorsement of India&apos;s growing commercial shipbuilding ecosystem.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/035bbdd5-5795-4239-b6fe-750a51817d4d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Reliance Naval and Engineering Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INFOBEAN] Infobeans Technologies Ltd Announces 3:1 Bonus and 173% YoY Increase in PAT for Q3 FY26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Infobeans+Technologies+Ltd&title=Infobeans+Technologies+Ltd+Announces+3%3A1+Bonus+and+173%25+YoY+Increase+in+PAT+for+Q3+FY26&newsId=52728b10-b5a0-4933-814f-fcfcbda4a44f&token=NTI3MjhiMTAtYjVh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">52728b10-b5a0-4933-814f-fcfcbda4a44f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Infobeans Technologies Limited, a leading global AI-driven digital transformation firm, has reported its Q3 FY26 results, showcasing a 38% year-on-year increase in revenue and a significant 173% jump in Profit After Tax (PAT). The company also announced a 3:1 bonus share issue, reflecting its confidence in its growth trajectory. The financial performance was driven by strong demand across all geographies and improvements in EBITDA and PAT margins.</p><ul><li>Revenue growth of 38% YoY, 30% in USD terms</li><li>PAT surged by 173% YoY</li><li>EBITDA improved by 89% YoY</li><li>Announced a 3:1 bonus share issue</li><li>Expanded client base and increased internal capacity</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b32ae427-4f3f-4c66-9f43-4a82616b83c1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Infobeans Technologies Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[COFORGE] Coforge Ltd Reports 28.5% YoY Revenue Growth in Q3 FY26, Signs Six Large Deals Worth $593 Mn</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Coforge+Ltd&title=Coforge+Ltd+Reports+28.5%25+YoY+Revenue+Growth+in+Q3+FY26%2C+Signs+Six+Large+Deals+Worth+%24593+Mn&newsId=115b7a8c-858c-4bac-b2c1-87d971546e9c&token=MTE1YjdhOGMtODU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">115b7a8c-858c-4bac-b2c1-87d971546e9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:01:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Coforge Ltd, a leading global IT solutions and services organization, announced its financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a 5.1% QoQ and 28.5% YoY growth in revenue, reaching INR 4,188 crore / USS 478.2 million. EBITDA stood at USS 83.4 Mn, up 37.7% YoY in USD terms. Six large deals were signed during the quarter, contributing to a $593 Mn TCV order intake. The executable order book stands at $1.72 Bn, up 30% YoY. The company&apos;s headcount stands at 35,341, with a net addition of 445 sequentially. The LTM Attrition Rate dropped to 10.9% against 11.4% in the last quarter.</p><ul><li>Revenue up 5.1% QoQ, 28.5% YoY and 37.3% YTD</li><li>Six large deals signed during the quarter, contributing to $593 Mn TCV order intake</li><li>Executable order book stands at $1.72 Bn, up 30% YoY</li><li>Headcount at 35,341, with a net addition of 445 sequentially</li><li>LTM Attrition Rate dropped to 10.9% against 11.4% in the last quarter</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/85147d46-856e-4bd8-adf5-da7a31f26ad0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Coforge Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INFOBEAN] Infobeans Technologies Ltd. Fixes Record Date for Bonus Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Infobeans+Technologies+Ltd&title=Infobeans+Technologies+Ltd.+Fixes+Record+Date+for+Bonus+Equity+Shares&newsId=1103363b-d7d0-479a-ad3d-bb3ff536692e&token=MTEwMzM2M2ItZDdk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1103363b-d7d0-479a-ad3d-bb3ff536692e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Bonus</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Infobeans Technologies Ltd. has announced that the record date for determining the entitlement of members to receive bonus equity shares will be 27th February, 2026. This decision was made following the outcome of the Board Meeting held on 22nd January, 2026.</p><ul><li>Infobeans Technologies Ltd. has set the record date for bonus equity shares determination.</li><li>The record date is 27th February, 2026.</li><li>The decision was made following the Board Meeting on 22nd January, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/50a21b8f-81ff-4203-b182-80fbba85a1f1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Infobeans Technologies Ltd | Category: Bonus</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHANTIGEAR] Shanthi Gears Ltd: Interim Dividend Declared, CFO to Step Down, Q3 Financial Results Released</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHANTHI+GEARS+LTD.&title=Shanthi+Gears+Ltd%3A+Interim+Dividend+Declared%2C+CFO+to+Step+Down%2C+Q3+Financial+Results+Released&newsId=854b4ce2-eb07-4228-b18d-570ef297e196&token=ODU0YjRjZTItZWIw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">854b4ce2-eb07-4228-b18d-570ef297e196</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:47:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shanthi Gears Ltd has declared an interim dividend of Rs. 3/- per Equity Share for the financial year 2025-26. The company&apos;s Chief Financial Officer, Mr. Ranjan Kumar Pati, will be stepping down effective from 19th March 2026. The company has also released its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025, showing a revenue of X116.82 Crores and a profit before tax of X21.59 Crores.</p><ul><li>Interim dividend of Rs. 3/- per Equity Share declared for the financial year 2025-26</li><li>Mr. Ranjan Kumar Pati, CFO, to step down from his position effective from 19th March 2026</li><li>Revenue of X116.82 Crores recorded in Q3 FY26</li><li>Profit before tax of X21.59 Crores in Q3 FY26</li><li>Achieved Return on average Invested Capital (ROIC) of 31% in Q3 FY26</li><li>Negative Free Cash Flow of X1.72 Crores during Q3 FY26</li><li>Highest-ever order booking of 169 Crores in Q3 FY26 with 28% growth over Q3FY25</li><li>Unexecuted order book as on 31st December 2025 stood at X 305 Crores</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9f657956-f5fc-4444-a120-4a3edf4d9503.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHANTHI GEARS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>