<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:46:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[BENARAS] Benares Hotels Ltd Appoints Sumit Singh Deol as Chief Executive Officer (CEO) w.e.f. 24.02.2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BENARES+HOTELS+LTD.&title=Benares+Hotels+Ltd+Appoints+Sumit+Singh+Deol+as+Chief+Executive+Officer+%28CEO%29+w.e.f.+24.02.2026&newsId=c415c955-6ad1-4167-bc80-dee736910906&token=YzQxNWM5NTUtNmFk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c415c955-6ad1-4167-bc80-dee736910906</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:45:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Benares Hotels Ltd announced the appointment of Mr. Sumit Singh Deol as the Chief Executive Officer (CEO) and Key Managerial Personnel (KMP) of the company, effective from February 24, 2026. The appointment was made during a board meeting, based on the recommendations of the Nomination and Remuneration Committee. Mr. Deol is an experienced professional in the field of Food &amp; Beverage and General Management, having worked with IHCL since 2010. He has been recognized with various awards for his contributions.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Sumit Singh Deol as Chief Executive Officer (CEO) of Benares Hotels Ltd.</li><li>Mr. Deol&apos;s vast experience in Food &amp; Beverage and General Management.</li><li>The appointment is effective from February 24, 2026.</li><li>Mr. Deol has been awarded various laurels for his contributions.</li><li>The decision was made during a board meeting based on the recommendations of the Nomination and Remuneration Committee.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a29479d1-addf-419e-95b1-1d43b4c43db0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BENARES HOTELS LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CENTUM] Centum Electronics Secures Order from HAL for AESA Radar System Worth INR 78 Crore in Phase-1</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CENTUM+ELECTRONICS+LTD.&title=Centum+Electronics+Secures+Order+from+HAL+for+AESA+Radar+System+Worth+INR+78+Crore+in+Phase-1&newsId=aba1665c-6bd4-431d-96da-82932ce42c87&token=YWJhMTY2NWMtNmJk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aba1665c-6bd4-431d-96da-82932ce42c87</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:43:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Centum Electronics Limited, a leading Indian electronics system design and manufacturing company, has received an order from Hindustan Aeronautics Limited (HAL) for the design and development of Active Electronically Scanned Array (AESA) Radar Systems for the Utility Helicopter—Maritime (UH-M) platform. The Phase-1 order, worth INR 78 crore, involves the delivery of AESA radar systems over the next two financial years. Upon successful execution, the programme is expected to progress to Phase-2, involving serial production and supply of AESA radar systems over five years, with an estimated value of INR 500 crore. This order marks a significant milestone for Centum, demonstrating its capabilities in advanced radar and mission-critical defence electronics.</p><ul><li>Centum Electronics secures order from HAL for AESA Radar Systems worth INR 78 crore in Phase-1.</li><li>Order involves design and development of AESA radar systems for Utility Helicopter—Maritime (UH-M) platform.</li><li>Successful execution of Phase-1 may lead to Phase-2 with an estimated value of INR 500 crore.</li><li>Centum to demonstrate advanced radar and mission-critical defence electronics capabilities.</li><li>Order strengthens long-standing relationship between Centum and HAL.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cb184900-07cc-4f35-a320-15643fe0e382.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CENTUM ELECTRONICS LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CYIENT] Cyient Foundation Recognises Student Innovations at Pitch Fest 2026 with Cash Awards</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Cyient+Limited&title=Cyient+Foundation+Recognises+Student+Innovations+at+Pitch+Fest+2026+with+Cash+Awards&newsId=b59d8178-aa93-4d0e-a696-e02e8c1f08d0&token=YjU5ZDgxNzgtYWE5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b59d8178-aa93-4d0e-a696-e02e8c1f08d0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:43:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Cyient Foundation Pitch Fest 2026, organized in partnership with ICT Academy, brought together promising student entrepreneurs from leading engineering institutions across Telangana and Andhra Pradesh. The initiative witnessed an enthusiastic response, with over 2,000 students from 40 colleges participating. Following multiple rounds of evaluation and live pitching before an eminent jury, five outstanding ideas were selected as winners, with each winning team receiving a cash award in recognition of their innovation and entrepreneurial spirit.</p><ul><li>Cyient Foundation and ICT Academy organized Pitch Fest 2026 for student entrepreneurs across Telangana and Andhra Pradesh</li><li>Over 2,000 students from 40 colleges participated in the initiative</li><li>Five winning teams received cash awards for their innovative and socially relevant business ideas</li><li>The programme aimed to foster innovation, problem-solving, and startup thinking among students</li><li>Cyient Foundation&apos;s continued commitment to empowering youth through education, skill development, and innovation-led opportunities</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c30833b4-4041-402d-8055-c8558041fcd8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Cyient Limited | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IDFCFIRSTB] IDFC First Bank Pays INR 583 Crore to Haryana Government Despite Ongoing Fraud Investigation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IDFC+First+Bank+Ltd&title=IDFC+First+Bank+Pays+INR+583+Crore+to+Haryana+Government+Despite+Ongoing+Fraud+Investigation&newsId=8cef1099-5ec3-49fd-b360-2287dd9b5b50&token=OGNlZjEwOTktNWVj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8cef1099-5ec3-49fd-b360-2287dd9b5b50</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:43:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>IDFC First Bank Ltd. has paid INR 583 crore to the relevant departments of the Haryana Government, which includes the principal and interest claimed, despite an ongoing investigation in the matter. The payment was made in accordance with the bank&apos;s principle-based approach, which prioritizes customer interests. The bank remains committed to working with the Haryana Government departments and law enforcement agencies to pursue actions against the perpetrators and recover its dues. As of December 31, 2025, the bank has a strong financial position with high asset quality, strong capital adequacy, and a growing customer base. The bank is currently in an investment stage, focusing on building out products, technology, distribution, and other universal banking solutions. The bank expects to be strongly back in the trajectory of profits from FY’27 onwards.</p><ul><li>IDFC First Bank paid INR 583 crore to Haryana Government departments despite an ongoing fraud investigation.</li><li>The payment was made in accordance with the bank&apos;s principle-based approach and commitment to customer interests.</li><li>The bank remains committed to pursuing actions against the perpetrators and recovering its dues.</li><li>As of December 31, 2025, the bank has a strong financial position with high asset quality and strong capital adequacy.</li><li>The bank is currently in an investment stage, focusing on building out products, technology, distribution, and other universal banking solutions.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c6af9247-02cf-46df-ac66-01c74b4ce07a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IDFC First Bank Ltd | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SPARC] Sun Pharma Advanced Research Company Ltd Addendum to Valuation Report</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SUN+PHARMA+ADVANCED+RESEARCH+COMPANY+LTD.&title=Sun+Pharma+Advanced+Research+Company+Ltd+Addendum+to+Valuation+Report&newsId=4f2acb0b-47f1-46d6-9a07-292e5d2f88fe&token=NGYyYWNiMGItNDdm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4f2acb0b-47f1-46d6-9a07-292e5d2f88fe</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:42:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Valuation Report</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sun Pharma Advanced Research Company Ltd has submitted an addendum to the valuation report in response to a query from the National Stock Exchange of India. The addendum clarifies certain points in the original valuation report, including the scope of information and the reasoning for not using the Discounted Cash Flow (DCF) method. The company&apos;s operations, which are predominantly focused on pre-clinical research, clinical trial execution, and development of novel pharmaceutical technologies, make it difficult to project future cash flows reliably. The company does not have an established or recurring revenue generating business model, and any income from R&amp;D outcomes is inherently uncertain. The management has not furnished any financial projections for the company, making the DCF method inappropriate for valuing the company.</p><ul><li>Addendum to the Valuation Report submitted to the National Stock Exchange of India</li><li>Clarifications provided in response to a query from the National Stock Exchange of India</li><li>Difficulty in projecting future cash flows due to the nature of the company&apos;s operations</li><li>Lack of an established or recurring revenue generating business model</li><li>Inappropriateness of the DCF method for valuing the company due to the lack of predictable future revenues</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b177cbbe-88d9-43a8-a455-6f4e40af350a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SUN PHARMA ADVANCED RESEARCH COMPANY LTD. | Category: Valuation Report</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SOMAPPR] KS Smart Solutions Private Limited Wins ₹ 33.80 Crore Project from Haryana State Electronics Development Corporation Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SOMA+PAPERS+%26+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=KS+Smart+Solutions+Private+Limited+Wins+%E2%82%B9+33.80+Crore+Project+from+Haryana+State+Electronics+Development+Corporation+Limited&newsId=3c5a67bf-6570-40da-9c74-4f5013654b77&token=M2M1YTY3YmYtNjU3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3c5a67bf-6570-40da-9c74-4f5013654b77</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:42:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>KS Smart Solutions Private Limited, a wholly owned subsidiary of KS Smart Technologies Ltd, has been awarded a project valued at approximately ₹ 33.80 crore by Haryana State Electronics Development Corporation Limited, a State Government undertaking. The project involves the deployment of 29,236 smartphones embedded with Poshan Tracking Software under the World Bank aided ICDS Project-1II of the Social Welfare and Nutritious Meal Programme Department, Government of Tamil Nadu.</p><ul><li>KS Smart Solutions Private Limited has been awarded a project worth approximately ₹ 33.80 crore by Haryana State Electronics Development Corporation Limited.</li><li>The project involves the deployment of 29,236 smartphones embedded with Poshan Tracking Software under the World Bank aided ICDS Project-1II.</li><li>The project is for the Social Welfare and Nutritious Meal Programme Department, Government of Tamil Nadu.</li><li>The project is expected to be completed by not later than 21.05.2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1343ffa3-fc5b-4991-aa0e-7c0325606cf6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SOMA PAPERS & INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZSANMCOM] Sanmitra Commercial Ltd Board Meeting on 27/02/2026: Composition Changes, Committee Reconstitution, and Other Decisions</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SANMITRA+COMMERCIAL+LTD.&title=Sanmitra+Commercial+Ltd+Board+Meeting+on+27%2F02%2F2026%3A+Composition+Changes%2C+Committee+Reconstitution%2C+and+Other+Decisions&newsId=185105ec-f746-47cc-a4b3-f86ea9064b7e&token=MTg1MTA1ZWMtZjc0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">185105ec-f746-47cc-a4b3-f86ea9064b7e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:41:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sanmitra Commercial Ltd has informed BSE that a Board of Directors meeting is scheduled for 27th February 2026. The agenda includes considering and approving changes in the Board composition following the open offer process, reconstitution of various Committees, and addressing other incidental and ancillary matters. The meeting will be held in accordance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, and the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</p><ul><li>Change in the composition of the Board of Directors following the open offer process</li><li>Reconstitution of various Committees of the Board</li><li>Addressing other incidental and ancillary matters</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ef135a7f-b89b-4a0d-beea-4aaf53dd5620.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SANMITRA COMMERCIAL LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CPPLUS] Aditya Infotech Ltd Promoters Plan to Sell 2% Shares to Comply with Minimum Public Shareholding</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Aditya+Infotech+Ltd&title=Aditya+Infotech+Ltd+Promoters+Plan+to+Sell+2%25+Shares+to+Comply+with+Minimum+Public+Shareholding&newsId=fd96df25-561b-46da-a9d3-dec1826999da&token=ZmQ5NmRmMjUtNTYx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd96df25-561b-46da-a9d3-dec1826999da</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:38:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Sale</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Aditya Infotech Ltd promoters, Hari Khemka Business Family Trust and Mr. Rishi Khemka, have expressed their intention to sell Equity Shares of the Company to meet the minimum public shareholding requirements. The proposed sale will involve up to 2% of the total paid-up equity share capital, amounting to 23,55,961 shares, within a period starting from February 25, 2026, and ending on March 05, 2026, or earlier, depending on the completion of the sale. The current promoter and promoter group shareholding stands at 76.74% of the total paid-up equity share capital.</p><ul><li>Aditya Infotech Ltd promoters plan to sell Equity Shares to meet minimum public shareholding requirements.</li><li>The proposed sale involves up to 2% of the total paid-up equity share capital, amounting to 23,55,961 shares.</li><li>The sale period is set to begin on February 25, 2026, and end on March 05, 2026, or earlier.</li><li>The current promoter and promoter group shareholding is 76.74% of the total paid-up equity share capital.</li><li>No promoter or promoter group member will buy shares in the open market during the sale period.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2a020cb4-2b96-412a-bfd7-6c57308ab2b7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Aditya Infotech Ltd | Category: Sale</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ANGELONE] Angel One Ltd. Approves Allotment of 5,000 Non-Convertible Debentures worth INR 50 Crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Angel+One+Ltd&title=Angel+One+Ltd.+Approves+Allotment+of+5%2C000+Non-Convertible+Debentures+worth+INR+50+Crore&newsId=b27d24f3-0055-4655-93e2-4f73961c0ec8&token=YjI3ZDI0ZjMtMDA1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b27d24f3-0055-4655-93e2-4f73961c0ec8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:36:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Angel One Ltd. announced the allotment of 5,000 Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs) worth INR 50 Crore. The NCDs, having a face value of INR 1,00,000 each, will be listed on the Wholesale Debt Market Segment of the National Stock Exchange of India Limited (NSE). The tenure of the instrument is 18 months, with the first coupon to be paid on August 25, 2026, and the principal to be redeemed on August 25, 2027. The company has created a first pari-passu charge by way of hypothecation over all present and future trade receivables and loans in the form of margin trading facilities of the Company.</p><ul><li>Angel One Ltd. allotted 5,000 Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs) worth INR 50 Crore.</li><li>The NCDs are proposed to be listed on the Wholesale Debt Market Segment of the National Stock Exchange of India Limited (NSE).</li><li>The tenure of the instrument is 18 months.</li><li>The first coupon will be paid on August 25, 2026, and the principal will be redeemed on August 25, 2027.</li><li>A first pari-passu charge by way of hypothecation has been created over the company&apos;s assets.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/993f3b02-a253-4bba-b5c2-b8a48b8c434b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Angel One Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UMAEXPORTS] Uma Exports Ltd: Non-Executive Non-Independent Director, Ms. Mansi Khemka, Resigns Effective February 24, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Uma+Exports+Ltd&title=Uma+Exports+Ltd%3A+Non-Executive+Non-Independent+Director%2C+Ms.+Mansi+Khemka%2C+Resigns+Effective+February+24%2C+2026&newsId=e4f0bb26-1652-4e6b-a2bc-2eaed8e3d790&token=ZTRmMGJiMjYtMTY1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e4f0bb26-1652-4e6b-a2bc-2eaed8e3d790</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 09:36:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Uma Exports Ltd has announced the resignation of its Non-Executive Non-Independent Director, Ms. Mansi Khemka, with effect from the close of business hours on February 24, 2026. The resignation is due to her pre-occupancy in her own business ventures. Ms. Khemka confirmed that there are no other material reasons for her resignation. The company has provided the necessary details as per Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015 and the Master Circular SEBI/HO/CFD/PoD2/CIR/P/0155 dated November 11, 2024.</p><ul><li>Ms. Mansi Khemka has resigned as a Non-Executive Non-Independent Director of Uma Exports Ltd.</li><li>The resignation is effective from the close of business hours on February 24, 2026.</li><li>The resignation is due to Ms. Khemka&apos;s pre-occupancy in her own business ventures.</li><li>Ms. Khemka confirmed that there are no other material reasons for her resignation.</li><li>The company has provided the necessary details as per SEBI regulations and Master Circular.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e580ae75-58c7-4ef9-bd96-8b5164552d81.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Uma Exports Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>