<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 12:38:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[GOCOLORS] Go Fashion (India) Ltd Announces Board Meeting to Consider Buy-Back of Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Go+Fashion+%28India%29+Ltd&title=Go+Fashion+%28India%29+Ltd+Announces+Board+Meeting+to+Consider+Buy-Back+of+Equity+Shares&newsId=d9f014ad-7027-43de-900a-b91fc50bd0e7&token=ZDlmMDE0YWQtNzAy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d9f014ad-7027-43de-900a-b91fc50bd0e7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 12:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Go Fashion (India) Ltd has informed the BSE that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on 29/01/2026. The agenda includes consideration and approval of Update on board meeting &amp; Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and year to date ended December 31* 2025, and a proposal for buy-back of equity shares of the Company in accordance with the SEBI (Buy-Back of Securities) Regulations, 2018, as amended.</p><ul><li>Go Fashion (India) Ltd has scheduled a Board Meeting on 29/01/2026</li><li>The agenda includes consideration and approval of Update on board meeting &amp; Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>The Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and year to date ended December 31* 2025 will be considered</li><li>A proposal for buy-back of equity shares of the Company will be discussed</li><li>The buy-back proposal will be in accordance with the SEBI (Buy-Back of Securities) Regulations, 2018, as amended</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/aca511e1-52a4-4317-9774-470187048eb4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Go Fashion (India) Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CAPPIPES] Captain Pipes Ltd to Approve Q4 &amp; FY2025 Results on Feb 7, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Captain+Pipes+Ltd&title=Captain+Pipes+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+%26+FY2025+Results+on+Feb+7%2C+2026&newsId=57a9a010-89b6-4bfa-92b6-02870597b69a&token=NTdhOWEwMTAtODli</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57a9a010-89b6-4bfa-92b6-02870597b69a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 12:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Captain Pipes Ltd has scheduled a Board Meeting on February 7, 2026, to consider and approve the standalone and consolidated unaudited financial results for the quarter and year ended on December 31, 2025. The trading window for directors, promoters, designated employees, and connected persons will be closed from January 1, 2026, and will reopen 48 hours after the results are made public.</p><ul><li>Captain Pipes Ltd to hold a Board Meeting on February 7, 2026</li><li>Meeting to consider and approve Q4 and FY2025 financial results</li><li>Trading window for insiders to close from January 1, 2026</li><li>Trading window to reopen 48 hours after results are made public</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/293c4eae-9cd8-477b-9df0-ca3b05207880.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Captain Pipes Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CPL] Captain Polyplast Ltd. to Approve Q3 FY2025-26 Financial Results on Feb 7, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Captain+Polyplast+Ltd&title=Captain+Polyplast+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q3+FY2025-26+Financial+Results+on+Feb+7%2C+2026&newsId=a8125447-2ae2-42cf-ab39-84406b02acca&token=YTgxMjU0NDctMmFl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8125447-2ae2-42cf-ab39-84406b02acca</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 12:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Captain Polyplast Ltd. has informed BSE that their Board of Directors will meet on February 7, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025. The Trading Window Close Period has commenced from December 1, 2026, and will end 48 hours after the results are made public.</p><ul><li>Captain Polyplast Ltd. to consider and approve Q3 FY2025-26 financial results</li><li>Board meeting scheduled on 7th February 2026</li><li>Financial results pertain to the quarter ended on 31st December 2025</li><li>Trading Window Close Period from December 1, 2026, to 48 hours after results are made public</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/69be9186-da69-4cf7-9eeb-f9a85447f9a9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Captain Polyplast Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASTONEALAB] Astonea Labs Ltd Incorporates Wholly-Owned Foreign Subsidiary in the USA</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Astonea+Labs+Ltd&title=Astonea+Labs+Ltd+Incorporates+Wholly-Owned+Foreign+Subsidiary+in+the+USA&newsId=d232b86a-93bf-463e-99e4-48605a1e6197&token=ZDIzMmI4NmEtOTNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d232b86a-93bf-463e-99e4-48605a1e6197</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Astonea Labs Limited has incorporated a wholly-owned foreign subsidiary, Astonea LLC, in Sheridan, Wyoming, USA. The new subsidiary, which was incorporated on 25th January 2026, will be engaged in the business of Pharmaceuticals, Food Supplements, and Cosmetics. Astonea Labs Limited holds 100% of the membership interests of Astonea LLC, making it a wholly-owned foreign subsidiary. The promoters/promoter group have no interest in Astonea LLC, except to the extent of their interest as members of Astonea Labs Limited. Astonea LLC is newly incorporated and has no history of last 3 years turnover. The entity is present in the United States of America (USA) and has a GSTIN NO.: 06AAPCA4446E1ZP and CIN: L24304CH2017PLC041482.</p><ul><li>Astonea Labs Ltd incorporates a wholly-owned foreign subsidiary, Astonea LLC, in the USA</li><li>Astonea LLC is engaged in the business of Pharmaceuticals, Food Supplements, and Cosmetics</li><li>Astonea Labs Limited holds 100% of the membership interests of Astonea LLC</li><li>Astonea LLC is a newly incorporated entity with no history of last 3 years turnover</li><li>Astonea LLC is present in the United States of America (USA)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b4109f30-8cfb-4a21-a845-92f0cd7eeb7d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Astonea Labs Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MIC] MIC Electronics Ltd to Approve Q3 FY2025-26 Financial Results on Jan 31, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MIC+ELECTRONICS+LTD.&title=MIC+Electronics+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+FY2025-26+Financial+Results+on+Jan+31%2C+2026&newsId=7cb34908-7086-4074-843c-8b4be3b3d8cf&token=N2NiMzQ5MDgtNzA4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7cb34908-7086-4074-843c-8b4be3b3d8cf</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>MIC Electronics Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 31, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited (Standalone &amp; Consolidated) Financial Results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will also consider the Limited Review Report of the Statutory Auditors for the same quarter.</p><ul><li>MIC Electronics Ltd to approve Q3 FY2025-26 financial results on January 31, 2026</li><li>The approval will include Unaudited Standalone &amp; Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025</li><li>The meeting will also consider the Limited Review Report of the Statutory Auditors for the same quarter</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fa131582-c062-4bff-b725-ed11ed19bb16.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MIC ELECTRONICS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VEL] Vaxfab Enterprises Ltd. Corrects Typographic Error in Warrant Conversion Shares Allotment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vaxfab+Enterprises+Ltd&title=Vaxfab+Enterprises+Ltd.+Corrects+Typographic+Error+in+Warrant+Conversion+Shares+Allotment&newsId=4067a81e-ba26-4884-b21b-8ee987dfd9e8&token=NDA2N2E4MWUtYmEy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4067a81e-ba26-4884-b21b-8ee987dfd9e8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vaxfab Enterprises Ltd. has corrected a typographic error in the number of equity shares allotted pursuant to conversion of warrants by three individuals. The corrected allotment figures are 95,147 shares to Mr. Rakesh Shamji Patel, 118,934 shares to Mr. Sameet Khatri, and 237,869 shares to Ms. Mita Hitesh Ajmera. Additionally, the company&apos;s Board of Directors approved the allotment of 34,39,136 equity shares to investor(s) upon conversion of warrants at a price of Rs. 21.02 per share. This allotment increased the company&apos;s Paid-up Equity Share Capital to Rs. 16,04,94,890.</p><ul><li>Vaxfab Enterprises Ltd. corrects a typographic error in the number of equity shares allotted pursuant to conversion of warrants.</li><li>The corrected allotment figures for Mr. Rakesh Shamji Patel, Mr. Sameet Khatri, and Ms. Mita Hitesh Ajmera have been provided.</li><li>The company&apos;s Board of Directors approved the allotment of 34,39,136 equity shares to investor(s) upon conversion of warrants.</li><li>The Equity Shares allotted on exercise of conversion of Warrants shall rank pari-passu in all respects with the existing Equity Shares of the Company.</li><li>The Paid-up Equity Share Capital of the Company increased to Rs. 16,04,94,890 after the aforementioned allotment.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bd5f8981-ff28-4840-baeb-65d5ca1a92b0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vaxfab Enterprises Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PSB] Punjab &amp; Sind Bank Branches May Be Affected by Proposed U.F.B.U. Strike on January 27, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PUNJAB+%26+SIND+BANK&title=Punjab+%26+Sind+Bank+Branches+May+Be+Affected+by+Proposed+U.F.B.U.+Strike+on+January+27%2C+2026&newsId=5eefdc29-a155-4adc-b8c5-d1b9a3b10ebc&token=NWVlZmRjMjktYTE1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5eefdc29-a155-4adc-b8c5-d1b9a3b10ebc</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:29:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Strike</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The United Forum of Bank Unions (U.F.B.U.) has announced its decision to go on strike on Tuesday, January 27, 2026, due to various issues and demands. Punjab &amp; Sind Bank has been notified of this development and is taking steps to ensure the smooth functioning of its branches and offices on the day of the strike. However, should the strike take place, the normal functioning of the bank&apos;s branches and offices may be impacted.</p><ul><li>United Forum of Bank Unions (U.F.B.U.) has announced a strike on January 27, 2026</li><li>Punjab &amp; Sind Bank taking steps to ensure smooth functioning of branches and offices</li><li>Strike may affect normal functioning of Punjab &amp; Sind Bank branches and offices</li><li>Strike is due to various issues and demands</li><li>Bank notifying stakeholders of the proposed strike</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4385e3ba-10d8-4aed-bb78-02306fb9b510.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PUNJAB & SIND BANK | Category: Strike</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ALPHAIND] Alphalogic Industries Ltd Wins Order from Blink Commerce for Storage Racking System Worth INR 2.75 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Alphalogic+Industries+Ltd&title=Alphalogic+Industries+Ltd+Wins+Order+from+Blink+Commerce+for+Storage+Racking+System+Worth+INR+2.75+Crores&newsId=0259ac7a-b561-437d-a339-c1d201385a5e&token=MDI1OWFjN2EtYjU2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0259ac7a-b561-437d-a339-c1d201385a5e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 09:50:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Alphalogic Industries Ltd has won an order from Blink Commerce Private Limited, also known as Blinkit, for the design, manufacture, supply, and installation of a Storage Racking System. The order is worth INR 2.75 crores (Rupees Two Crore Seventy-Five Lakh Sixty-Four Thousand Six Hundred Eleven and Twenty Paise) inclusive of GST. The order covers Blinkit&apos;s units in Chennai, Thane, Mumbai, Bangalore, Rangareddy Dist, Thiruvananthapuram, Srikakulam, and Indore.</p><ul><li>Alphalogic Industries Ltd wins order from Blink Commerce Private Limited for Storage Racking System worth INR 2.75 crores.</li><li>The order covers Blinkit&apos;s units in Chennai, Thane, Mumbai, Bangalore, Rangareddy Dist, Thiruvananthapuram, Srikakulam, and Indore.</li><li>The order is for the design, manufacture, supply, and installation of a Storage Racking System.</li><li>The order is worth INR 2.75 crores (Rupees Two Crore Seventy-Five Lakh Sixty-Four Thousand Six Hundred Eleven and Twenty Paise) inclusive of GST.</li><li>This is in accordance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/20059f38-0ed4-45e1-b05b-a15bb2de92e9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Alphalogic Industries Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WAAREERTL] Waaree Renewable Technologies to Acquire 55% Stake in Associated Power Structures for INR 1,225 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Waaree+Renewable+Technologies+Ltd&title=Waaree+Renewable+Technologies+to+Acquire+55%25+Stake+in+Associated+Power+Structures+for+INR+1%2C225+Crores&newsId=da3af27e-5c78-421e-bcd3-631c6cec7ddd&token=ZGEzYWYyN2UtNWM3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">da3af27e-5c78-421e-bcd3-631c6cec7ddd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 09:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd. has approved the acquisition of approximately 55% of the stake in Associated Power Structures Ltd. (ASPL) for a total consideration of INR 1,225 crores. The acquisition is a mix of primary and secondary shares. ASPL, established in 1996, is in the business of power transmission and distribution into the infrastructure sector. Post-acquisition, ASPL will become a subsidiary of Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd. The transaction is not a related party transaction and none of the promoter/promoter group/group companies have any interest in the entity being acquired. The acquisition is part of Waaree&apos;s strategic initiative to expand its presence and strengthen its capabilities across the renewable energy and energy efficiency ecosystem.</p><ul><li>Waaree Renewable Technologies to acquire approximately 55% stake in Associated Power Structures Limited</li><li>Total consideration of INR 1,225 crores (mix of primary and secondary shares)</li><li>ASPL operates in the power transmission and distribution sector</li><li>Acquisition to strengthen Waaree&apos;s capabilities across the renewable energy ecosystem</li><li>ASPL to become a subsidiary of Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bcd09c5e-51a1-4daf-83e9-8310b05fa8a3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WAAREERTL] Waaree Renewable Technologies to Acquire 55% Stake in Associated Power Structures for INR 1,225 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Waaree+Renewable+Technologies+Ltd&title=Waaree+Renewable+Technologies+to+Acquire+55%25+Stake+in+Associated+Power+Structures+for+INR+1%2C225+Crores&newsId=48a4b8bc-c40f-4907-ae5c-f83f40373550&token=NDhhNGI4YmMtYzQw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48a4b8bc-c40f-4907-ae5c-f83f40373550</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 09:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd. has approved a term sheet for the proposed acquisition of 55% stake in Associated Power Structures Limited (ASPL) for a total consideration of INR 1,225 crores. The acquisition is a mix of primary and secondary shares. ASPL, established in 1996, is in the business of Power transmission and distribution into the infrastructure sector. The acquisition will make ASPL a subsidiary of Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd. The transaction is not a related party transaction and none of the promoter/promoter group/group companies have any interest in the entity being acquired. The acquisition is part of WRITL’s strategic initiative to expand its presence and strengthen its capabilities across the renewable energy and energy efficiency ecosystem.</p><ul><li>Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd. to acquire 55% stake in Associated Power Structures Limited</li><li>Total consideration of INR 1,225 crores</li><li>ASPL to become a subsidiary of Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd.</li><li>ASPL established in 1996, in the business of Power transmission and distribution</li><li>Transaction is not a related party transaction</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ed200c08-af3d-4db7-9a1a-32b5dddb6242.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>