<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:21:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[NSLNISP] Smt. Priyadarshini Gaddam Retires as Director (Personnel) from NMDC Steel Ltd Board</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NMDC+Steel+Ltd&title=Smt.+Priyadarshini+Gaddam+Retires+as+Director+%28Personnel%29+from+NMDC+Steel+Ltd+Board&newsId=7577f923-700d-4d04-b80d-411d5c85ff2e&token=NzU3N2Y5MjMtNzAw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7577f923-700d-4d04-b80d-411d5c85ff2e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:01:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>NMDC Steel Ltd announced the retirement of Smt. Priyadarshini Gaddam as Director (Personnel) from its Board. The retirement follows the Ministry of Steel, Government of India Order No. 3(3)/2020-BLA dated 28.02.2025 and the earlier Order dated 20.03.2023. Smt. Gaddam reached the age of superannuation on 31.01.2026, resulting in her ceasing to be a Director (Personnel) on the Board of the company on the same date.</p><ul><li>Smt. Priyadarshini Gaddam retires as Director (Personnel) from NMDC Steel Ltd Board.</li><li>The retirement follows the Ministry of Steel, Government of India Order No. 3(3)/2020-BLA dated 28.02.2025 and the earlier Order dated 20.03.2023.</li><li>Smt. Gaddam reached the age of superannuation on 31.01.2026.</li><li>NMDC Steel Ltd provided an updated list of Directors on the Board.</li><li>The company is a Government of India Enterprise.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c3a58556-39c0-4288-8f80-bdd5f0e008f1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NMDC Steel Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MOIL] Moil Ltd Increases Manganese Ore Prices by 5-10% for February 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MOIL+LTD.&title=Moil+Ltd+Increases+Manganese+Ore+Prices+by+5-10%25+for+February+2026&newsId=4a42348e-d1c0-4e74-b2b8-9486fdce4dcd&token=NGE0MjM0OGUtZDFj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a42348e-d1c0-4e74-b2b8-9486fdce4dcd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Moil Ltd, in line with its business practice, has fixed/revised prices of different grades of Manganese Ore and other products, effective from 01.02.2026. The prices of all Ferro grades of manganese ore with Manganese content of Mn- 44% and above have been increased by 5%. The prices of all other Ferro grades of manganese ore with Manganese content below Mn-44% have also been increased by 5%, except BG4584 which continues the January 2026 price for the month of February 2026. The prices of SMGR (Mn-30%), Fines grades, and Chemical grades have been increased by 5%. The prices of SMGR (Mn 25%) and SMGR (Mn 20%) grades have been continued for the month of February 2026. The prices of Metal Mandi Fines have been continued, except for UKF532 which has seen a 10% increase. The basic price of EMD has been continued for the month of February 2026.</p><ul><li>Moil Ltd increases Manganese Ore prices by 5-10% for February 2026</li><li>Prices of Ferro grades of manganese ore with Mn- 44% and above increased by 5%</li><li>Prices of other Ferro grades of manganese ore, SMGR, Fines, and Chemical grades increased by 5%</li><li>Prices of SMGR (Mn 25%) and SMGR (Mn 20%) grades continued for February 2026</li><li>Price of UKF532 Metal Mandi Fines increased by 10% for February 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/89616f3d-60ee-4e9d-a1f2-849b85d2f501.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MOIL LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GUJINV] Gujarat Investa Ltd to Approve Q3 Financial Results and Contemplate Fund Raising in Upcoming Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GUJARAT+INVESTA+LTD.&title=Gujarat+Investa+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+Financial+Results+and+Contemplate+Fund+Raising+in+Upcoming+Board+Meeting&newsId=7b4daa2f-db3f-440f-9e3e-7a6d9cb7de1c&token=N2I0ZGFhMmYtZGIz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b4daa2f-db3f-440f-9e3e-7a6d9cb7de1c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gujarat Investa Ltd, formerly known as Ashtasiddhi Industries Limited, has announced a Board meeting scheduled for 7th February, 2026. The meeting aims to approve the unaudited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended on 31st December, 2025. The company also plans to consider and evaluate a proposal to raise funds through the issuance of Equity Shares/warrants by way of Preferential Allotment or any other method as may be decided by the Board. The meeting will also fix the day, date, time, and venue of the meeting and approve the draft notice for raising funds. The trading window for the shares of the company, which was closed with effect from 1st January, 2026, will remain closed till 48 hours after the announcement of the unaudited financial results.</p><ul><li>Gujarat Investa Ltd to approve Q3 financial results for the period ended on 31st December, 2025</li><li>Company to consider and evaluate a proposal to raise funds through Equity Shares/warrants by way of Preferential Allotment</li><li>The meeting will fix the day, date, time, and venue of the meeting and approve the draft notice for raising funds</li><li>Trading window for the shares of the company to remain closed till 48 hours after the announcement of the financial results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ad972951-3fee-4d94-a58c-a9245af37320.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GUJARAT INVESTA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TFCILTD] Tourism Finance Corporation of India to Invest up to 5% in Oxyzo Credit Fund I</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TOURISM+FINANCE+CORPORATION+OF+INDIA+LTD.&title=Tourism+Finance+Corporation+of+India+to+Invest+up+to+5%25+in+Oxyzo+Credit+Fund+I&newsId=01e3542a-24af-4104-b330-b47348aa808c&token=MDFlMzU0MmEtMjRh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01e3542a-24af-4104-b330-b47348aa808c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tourism Finance Corporation of India Ltd (TFCI) has announced its decision to invest up to 5% of its corpus fund in Oxyzo Credit Fund I. This debt-focused Alternative Investment Fund is registered with the Securities and Exchange Board of India and targets diversified sectors. This information was disclosed in continuation to a previous letter dated January 30, 2026.</p><ul><li>TFCI to invest up to 5% in Oxyzo Credit Fund I</li><li>Oxyzo Credit Fund I is a debt-focused Alternative Investment Fund</li><li>Registered with the Securities and Exchange Board of India</li><li>Targets diversified sectors</li><li>Disclosed in continuation to a previous letter dated January 30, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b4b1f187-6613-49ad-9997-4fe8bcefd31e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TOURISM FINANCE CORPORATION OF INDIA LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HEROMOTOCO] Hero MotoCorp Marks 25 Consecutive Years of Market Leadership, Records 26% Dispatch Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HERO+MOTOCORP+LTD.&title=Hero+MotoCorp+Marks+25+Consecutive+Years+of+Market+Leadership%2C+Records+26%25+Dispatch+Growth&newsId=0559a580-ebf7-40ee-bc7f-f173c0fe6747&token=MDU1OWE1ODAtZWJm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0559a580-ebf7-40ee-bc7f-f173c0fe6747</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Hero MotoCorp, the world&apos;s largest two-wheeler manufacturer, has maintained its market leadership for 25 consecutive years. The company recorded dispatches of 557,871 units in January 2026, a robust 26% growth compared to 442,873 units in January 2025. The strong growth was driven by the scooter segment and the motorcycle portfolio, led by Xoom, Destini, Xtreme, and Glamour X. VIDA, Hero MotoCorp’s Emerging Mobility business, continued its market share performance with 13,000 VAHAN registrations in January 2026. The company’s Global Business maintained strong momentum with a 24% dispatch growth. Hero MotoCorp was recognized as an ESG Leader among automotive companies and VIDA’s DIRT.E K3 was recognized as a CES 2026 Innovation Award Honoree.</p><ul><li>Hero MotoCorp maintained its position as the world&apos;s largest two-wheeler manufacturer for 25 consecutive years</li><li>The company recorded dispatches of 557,871 units in January 2026, a 26% growth compared to January 2025</li><li>Strong growth in the scooter segment and motorcycle portfolio, led by Xoom, Destini, Xtreme, and Glamour X</li><li>VIDA continued its market share performance with 13,000 VAHAN registrations in January 2026</li><li>Hero MotoCorp&apos;s Global Business maintained strong momentum with a 24% dispatch growth</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8a9dc1fe-cb6d-4531-bce0-a72a72af251b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HERO MOTOCORP LTD. | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NMDC] NMDC Ltd Announces Change in Board of Directors: Smt. Priyadarshini Gaddam Retires</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NMDC+LTD.&title=NMDC+Ltd+Announces+Change+in+Board+of+Directors%3A+Smt.+Priyadarshini+Gaddam+Retires&newsId=5fb92d22-dcb5-4952-980f-1f4680059aa6&token=NWZiOTJkMjItZGNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5fb92d22-dcb5-4952-980f-1f4680059aa6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 10:01:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>NMDC Ltd, a prominent name in the steel industry, has announced a change in its Board of Directors. Smt. Priyadarshini Gaddam, Director (Personnel), has ceased to be a member of the Board as she has reached the age of superannuation on 31.01.2026. The Ministry of Steel, Government of India, had appointed her as Director (Personnel) on the Board of NMDC Limited. The updated list of Directors on the Board of NMDC Limited is now available.</p><ul><li>Smt. Priyadarshini Gaddam has retired as Director (Personnel) from the Board of NMDC Ltd.</li><li>She reached the age of superannuation on 31.01.2026 and has been relieved from the services of the company.</li><li>The Ministry of Steel, Government of India, had appointed her as Director (Personnel) on the Board of NMDC Limited.</li><li>The list of Directors on the Board of NMDC Limited has been updated.</li><li>The change in the Board of Directors is in compliance with Regulation 30 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d7ca69bc-3b15-4071-b89a-e8dc727878a6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NMDC LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RECLTD] REC Ltd: Shri Harsh Baweja Retires as Director (Finance); Shri Jitendra Srivastava Takes Additional Charge</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=REC+Ltd&title=REC+Ltd%3A+Shri+Harsh+Baweja+Retires+as+Director+%28Finance%29%3B+Shri+Jitendra+Srivastava+Takes+Additional+Charge&newsId=3c20d47f-fde4-4958-978f-cdd8c7bbe3b2&token=M2MyMGQ0N2YtZmRl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3c20d47f-fde4-4958-978f-cdd8c7bbe3b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 10:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>REC Ltd has announced a change in its Board of Directors. Shri Harsh Baweja, Director (Finance), has superannuated from the services of the company on January 31, 2026, and has ceased to be the Director (Finance) and Chief Financial Officer of REC with effect from February 1, 2026. The Ministry of Power, Government of India, has entrusted the additional charge of the post of Director (Finance) to Shri Jitendra Srivastava (IAS), Chairman &amp; Managing Director of REC, for a period of 3 months or until the appointment of a regular incumbent to the post or until further order, whichever is earlier.</p><ul><li>Shri Harsh Baweja has retired as Director (Finance) of REC Ltd.</li><li>Shri Jitendra Srivastava has been given additional charge as Director (Finance) of REC Ltd.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f3d4c45e-fc24-464f-9c7f-d4a9f8faf595.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: REC Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GTIL] Madhusudan Sarda &amp; Urvashi Sarda Acquire Shares in Gabion Technologies India Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Gabion+Technologies+India+Ltd&title=Madhusudan+Sarda+%26+Urvashi+Sarda+Acquire+Shares+in+Gabion+Technologies+India+Limited&newsId=8111c47f-3069-4a22-9f5d-3c5471f3e827&token=ODExMWM0N2YtMzA2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8111c47f-3069-4a22-9f5d-3c5471f3e827</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 10:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Madhusudan Sarda and Urvashi Sarda, promoters and key management personnel of Gabion Technologies India Limited, have acquired shares in the company through open market purchases. The acquisitions were made on 30th January, 2026. Madhusudan Sarda, the Managing Director, acquired 14,400 shares, increasing his total holding to 56,25,190 shares, representing 41.436% of the company&apos;s total voting rights. Urvashi Sarda, a Whole-time Director, also acquired shares, but the specific details were not provided in the text.</p><ul><li>Madhusudan Sarda and Urvashi Sarda, promoters of Gabion Technologies India Limited, have acquired shares in the company.</li><li>The acquisitions were made through open market purchases on 30th January, 2026.</li><li>Madhusudan Sarda acquired 14,400 shares, increasing his total holding to 56,25,190 shares, representing 41.436% of the company&apos;s total voting rights.</li><li>Urvashi Sarda also acquired shares, but the specific details were not provided in the text.</li><li>The acquisitions were made in compliance with SEBI regulations 29(2) of the SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011 and Regulation 7(2) of the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2A5BEAD1_EDFB_4DFC_92E8_AF41D6A675D5_152933.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Gabion Technologies India Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VGUARD] V-Guard Industries Ltd Receives Audit Objection from Superintendent, CGST Audit Group 12, Haldwani, Kashipur Circle, Uttarakhand</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=V-GUARD+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=V-Guard+Industries+Ltd+Receives+Audit+Objection+from+Superintendent%2C+CGST+Audit+Group+12%2C+Haldwani%2C+Kashipur+Circle%2C+Uttarakhand&newsId=9ccb9030-67b6-427e-8c8c-1064cbeae282&token=OWNjYjkwMzAtNjdi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ccb9030-67b6-427e-8c8c-1064cbeae282</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>V-Guard Industries Ltd has received an audit objection from the Superintendent, CGST Audit Group 12, Haldwani, Kashipur Circle, Uttarakhand under section 65 of the CGST Act. The objection is regarding excess availment of ITC for the financial years 2020-21 to 2023-24. The demanded amount is 17,75,91,297 with applicable interest and penalty under section 74. The company is evaluating the intimation for taking appropriate steps to reply to the same.</p><ul><li>V-Guard Industries Ltd has received an audit objection from the Superintendent, CGST Audit Group 12, Haldwani, Kashipur Circle, Uttarakhand.</li><li>The objection is regarding excess availment of ITC for the financial years 2020-21 to 2023-24.</li><li>The demanded amount is 17,75,91,297 with applicable interest and penalty under section 74.</li><li>The company is evaluating the intimation for taking appropriate steps to reply to the same.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8ea35891-d8c8-4720-a983-33ce194080e2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: V-GUARD INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EICHERMOT] Eicher Motors&apos; Subsidiary, VE Commercial Vehicles, Reports 24.9% Growth in Sales Volume for January 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=EICHER+MOTORS+LTD.&title=Eicher+Motors%27+Subsidiary%2C+VE+Commercial+Vehicles%2C+Reports+24.9%25+Growth+in+Sales+Volume+for+January+2026&newsId=d91b6a29-13ed-4358-8f05-3804cfd04aa5&token=ZDkxYjZhMjktMTNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d91b6a29-13ed-4358-8f05-3804cfd04aa5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 09:37:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Eicher Motors Ltd. has released the monthly business update for its unlisted subsidiary, VE Commercial Vehicles (VECV), for January 2026. The update reveals a 24.9% year-over-year growth in sales volume for VECV, with total sales reaching 10,601 units compared to 8,489 units in January 2025. This growth is driven by various segments, including Eicher Trucks and Buses, SCV/LMD Trucks, HD Trucks, and Buses. Total domestic sales have increased by 23.6%, with exports growing by 51.8%.</p><ul><li>VE Commercial Vehicles reports a 24.9% YoY growth in sales volume for January 2026</li><li>Total sales for the month reach 10,601 units compared to 8,489 units in January 2025</li><li>Domestic sales increase by 23.6%, with exports growing by 51.8%</li><li>Eicher Trucks and Buses segment records 7.0% growth in sales volume</li><li>SCV/LMD Trucks, HD Trucks, and Buses segments also show positive growth</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8341a8db-8add-4d0d-9e62-6722dc04a866.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: EICHER MOTORS LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>