<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 21:17:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[MADHAV] Madhav Marbles &amp; Granites Ltd. to Consider Related Party Transactions on March 05, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MADHAV+MARBLES+%26+GRANITES+LTD.&title=Madhav+Marbles+%26+Granites+Ltd.+to+Consider+Related+Party+Transactions+on+March+05%2C+2026&newsId=08751009-9609-4bef-bd24-20dc6681042c&token=MDg3NTEwMDktOTYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08751009-9609-4bef-bd24-20dc6681042c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 17:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Madhav Marbles &amp; Granites Ltd. has informed the BSE that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on March 05, 2026. The Board will consider and approve the proposal for entering into Related Party Transactions with Madhav Surfaces FZC LLC, which is a Related Party. This information is provided by Priyanka Manawat, Company Secretary of Madhav Marbles &amp; Granites Ltd.</p><ul><li>Madhav Marbles &amp; Granites Ltd. scheduled a Board Meeting on March 05, 2026</li><li>The Board will consider entering into Related Party Transactions with Madhav Surfaces FZC LLC</li><li>Madhav Surfaces FZC LLC is a Related Party of Madhav Marbles &amp; Granites Ltd.</li><li>Priyanka Manawat, Company Secretary, provided the information</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3e101e4a-2915-4be8-85df-96157e87fa86.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MADHAV MARBLES & GRANITES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADFFOODS] General Manager — Supply Chain of Adf Foods Ltd Resigns for New Opportunities</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADF+FOODS+LTD.-%24&title=General+Manager+%E2%80%94+Supply+Chain+of+Adf+Foods+Ltd+Resigns+for+New+Opportunities&newsId=7bb81ec1-4212-4d25-bf26-237c8f86d7a5&token=N2JiODFlYzEtNDIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7bb81ec1-4212-4d25-bf26-237c8f86d7a5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 17:11:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Adf Foods Ltd has announced the resignation of Mr. Jeetendra Joshi, General Manager — Supply Chain, who will be leaving the company effective from the closure of business hours on 28 February, 2026. The decision is made so that he can pursue new opportunities and challenges. The company assures that the supply chain operations will continue to run smoothly and remain unaffected by this change. There is no other material reason for the resignation other than the reason mentioned above.</p><ul><li>Mr. Jeetendra Joshi, General Manager — Supply Chain, has resigned from Adf Foods Ltd.</li><li>He will be leaving the company on 28 February, 2026 to pursue new opportunities and challenges.</li><li>Adf Foods Ltd confirms that supply chain operations will not be affected by this change.</li><li>There is no other material reason for the resignation other than the reason mentioned above.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8460b1d0-6eb1-43b9-9ab2-f1432c0b02c4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADF FOODS LTD.-$ | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[POWERGRID] Power Grid Corporation Fined Rs. 5,42,800 Each by BSE and NSE for Non-Compliance with Board Composition Requirement</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=POWER+GRID+CORPORATION+OF+INDIA+LTD.&title=Power+Grid+Corporation+Fined+Rs.+5%2C42%2C800+Each+by+BSE+and+NSE+for+Non-Compliance+with+Board+Composition+Requirement&newsId=b06922e1-71a8-4dcf-b9ef-59932228ce33&token=YjA2OTIyZTEtNzFh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b06922e1-71a8-4dcf-b9ef-59932228ce33</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 15:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd. has received notices from BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange of India Limited regarding non-compliance with the requirement related to composition of the Board (Regulation 17(1) of SEBI LODR) during the quarter ended 31st December, 2025. Both BSE and NSE have imposed a fine of Rs. 5,42,800 each, including GST, for such non-compliance. The company, being a Government Company, has taken up the matter with the Administrative Ministry i.e. Ministry of Power for filling up the vacant posts of Independent Directors. Power Grid Corporation has requested BSE &amp; NSE to grant waiver of fine w.r.t. non-compliance with the Regulation 17(1) of the SEBI LODR.</p><ul><li>Power Grid Corporation fined Rs. 5,42,800 each by BSE and NSE</li><li>Non-compliance with Regulation 17(1) of SEBI LODR</li><li>Relates to composition of the Board during the quarter ended 31st December, 2025</li><li>Power Grid Corporation is a Government Company within the meaning of Section 2(45) of the Companies Act, 2013</li><li>Company has requested BSE &amp; NSE to grant waiver of fine w.r.t. non-compliance with the Regulation 17(1) of the SEBI LODR</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/375f7093-890d-41b9-ba94-5e0d07c20e4a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: POWER GRID CORPORATION OF INDIA LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VASWANI] Vaswani Industries Ltd. Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025, Revealing Increased Revenue and Profit</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VASWANI+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Vaswani+Industries+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Revealing+Increased+Revenue+and+Profit&newsId=d39261ee-da0f-41af-8f68-69efbea0e6b9&token=ZDM5MjYxZWUtZGEw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d39261ee-da0f-41af-8f68-69efbea0e6b9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 15:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Vaswani Industries Ltd. has announced its un-audited standalone financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations has increased by 38.64% for the quarter and 42.35% for the nine months period, compared to the same periods in 2024. The profit before tax and exceptional items has also increased by 65.49% for the quarter and 45.58% for the nine months period. However, the profit for the period has decreased by 795.29 due to exceptional items and tax expense. The company&apos;s earnings per equity share (Par value Rs. 10 each) for the quarter are Rs. 0.24 (Basic) and Rs. 0.24 (Diluted). The financial results were reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations increased by 38.64% for the quarter and 42.35% for the nine months period.</li><li>Profit before tax and exceptional items increased by 65.49% for the quarter and 45.58% for the nine months period.</li><li>Profit for the period decreased by 795.29 due to exceptional items and tax expense.</li><li>Earnings per equity share (Par value Rs. 10 each) for the quarter are Rs. 0.24 (Basic) and Rs. 0.24 (Diluted).</li><li>Financial results reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/22bdc5e0-5734-4d12-898b-cbd5899b3787.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VASWANI INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PICTUREHS] Picturehouse Media Ltd: Independent Director, Mr. Gautam Shahi, Resigns</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PICTUREHOUSE+MEDIA+LTD.&title=Picturehouse+Media+Ltd%3A+Independent+Director%2C+Mr.+Gautam+Shahi%2C+Resigns&newsId=f9b61002-7a2b-49e6-adf1-907a1eff978f&token=ZjliNjEwMDItN2Ey</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9b61002-7a2b-49e6-adf1-907a1eff978f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 15:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Picturehouse Media Ltd announced the resignation of its Independent Director, Mr. Gautam Shahi, with effect from the close of business hours on 28th February 2026. The decision was due to a significant increase in Mr. Shahi&apos;s professional commitments in his legal practice, making it difficult for him to devote the required time and attention to his role as an Independent Director. Mr. Shahi confirmed that there are no other material reasons for his resignation.</p><ul><li>Mr. Gautam Shahi resigns from his position as Independent Director of Picturehouse Media Ltd.</li><li>The resignation is effective from the close of business hours on 28th February 2026.</li><li>The decision is due to increased professional commitments in Mr. Shahi&apos;s legal practice.</li><li>Mr. Shahi confirms no other material reasons for his resignation.</li><li>Picturehouse Media Ltd complies with the applicable provisions of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9f6ecbfc-d61e-41d7-af62-5febdca48016.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PICTUREHOUSE MEDIA LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KESAR] Kesar India Ltd Approves Allotment of 5,74,319 Equity Shares to Non-Promoters</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kesar+India+Ltd&title=Kesar+India+Ltd+Approves+Allotment+of+5%2C74%2C319+Equity+Shares+to+Non-Promoters&newsId=b1042f1a-78f3-47ad-9914-f1a2d1ff634b&token=YjEwNDJmMWEtNzhm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b1042f1a-78f3-47ad-9914-f1a2d1ff634b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 15:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Kesar India Ltd, in a meeting of the Preferential Issue Committee of the Board of Directors, approved the allotment of 5,74,319 equity shares to non-promoter allottees. The shares are being allotted pursuant to the conversion of 3,74,319 fully convertible warrants allotted on September 18, 2025, at an issue price of Rs. 350 each. The allottees include Gunjan Agarwal, Priyank Dhirendra Shah, Mohit Rajeshkumar Atlani, Mihir Atlani, Yash Suresh Atlani, Prachi Pranav Bhagat, Chintan Viijay Makhecha, Dhavan Govindram Medtiya, and Piyush Narayanlal Medtiya. The paid-up equity share capital of the company will increase to Rs. 28,57,32,290 divided into 2,85,73,229 equity shares of face value of Rs. 10 each.</p><ul><li>Kesar India Ltd approves allotment of 5,74,319 equity shares to non-promoter allottees.</li><li>The allotment is pursuant to the conversion of 3,74,319 fully convertible warrants allotted on September 18, 2025.</li><li>The allottees include Gunjan Agarwal, Priyank Dhirendra Shah, Mohit Rajeshkumar Atlani, Mihir Atlani, Yash Suresh Atlani, Prachi Pranav Bhagat, Chintan Viijay Makhecha, Dhavan Govindram Medtiya, and Piyush Narayanlal Medtiya.</li><li>The paid-up equity share capital of the company will increase to Rs. 28,57,32,290 divided into 2,85,73,229 equity shares of face value of Rs. 10 each.</li><li>The meeting of the Preferential Issue Committee of the Board of Directors was commenced at 07:45 P.M. and concluded at 08:00 P.M.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/93974a61-5ce3-44b3-adaf-c6f49f72d78d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kesar India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PVP] Independent Director, Mr. Gautam Shahi, Resigns from PVP Ventures Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PVP+VENTURES+LTD.&title=Independent+Director%2C+Mr.+Gautam+Shahi%2C+Resigns+from+PVP+Ventures+Ltd&newsId=7973ed80-3cc4-4753-9854-7f193d08d375&token=Nzk3M2VkODAtM2Nj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7973ed80-3cc4-4753-9854-7f193d08d375</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 14:51:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>PVP Ventures Ltd announced the resignation of its Independent Director, Mr. Gautam Shahi, with effect from the close of business hours on 28th February 2026. The decision was due to a significant increase in Mr. Shahi&apos;s professional commitments in his legal practice, making it difficult for him to devote the required time and attention to his role as an Independent Director. Mr. Shahi confirmed that there are no other material reasons for his resignation.</p><ul><li>Mr. Gautam Shahi resigns from his position as Independent Director of PVP Ventures Ltd</li><li>The resignation is effective from the close of business hours on 28th February 2026</li><li>The decision is due to increased professional commitments in Mr. Shahi&apos;s legal practice</li><li>Mr. Shahi confirmed that there are no other material reasons for his resignation</li><li>PVP Ventures Ltd complies with the applicable provisions of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1e01041d-aed6-4eec-af93-206e664f1bd6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PVP VENTURES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VASWANI] Vaswani Industries Ltd. Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VASWANI+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Vaswani+Industries+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025&newsId=a6567a9d-9c94-407a-b72f-55189924bbba&token=YTY1NjdhOWQtOWM5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a6567a9d-9c94-407a-b72f-55189924bbba</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 14:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Vaswani Industries Ltd. has announced its un-audited standalone financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations for the quarter is Rs. 8,501.03 lakhs and for the nine months is Rs. 32,411.88 lakhs. The net profit for the quarter is Rs. 796.42 lakhs and for the nine months is Rs. 13,432 lakhs. The total comprehensive income for the period is (Rs. 795.29) lakhs.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter is Rs. 8,501.03 lakhs</li><li>Revenue from operations for the nine months is Rs. 32,411.88 lakhs</li><li>Net profit for the quarter is Rs. 796.42 lakhs</li><li>Net profit for the nine months is Rs. 13,432 lakhs</li><li>Total comprehensive income for the period is (Rs. 795.29) lakhs</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c85b309b-59e1-4e2f-8bbe-485e5f9eb2d9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VASWANI INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PERSISTENT] Persistent Systems Ltd Establishes Wholly Owned Foreign Enterprise in China</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PERSISTENT+SYSTEMS+LTD.&title=Persistent+Systems+Ltd+Establishes+Wholly+Owned+Foreign+Enterprise+in+China&newsId=b8ed95bc-90b9-412c-8846-da169d1c0bae&token=YjhlZDk1YmMtOTBi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8ed95bc-90b9-412c-8846-da169d1c0bae</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 14:41:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Persistent Systems Pte. Ltd., Singapore, a wholly owned subsidiary of Persistent Systems Ltd, has established a Wholly Owned Foreign Enterprise (WFOE) in China. The new entity, Baixinteng System Service (Shanghai) Co. Ltd., also known as Persistent Systems (Shanghai) Co. Ltd., received its Business License from the Shanghai Administration for Market Regulation (SAMR) on February 28, 2026.</p><ul><li>Persistent Systems Pte. Ltd., Singapore, a wholly owned subsidiary of Persistent Systems Ltd, has established a Wholly Owned Foreign Enterprise (WFOE) in China.</li><li>The new entity is named Baixinteng System Service (Shanghai) Co. Ltd., also known as Persistent Systems (Shanghai) Co. Ltd.</li><li>The company has received the Business License from the Shanghai Administration for Market Regulation (SAMR) in China.</li><li>This expansion is in line with the company&apos;s strategic growth plans.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2c7bad3e-61bd-469e-9d3b-78fa5bcd51a4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PERSISTENT SYSTEMS LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GTIL] Gabion Technologies India Ltd Appoints Ms. Sonal Jhanwar as Company Secretary &amp; Compliance Officer and M/s. Himanshu SK Gupta &amp; Associates as Secretarial Auditor for F.Y. 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Gabion+Technologies+India+Ltd&title=Gabion+Technologies+India+Ltd+Appoints+Ms.+Sonal+Jhanwar+as+Company+Secretary+%26+Compliance+Officer+and+M%2Fs.+Himanshu+SK+Gupta+%26+Associates+as+Secretarial+Auditor+for+F.Y.+2025-26&newsId=ba729a25-b043-4446-8e6b-49caa65b3bb8&token=YmE3MjlhMjUtYjA0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba729a25-b043-4446-8e6b-49caa65b3bb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 14:31:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gabion Technologies India Ltd has appointed Ms. Sonal Jhanwar as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer and M/s. Himanshu SK Gupta &amp; Associates as the Secretarial Auditor for the financial year 2025-26. Ms. Sonal Jhanwar is a Qualified Company Secretary with experience in handling secretarial and compliance functions of listed and unlisted companies. M/s. Himanshu SK Gupta &amp; Associates is a peer-reviewed firm of Practicing Company Secretaries offering comprehensive corporate advisory and compliance solutions.</p><ul><li>Ms. Sonal Jhanwar appointed as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer of Gabion Technologies India Ltd.</li><li>M/s. Himanshu SK Gupta &amp; Associates appointed as Secretarial Auditor for the financial year 2025-26.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4e1fbcd9-cdbd-4704-86f4-5ccd49d273f5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Gabion Technologies India Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>