<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:50:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[BLBLIMITED] BLB Ltd Promoter Brij Rattan Bagri Reverses Share Purchase Due to Short Delivery</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BLB+LTD.&title=BLB+Ltd+Promoter+Brij+Rattan+Bagri+Reverses+Share+Purchase+Due+to+Short+Delivery&newsId=81183f04-196f-411a-8cce-688e1325bcd0&token=ODExODNmMDQtMTk2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">81183f04-196f-411a-8cce-688e1325bcd0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:47:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>BLB Ltd Promoter and Director, Brij Rattan Bagri, has reversed the purchase of 1,095 shares of the company due to short delivery by the Stock Exchange. The shares were purchased on 20 February 2026 at Rs. 20.45/- each, but were not delivered on the payout day, 23 February 2026. Bagri&apos;s present holding stands at 2,38,04,628 shares after the reversal.</p><ul><li>Brij Rattan Bagri, Promoter and Director of BLB Ltd, reverses share purchase due to short delivery.</li><li>1,095 shares purchased on 20 February 2026 at Rs. 20.45/- each were not delivered on the payout day.</li><li>Bagri&apos;s present share holding stands at 2,38,04,628 shares after the reversal.</li><li>The shares were short delivered by the Stock Exchange.</li><li>The aforesaid shares were closed out by the Stock Exchange and were not delivered.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3c2bf805-a555-41a2-a8ed-d0694d598259.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BLB LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TECHIN] Techindia Nirman Ltd Receives Warning Letters from Stock Exchanges for Non-Compliance in CIRP Disclosures</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TECHINDIA+NIRMAN+LIMITED&title=Techindia+Nirman+Ltd+Receives+Warning+Letters+from+Stock+Exchanges+for+Non-Compliance+in+CIRP+Disclosures&newsId=b706a1e4-9648-4fab-beed-d9376c67147b&token=YjcwNmExZTQtOTY0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b706a1e4-9648-4fab-beed-d9376c67147b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:46:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Techindia Nirman Ltd has received warning letters from the National Stock Exchange of India Limited and BSE Limited regarding non-compliance and delayed compliance in connection with disclosures pertaining to the Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP) of the Company. The Company acknowledges the delay in submission of disclosures relating to the financial default and initiation of CIRP, including intimation pursuant to the NCLT order and appointment of the Resolution Professional. The delay occurred due to operational reasons. The Company has taken necessary corrective and preventive measures to avoid recurrence of such lapses in future.</p><ul><li>Techindia Nirman Ltd received warning letters from National Stock Exchange of India Limited and BSE Limited</li><li>The warning letters were issued due to non-compliance and delayed compliance in CIRP disclosures</li><li>The Company acknowledges the delay in submission of disclosures relating to financial default and initiation of CIRP</li><li>The delay occurred due to operational reasons</li><li>The Company has taken necessary corrective and preventive measures to avoid recurrence of such lapses in future</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3f968b11-b306-4195-8eba-53678284e18e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TECHINDIA NIRMAN LIMITED | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TATACAP] Tata Capital Housing Finance to Raise Rs. 650 Crore via Rights Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Tata+Capital+Ltd&title=Tata+Capital+Housing+Finance+to+Raise+Rs.+650+Crore+via+Rights+Issue&newsId=1cc6ab4c-58b9-4920-95a8-5553e3a922ba&token=MWNjNmFiNGMtNThi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1cc6ab4c-58b9-4920-95a8-5553e3a922ba</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:45:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Tata Capital Limited has informed the stock exchanges about the approval by the Board of Directors of Tata Capital Housing Finance Limited (TCHFL), a wholly owned subsidiary, for the offer and issuance of equity shares worth Rs. 650,02,04,730 (Rupees Six Hundred Fifty crore, Two Lakhs Four Thousand Seven Hundred and Thirty only) on a rights basis to Tata Capital Limited. The decision was made at the TCHFL board meeting held on February 25, 2026.</p><ul><li>Tata Capital Housing Finance Limited to raise Rs. 650 crore via rights issue.</li><li>The decision was approved at the TCHFL board meeting held on February 25, 2026.</li><li>The rights issue is for Tata Capital Limited, a wholly owned subsidiary of Tata Capital.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7853e108-4c68-4dcb-ab52-318175cdfc94.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Tata Capital Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[OASIS] Oasis Tradelink Ltd. to Shift Registered Office and Convene Extraordinary General Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Oasis+Tradelink+Ltd&title=Oasis+Tradelink+Ltd.+to+Shift+Registered+Office+and+Convene+Extraordinary+General+Meeting&newsId=934a0a2f-0c9d-41f0-9032-70208ab4fde2&token=OTM0YTBhMmYtMGM5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">934a0a2f-0c9d-41f0-9032-70208ab4fde2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:44:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Oasis Tradelink Ltd. has announced its decision to shift its registered office from Ahmedabad to Bharuch, Gujarat, subject to approval from members through a special resolution. The company has also approved the notice for an Extraordinary General Meeting (EGM) to be held on March 23, 2026, through Video Conferencing (VC) or Other Audio-Visual Means (OAVM). The EGM will seek shareholders&apos; approval for the office shift. The meeting will be scrutinized by M/s. Somani &amp; Associates, Practicing Company Secretaries.</p><ul><li>Oasis Tradelink Ltd. plans to shift its registered office from Ahmedabad to Bharuch, Gujarat.</li><li>The shift is subject to approval from members through a special resolution.</li><li>The company has approved the notice for an Extraordinary General Meeting (EGM) on March 23, 2026.</li><li>The EGM will be held through Video Conferencing (VC) or Other Audio-Visual Means (OAVM).</li><li>M/s. Somani &amp; Associates, Practicing Company Secretaries, will scrutinize the EGM.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a4446f08-fce9-4b11-9184-937cc3e37607.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Oasis Tradelink Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BEL] Bharat Electronics Secures Additional Orders Worth Rs. 733 Crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BHARAT+ELECTRONICS+LTD.&title=Bharat+Electronics+Secures+Additional+Orders+Worth+Rs.+733+Crore&newsId=8769759a-6ab2-412f-9d6c-b022bf831c72&token=ODc2OTc1OWEtNmFi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8769759a-6ab2-412f-9d6c-b022bf831c72</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Bharat Electronics Limited (BEL), a Navratna Defence Public Sector Undertaking, has secured additional orders worth Rs. 733 Crore since the last disclosure on 06th Feb 2026. The major orders received include TR modules, communication equipment, encryptors, radars, jammers, software solutions, test equipment, upgrades, spares, services etc.</p><ul><li>BEL secures additional orders worth Rs. 733 Crore</li><li>Orders include TR modules, communication equipment, encryptors, radars, jammers, software solutions, test equipment, upgrades, spares, services</li><li>Orders received since last disclosure on 06th Feb 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5c942516-66dd-4212-8b60-152285ab35a8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BHARAT ELECTRONICS LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BINDALAGRO] Oswal Greentech Ltd Updates Authorised Officials for Material Events Disclosure</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Oswal+Greentech+Ltd&title=Oswal+Greentech+Ltd+Updates+Authorised+Officials+for+Material+Events+Disclosure&newsId=909eb7c9-3313-4606-a73e-3c78e79eff65&token=OTA5ZWI3YzktMzMx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">909eb7c9-3313-4606-a73e-3c78e79eff65</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Oswal Greentech Ltd has announced a revised list of officials authorized for determining and disclosing material events or information under Regulation 30 of the Listing Regulations to the stock exchanges. The new list, effective from March 01, 2026, includes Mrs. Aruna Oswal as Whole time Director, Mr. Moxit Bhupendra Modi as Chief Financial Officer, and Mrs. Purva Jhanwar as Company Secretary. The contact details for each official are also provided.</p><ul><li>Oswal Greentech Ltd updates the list of officials authorized for material events disclosure</li><li>Mrs. Aruna Oswal appointed as Whole time Director</li><li>Mr. Moxit Bhupendra Modi appointed as Chief Financial Officer</li><li>Mrs. Purva Jhanwar appointed as Company Secretary</li><li>New list to be effective from March 01, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8fe724f4-83b1-46da-a751-6287c192ba18.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Oswal Greentech Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AWFIS] Awfis Space Solutions Ltd Executes Loan Documentations with ICICI Bank Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Awfis+Space+Solutions+Ltd&title=Awfis+Space+Solutions+Ltd+Executes+Loan+Documentations+with+ICICI+Bank+Limited&newsId=c961270c-59eb-49d8-9196-0657e71cf4d6&token=Yzk2MTI3MGMtNTll</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c961270c-59eb-49d8-9196-0657e71cf4d6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Loan</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Awfis Space Solutions Ltd has executed loan documentations on February 25, 2026 to avail credit facilities from ICICI Bank Limited. This information was disclosed in compliance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI LODR Regulations and was intimated to the stock exchanges on November 11, 2025 and February 02, 2026. The details of the loan facilities will be available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Awfis Space Solutions Ltd has executed loan documentations with ICICI Bank Limited.</li><li>The loan documentations were executed on February 25, 2026.</li><li>The credit facilities are aimed at availing loan facilities from ICICI Bank Limited.</li><li>The company has complied with Regulation 30 of the SEBI LODR Regulations.</li><li>The relevant information was intimated to the stock exchanges on November 11, 2025 and February 02, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/02284679-2f58-4334-9dfa-114b5ca51cc3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Awfis Space Solutions Ltd | Category: Loan</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AMARSEC] Amarnath Securities Ltd Board Meeting on March 5, 2026: Key Proposals and Appointments</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Amarnath+Securities+Ltd&title=Amarnath+Securities+Ltd+Board+Meeting+on+March+5%2C+2026%3A+Key+Proposals+and+Appointments&newsId=73a97654-4c3b-4531-962a-ac5f5357dbc7&token=NzNhOTc2NTQtNGMz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73a97654-4c3b-4531-962a-ac5f5357dbc7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 09:07:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Amarnath Securities Ltd has announced a Board Meeting scheduled on March 5, 2026. The agenda includes consideration and approval of a proposal for the issue of equity shares on a preferential basis for cash and/or other than cash. The meeting will also seek approval from members for the appointment of M/s. H K Shah &amp; Co., Chartered Accountants as statutory auditors for five years from FY 2025-26 to FY 2029-30. Additionally, the Board will discuss changes in designations of two directors and appoint a scrutinizer for the postal ballot process. The trading window for dealing in securities of the Company will be closed for designated persons as per the applicable provisions.</p><ul><li>Consideration and approval of equity shares issue on preferential basis</li><li>Appointment of M/s. H K Shah &amp; Co., Chartered Accountants as statutory auditors</li><li>Changes in designations of two directors</li><li>Appointment of scrutinizer for postal ballot process</li><li>Closure of trading window for designated persons</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/46913f81-7a9b-4722-9a07-3a90d12d8639.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Amarnath Securities Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[3BFILMS] 3B Films Ltd: Independent Director Resigns Due to Increased Professional Commitments</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=3B+Films+Ltd&title=3B+Films+Ltd%3A+Independent+Director+Resigns+Due+to+Increased+Professional+Commitments&newsId=6ea99ba5-704f-44dc-a2f0-9f41053e131e&token=NmVhOTliYTUtNzA0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ea99ba5-704f-44dc-a2f0-9f41053e131e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:57:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>3B Films Ltd, previously known as 3B Films Private Limited, has announced the resignation of an independent director due to increased professional commitments. The company had experienced a server issue that delayed the disclosure of this information. The resignation was submitted on February 16, 2026, and the director expressed gratitude for the trust and confidence shown during their tenure.</p><ul><li>An independent director of 3B Films Ltd has resigned due to increased professional commitments.</li><li>The company had a server issue that delayed the disclosure of the resignation.</li><li>The director expressed gratitude for the trust and confidence shown during their tenure.</li><li>The resignation was submitted on February 16, 2026.</li><li>The company has arranged to file the necessary forms with the Registrar of Companies.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e6e36fee-808e-40ca-8fd7-780210932863.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: 3B Films Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MARICO] Marico&apos;s Nihar Shanti Pathshala Funwala Strengthens Early Childhood Education in 100 Anganwadi Centres</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MARICO+LTD.&title=Marico%27s+Nihar+Shanti+Pathshala+Funwala+Strengthens+Early+Childhood+Education+in+100+Anganwadi+Centres&newsId=fa23ed64-d6cc-4dfc-8ed6-72ef9e70918d&token=ZmEyM2VkNjQtZDZj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa23ed64-d6cc-4dfc-8ed6-72ef9e70918d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:52:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Marico Limited&apos;s CSR programme, Nihar Shanti Pathshala Funwala, in partnership with Sesame Workshop India, has fortified foundational early childhood education for over 1,700 children across 100 Anganwadi centres in Bahraich, Uttar Pradesh. The programme, focusing on Foundational Literacy and Numeracy, supports Anganwadi workers, engages parents, and collaborates with government systems to improve learning levels for children aged 3-6 years. The initiative has trained 100 Anganwadi workers, 100 helpers, and 1500 parents/caregivers so far.</p><ul><li>Marico’s flagship CSR programme for education, Nihar Shanti Pathshala Funwala, in partnership with Sesame Workshop India, has been launched in 100 Anganwadi centres in Bahraich, Uttar Pradesh.</li><li>The programme focuses on Foundational Literacy and Numeracy and adopts a holistic approach to support Anganwadi workers, engage parents, and improve learning levels for children aged 3-6 years.</li><li>The initiative has trained 100 Anganwadi workers, 100 helpers, and 1500 parents/caregivers so far.</li><li>The programme aligns with the National Education Policy 2020 and National Curriculum Framework 2022, and includes structured training for Anganwadi workers and helpers, deployment of innovative teaching-learning materials, and community participation through positive parenting sessions and Early Childhood Care and Education melas.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7ec13b98-4914-4d2f-a3c5-6c8f6d3fbaa9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MARICO LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>