<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:57:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SALZER] Salzer Electronics Ltd.: Approval of Q3 and Nine-Month Financial Results for 2025, Re-Appointment of Managing Director, and Appointment of New CFO</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SALZER+ELECTRONICS+LTD.-%24&title=Salzer+Electronics+Ltd.%3A+Approval+of+Q3+and+Nine-Month+Financial+Results+for+2025%2C+Re-Appointment+of+Managing+Director%2C+and+Appointment+of+New+CFO&newsId=3c8fdb8f-e036-44aa-9c4b-f0236d967fbc&token=M2M4ZmRiOGYtZTAz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3c8fdb8f-e036-44aa-9c4b-f0236d967fbc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:56:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Salzer Electronics Ltd. has announced its standalone and consolidated unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine-month period ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s Managing Director, Mr. R. Doraiswamy, has been re-appointed for a further term of three years, and Mr. Raman Krishnamoorthy has been appointed as the new Chief Financial Officer (CFO) and Key Managerial Personnel, replacing Mr. D. Rajesh Kumar who will continue as Joint Managing Director.</p><ul><li>Approval of standalone and consolidated unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine-month period ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Re-appointment of Mr. R. Doraiswamy as Managing Director for a further term of three years</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Raman Krishnamoorthy as the new Chief Financial Officer and Key Managerial Personnel</li><li>Mr. D. Rajesh Kumar to relinquish the office of Chief Financial Officer on March 31, 2026, and continue as Joint Managing Director</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f92d0c0e-d770-43c2-9b0c-435b3cbde941.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SALZER ELECTRONICS LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NPST] Network People Services Technologies Ltd Reports Q3 Results for 2025 with a Profit of ₹ 2,871.64 Crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Network+People+Services+Technologies+Ltd&title=Network+People+Services+Technologies+Ltd+Reports+Q3+Results+for+2025+with+a+Profit+of+%E2%82%B9+2%2C871.64+Crore&newsId=1edc4c4e-5af5-4834-80dc-dea9dda45d61&token=MWVkYzRjNGUtNWFm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1edc4c4e-5af5-4834-80dc-dea9dda45d61</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:54:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Network People Services Technologies Ltd, a company primarily engaged in providing software and payment solutions to the banking and finance sector, has reported its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a profit of ₹ 2,871.64 Crore for the period. The results were reviewed and recommended by the Audit Committee of the Board and approved by the board of directors in their meeting held on February 11, 2026. The company operates under a single segment and has adopted Indian Accounting Standard (IND AS) from financial year 2024-25. The financial statements were prepared as per Ind AS for the financial year 2024-25 and the comparative numbers reported for Quarter and nine months ended December 2024 are restated to make it comparable. The Government of India had announced the implementation of four Labour Codes effective 21st November 2025, but there is no incremental impact of this on company&apos;s results.</p><ul><li>Profit of ₹ 2,871.64 Crore for the period</li><li>Single segment operation under Ind AS</li><li>Financial statements prepared as per Ind AS for the financial year 2024-25</li><li>Comparative numbers restated for Quarter and nine months ended December 2024</li><li>No incremental impact of Labour Codes implementation</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1ed9f0d6-955c-48fb-9852-c4c0be1de4ef.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Network People Services Technologies Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MSRINDIA] MSR India Ltd to Consider and Approve Un-audited Financial Results on February 14, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MSR+INDIA+LTD.&title=MSR+India+Ltd+to+Consider+and+Approve+Un-audited+Financial+Results+on+February+14%2C+2026&newsId=f6ce251e-83d3-4306-9880-48d24cffed3f&token=ZjZjZTI1MWUtODNk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6ce251e-83d3-4306-9880-48d24cffed3f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:51:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>MSR India Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 14, 2026, to consider and approve the Un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31.12.2025. The meeting will be held at the company&apos;s registered office at 03.00 P.M. The company has also informed that the trading window for dealing in securities of the company by the designated persons, their immediate relatives and all connected persons covered under the Company’s Code of Conduct shall remain closed from 01.01.2026 till 48 hours after the declaration of the results.</p><ul><li>MSR India Ltd to consider and approve Un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31.12.2025</li><li>Board Meeting scheduled on 14th February, 2026</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities of the company to remain closed from 01.01.2026 till 48 hours after the declaration of results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b9a6e2d3-ea0d-470d-9932-0cde9647d554.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MSR INDIA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GOCLCORP] GOCL Corporation Ltd. Reports Q3 and Nine-Months Results for 2025, Board Approves Financial Statements</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GOCL+Corporation+Ltd-%24&title=GOCL+Corporation+Ltd.+Reports+Q3+and+Nine-Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Board+Approves+Financial+Statements&newsId=2067e686-072e-4461-a725-fe8f23cdcf05&token=MjA2N2U2ODYtMDcy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2067e686-072e-4461-a725-fe8f23cdcf05</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:51:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>GOCL Corporation Ltd. has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s standalone and consolidated un-audited financial results were approved in a Board meeting. The results and limited review reports were submitted by Haribhakti &amp; Co. LLP, the company&apos;s auditors.</p><ul><li>GOCL Corporation Ltd. reported its unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s Board of Directors approved the un-audited financial results (Standalone and Consolidated) for the quarter and nine-months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The financial results were submitted by Haribhakti &amp; Co. LLP, the company&apos;s auditors, along with limited review reports.</li><li>The meeting of the Board of Directors commenced at 07:00 p.m. and concluded at about 08:10 p.m.</li><li>The financial results are prepared in accordance with the recognition and measurement principles laid down in Indian Accounting Standard 34.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b3a1fa91-9d46-47cb-8dbb-caba46cb467a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GOCL Corporation Ltd-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BOMDYEING] Bombay Dyeing &amp; Manufacturing Company Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BOMBAY+DYEING+%26+MFG.CO.LTD.&title=Bombay+Dyeing+%26+Manufacturing+Company+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=31972953-e837-4743-a672-ffef28f61c88&token=MzE5NzI5NTMtZTgz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">31972953-e837-4743-a672-ffef28f61c88</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:49:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Bombay Dyeing &amp; Manufacturing Company Ltd has reported its unaudited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The company&apos;s board approved these results in a meeting held on 11th February, 2026. The company will also publish an extract of these results in accordance with Regulation 47(1)(b) of the Listing Regulations. The Chief Financial Officer and Chief Risk Officer (CFO &amp; CRO), Mr. Khiroda Jena, has tendered his resignation effective from 13th February, 2026.</p><ul><li>Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December, 2025 approved.</li><li>Company to publish Extract of Unaudited Financial Results as per Regulation 47(1)(b) of the Listing Regulations.</li><li>Resignation of the Chief Financial Officer and Chief Risk Officer (CFO &amp; CRO), Mr. Khiroda Jena, noted.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/16ba9a56-c507-44e1-8f65-6990dc21091b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BOMBAY DYEING & MFG.CO.LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PAVNAIND] Pavna Industries&apos; PAT Surges by 297.37% in Q3FY26; Announces MoU with Uttar Pradesh Government</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Pavna+Industries+Ltd&title=Pavna+Industries%27+PAT+Surges+by+297.37%25+in+Q3FY26%3B+Announces+MoU+with+Uttar+Pradesh+Government&newsId=9706850f-6b61-47a3-aa00-b16d4d6e163d&token=OTcwNjg1MGYtNmI2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9706850f-6b61-47a3-aa00-b16d4d6e163d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:44:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Pavna Industries Limited, a leading automotive components manufacturer, announced its financial results for the third quarter and nine months ending 31st December 2025. The company reported a significant increase in revenue, EBITDA, and PAT, demonstrating strong operational performance. Pavna Industries also achieved key strategic milestones, including signing an MoU with the Government of Uttar Pradesh to invest Rs 250 crore over the next 3-5 years, inaugurating a state-of-the-art R&amp;D Centre in Noida, and acquiring additional land near the upcoming Jewar Airport.</p><ul><li>Pavna Industries&apos; PAT surged by 297.37% in Q3FY26</li><li>Revenue increased by 36.00% and EBITDA by 30.15% in Q3FY26</li><li>Signed MoU with Uttar Pradesh Government to invest Rs 250 crore over the next 3-5 years</li><li>Inaugurated a state-of-the-art R&amp;D Centre in Noida</li><li>Acquired additional 4.33 acres of land near the upcoming Jewar Airport</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5fec5011-75ba-44f5-b3f9-8e1bac499a09.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Pavna Industries Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ICICIAMC] ICICI Prudential AMC Receives RBI Approval to Acquire Shares in Seven Banks</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ICICI+Prudential+Asset+Management+Company+Ltd&title=ICICI+Prudential+AMC+Receives+RBI+Approval+to+Acquire+Shares+in+Seven+Banks&newsId=b2465f75-4c17-4ca4-bd89-8b6da9062022&token=YjI0NjVmNzUtNGMx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b2465f75-4c17-4ca4-bd89-8b6da9062022</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:44:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>ICICI Prudential Asset Management Company Ltd. has received approval from the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) to acquire shares or voting rights in seven banks, subject to certain conditions. The approval was granted to the AMC and the group entities of ICICI Bank Limited under the Reserve Bank of India (Acquisition of Shares and Taking of Loans by Financial Institution) Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The AMC will acquire the shares on behalf of schemes of ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund, Alternative Investment Funds, and clients of Portfolio Management Services. The seven banks are Bandhan Bank Limited, City Union Bank Limited, Equitas Small Finance Bank Limited, The Federal Bank Limited, HDFC Bank Limited, IDFC First Bank Limited, The Karur Vysya Bank Limited, and RBL Bank Limited.</p><ul><li>ICICI Prudential AMC received approval from RBI to acquire shares in seven banks</li><li>The approval is subject to certain conditions and compliance with statutory and regulatory provisions</li><li>The AMC will acquire shares on behalf of ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund, Alternative Investment Funds, and Portfolio Management Services clients</li><li>The seven banks include Bandhan Bank, City Union Bank, Equitas Small Finance Bank, The Federal Bank, HDFC Bank, IDFC First Bank, The Karur Vysya Bank, and RBL Bank</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/47175f40-c95f-4542-9573-4ffcdacd3ad3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ICICI Prudential Asset Management Company Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BOMDYEING] Bombay Dyeing &amp; Manufacturing Company Ltd Announces Q3 and 9M Unaudited Financial Results for 2025 and Resignation of CFO &amp; CRO</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BOMBAY+DYEING+%26+MFG.CO.LTD.&title=Bombay+Dyeing+%26+Manufacturing+Company+Ltd+Announces+Q3+and+9M+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+2025+and+Resignation+of+CFO+%26+CRO&newsId=e1f9a0c5-b93b-4f03-a623-ae1f2511a439&token=ZTFmOWEwYzUtYjkz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e1f9a0c5-b93b-4f03-a623-ae1f2511a439</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:42:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Bombay Dyeing &amp; Manufacturing Company Ltd has announced its unaudited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended 31 December, 2025. The company&apos;s board approved the results during its meeting on 11 February, 2026. The company will also publish an extract of the unaudited financial results. Furthermore, the board noted the resignation of Mr. Khiroda Jena, the Chief Financial Officer &amp; Chief Risk Officer, with effect from the close of business hours on 13 February, 2026.</p><ul><li>Bombay Dyeing &amp; Manufacturing Company Ltd announced its unaudited financial results for Q3 and 9M 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s board approved the results during its meeting on 11 February, 2026.</li><li>The company will publish an extract of the unaudited financial results.</li><li>Mr. Khiroda Jena, the Chief Financial Officer &amp; Chief Risk Officer, tendered his resignation effective from 13 February, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1e585f4b-9ec1-4388-bf3a-0d0075796218.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BOMBAY DYEING & MFG.CO.LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NPST] Network People Services Technologies Ltd. Deviates from Preferential Allotment Objects for Operational Expenses</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Network+People+Services+Technologies+Ltd&title=Network+People+Services+Technologies+Ltd.+Deviates+from+Preferential+Allotment+Objects+for+Operational+Expenses&newsId=9197807b-c92e-4c66-a275-6b1b1586e511&token=OTE5NzgwN2ItYzky</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9197807b-c92e-4c66-a275-6b1b1586e511</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:42:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Network People Services Technologies Ltd. has reported a deviation from the objects for which funds were raised through preferential allotment in September 2025. The company utilized 3.18 crore towards rent and salary payments, which were classified under General Corporate Purpose (GCP). The Audit Committee and the Board of Directors have clarified that these expenses are essential operational expenditures and fall within the scope of General Corporate Purposes as disclosed in the offer document.</p><ul><li>Funds raised through preferential allotment in September 2025.</li><li>Deviation from objects for funds utilization.</li><li>3.18 crore utilized for rent and salary payments.</li><li>Classified under General Corporate Purpose (GCP).</li><li>Audit Committee and Board&apos;s clarification on the deviation.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/887c5748-b600-4a9d-b010-b6204dc2d13d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Network People Services Technologies Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NPST] Network People Services Technologies Ltd Utilizes Preferential Allotment Proceeds Towards Operational Expenses</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Network+People+Services+Technologies+Ltd&title=Network+People+Services+Technologies+Ltd+Utilizes+Preferential+Allotment+Proceeds+Towards+Operational+Expenses&newsId=d2a6a58a-77f1-4ade-bbc3-66fe6b9d8f28&token=ZDJhNmE1OGEtNzdm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2a6a58a-77f1-4ade-bbc3-66fe6b9d8f28</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 15:42:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Network People Services Technologies Ltd has utilized a portion of the issue proceeds towards General Corporate Purposes, including rent and salary payments, which has been classified under General Corporate Purpose (GCP). This amounts to Rs.3.18 crore. The company has utilized the proceeds in form of reimbursement towards the expenses incurred from the current account. The utilization of proceeds towards object 1 and object 2 includes salary expenses which are categorized on the basis of the CFO&apos;s undertaking defining the role of staff for which the salary expenses were incurred and linking it to the object.</p><ul><li>Network People Services Technologies Ltd has utilized Rs.3.18 crore towards rent and salary payments.</li><li>The utilization of proceeds is classified under General Corporate Purpose (GCP).</li><li>The company has utilized the proceeds in form of reimbursement towards the expenses incurred from the current account.</li><li>The utilization of proceeds towards object 1 and object 2 includes salary expenses.</li><li>The expenses are routine and essential operational expenditures, duly accounted for in the Profit &amp; Loss.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8c027710-c290-4105-8d0b-8b0d862b61a9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Network People Services Technologies Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>