<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 18:45:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[GRERENEW] GRE Renew Enertech Ltd Secures EPC Contracts Worth INR 19.28 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GRE+Renew+Enertech+Ltd&title=GRE+Renew+Enertech+Ltd+Secures+EPC+Contracts+Worth+INR+19.28+Crores&newsId=fe45f486-7e04-4cf1-9643-fb7f4d8e4068&token=ZmU0NWY0ODYtN2Uw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe45f486-7e04-4cf1-9643-fb7f4d8e4068</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>GRE Renew Enertech Ltd has received multiple orders from domestic entities for execution of Engineering, Procurement and Construction (EPC) contracts on a turnkey basis. The total value of these orders is INR 19,27,73,351 (Rupees Nineteen Crores Twenty-Seven Lakhs Seventy-Three Thousand Three Hundred Fifty-One only), inclusive of applicable taxes. The contracts were received from Pragna Pharma Private Limited, Pragna Dyechem Private Limited, and Green Leaf Chem Tech Private Limited. The contracts are routine in nature and have been received in the ordinary course of the company&apos;s existing EPC operations. The terms and conditions of the orders are standard commercial terms customary to such contracts and do not contain any unusual or extraordinary stipulations.</p><ul><li>GRE Renew Enertech Ltd has secured EPC contracts worth INR 19.28 crores</li><li>The contracts have been received from domestic entities</li><li>The orders are for turnkey EPC projects</li><li>The contracts are routine and received in the ordinary course of business</li><li>The terms and conditions of the orders are standard and customary</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f98c60a0-3d5d-4454-a1b6-e68d0723fbb9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GRE Renew Enertech Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SANCODE] Sancode Technologies Ltd. Announces Increase in Authorized Share Capital and Issuance of Convertible Warrants</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sancode+Technologies+Ltd&title=Sancode+Technologies+Ltd.+Announces+Increase+in+Authorized+Share+Capital+and+Issuance+of+Convertible+Warrants&newsId=f8e5d6d1-a887-4319-87c5-94842da5a3fe&token=ZjhlNWQ2ZDEtYTg4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f8e5d6d1-a887-4319-87c5-94842da5a3fe</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sancode Technologies Ltd. announced the outcomes of its Board Meeting held on 26th February, 2026. The company has approved an increase in the authorized share capital and the issuance of up to 23,25,582 convertible warrants. The warrants will be issued to promoters and non-promoters on a preferential basis, subject to the approval of shareholders in the ensuing General Meeting. The conversion ratio of each warrant is 1:1, and the conversion can be exercised at any time within a period of 18 months from the date of issue. The company has also appointed Mr. Ramraj Singh Thakur as the Company Secretary and Compliance Officer, and Dilip Swarnkar &amp; Associates as scrutinizers for scrutinizing the voting and issuance of the Scrutinizer Report.</p><ul><li>Increase in the authorized share capital from Rs. 6,50,00,000/- to Rs. 10,00,00,000/-</li><li>Issuance of up to 23,25,582 convertible warrants at an issue price of Rs. 172/- each</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Ramraj Singh Thakur as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer</li><li>Appointment of Dilip Swarnkar &amp; Associates as scrutinizers for scrutinizing the voting and issuance of the Scrutinizer Report</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c26049fb-32c8-4878-9396-f26db5f8c527.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sancode Technologies Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EMUDHRA] eMudhra Unveils Trust Infrastructure for Secure AI Economy</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=eMudhra+Ltd&title=eMudhra+Unveils+Trust+Infrastructure+for+Secure+AI+Economy&newsId=8eac2fc5-6824-4226-bc84-58cd9fad5296&token=OGVhYzJmYzUtNjgy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8eac2fc5-6824-4226-bc84-58cd9fad5296</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>eMudhra, a global provider of digital identity and authentication services, has announced the launch of its Agentic AI Security Platform. This trust infrastructure is designed to secure autonomous AI systems by providing verifiable identity, authentication, and governance controls for AI agents operating across enterprise and public digital environments. The platform enables organizations to establish cryptographic identities for AI agents, enforce policy-driven authorization, and maintain verifiable audit trails for AI-initiated actions. It is designed to support evolving regulatory requirements and post-quantum security transitions.</p><ul><li>Launch of Agentic AI Security Platform for secure AI systems</li><li>Provides verifiable identity, authentication, and governance controls for AI agents</li><li>Enables cryptographic identities for AI agents and policy-driven authorization</li><li>Supports evolving regulatory requirements and post-quantum security transitions</li><li>Designed to integrate with enterprise security environments and digital public infrastructure</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9bdb4713-dd12-4f0a-bee1-0d0eebe30846.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: eMudhra Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RECLTD] REC Ltd Transfers Entire Shareholding of Umred Power Transmission Limited to Successful Bidder</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=REC+Ltd&title=REC+Ltd+Transfers+Entire+Shareholding+of+Umred+Power+Transmission+Limited+to+Successful+Bidder&newsId=1b66c63b-0567-4ae6-94e6-2069998a882b&token=MWI2NmM2M2ItMDU2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b66c63b-0567-4ae6-94e6-2069998a882b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>REC Power Development and Consultancy Limited (RECPDCL), a wholly owned subsidiary of REC Limited, has transferred the entire shareholding of Umred Power Transmission Limited to the successful bidder selected through a tariff based competitive bidding process. The transfer took place on February 26, 2026, and includes all assets and liabilities of the SPV. The consideration for the sale and transfer is determined in accordance with the Guidelines issued by the Ministry of Power, Government of India. This transaction does not fall under related party transactions and is not a slump sale.</p><ul><li>REC Ltd transfers shareholding of Umred Power Transmission Limited to successful bidder</li><li>Transfer includes all assets and liabilities of the SPV</li><li>Transaction amount is 22,34,28,481/- inclusive of professional fee, reimbursement of expenses and taxes</li><li>Transaction does not fall under related party transactions</li><li>Consideration determined in accordance with Ministry of Power Guidelines</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/94eb6b25-3436-49c0-9bf7-b8cbb73684e4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: REC Ltd | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KIRLOSIND] Kirloskar Industries Subsidiary, Kirloskar Ferrous Industries Limited, Announces 1x1 Virtual Meetings with Institutional Investors and Analysts</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kirloskar+Industries+Ltd&title=Kirloskar+Industries+Subsidiary%2C+Kirloskar+Ferrous+Industries+Limited%2C+Announces+1x1+Virtual+Meetings+with+Institutional+Investors+and+Analysts&newsId=9fd06ed8-ab14-4b96-8cb1-8ca6dbaabf20&token=OWZkMDZlZDgtYWIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9fd06ed8-ab14-4b96-8cb1-8ca6dbaabf20</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 17:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kirloskar Industries Ltd. has shared an update about its subsidiary, Kirloskar Ferrous Industries Limited (KFIL). KFIL has informed the stock exchanges about scheduled 1x1 virtual meetings with institutional investors, analysts, and financial institutions. The meetings are planned with EMKAY Global, Bandhan Mutual Fund, and HDFC Mutual Fund. The schedule is subject to changes due to unforeseen circumstances.</p><ul><li>Kirloskar Industries Ltd. shares update about its subsidiary, Kirloskar Ferrous Industries Limited (KFIL)</li><li>KFIL to conduct 1x1 virtual meetings with institutional investors, analysts, and financial institutions</li><li>Scheduled meetings with EMKAY Global, Bandhan Mutual Fund, and HDFC Mutual Fund</li><li>Meetings are subject to changes due to unforeseen circumstances</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/63aba8a3-1be7-4f1d-9813-f8e3b406a74b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kirloskar Industries Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PASHUPATI] Pashupati Cotspin Ltd Announces 1:10 Stock Split and Capital Alteration</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Pashupati+Cotspin+Ltd&title=Pashupati+Cotspin+Ltd+Announces+1%3A10+Stock+Split+and+Capital+Alteration&newsId=7967bab1-c3a4-41e1-88d7-5438957d0e44&token=Nzk2N2JhYjEtYzNh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7967bab1-c3a4-41e1-88d7-5438957d0e44</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 16:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Split</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pashupati Cotspin Ltd, a textile company, announced a sub-division of one existing equity share with a face value of Rs. 10/- into 10 equity shares with a face value of Rs. 1/- each. The decision was made at the 8th Board Meeting held on February 26, 2026. The sub-division is subject to approval from shareholders and necessary regulatory authorities. The company also approved alteration of the Capital Clause of the Memorandum of Association to give effect to the aforesaid sub-division of equity shares. The appointment of a Scrutinizer to scrutinize the Postal Ballot process was also approved.</p><ul><li>Pashupati Cotspin Ltd announces a 1:10 stock split</li><li>The sub-division is subject to approval from shareholders and necessary regulatory authorities</li><li>The company also approved alteration of the Capital Clause of the Memorandum of Association</li><li>Appointment of a Scrutinizer to scrutinize the Postal Ballot process was also approved</li><li>The decision was made at the 8th Board Meeting held on February 26, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d0128b13-db43-4a83-abe7-658ac1028386.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Pashupati Cotspin Ltd | Category: Split</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZAGGLE] Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd Enters Agreement with SuperKing Ventures Private Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Zaggle+Prepaid+Ocean+Services+Ltd&title=Zaggle+Prepaid+Ocean+Services+Ltd+Enters+Agreement+with+SuperKing+Ventures+Private+Limited&newsId=20410fc6-6333-4908-8fff-c33aff7e303a&token=MjA0MTBmYzYtNjMz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">20410fc6-6333-4908-8fff-c33aff7e303a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 16:41:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Limited has entered into an agreement with SuperKing Ventures Private Limited. Zaggle will offer its Zaggle Corporate Expense cards to employees and associates of Superking Ventures Private Limited. The contract is domestic, has a one-year execution period, and does not involve related party transactions.</p><ul><li>Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Limited has entered into an agreement with SuperKing Ventures Private Limited</li><li>Zaggle will offer its Zaggle Corporate Expense cards to employees and associates of Superking Ventures Private Limited</li><li>The contract is domestic</li><li>The contract has a one-year execution period</li><li>The contract does not involve related party transactions</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b32c081a-58b5-4528-8418-3fad75c63229.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZAGGLE] Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd Enters Agreement with Chennai Super Kings Cricket Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Zaggle+Prepaid+Ocean+Services+Ltd&title=Zaggle+Prepaid+Ocean+Services+Ltd+Enters+Agreement+with+Chennai+Super+Kings+Cricket+Limited&newsId=34984fac-dcf3-48fa-9491-926453b54400&token=MzQ5ODRmYWMtZGNm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">34984fac-dcf3-48fa-9491-926453b54400</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 16:41:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Partnership</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Limited has entered into an agreement with Chennai Super Kings Cricket Limited. Zaggle will offer its Zaggle Corporate Expense cards to employees and associates of Chennai Super Kings Cricket Limited. The contract is domestic, has a one-year time period, and is not a related party transaction.</p><ul><li>Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd has entered into a partnership with Chennai Super Kings Cricket Limited</li><li>Zaggle will offer its Zaggle Corporate Expense cards to employees and associates of Chennai Super Kings Cricket Limited</li><li>The contract is domestic and has a one-year time period</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/39287188-0f1a-408a-846b-162727a68658.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd | Category: Partnership</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZAGGLE] Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Limited Enters Agreement with Saurashtra Cement Limited for Employee Expense Management &amp; Benefits</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Zaggle+Prepaid+Ocean+Services+Ltd&title=Zaggle+Prepaid+Ocean+Services+Limited+Enters+Agreement+with+Saurashtra+Cement+Limited+for+Employee+Expense+Management+%26+Benefits&newsId=0b949f6b-58c8-4be3-b36c-1b0f26846909&token=MGI5NDlmNmItNThj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b949f6b-58c8-4be3-b36c-1b0f26846909</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 16:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Limited has entered into an agreement with Saurashtra Cement Limited to provide Zaggle Save, an Employee Expense Management &amp; Benefits solution. The agreement details are provided in Annexure-A as per the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The order is domestic, and the time period for execution is not specified in the text.</p><ul><li>Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Limited has entered into an agreement with Saurashtra Cement Limited</li><li>Zaggle will provide Zaggle Save (Employee Expense Management &amp; Benefits) to Saurashtra Cement Limited</li><li>The order is domestic and has no specified time period for execution</li><li>The agreement details are provided in Annexure-A as per the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/268a5fbd-efb5-448a-883a-98440c3364d7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZHINUDYP] Hindusthan Udyog Ltd. Re-appoints Mr. S.K. Roychowdhury as Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HINDUSTHAN+UDYOG+LTD.&title=Hindusthan+Udyog+Ltd.+Re-appoints+Mr.+S.K.+Roychowdhury+as+Independent+Director&newsId=1631e081-d852-4662-8cf3-d65354de2301&token=MTYzMWUwODEtZDg1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1631e081-d852-4662-8cf3-d65354de2301</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 16:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hindusthan Udyog Ltd. announced the re-appointment of Mr. Sanjib Kumar Roychowdhury as an Independent Director at their Board of Directors meeting on 26th February, 2026. The re-appointment is subject to the approval of the shareholders. The meeting commenced at 2:00 P.M. and concluded at 3:00 P.M. The company&apos;s registered office is located at &apos;TRINITY PLAZA&apos;, 3rd Floor, 84/1A, Topsia Road, (South), Kolkata- 700 046, India. The company&apos;s CIN number is L27120WB1947PLCO15767.</p><ul><li>Re-appointment of Mr. Sanjib Kumar Roychowdhury as an Independent Director</li><li>Subject to the approval of the shareholders</li><li>Meeting commenced at 2:00 P.M. and concluded at 3:00 P.M.</li><li>Registered office located at &apos;TRINITY PLAZA&apos;, 3rd Floor, 84/1A, Topsia Road, (South), Kolkata- 700 046, India</li><li>Company&apos;s CIN number is L27120WB1947PLCO15767</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2c67ed70-6c16-47c7-8c7b-324f8098771c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HINDUSTHAN UDYOG LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>