<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:48:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SHRADDHA] Shraddha Prime Projects Ltd: Resignation of Non-Executive Independent Director Ms. Ankita Gupta</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shraddha+Prime+Projects+Ltd&title=Shraddha+Prime+Projects+Ltd%3A+Resignation+of+Non-Executive+Independent+Director+Ms.+Ankita+Gupta&newsId=c0957f1a-a6b7-46a4-a48d-dc0c9aa1f024&token=YzA5NTdmMWEtYTZi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c0957f1a-a6b7-46a4-a48d-dc0c9aa1f024</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:48:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shraddha Prime Projects Ltd has revised its intimation regarding the resignation of its Non-Executive Independent Director, Ms. Ankita Gupta. The designation was inadvertently mentioned as Non-Executive Non-Independent Director due to a typographical error, which has now been corrected to Non-Executive Independent Director. The resignation is due to professional commitments and personal reasons, with no other material reasons. The resignation will be effective from the close of business hours on February 14, 2026.</p><ul><li>Revision of intimation regarding the resignation of Non-Executive Independent Director Ms. Ankita Gupta</li><li>Correction of designation from Non-Executive Non-Independent Director to Non-Executive Independent Director</li><li>Resignation due to professional commitments and personal reasons</li><li>No other material reasons for resignation</li><li>Resignation effective from the close of business hours on February 14, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dca9c0bd-0a46-4b46-8b52-fab2f1a682bb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shraddha Prime Projects Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASHIS] Ashiana Ispat Limited Approves Q3 Results and Appoints New Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ASHIANA+ISPAT+LTD.&title=Ashiana+Ispat+Limited+Approves+Q3+Results+and+Appoints+New+Director&newsId=c623303b-5d11-474e-84e0-52936563c270&token=YzYyMzMwM2ItNWQx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c623303b-5d11-474e-84e0-52936563c270</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ashiana Ispat Limited, at its meeting held on 14-02-2026, approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31 December 2025. The company also appointed Ms. Sarita Jain as an Additional Director (Non-executive, Non-Independent Director) with effect from 14-02-2026.</p><ul><li>Ashiana Ispat Limited approved the unaudited financial results for Q3 2025</li><li>Ms. Sarita Jain appointed as an Additional Director (Non-executive, Non-Independent Director)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9cb54fdc-9a5b-42e7-8190-1dccdd39cb67.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ASHIANA ISPAT LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[POLYCAB] Polycab India Ltd Appoints Mr. Gyan Pandey as Executive President and Chief Digital &amp; Information Officer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Polycab+India+Ltd&title=Polycab+India+Ltd+Appoints+Mr.+Gyan+Pandey+as+Executive+President+and+Chief+Digital+%26+Information+Officer&newsId=0c0e2dfa-5b8c-4242-9b16-6657d106a0d5&token=MGMwZTJkZmEtNWI4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c0e2dfa-5b8c-4242-9b16-6657d106a0d5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:48:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Polycab India Ltd has appointed Mr. Gyan Pandey as Executive President and Chief Digital &amp; Information Officer with effect from February 16, 2026. Mr. Pandey, aged 57, has completed his Bachelor of Commerce (Hons.) from the University of Calcutta and has obtained various management certifications from IIM-B &amp; IIM-C. He has over 25 years of experience in Information and Technology, with leadership roles in Voltas, Aurobindo Pharma, and Oracle. His work areas include driving enterprise-level digital strategies, IoT-led manufacturing initiatives, data-driven platforms, and Scalable AI/Gen AI adoption for business cases. He will oversee the functioning &amp; initiatives of Digital, IT &amp; cybersecurity functions.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Gyan Pandey as Executive President and Chief Digital &amp; Information Officer</li><li>Mr. Pandey&apos;s professional journey includes leadership roles across prominent organizations like Voltas, Aurobindo Pharma and Oracle</li><li>Mr. Pandey has over 25 years of experience in Information and Technology</li><li>Mr. Pandey will oversee the functioning &amp; initiatives of Digital, IT &amp; cybersecurity functions</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5f35fe95-555a-44b7-b6a5-7dade6ee9e85.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Polycab India Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DLCL] Dr Lalchandani Labs Extends Rights Issue Closing Date Until February 27, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Dr+Lalchandani+Labs+Ltd&title=Dr+Lalchandani+Labs+Extends+Rights+Issue+Closing+Date+Until+February+27%2C+2026&newsId=e54b84a0-ffba-4bb6-ad9c-964157cd68ca&token=ZTU0Yjg0YTAtZmZi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e54b84a0-ffba-4bb6-ad9c-964157cd68ca</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Right Issue</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dr Lalchandani Labs Ltd. has announced the extension of the closing date of its ongoing rights issue from February 20, 2026, to February 27, 2026. The extension is granted to facilitate better participation from eligible shareholders and to provide them with adequate time to subscribe to the Rights Issue. The on-market trading in Rights Entitlements, which was originally scheduled to close on February 17, 2026, has also been extended to Tuesday, February 24, 2026. The finalization of the basis of allotment is scheduled for Monday, March 02, 2026, with the date of allotment and credit also set for the same day. The date of listing is set for Thursday, March 05, 2026. There are no other modifications to the Letter of Offer (LOF), Composite Application Form (CAF), or other issue-related documents.</p><ul><li>Dr Lalchandani Labs extends the closing date of its rights issue until February 27, 2026.</li><li>The extension aims to facilitate better participation from eligible shareholders.</li><li>The on-market trading in Rights Entitlements has been extended to February 24, 2026.</li><li>The finalization of the basis of allotment is scheduled for March 02, 2026.</li><li>The date of listing is set for March 05, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5bc92445-31d0-4a22-a0e7-b7c084ebe879.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Dr Lalchandani Labs Ltd | Category: Right Issue</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[APOLLOTYRE] Apollo Tyres Ltd to Participate in Kotak Chasing Growth 2026 and IIFL&apos;s 17th Enterprising India | Mumbai Global Investors&apos; Conference</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=APOLLO+TYRES+LTD.&title=Apollo+Tyres+Ltd+to+Participate+in+Kotak+Chasing+Growth+2026+and+IIFL%27s+17th+Enterprising+India+%7C+Mumbai+Global+Investors%27+Conference&newsId=2757c1d3-7d18-4df1-be0d-29cd41161eec&token=Mjc1N2MxZDMtN2Qx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2757c1d3-7d18-4df1-be0d-29cd41161eec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Apollo Tyres Ltd has announced its participation in two upcoming investor conferences. The first is the Kotak Chasing Growth 2026, scheduled for February 23, 2026, in Mumbai. The second is IIFL&apos;s 17th Enterprising India | Mumbai Global Investors&apos; Conference, set to take place on February 24, 2026. The company&apos;s participation in these events is in compliance with Regulation 30(6) and 46(2) of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The company has also disclosed this information on its website, www.apollotyres.com. Please note that the schedule is subject to change due to unforeseen circumstances on the part of the investors or the company.</p><ul><li>Apollo Tyres Ltd to participate in Kotak Chasing Growth 2026 in Mumbai</li><li>The company will also participate in IIFL&apos;s 17th Enterprising India | Mumbai Global Investors&apos; Conference</li><li>Participation is in compliance with SEBI regulations</li><li>Information disclosed on the company&apos;s website</li><li>Schedule subject to change due to unforeseen circumstances</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/10882216-b355-4f97-b185-ae5c00a83523.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: APOLLO TYRES LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CONCORD] Concord Drugs Ltd. Clarifies Inadvertent Omission in Labour Codes Disclosure</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Concord+Drugs+Ltd&title=Concord+Drugs+Ltd.+Clarifies+Inadvertent+Omission+in+Labour+Codes+Disclosure&newsId=deb3508b-9cf9-4cf5-ab35-fb38edd9fad5&token=ZGViMzUwOGItOWNm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">deb3508b-9cf9-4cf5-ab35-fb38edd9fad5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:41:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Concord Drugs Ltd. has issued a clarification regarding an inadvertent omission in a previous disclosure related to the implementation of Labour Codes. The omission was noted in the disclosure submitted on 14th February 2026, following a Board Meeting. The company has now provided the complete paragraph regarding the implementation of the Labour Codes under the Financial Results disclosure. The New Labour Codes, which consolidate 29 existing labour legislations into four codes, have been effective from November 21, 2025. However, the corresponding supporting rules under these codes are yet to be notified. The company is continuously monitoring the finalisation of Central/State Rules and clarifications from the Government on other aspects of the New Labour Codes. The company has estimated and accounted for incremental liability for employees, which is not material to the financial results.</p><ul><li>Concord Drugs Ltd. has clarified an inadvertent omission in a previous disclosure related to the implementation of Labour Codes.</li><li>The omission was noted in the disclosure submitted on 14th February 2026, following a Board Meeting.</li><li>The company has now provided the complete paragraph regarding the implementation of the Labour Codes under the Financial Results disclosure.</li><li>The New Labour Codes have been effective from November 21, 2025, but the corresponding supporting rules under these codes are yet to be notified.</li><li>The company is continuously monitoring the finalisation of Central/State Rules and clarifications from the Government on other aspects of the New Labour Codes.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fff987ac-1b73-4d0c-9a26-3e57acdac087.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Concord Drugs Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AYE] Aye Finance Ltd Closes Trading Window for Designated Persons and Immediate Relatives</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AYE&title=Aye+Finance+Ltd+Closes+Trading+Window+for+Designated+Persons+and+Immediate+Relatives&newsId=c5f5ef39-3601-4562-a51c-e8b08b21d51d&token=YzVmNWVmMzktMzYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5f5ef39-3601-4562-a51c-e8b08b21d51d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Trading Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Aye Finance Ltd has announced the closure of its trading window for all designated persons and their immediate relatives. This decision is in compliance with the &apos;Code of Conduct for Regulating, Monitoring and Reporting of Trading by Designated Persons &amp; their Immediate Relatives&apos; of the company and the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015. The trading window will be closed from Monday, February 16, 2026, and will remain closed until 48 hours after the announcement of the financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, to the Stock Exchanges. All designated persons of the company and their immediate relatives have been informed not to trade in the securities of the company during this period.</p><ul><li>Aye Finance Ltd closes trading window for designated persons and their immediate relatives</li><li>Closure in compliance with the &apos;Code of Conduct for Regulating, Monitoring and Reporting of Trading by Designated Persons &amp; their Immediate Relatives&apos; and SEBI regulations</li><li>Trading window to remain closed from Monday, February 16, 2026</li><li>Closure to continue until 48 hours after the announcement of financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Designated persons and their immediate relatives informed not to trade in the securities of the company during the closure period</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/22fbdf22-f29e-480f-ba7c-c94e782e9596.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AYE | Category: Trading Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ALKEM] Alkem Laboratories Subsidiary Enzene Achieves Zero Data Integrity Observations in USFDA Inspection</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Alkem+Laboratories+Ltd&title=Alkem+Laboratories+Subsidiary+Enzene+Achieves+Zero+Data+Integrity+Observations+in+USFDA+Inspection&newsId=89c3ab9c-3653-4c8c-a6d5-5d68dc3191ad&token=ODljM2FiOWMtMzY1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">89c3ab9c-3653-4c8c-a6d5-5d68dc3191ad</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>USFDA</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Alkem Laboratories Ltd. has announced the completion of a Pre-Approval Inspection (PAI) by the United States Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) at the manufacturing facility of its subsidiary, Enzene Biosciences Limited, in India. The USFDA inspection, conducted on 13 February, 2026, resulted in 6 procedural observations. However, Enzene is proud to announce that it has received zero observations related to data integrity, a critical validation of its quality systems and the reliability of its regulatory filings. Enzene is preparing and submitting its response to the USFDA within the stipulated timeline and has initiated appropriate corrective and preventive actions. This development underscores Alkem&apos;s commitment to maintaining high standards of quality and regulatory compliance.</p><ul><li>USFDA completes Pre-Approval Inspection at Alkem Laboratories&apos; subsidiary Enzene Biosciences Limited&apos;s manufacturing facility in India</li><li>Enzene achieves zero data integrity observations, a critical validation of its quality systems and regulatory filings reliability</li><li>Enzene to submit response to USFDA within stipulated timeline</li><li>Enzene initiates appropriate corrective and preventive actions</li><li>Alkem Laboratories maintains high standards of quality and regulatory compliance</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dc69f515-1982-446a-b3ea-aa6fc3d94caa.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Alkem Laboratories Ltd | Category: USFDA</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VRWODAR] Mrs. Nidhi Kirti Bhatt Resigns as Independent Director from VR Woodart Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=V+R+WOODART+LTD.&title=Mrs.+Nidhi+Kirti+Bhatt+Resigns+as+Independent+Director+from+VR+Woodart+Ltd&newsId=8a231e67-0cfe-48df-b6c7-6383714b1b9a&token=OGEyMzFlNjctMGNm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a231e67-0cfe-48df-b6c7-6383714b1b9a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mrs. Nidhi Kirti Bhatt has resigned as Independent Director from VR Woodart Ltd, formerly known as Megamont Limited, with effect from the close of working hours on 16th February 2026 due to personal reasons. The resignation is voluntary and there are no other material reasons or circumstances connected with it. Mrs. Bhatt expressed her gratitude for the opportunity to serve on the Board and confirmed that she has no claims or dues outstanding against the Company.</p><ul><li>Mrs. Nidhi Kirti Bhatt resigns as Independent Director from VR Woodart Ltd</li><li>Resignation is due to personal reasons</li><li>Resignation is voluntary</li><li>No other material reasons or circumstances connected with the resignation</li><li>Mrs. Bhatt expresses gratitude for the opportunity to serve on the Board</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5fa117e6-1dcc-4fcd-93ef-41e499e08b43.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: V R WOODART LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TGBHOTELS] Corrigendum: Appointment of New CFO at TGB Banquets and Hotels Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TGB+BANQUETS+AND+HOTELS+LTD.&title=Corrigendum%3A+Appointment+of+New+CFO+at+TGB+Banquets+and+Hotels+Ltd&newsId=a7e13b3e-82a3-4b4c-b8b6-0bfa70386713&token=YTdlMTNiM2UtODJh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a7e13b3e-82a3-4b4c-b8b6-0bfa70386713</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 09:29:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>TGB Banquets and Hotels Ltd has issued a corrigendum to clarify a typographical error in their previous announcement regarding the appointment of a new Chief Financial Officer (KMP). The error was in the &apos;Reason for Change&apos; section, where the name of the appointee was incorrectly stated. The correct information is that Mr. Prakash Shrivastav, a Chartered Accountant, has been appointed as the Chief Financial Officer (KMP) of the company. All other information provided in the original announcement remains unchanged.</p><ul><li>TGB Banquets and Hotels Ltd has issued a corrigendum to correct a typographical error in their previous announcement.</li><li>The error was in the &apos;Reason for Change&apos; section of the announcement.</li><li>Mr. Prakash Shrivastav has been appointed as the Chief Financial Officer (KMP) of the company.</li><li>All other information provided in the original announcement remains unchanged.</li><li>The corrigendum is also available on the company&apos;s website.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/16e9836e-ad2b-4c48-807b-572edd60bddb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TGB BANQUETS AND HOTELS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>