<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:59:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[BALKRISIND] Balkrishna Industries Sets Record Date for Commercial Paper Redemption</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BALKRISHNA+INDUSTRIES+LTD.-%24&title=Balkrishna+Industries+Sets+Record+Date+for+Commercial+Paper+Redemption&newsId=e9df8fad-1585-4316-abf2-b41751af506b&token=ZTlkZjhmYWQtMTU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9df8fad-1585-4316-abf2-b41751af506b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:57:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Balkrishna Industries Limited has announced the record date for the redemption of its commercial paper. The record date for the commercial paper of Rs. 100 crores is 27th February 2026. This date is significant as it is the date on which the company will determine which shareholders are eligible to receive the commercial paper that is being redeemed.</p><ul><li>Balkrishna Industries Limited has set the record date for the redemption of its commercial paper.</li><li>The record date for the commercial paper of Rs. 100 crores is 27th February 2026.</li><li>The company will determine shareholder eligibility for the commercial paper redemption on this date.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a1f00f46-3caf-4e15-a7cc-b082c788b6a8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BALKRISHNA INDUSTRIES LTD.-$ | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUGSLLOYD] Promoter Santosh Kumar Shah Acquires Shares of Sugs Lloyd Ltd Through On-Market Transactions</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sugs+Lloyd+Ltd&title=Promoter+Santosh+Kumar+Shah+Acquires+Shares+of+Sugs+Lloyd+Ltd+Through+On-Market+Transactions&newsId=a89ac152-a47b-4785-b805-a3e5462aab72&token=YTg5YWMxNTItYTQ3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a89ac152-a47b-4785-b805-a3e5462aab72</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Promoter Santosh Kumar Shah of Sugs Lloyd Ltd has acquired equity shares of the company through on-market transactions in February 2023. The total number of shares acquired by the promoter amounts to 39,000, with a total value of INR 8,93,970. The transactions were executed on the BSE SME platform.</p><ul><li>Promoter Santosh Kumar Shah acquired 39,000 equity shares of Sugs Lloyd Ltd</li><li>Total value of shares acquired is INR 8,93,970</li><li>Transactions were executed on BSE SME platform</li><li>Shares were acquired through on-market purchases</li><li>Acquisition took place in February 2023</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/76be8d20-fec8-4224-bd34-a3a6032a8bd4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sugs Lloyd Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PINELABS] Pine Labs Wins Multi-Year Contracts from Top 3 Indian OMCs for Nationwide Digital Payments Platform Modernisation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Pine+Labs+Ltd&title=Pine+Labs+Wins+Multi-Year+Contracts+from+Top+3+Indian+OMCs+for+Nationwide+Digital+Payments+Platform+Modernisation&newsId=05f8a188-ad56-4783-b2eb-8158368c3d96&token=MDVmOGExODgtYWQ1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05f8a188-ad56-4783-b2eb-8158368c3d96</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:52:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Global fintech platform Pine Labs has been awarded multiple landmark contracts from three leading Oil and Marketing Companies (OMCs) in India: Bharat Petroleum Corporation Limited (BPCL), Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Limited (HPCL), and Indian Oil Corporation Limited (IOCL). Under the contracts, Pine Labs will deploy, manage, and maintain the digital payments infrastructure at petrol pumps and merchant outlets across India. These are multi-year contracts aimed at leveraging Pine Labs&apos; expertise in managing payment rails for swifter, secure, seamless money movements at the point of sale. The contracts will cumulate to nearly 130,000 digital payments acceptance devices to be deployed and maintained pan India. Pine Labs will also manage IOCL&apos;s loyalty rewards platform called XTRAPOWER.</p><ul><li>Pine Labs has won multi-year contracts from top 3 Indian OMCs: BPCL, HPCL, and IOCL</li><li>Contracts involve deploying, managing, and maintaining digital payments infrastructure at petrol pumps and merchant outlets across India</li><li>Contracts aim to leverage Pine Labs&apos; expertise in managing payment rails for secure and seamless money movements</li><li>Nearly 130,000 digital payments acceptance devices to be deployed and maintained pan India</li><li>Pine Labs will manage IOCL&apos;s loyalty rewards platform called XTRAPOWER</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1f395d6b-f16f-48e8-b176-c18ac61013f1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Pine Labs Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AGSTRA] AGS Transact Technologies Ltd. Extends CIRP Period by 90 Days</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AGS+Transact+Technologies+Ltd&title=AGS+Transact+Technologies+Ltd.+Extends+CIRP+Period+by+90+Days&newsId=4ca6ced9-1df5-485a-af54-1b02a39e4ab4&token=NGNhNmNlZDktMWRm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4ca6ced9-1df5-485a-af54-1b02a39e4ab4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:52:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>In the 7th and adjourned 7th meeting of the Committee of Creditors (CoC) held on 12th and 16th February 2026 respectively, a significant decision was made through an E-Voting process. The CoC members approved the resolution for an extension of the Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP) period by 90 days. This decision is in accordance with the Insolvency and Bankruptcy Board of India (Insolvency Resolution Process for Corporate Persons) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>AGS Transact Technologies Ltd. extends CIRP period by 90 days</li><li>Decision made in the 7th and adjourned 7th meeting of the Committee of Creditors</li><li>Approval given through E-Voting process</li><li>In line with the Insolvency and Bankruptcy Board of India (Insolvency Resolution Process for Corporate Persons) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7f100825-1380-4840-ad3d-b29cc6c891a0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AGS Transact Technologies Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BALKRISIND] Balkrishna Industries Sets Record Date for Commercial Paper Redemption</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BALKRISHNA+INDUSTRIES+LTD.-%24&title=Balkrishna+Industries+Sets+Record+Date+for+Commercial+Paper+Redemption&newsId=cfd1122a-e73e-4d5a-a21d-0166c8d83c99&token=Y2ZkMTEyMmEtZTcz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cfd1122a-e73e-4d5a-a21d-0166c8d83c99</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:49:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Balkrishna Industries Limited has announced the record date for the redemption of its commercial paper. The record date for the commercial paper of Rs. 100 crores is 27th February 2026. This date is significant as it is the date on which the company will determine which shareholders are eligible to receive the commercial paper that is being redeemed.</p><ul><li>Balkrishna Industries Limited has set the record date for the redemption of its commercial paper.</li><li>The record date for the commercial paper of Rs. 100 crores is 27th February 2026.</li><li>The company&apos;s commercial paper matures on 2nd March 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/002aa8c5-a8e9-4cd3-ab1d-d94b32559dce.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BALKRISHNA INDUSTRIES LTD.-$ | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TIL] TIL Ltd Announces Rights Issue and Acquisition of Tulip Compression Private Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TIL+LTD.&title=TIL+Ltd+Announces+Rights+Issue+and+Acquisition+of+Tulip+Compression+Private+Limited&newsId=85062795-8d8d-4d9b-b374-04df5774f404&token=ODUwNjI3OTUtOGQ4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85062795-8d8d-4d9b-b374-04df5774f404</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>TIL Ltd has announced a rights issue of up to Rs. 200 crores and the acquisition of 60% stake in Tulip Compression Private Limited (TCPL) from Gainwell Commosales Private Limited. The rights issue will be on a rights basis to eligible equity shareholders, while the acquisition is subject to shareholder approval in the upcoming Extra-ordinary General Meeting. TCPL, a subsidiary of Gainwell Commosales Private Limited, operates in the design, packaging, servicing, and manufacturing of equipment used in CNG, LNG, and hydrogen refueling infrastructure. The acquisition will lead to strategic alignment and operational synergies between the two companies, with TIL&apos;s manufacturing capabilities supporting TCPL&apos;s transition from packaging to deeper manufacturing.</p><ul><li>TIL Ltd to raise up to Rs. 200 crores through rights issue</li><li>Acquisition of 60% stake in Tulip Compression Private Limited</li><li>TCPL operates in CNG, LNG, and hydrogen refueling infrastructure</li><li>Strategic alignment and operational synergies between the two companies</li><li>Acquisition subject to shareholder approval</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6bee899e-e944-4461-aa9f-38af1ad3c7b7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TIL LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADANIPORTS] Adani Ports Raises Rs. 1,000 Crore via Private Placement of NCDs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADANI+PORTS+AND+SPECIAL+ECONOMIC+ZONE+LTD.&title=Adani+Ports+Raises+Rs.+1%2C000+Crore+via+Private+Placement+of+NCDs&newsId=150fbc6b-4a83-432a-93ae-7c1787733098&token=MTUwZmJjNmItNGE4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">150fbc6b-4a83-432a-93ae-7c1787733098</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone Ltd. has successfully raised Rs. 1,000 crore by allotting 1,00,000 Rated, Listed, Secured, Redeemable, Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs) of the face value of Rs. 1,00,000/- each on a private placement basis. The tenure of these NCDs is 5 years and they will be listed on the Wholesale Debt Market segment of BSE Limited. The Finance Committee meeting for this purpose was held from 11:30 a.m. to 12:00 noon. The information has also been uploaded on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Adani Ports raises Rs. 1,000 crore through NCDs</li><li>1,00,000 NCDs of Rs. 1,00,000/- each allotted</li><li>NCDs have a tenure of 5 years</li><li>NCDs to be listed on BSE Limited&apos;s Wholesale Debt Market segment</li><li>Finance Committee meeting held for the purpose</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d8bd73f1-7ff8-4d76-95dc-724f69432726.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADANI PORTS AND SPECIAL ECONOMIC ZONE LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[APIL] Mark Corporate Advisors Submits Detailed Public Statement for Avi Products India Ltd&apos;s Open Offer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Avi+Products+India+Ltd&title=Mark+Corporate+Advisors+Submits+Detailed+Public+Statement+for+Avi+Products+India+Ltd%27s+Open+Offer&newsId=c0c04f74-bcf8-4c63-9fe7-183c7daae915&token=YzBjMDRmNzQtYmNm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c0c04f74-bcf8-4c63-9fe7-183c7daae915</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:40:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mark Corporate Advisors Pvt Ltd, the manager to the offer, has submitted a Detailed Public Statement (DPS) to BSE for the open offer to public shareholders of AVI Products India Limited (AVI). The DPS, as required under SEBI (SAST) Regulations, 2011, has been published in BusinessStandard. The DPS contains detailed information about the open offer and the target company.</p><ul><li>Mark Corporate Advisors Pvt Ltd has submitted a Detailed Public Statement (DPS) for Avi Products India Ltd&apos;s open offer to public shareholders.</li><li>The DPS has been published in BusinessStandard as required under SEBI (SAST) Regulations, 2011.</li><li>The DPS contains detailed information about the open offer and the target company.</li><li>All capitalised terms in the DPS have the same meaning as specified in the enclosed DPS.</li><li>Mark Corporate Advisors Private Limited requests for the DPS to be disseminated on the website.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/10D1CE59-50B0-4381-9F5A-59DCAA6728C2-120008.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Avi Products India Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[USK] Udayshivakumar Infra Ltd Promoter Acquires Equity Shares Worth INR 3,62,93,569</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Udayshivakumar+Infra+Ltd&title=Udayshivakumar+Infra+Ltd+Promoter+Acquires+Equity+Shares+Worth+INR+3%2C62%2C93%2C569&newsId=e98cea1d-cd59-4453-b271-f1a5e3b8af6d&token=ZTk4Y2VhMWQtY2Q1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e98cea1d-cd59-4453-b271-f1a5e3b8af6d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:27:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pursuant to Regulation 7(2) (b) of SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, Udayshivakumar Infra Ltd has received disclosures from its Promoter and Managing Director, Mr. Udayshivakumar, in Form C. The disclosures pertain to the acquisition of Equity Shares of the company. The total value of the acquired shares is INR 3,62,93,569. The shares were acquired on 20th February 2026.</p><ul><li>Udayshivakumar Infra Ltd Promoter acquires equity shares</li><li>Total value of the acquired shares is INR 3,62,93,569</li><li>Shares were acquired on 20th February 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/915fbf12-c018-4f22-ad83-21d54492842d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Udayshivakumar Infra Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[URBANCO] Urban Company&apos;s InstaHelp Crosses 50,000 Daily Bookings in Less Than 1 Year of Launch</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Urban+Company+Ltd&title=Urban+Company%27s+InstaHelp+Crosses+50%2C000+Daily+Bookings+in+Less+Than+1+Year+of+Launch&newsId=5f8569b6-6441-4cbf-8dd2-7b7e434821ae&token=NWY4NTY5YjYtNjQ0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f8569b6-6441-4cbf-8dd2-7b7e434821ae</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:22:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Urban Company Limited, formerly known as UrbanClap Technologies India Limited &amp; UrbanClap Technologies India Private Limited, announced that InstaHelp, its quick service housekeeping vertical, crossed 50,000 daily bookings on Sunday, 22 February 2026. InstaHelp offers high-quality housekeeping services for tasks like cleaning, dishwashing, laundry, and meal preparation, all within 10-15 minutes from the time of booking. The milestone represents a peak day, and long-term growth will be shaped by sustained customer retention, service quality, and scaling availability of professionals. Urban Company&apos;s India Consumer Services business reached the milestone of 50,000 bookings in a day approximately 6 years from the start of operations.</p><ul><li>Urban Company&apos;s InstaHelp crossed 50,000 daily bookings on 22 February 2026</li><li>InstaHelp offers high-quality housekeeping services within 10-15 minutes</li><li>The milestone represents a peak day</li><li>Long-term growth will be shaped by sustained customer retention, service quality, and scaling availability of professionals</li><li>Urban Company&apos;s India Consumer Services business reached 50,000 bookings in a day approximately 6 years from the start of operations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7c4ce0f1-8aff-4d45-ab9b-582b6907d10f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Urban Company Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>