<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:38:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[GENNEX] Gennex Laboratories Ltd Appoints Ms. Khushbu Kachhawa as Additional (Non-Executive &amp; Independent) Women Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GENNEX+LABORATORIES+LTD.&title=Gennex+Laboratories+Ltd+Appoints+Ms.+Khushbu+Kachhawa+as+Additional+%28Non-Executive+%26+Independent%29+Women+Director&newsId=29b4ac35-ce90-41a9-b8b8-19afeda889f1&token=MjliNGFjMzUtY2U5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29b4ac35-ce90-41a9-b8b8-19afeda889f1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:38:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gennex Laboratories Ltd has announced the appointment of Ms. Khushbu Kachhawa as an Additional (Non-Executive &amp; Independent) Women Director, subject to the approval of shareholders. Ms. Kachhawa is not related to the Promoter or Promoter Group and fulfills the criteria as required under the provisions of the Companies Act, 2013 and the Rules framed thereunder and the Listing Regulations. She has about 5 years of experience in handling business affairs and corporate secretarial matters.</p><ul><li>Ms. Khushbu Kachhawa appointed as Additional (Non-Executive &amp; Independent) Women Director</li><li>Appointment is subject to the approval of shareholders</li><li>Ms. Kachhawa is not related to the Promoter or Promoter Group</li><li>She fulfills the criteria as required under the Companies Act, 2013 and the Listing Regulations</li><li>Ms. Kachhawa has about 5 years of experience in handling business affairs and corporate secretarial matters</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/852ad304-4745-433f-b3f0-de6a9db6b360.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GENNEX LABORATORIES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PANCHSHEEL] Panchsheel Organics Declares Interim Dividend of 8% for Q3 &amp; Q4 FY2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PANCHSHEEL+ORGANICS+LTD.&title=Panchsheel+Organics+Declares+Interim+Dividend+of+8%25+for+Q3+%26+Q4+FY2025-26&newsId=6d0933f8-ec1e-4b83-b503-0dd1a8edf51c&token=NmQwOTMzZjgtZWMx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d0933f8-ec1e-4b83-b503-0dd1a8edf51c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Panchsheel Organics Ltd, in a recent Board of Directors meeting, declared an interim dividend for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The dividend is set at Rs. 0.80/- per share on Equity Shares of face value of Rs. 10/- each, amounting to 8% of the paid-up share capital. The record date for the purpose of payment of Interim dividend is fixed as Friday, February 20, 2026. The meeting was held from 04.00 P.M. to 05:10 P.M.</p><ul><li>Panchsheel Organics declares an interim dividend of 8% for Q3 and Q4 FY2025-26</li><li>The dividend is set at Rs. 0.80/- per share on Equity Shares of face value of Rs. 10/- each</li><li>The record date for the purpose of payment of Interim dividend is fixed as Friday, February 20, 2026</li><li>The meeting was held from 04.00 P.M. to 05:10 P.M.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dbf7fb3a-c13c-4e86-a923-9b7320dd471a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PANCHSHEEL ORGANICS LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MADHURIND] Madhur Industries Ltd. Announces Q3 and Nine-Month Unaudited Financial Results for FY 2025-2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MADHUR+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Madhur+Industries+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+Nine-Month+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+FY+2025-2026&newsId=302029c0-44a8-4e54-8671-5b1e7db05924&token=MzAyMDI5YzAtNDRh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">302029c0-44a8-4e54-8671-5b1e7db05924</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Madhur Industries Limited has announced its unaudited financial results for the third quarter and nine-month period ended on 31st December 2025. The Board of Directors approved the standalone unaudited financial results, which were reviewed by the Audit Committee and the statutory auditors. The company&apos;s revenue from operations and total income have increased compared to the previous period. The trading window for dealing in the company&apos;s shares will reopen after 48 hours from the declaration of the results.</p><ul><li>Madhur Industries Limited announced its unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine-month period ended on 31st December 2025.</li><li>The Board of Directors approved the standalone unaudited financial results.</li><li>The Audit Committee and statutory auditors reviewed the results.</li><li>Revenue from operations and total income have increased compared to the previous period.</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the company&apos;s shares to reopen after 48 hours from the declaration of results.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8a7a0937-6eb1-4976-a52c-c673fcc0b7aa.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MADHUR INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MBLINFRA] MBL Infrastructure Ltd. Announces Q3 &amp; Nine Months Results for 2025, Board Meeting Outcomes, and Investment Confidence</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MBL+Infrastructure+Ltd&title=MBL+Infrastructure+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Board+Meeting+Outcomes%2C+and+Investment+Confidence&newsId=6f576203-e672-48dd-95cb-25b01ccf93cd&token=NmY1NzYyMDMtZTY3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f576203-e672-48dd-95cb-25b01ccf93cd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:37:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>MBL Infrastructure Ltd. announced the financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025, revealing a revenue from operations of 6592 Lakhs and 17284 Lakhs respectively. The company&apos;s net profit before tax stands at 5133 Lakhs and 16442 Lakhs for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The Board of Directors convened on 14th February 2026, discussing the un-audited financial results, compliance with regulations, and submitting waiver applications to stock exchanges. MBL is confident in the realisable amount of their investments in subsidiaries, despite pending legal proceedings and arbitration, with claims filed against cancellation/termination of projects. The company is also under Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP) with a qualified Resolution Plan submission.</p><ul><li>Q3 &amp; Nine Months Results for 2025 announced</li><li>Revenue from operations: 6592 Lakhs (Q3) &amp; 17284 Lakhs (Nine Months)</li><li>Net profit before tax: 5133 Lakhs (Q3) &amp; 16442 Lakhs (Nine Months)</li><li>Board meeting discusses un-audited financial results and regulatory compliance</li><li>Confidence in realisable amount of investments in subsidiaries</li><li>Company under Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dbc4098f-29ba-4a86-b001-cb7beb01e5ce.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MBL Infrastructure Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VANICOM] Vani Commercials Ltd. Approves Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025, Addresses Cyber Security Incident</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vani+Commercials+Ltd&title=Vani+Commercials+Ltd.+Approves+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Addresses+Cyber+Security+Incident&newsId=99b6722b-7ae8-4d43-87e2-3333c84a9db4&token=OTliNjcyMmItN2Fl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">99b6722b-7ae8-4d43-87e2-3333c84a9db4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:35:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vani Commercials Ltd. held its board meeting on 14th February, 2026, where it approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The company reported a profit before exceptional items and tax for the nine months ended at INR 3,40,67,000. A cyber security incident involving a deceitful app was reported and the company has taken corrective actions. The financial results are subjected to a limited review by statutory auditors.</p><ul><li>Vani Commercials Ltd. approved the unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December, 2025.</li><li>The company reported a profit before exceptional items and tax for the nine months ended at INR 3,40,67,000.</li><li>A cyber security incident involving a deceitful app was reported and the company has taken corrective actions.</li><li>The financial results are subjected to a limited review by statutory auditors.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c975bc47-1e43-43f6-8432-a840bdb41515.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vani Commercials Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GIANLIFE] Gian Life Care Ltd. Approves Q3 Results with Cash Balance of ₹ 743.78 Lakhs and Unpaid Dues of ₹ 426.66 Lakhs and ₹ 359.78 Lakhs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Gian+Life+Care+Ltd&title=Gian+Life+Care+Ltd.+Approves+Q3+Results+with+Cash+Balance+of+%E2%82%B9+743.78+Lakhs+and+Unpaid+Dues+of+%E2%82%B9+426.66+Lakhs+and+%E2%82%B9+359.78+Lakhs&newsId=397b6a2d-4d2e-4303-855d-ad37004beadc&token=Mzk3YjZhMmQtNGQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">397b6a2d-4d2e-4303-855d-ad37004beadc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:35:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gian Life Care Ltd. announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter/period ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s board of directors approved the results during their meeting on February 14, 2026. The highlights of the meeting include the approval of financial results, the inability of the company to provide sufficient and appropriate audit evidence for the high cash balance, and the existence of unpaid statutory dues and an outstanding bank loan classified as Non-Performing Asset (NPA). The company&apos;s head office is located in Noida and the branch office in Navi Mumbai.</p><ul><li>Approval of unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 2025</li><li>Company&apos;s inability to provide sufficient and appropriate audit evidence for a high cash balance of ₹ 743.78 Lakhs</li><li>Existence of unpaid statutory dues amounting to ₹ 426.66 Lakhs</li><li>Outstanding bank loan classified as Non-Performing Asset (NPA) amounting to ₹ 359.78 Lakhs</li><li>The company&apos;s head office in Noida and branch office in Navi Mumbai</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5e85a151-f27f-476f-9919-ced4c20eb704.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Gian Life Care Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PRAKASH] Prakash Industries Reports Q3 Results with ¥ 87 Crores Profit, Expects Strong Steel Demand</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PRAKASH+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Prakash+Industries+Reports+Q3+Results+with+%C2%A5+87+Crores+Profit%2C+Expects+Strong+Steel+Demand&newsId=326a3e65-4f38-4dd3-8963-c4561b48c50b&token=MzI2YTNlNjUtNGYz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">326a3e65-4f38-4dd3-8963-c4561b48c50b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:34:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Prakash Industries Ltd. has announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The company reported a profit after tax of ¥ 87 Crores for the quarter, an increase from ¥ 84 Crores in the corresponding quarter of the previous financial year. For the nine months ended 31st December, 2025, the company achieved a profit after tax of ¥ 240 Crores, resulting in an Earning Per Share (EPS) of ¥ 13.39. The company expects to witness strong steel demand in the country due to the government’s focus on construction and infrastructure activities. In terms of operations, the Bhaskarpara coal mine extracted ~2.52 lac MT of coal during the quarter and is projected to achieve over 1 Mn MT of coal in FY2026. The company is also in the process of enhancing the mining plan from 1 Mn MT per annum to 1.2 Mn MT per annum.</p><ul><li>Prakash Industries reports a profit after tax of ¥ 87 Crores for Q3 2025</li><li>Profit after tax for the nine months ended 31st December, 2025, is ¥ 240 Crores</li><li>Earning Per Share (EPS) of ¥ 13.39 for the nine months ended 31st December, 2025</li><li>Expects strong steel demand in the country due to government’s focus on construction and infrastructure activities</li><li>Projected to achieve over 1 Mn MT of coal in FY2026 from Bhaskarpara coal mine</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4e1feedb-369f-4f93-ab2c-cacb5b6b5e3d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PRAKASH INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EUROMULTI] Euro Multivision Ltd Delays Unaudited Financial Results Submission for Q3 and Nine Months of FY 2025-2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Euro+Multivision+Ltd&title=Euro+Multivision+Ltd+Delays+Unaudited+Financial+Results+Submission+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+of+FY+2025-2026&newsId=74d8f924-7744-469e-b16a-229df547a9dc&token=NzRkOGY5MjQtNzc0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74d8f924-7744-469e-b16a-229df547a9dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:34:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Euro Multivision Ltd, a company undergoing reconstruction, has announced a delay in submitting its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31.12.2025. The delay is due to the new management&apos;s ongoing process of regularizing statutory and regulatory compliances and collating necessary documents/information. The company is also reconstructing and verifying its financial records for the relevant and prior financial periods beginning from the quarter ended September 2022. The pending financial results will be submitted in due course in compliance with the applicable provisions of the Companies Act, 2013 and the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>New management has taken over Euro Multivision Ltd under Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code, 2016 (IBC)</li><li>Company is currently in the process of regularizing statutory and regulatory compliances</li><li>Financial records for the relevant and prior financial periods are being reconstructed and verified</li><li>Unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31.12.2025 will be submitted in due course</li><li>Pending financial results will be submitted in compliance with the applicable provisions of the Companies Act, 2013 and the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cfa25356-f914-473e-bbcd-387b87fa83bd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Euro Multivision Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MARBLE] Marble City India Ltd Announces Q3 2025 Financial Results with 1,808.57 Lakhs Net Revenue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Marble+City+India+Ltd&title=Marble+City+India+Ltd+Announces+Q3+2025+Financial+Results+with+1%2C808.57+Lakhs+Net+Revenue&newsId=0e898e5d-0f35-423f-8c63-ecf527d871ff&token=MGU4OThlNWQtMGYz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e898e5d-0f35-423f-8c63-ecf527d871ff</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:34:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Marble City India Ltd, a company based in Rajasthan, India, announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter ended on 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s net revenue from operations stands at 1,808.57 Lakhs, marking a increase from the previous quarter. The total income stands at 1,879.07 Lakhs. The company&apos;s expenses for the quarter amounted to 1,848.34 Lakhs, resulting in a profit before exceptional items and tax of 30.73 Lakhs. The profit for the period from continuing operations is 27.38 Lakhs. The earnings per equity share for continuing operations is not provided in the document.</p><ul><li>Net Revenue from operations stands at 1,808.57 Lakhs</li><li>Total income stands at 1,879.07 Lakhs</li><li>Profit before exceptional items and tax is 30.73 Lakhs</li><li>Profit for the period from continuing operations is 27.38 Lakhs</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/487b957c-5d61-48ba-b6a7-e2398dcddeb8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Marble City India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHAHALLOYS] Shah Alloys Ltd Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for FY2026, Reports Net Profit</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHAH+ALLOYS+LTD.&title=Shah+Alloys+Ltd+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+FY2026%2C+Reports+Net+Profit&newsId=0316ac19-f71b-4c45-98b8-13192241ed64&token=MDMxNmFjMTktZjcx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0316ac19-f71b-4c45-98b8-13192241ed64</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shah Alloys Ltd announced the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended as on December 31, 2026. The company reported a net profit after tax of Rs 2,07,73,000 for the quarter and Rs 5,75,67,000 for the nine months period. The results were reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors in a meeting held on February 14, 2026. The company also reported a qualified opinion from its auditors due to certain accounting practices.</p><ul><li>Shah Alloys Ltd reported a net profit after tax of Rs 2,07,73,000 for Q3 FY2026 and Rs 5,75,67,000 for the nine months period.</li><li>The results were reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors in a meeting held on February 14, 2026.</li><li>The company reported a qualified opinion from its auditors due to certain accounting practices.</li><li>The company has not made any provision of interest on loans from banks for the quarter ended on 31st December, 2025.</li><li>The company has not assessed the impact of Effective Interest Method to the finance cost as per the requirement of Ind AS 109 ‘Financial Instruments’.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/09a03bd9-3cd6-4ac2-9fee-4a634528dfe9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHAH ALLOYS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>