<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 01:45:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[FOSECOIND] Foseco India Ltd. to Approve Q4 and FY2025 Financial Results and Recommend Final Dividend</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=FOSECO+INDIA+LTD.&title=Foseco+India+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q4+and+FY2025+Financial+Results+and+Recommend+Final+Dividend&newsId=65efdab9-2aba-4ff8-a04b-41c90c2e260f&token=NjVlZmRhYjktMmFi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65efdab9-2aba-4ff8-a04b-41c90c2e260f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:51:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Foseco India Ltd. has announced a Board Meeting scheduled for February 25, 2026, to consider and approve the Standalone and Consolidated Audited Financial Results for the quarter and year ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will also consider recommending the final dividend for the financial year ended December 31, 2025. The Trading Window for dealing in the securities of the Company, which had remained closed from January 1, 2026, will continue to remain closed until February 27, 2026, for all specified persons as per the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Foseco India Ltd. to approve Q4 and FY2025 financial results</li><li>Company to consider recommending final dividend for FY2025</li><li>Trading Window to remain closed until February 27, 2026, for specified persons</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ae23600f-e1a2-4784-8875-5ad789058001.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: FOSECO INDIA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LUMAXTECH] Lumax Auto Technologies&apos; Tax Demand Reduced by 70% in GST Appeal</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LUMAX+AUTO+TECHNOLOGIES+LTD.&title=Lumax+Auto+Technologies%27+Tax+Demand+Reduced+by+70%25+in+GST+Appeal&newsId=a2eae5fb-4deb-40b4-b3f4-44486f0113dd&token=YTJlYWU1ZmItNGRl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2eae5fb-4deb-40b4-b3f4-44486f0113dd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:44:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Lumax Auto Technologies Ltd. has received an Order-in-Appeal dated February 18, 2026, from the Office of The Joint Commissioner of State Tax, PUN-VAT-E-623, Department of Goods and Service Tax, Government of Maharashtra. The first appeal filed by the Company has been partly allowed, reducing the demand from Rs. 3,52,19,923/- (including Interest and penalty) to Rs. 1,03,78,580/- (including Interest and penalty) for the period from April 2019 to March 2020. The Company plans to file an appeal against this Order-in-Appeal before the Hon’ble Tribunal.</p><ul><li>Lumax Auto Technologies Ltd. received an Order-in-Appeal dated February 18, 2026, from the Office of The Joint Commissioner of State Tax.</li><li>The demand has been reduced from Rs. 3,52,19,923/- (including Interest and penalty) to Rs. 1,03,78,580/- (including Interest and penalty).</li><li>The first appeal was filed by the Company against the Adjudication Order dated July 19, 2024 u/s 73(9) of the Maharashtra Goods &amp; Services Tax Act, 2017 and u/s 20 of the IGST Act.</li><li>The demand was raised on account of tax not paid or short paid or erroneously refunded or input tax credit wrongly availed or utilized.</li><li>The Company plans to file an appeal against the said Order-in-Appeal before the Hon’ble Tribunal.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/41d8850e-6b50-4b56-848c-8a775f6ce43e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LUMAX AUTO TECHNOLOGIES LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MSUMI] Motherson Sumi Wiring India Ltd Receives ESG Rating of &apos;70&apos; from NSE Sustainability</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Motherson+Sumi+Wiring+India+Ltd&title=Motherson+Sumi+Wiring+India+Ltd+Receives+ESG+Rating+of+%2770%27+from+NSE+Sustainability&newsId=2f019c89-d78f-4531-b9c0-aab31f1b48c1&token=MmYwMTljODktZDc4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2f019c89-d78f-4531-b9c0-aab31f1b48c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Motherson Sumi Wiring India Ltd has been assigned an ESG Rating of ‘70’ by NSE Sustainability Ratings &amp; Analytics Limited. This rating is a reflection of the company’s performance on Environmental, Social and Governance parameters. The rating has been independently prepared by NSE Sustainability based on data available in the public domain. The company has not engaged NSE Sustainability for ESG Rating.</p><ul><li>Motherson Sumi Wiring India Ltd receives an ESG Rating of ‘70’ from NSE Sustainability</li><li>The rating is based on the company’s performance on Environmental, Social and Governance parameters</li><li>The rating is independently prepared by NSE Sustainability based on publicly available data</li><li>The company has not engaged NSE Sustainability for ESG Rating</li><li>NSE Sustainability Ratings &amp; Analytics Limited is the rating agency</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1794147a-9933-4397-854f-a873eea4ae8c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Motherson Sumi Wiring India Ltd | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STEELCO] Steelco Gujarat Ltd Cancels Record Date for Rights Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Steelco+Gujarat+Ltd&title=Steelco+Gujarat+Ltd+Cancels+Record+Date+for+Rights+Issue&newsId=52d911c4-4d71-4a78-b77e-6a864d9d083a&token=NTJkOTExYzQtNGQ3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">52d911c4-4d71-4a78-b77e-6a864d9d083a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Right Issue</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Steelco Gujarat Ltd has announced the cancellation of the Record Date for the Rights Issue, which was earlier set for February 24, 2026. This decision comes due to some fundamental changes that require attention. The company will announce a new Record Date along with other details regarding the issue&apos;s timeline in due course.</p><ul><li>Steelco Gujarat Ltd cancels the Record Date for the Rights Issue</li><li>New Record Date and timeline details will be announced later</li><li>Cancellation due to fundamental changes in the company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8b8348a1-bca3-4bff-96cc-845ef5a6a333.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Steelco Gujarat Ltd | Category: Right Issue</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ORACLECR] Credent Global Finance Ltd. Approves Allotment of 1,00,00,000 Equity Shares in QIP</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Oracle+Credit+Ltd&title=Credent+Global+Finance+Ltd.+Approves+Allotment+of+1%2C00%2C00%2C000+Equity+Shares+in+QIP&newsId=8a90910a-c933-4fb9-be23-4b4a0266cfaa&token=OGE5MDkxMGEtYzkz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a90910a-c933-4fb9-be23-4b4a0266cfaa</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 17:12:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Credent Global Finance Ltd. has approved the allotment of 1,00,00,000 Equity Shares of face value 2 each to eligible Qualified Institutional Buyers (QIB&apos;s) at an issue price of Rs. 30 per Equity Share, including a premium of Rs. 28 per Equity Share. The Issue opened on February 17, 2026 and closed on February 19, 2026. The paid-up equity share capital of the Company has increased from Rs. 10,29,22,460/- to Rs. 12,29,22,460/-. The shareholding pattern of the Company before and after the Issue will be submitted along with the listing application.</p><ul><li>Credent Global Finance Ltd. approved the allotment of 1,00,00,000 Equity Shares in a Qualified Institutional Placement (QIP)</li><li>The issue price was set at Rs. 30 per Equity Share, including a premium of Rs. 28 per Equity Share</li><li>The Issue opened on February 17, 2026 and closed on February 19, 2026</li><li>The paid-up equity share capital of the Company has increased from Rs. 10,29,22,460/- to Rs. 12,29,22,460/-</li><li>The shareholding pattern of the Company before and after the Issue will be submitted along with the listing application</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/54260453-373f-4cd8-88e0-b2bca7219d86.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Oracle Credit Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IFGLEXPOR] IFGL Refractories Ltd Starts New Line for Plastic Refractories Manufacturing</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IFGL+Refractories+Ltd&title=IFGL+Refractories+Ltd+Starts+New+Line+for+Plastic+Refractories+Manufacturing&newsId=46754bd8-231d-485a-a43d-85c24b88de9d&token=NDY3NTRiZDgtMjMx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">46754bd8-231d-485a-a43d-85c24b88de9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:41:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>IFGL Refractories Ltd has started a new line for manufacturing Plastic Refractories at its Visakhapatnam facility. The new line is based on technical know-how from the company&apos;s material subsidiary, Sheffield Refractories Ltd, UK. This expansion will allow the company to meet the increasing demand for Plastic Refractories from ferrous and non-ferrous industries, strengthening its robust monolithics portfolio. The project has involved a capital outlay of approximately Rs 2.10 crores, financed largely by internal accruals. The installed capacity is 10,000 MT per annum. This move is significant as there are very few domestic manufacturers in this sector, and it will help strengthen indigenous capacity and reduce reliance on imports.</p><ul><li>IFGL Refractories Ltd has started a new line for manufacturing Plastic Refractories.</li><li>The new line is based on technical know-how from the company&apos;s material subsidiary, Sheffield Refractories Ltd, UK.</li><li>The expansion will allow the company to meet the increasing demand for Plastic Refractories from ferrous and non-ferrous industries.</li><li>The project has involved a capital outlay of approximately Rs 2.10 crores, financed largely by internal accruals.</li><li>The new line will strengthen the company&apos;s robust monolithics portfolio and reduce reliance on imports.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bbf595b3-57cf-40fd-a498-3e0d55399cf2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IFGL Refractories Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KIMIABL] Kimia Biosciences Ltd: Additional Director Resigns Due to Personal Reasons</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kimia+Biosciences+Ltd&title=Kimia+Biosciences+Ltd%3A+Additional+Director+Resigns+Due+to+Personal+Reasons&newsId=2e31d2ce-2707-422d-be53-6cbea6533e50&token=MmUzMWQyY2UtMjcw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e31d2ce-2707-422d-be53-6cbea6533e50</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:34:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kimia Biosciences Ltd announced the resignation of Mr. Kaku Vijaya Shekhar Reddy, Additional Director (in the category of Executive Director), with effect from February 18, 2026. The company has accepted his resignation, which came into effect from the closure of business hours on February 19, 2026. The resignation was due to Mr. Reddy&apos;s personal reasons.</p><ul><li>Mr. Kaku Vijaya Shekhar Reddy has resigned from his position as Additional Director (in the category of Executive Director) at Kimia Biosciences Ltd.</li><li>The resignation will take effect from February 18, 2026.</li><li>The company has accepted the resignation, which came into effect from the closure of business hours on February 19, 2026.</li><li>The resignation is due to Mr. Reddy&apos;s personal reasons.</li><li>Kimia Biosciences Ltd is headquartered in Gurugram, Haryana, India.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1d2a3bbc-ceaf-4d57-ba5c-f788cf66f0e0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kimia Biosciences Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EXATO] Exato Technologies Ltd Secures USD 240,000 Export Order from Diligenta Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Exato+Technologies+Ltd&title=Exato+Technologies+Ltd+Secures+USD+240%2C000+Export+Order+from+Diligenta+Limited&newsId=ce791fac-a32b-491e-8e94-6b17642ad049&token=Y2U3OTFmYWMtYTMy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce791fac-a32b-491e-8e94-6b17642ad049</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:21:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Exato Technologies Ltd has announced that it has received an export order from Diligenta Limited, Peterborough, England for the supply of Software Licenses. The total value of the order is USD 2,40,000, inclusive of carriage and exclusive of any applicable taxes, duties, levies, or any government-imposed charges. This order reflects the company&apos;s growing international presence and its capabilities in providing software and technology-based solutions to global clients.</p><ul><li>Exato Technologies Ltd has secured an export order from Diligenta Limited, Peterborough, England for the supply of Software Licenses.</li><li>The total value of the order is USD 2,40,000, inclusive of carriage and exclusive of any applicable taxes, duties, levies, or any government-imposed charges.</li><li>This achievement reflects the continued dedication and expertise of Exato&apos;s team.</li><li>The order reinforces Exato&apos;s capabilities in providing software and technology-based solutions to global clients.</li><li>Exato looks forward to collaborating with Diligenta Limited in successfully executing this engagement.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/29d360f3-fcc6-450b-8672-0f6e1afc8a99.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Exato Technologies Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MINDSPACE] Mindspace Business Parks REIT to Meet Investors in Upcoming Conference</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Mindspace+Business+Parks+REIT&title=Mindspace+Business+Parks+REIT+to+Meet+Investors+in+Upcoming+Conference&newsId=63fb73eb-9502-4d43-85bf-c18f2b91863f&token=NjNmYjczZWItOTUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63fb73eb-9502-4d43-85bf-c18f2b91863f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 16:21:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mindspace Business Parks REIT has announced a conference for investors, including institutional investors, scheduled for February 23, 2026, at Kotak Grand Hyatt, Mumbai. The management team will be present for group meetings and one-on-one sessions. The presentation for the conference is available on the company&apos;s website. Please note that the schedule is subject to change.</p><ul><li>Mindspace Business Parks REIT to hold a conference for investors on February 23, 2026</li><li>The conference will take place at Kotak Grand Hyatt, Mumbai</li><li>The management team will be present for group meetings and one-on-one sessions</li><li>The presentation for the conference is available on the company&apos;s website</li><li>The schedule is subject to change due to factors such as changes in the investors&apos;, organizers&apos;, or management team&apos;s plans</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/68900209-ca5f-44c9-8ee7-d6b209a28c86.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Mindspace Business Parks REIT | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MACH] Mac Hotels Ltd. Announces Board Meeting Decisions: Capital Increase, Preferential Issue of Equity Shares &amp; Warrants, and EGM</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Mac+Hotels+Ltd&title=Mac+Hotels+Ltd.+Announces+Board+Meeting+Decisions%3A+Capital+Increase%2C+Preferential+Issue+of+Equity+Shares+%26+Warrants%2C+and+EGM&newsId=f6173fb2-8d82-4d4d-86f7-a26c1edd62c1&token=ZjYxNzNmYjItOGQ4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6173fb2-8d82-4d4d-86f7-a26c1edd62c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:52:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Mac Hotels Ltd. announced the outcomes of its board meeting held on February 19, 2026. The board approved several proposals, including an increase in the authorized share capital, a preferential issue of equity shares and warrants, and the convening of an Extraordinary General Meeting (EGM) to seek shareholder approval. The company will also provisionally approve the acquisition of approximately 25% share capital of Herald Technocraft Private Limited and modify its main object, subject to necessary approvals.</p><ul><li>Approval of an increase in the authorized share capital from Rs. 9,00,00,000 to Rs. 18,00,00,000 divided into 1,80,00,000 Equity Shares of Rs. 10/- each.</li><li>Preferential issue of up to 48,00,500 Equity Shares at a price of Rs. 45 per share, and up to 73,68,712 convertible warrants to identified promoters, members of promoter group, and non-promoter persons/entities.</li><li>Convening of an Extraordinary General Meeting (EGM) on March 21, 2026, to seek necessary approval from shareholders.</li><li>Provisional approval for the acquisition of approximately 25% share capital of Herald Technocraft Private Limited.</li><li>Change in the main object of the company by adding various manufacturing, buying, selling, and trading activities in different industries.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/38a17ecd-cc7d-4e7b-a112-f04f57593294.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Mac Hotels Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>