<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 04:05:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[JONJUA] Jonjua Overseas Ltd Approves 5:40 Bonus Share Allotment, Audit Committee&apos;s Submissions Reviewed</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jonjua+Overseas+Ltd&title=Jonjua+Overseas+Ltd+Approves+5%3A40+Bonus+Share+Allotment%2C+Audit+Committee%27s+Submissions+Reviewed&newsId=2a97b27f-a395-4db9-b90e-456d93d74229&token=MmE5N2IyN2YtYTM5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a97b27f-a395-4db9-b90e-456d93d74229</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 03:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Bonus</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jonjua Overseas Ltd announced a bonus share allotment of 5 bonus shares for every 40 shares held by the shareholders. The record date for the purpose is 23rd January 2026. The company&apos;s paid-up share capital has increased to Rs. 27,27,75,970 divided into 2,72,77,597 equity shares of Rs.10 each. The Board also reviewed the Audit Committee&apos;s submissions on the sale of movable goods (intangible) and approved necessary steps in this matter. The meeting started at 09:00 am and concluded at 09:15 am.</p><ul><li>Jonjua Overseas Ltd approves 5:40 bonus share allotment</li><li>Record date for bonus share allotment is 23rd January 2026</li><li>Company&apos;s paid-up share capital increases to Rs. 27,27,75,970</li><li>Board reviews Audit Committee&apos;s submissions on sale of movable goods (intangible)</li><li>Necessary steps approved in the sale of movable goods (intangible)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cac71157-e937-48c3-bd47-39a62f0005ef.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jonjua Overseas Ltd | Category: Bonus</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUNDRMBRAK] Sundaram Brake Linings Ltd. to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended on 31st December 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SUNDARAM+BRAKE+LININGS+LTD.&title=Sundaram+Brake+Linings+Ltd.+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+on+31st+December+2025&newsId=9798c988-14fa-4a1d-8b0f-fd38399aeae2&token=OTc5OGM5ODgtMTRm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9798c988-14fa-4a1d-8b0f-fd38399aeae2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 03:33:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sundaram Brake Linings Ltd. has informed the BSE that the meeting of the Board of Directors of the Company is scheduled on 6th February 2026. The Board will consider and approve the Unaudited financial results for the Quarter and Nine months ended on 31st December 2025. The trading window for dealing in the Company’s scrips by the Promoter &amp; Promoter Group, Directors and Designated Employees of the Company remains closed from 1st January 2026 to 8th February 2026, in accordance with the Company’s Code of Conduct to regulate, monitor and report trading by insiders, read with SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Sundaram Brake Linings Ltd. to approve Unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended on 31st December 2025</li><li>Board meeting scheduled on 6th February 2026</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the Company’s scrips by insiders closed from 1st January 2026 to 8th February 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8f923858-f0d8-4478-a677-83ceca010405.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SUNDARAM BRAKE LININGS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WOCKPHARMA] Wockhardt&apos;s Novel Antibiotic, Foviscu®, Matches Gold-Standard Meropenem in Phase 3 Trial</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=WOCKHARDT+LTD.&title=Wockhardt%27s+Novel+Antibiotic%2C+Foviscu%C2%AE%2C+Matches+Gold-Standard+Meropenem+in+Phase+3+Trial&newsId=a84bbf3b-5648-49dd-91ef-51e6113a6956&token=YTg0YmJmM2ItNTY0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a84bbf3b-5648-49dd-91ef-51e6113a6956</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 03:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Wockhardt Limited announced that its novel intravenous antibiotic Foviscu® (WCK 4282) has successfully met the primary endpoint in a Phase 3 clinical trial. The trial compared Foviscu® with meropenem, a &apos;last-line&apos; gold-standard carbapenem, in patients with complicated urinary tract infections (CUTI) and acute pyelonephritis caused by Gram-negative bacteria. Foviscu® demonstrated therapeutic equivalence with a similarly well-tolerated safety profile, potentially reducing carbapenem use and strengthening antibiotic stewardship. The antibiotic has been extensively evaluated and has been granted QIDP designation by the US FDA.</p><ul><li>Foviscu® successfully met the primary endpoint in a Phase 3 clinical trial</li><li>Foviscu® demonstrated therapeutic equivalence with meropenem</li><li>Foviscu® has potential to reduce carbapenem use and strengthen antibiotic stewardship</li><li>Foviscu® has been granted QIDP designation by the US FDA</li><li>Wockhardt has a portfolio of 6 products at various stages of clinical development and commercialization, all granted QIDP status by the US FDA</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/620b84e7-1699-42c3-9398-8ed8a663b5be.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: WOCKHARDT LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MUKKA] Mukka Proteins Strengthens Carbon Credit Portfolio with Verra-Listed BSF Project and Approved Capacity Expansion</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Mukka+Proteins+Ltd&title=Mukka+Proteins+Strengthens+Carbon+Credit+Portfolio+with+Verra-Listed+BSF+Project+and+Approved+Capacity+Expansion&newsId=7173158d-5c79-4305-949b-9cf92e6e9487&token=NzE3MzE1OGQtNWM3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7173158d-5c79-4305-949b-9cf92e6e9487</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 03:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Mukka Proteins Limited has announced a significant milestone in the development of its Black Soldier Fly (BSF)—based municipal wet-waste processing initiative in Bengaluru. The company&apos;s BSF-driven 300 TPD wet-waste processing operations have been formally listed on the Verra Registry under Project ID 5893, enabling the project to progress toward Verified Carbon Unit (VCU) issuance under the Verra Verified Carbon Standard (VCS) program. The project has entered the mandatory 30-day public comment period, and upon completion, the accredited validation and verification body will conduct its on-site assessment. Mukka Proteins has received incremental approval to expand its capacity up to 1,000 TPD within Bengaluru’s integrated waste-management framework. This phased structure ensures that while the current 300 TPD operations advance toward carbon credit issuance, future capacity additions will support progressively larger VCU generation, strengthening long-term sustainability and revenue-diversification potential.</p><ul><li>Mukka Proteins&apos; BSF project listed on Verra Registry, progressing toward Verified Carbon Unit issuance</li><li>Project entered mandatory 30-day public comment period</li><li>Incremental approval to expand capacity up to 1,000 TPD within Bengaluru’s integrated waste-management framework</li><li>Phased structure to ensure current operations advance toward carbon credit issuance</li><li>Future capacity additions to strengthen long-term sustainability and revenue-diversification potential</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ead114a1-0a61-4389-b3c0-327f078ae2d0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Mukka Proteins Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AADHARHFC] Blackstone-led Consortium to Acquire 25.82% Stake in Aadhar Housing Finance for $5.3 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Aadhar+Housing+Finance+Ltd&title=Blackstone-led+Consortium+to+Acquire+25.82%25+Stake+in+Aadhar+Housing+Finance+for+%245.3+Billion&newsId=ed9716ab-b781-4b0b-ac90-0a896c346be4&token=ZWQ5NzE2YWItYjc4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed9716ab-b781-4b0b-ac90-0a896c346be4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 03:20:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>JM Financial Ltd has submitted a Letter of Offer to the public shareholders of Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd. The offer, made by BCP Asia IT Holdco VII PTE. LTD., Blackstone Capital Partners (CYM) IX AIV-F L.P., and Blackstone Capital Partners ASIA ITL.P., is for up to 11,35,25,761 fully paid-up equity shares at a price of INR 469.97 per equity share, representing 25.82% of the expanded voting share capital. The offer is not conditional or subject to a minimum level of acceptance, and is in compliance with the SEBI (SAST) Regulations. The offer is not a competing offer and there have been no competing offers as of the date of this letter. The offer price may be subject to upward revision prior to the commencement of the last one (1) Working Day before the commencement of the Tendering Period.</p><ul><li>Blackstone-led consortium to acquire 25.82% stake in Aadhar Housing Finance</li><li>Offer price of INR 469.97 per equity share</li><li>Not a conditional offer or subject to a minimum level of acceptance</li><li>In compliance with the SEBI (SAST) Regulations</li><li>No competing offers as of the date of this letter</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/12D99BC9-ACA3-46B0-AF18-B111D432F6B9-084510.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AXISCADES] AXISCADES Partners with OGMA to Scale Global Aerospace and Defence MRO</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Axiscades+Technologies+Ltd&title=AXISCADES+Partners+with+OGMA+to+Scale+Global+Aerospace+and+Defence+MRO&newsId=656ca212-b35c-466a-a432-8bb504546ca2&token=NjU2Y2EyMTItYjM1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">656ca212-b35c-466a-a432-8bb504546ca2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 03:12:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Partnership</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>AXISCADES Technologies Limited has announced a strategic partnership with OGMA -— Industria Aeronautica de Portugal, a subsidiary of Embraer, for Aerospace Manufacturing, Maintenance, Repair, and Overhaul (MRO), airframe engineering, and certification services for both commercial and military platforms. The partnership aims to provide maintenance and support for Embraer and other manufacturers’ aircraft fleets in India, leveraging AXISCADES’ deep expertise in aircraft design, conversion, avionics, radar, electronic warfare, and drone technologies with OGMA’s century of proven capabilities in airframe and engine MRO.</p><ul><li>Strategic partnership between AXISCADES and OGMA for aerospace and defence MRO</li><li>Focus on high-value, long-term service activities</li><li>Merger of AXISCADES’ engineering capabilities with OGMA’s airframe and engine MRO expertise</li><li>Exploration of business opportunities in India, the UAE, and the MENA region</li><li>Leverage of OGMA’s established relationships with major OEMs such as Embraer, Airbus Defence, Rolls-Royce, Pratt &amp; Whitney, and others</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a5d4012e-6808-482a-9ddb-5c7885ef9802.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Axiscades Technologies Ltd | Category: Partnership</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TCIEXP*] TCI Express Ltd. May Recommend Interim Dividend for FY 25-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TCI+Express+Ltd&title=TCI+Express+Ltd.+May+Recommend+Interim+Dividend+for+FY+25-26&newsId=ebeeb2c3-ea44-473f-9de8-0f433e44b277&token=ZWJlZWIyYzMtZWE0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ebeeb2c3-ea44-473f-9de8-0f433e44b277</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>TCI Express Ltd. is set to convene a Board of Directors meeting on February 03, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The Board may also consider/recommend an interim dividend for the financial year 2025-26. The record date for the dividend, if declared, would be Saturday, February 07, 2026. The trading window for dealing in the equity shares of the Company will remain closed from Thursday, January 1, 2026, to 48 hours after the communication of the financial results.</p><ul><li>TCI Express Ltd. to consider interim dividend for FY 25-26</li><li>Board meeting scheduled for February 03, 2026</li><li>Un-audited financial results for Q3 and nine months ending December 31, 2025, to be approved</li><li>Record date for dividend payment set for Saturday, February 07, 2026</li><li>Trading window for equity shares closed from January 1, 2026, to 48 hours post financial results communication</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7ed374f4-c6c2-49aa-8d5a-5d9d0a53ed2a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TCI Express Ltd | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ALLTIME] EU Suspends GSP Benefits on Plastic Products for All Time Plastics Ltd Until 2028</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=All+Time+Plastics+Ltd&title=EU+Suspends+GSP+Benefits+on+Plastic+Products+for+All+Time+Plastics+Ltd+Until+2028&newsId=fd386b5b-e3b2-43f4-9d43-f28317f322be&token=ZmQzODZiNWItZTNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd386b5b-e3b2-43f4-9d43-f28317f322be</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>All Time Plastics Ltd has clarified the suspension of European Union (EU) Generalised Scheme of Preferences (GSP) benefits for certain product sections, including Section S-7a — Plastics and articles thereof, for India. The suspension, which started on 1 January 2023, has been extended until 31 December 2028. Plastic products exported by the Company fall under Section S-7a, and accordingly, GSP tariff benefits for such products have not been available since 1 January 2023. The Company confirms that there is no change in applicable duty rates or pricing arrangements for its EU customers.</p><ul><li>EU suspended GSP tariff preferences for certain product sections, including Section S-7a — Plastics and articles thereof, for India until 2028</li><li>Plastic products exported by All Time Plastics Ltd fall under Section S-7a and are not eligible for GSP tariff benefits since 1 January 2023</li><li>There is no change in applicable duty rates or pricing arrangements for the Company&apos;s EU customers</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e5456f96-3d02-48dd-ba29-1204ff364d45.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: All Time Plastics Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TCIEXP*] TCI Express Ltd. to Consider Interim Dividend in February 2026 Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TCI+Express+Ltd&title=TCI+Express+Ltd.+to+Consider+Interim+Dividend+in+February+2026+Board+Meeting&newsId=68a7696a-c501-41b9-b6c6-505e9cb1da99&token=NjhhNzY5NmEtYzUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68a7696a-c501-41b9-b6c6-505e9cb1da99</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>TCI Express Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 3, 2026, to consider and approve the recommendation of an interim dividend for the financial year 2025-26. The meeting will also consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. If declared, the record date for the purpose would be February 7, 2026. The trading window for dealing in the equity shares of the Company will remain closed from January 1, 2026, to 48 hours after the communication of the said financial results.</p><ul><li>TCI Express Ltd. to consider interim dividend for the financial year 2025-26</li><li>Board meeting scheduled on February 3, 2026, to consider and approve un-audited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Record date for interim dividend set for February 7, 2026</li><li>Trading window for equity shares to remain closed from January 1, 2026, to 48 hours after financial results communication</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9b0cb9d9-f454-4ed8-8f91-c81abd11701f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TCI Express Ltd | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TCIEXP*] TCI Express Ltd. May Declare Interim Dividend for FY 25-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TCI+Express+Ltd&title=TCI+Express+Ltd.+May+Declare+Interim+Dividend+for+FY+25-26&newsId=9cb3b1cc-5f04-4cf9-a0c0-ec9d9fbd9f96&token=OWNiM2IxY2MtNWYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9cb3b1cc-5f04-4cf9-a0c0-ec9d9fbd9f96</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>TCI Express Ltd. is set to convene a Board of Directors meeting on February 03, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The Board may also consider/recommend an interim dividend on the equity shares of the Company for the financial year 2025-26. The record date for the purpose would be Saturday, February 07, 2026. The trading window for dealing in the equity shares of the Company will be closed from Thursday, January 1, 2026, to 48 hours after the communication of the financial results. This disclosure is as per the SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirements) Regulation, 2015.</p><ul><li>TCI Express Ltd. to consider interim dividend for FY 25-26</li><li>Board meeting scheduled on February 03, 2026</li><li>Record date set for Saturday, February 07, 2026</li><li>Trading window for equity shares to close on January 1, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2efe21be-d679-4a53-afa5-a9b47bdd1802.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TCI Express Ltd | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>