<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:37:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[JAIPAN] Jaipan Industries Submits Revised Financial Results for Q3 2025 with Signed Limited Review Report</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JAIPAN+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Jaipan+Industries+Submits+Revised+Financial+Results+for+Q3+2025+with+Signed+Limited+Review+Report&newsId=6623c33a-4ccb-484b-a84e-bba9666a021a&token=NjYyM2MzM2EtNGNj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6623c33a-4ccb-484b-a84e-bba9666a021a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:27:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jaipan Industries Ltd. has submitted the revised filing of the Financial Results for the quarter ended 31st December, 2025, along with the duly signed Limited Review Report. The earlier submission did not contain the Signed Limited Review Report. The company confirmed that there is no change in the financial figures/results already submitted earlier. The revised submission is being made solely for attaching the signed Limited Review Report. The Board of Directors of the Company held a meeting on Saturday, 14th February, 2026 to consider and approve the un-audited financial results of the Company for the Quarter ended 31st December, 2025 along with LRR.</p><ul><li>Jaipan Industries submits revised financial results for Q3 2025 with signed Limited Review Report.</li><li>No change in the financial figures/results already submitted earlier.</li><li>Board of Directors held a meeting to consider and approve the un-audited financial results of the Company for the Quarter ended 31st December, 2025 along with LRR.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/847674bc-b7a7-4c25-898b-b57614d6e7aa.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JAIPAN INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[YASTF] Yash Trading &amp; Finance Ltd CFO, Mr. Vishvajitsinh Dilipsinh Jadeja, Resigns Due to Other Professional Engagements</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=YASH+TRADING+%26+FINANCE+LTD.&title=Yash+Trading+%26+Finance+Ltd+CFO%2C+Mr.+Vishvajitsinh+Dilipsinh+Jadeja%2C+Resigns+Due+to+Other+Professional+Engagements&newsId=4d66cf51-47e5-4e16-a6c3-14f75e4389cd&token=NGQ2NmNmNTEtNDdl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d66cf51-47e5-4e16-a6c3-14f75e4389cd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:11:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Yash Trading &amp; Finance Ltd has announced the resignation of its Chief Financial Officer, Mr. Vishvajitsinh Dilipsinh Jadeja, due to other professional engagements. The resignation will be effective from the closing business hours of 16th February 2026. Mr. Jadeja confirmed that there are no material reasons for his resignation other than the stated professional engagements.</p><ul><li>Mr. Vishvajitsinh Dilipsinh Jadeja has resigned from the post of Chief Financial Officer (CFO) of Yash Trading &amp; Finance Ltd.</li><li>The resignation is due to other professional engagements.</li><li>The resignation will be effective from the closing business hours of 16th February 2026.</li><li>Mr. Jadeja confirmed that there are no material reasons for his resignation other than the stated professional engagements.</li><li>The company has requested to file the necessary e-forms with the Registrar of Companies (ROC) to give effect to the resignation.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d67352e3-4216-4335-9e0e-8417e4dcf568.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: YASH TRADING & FINANCE LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[YASTF] Yash Trading &amp; Finance Ltd Independent Director, Amarendra Mohapatra, Resigns Citing Other Professional Commitments</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=YASH+TRADING+%26+FINANCE+LTD.&title=Yash+Trading+%26+Finance+Ltd+Independent+Director%2C+Amarendra+Mohapatra%2C+Resigns+Citing+Other+Professional+Commitments&newsId=145c67e4-6ce7-46ca-8595-390ac59b2f10&token=MTQ1YzY3ZTQtNmNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">145c67e4-6ce7-46ca-8595-390ac59b2f10</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Yash Trading &amp; Finance Ltd announced the resignation of its Non-Executive Independent Director, Mr. Amarendra Mohapatra, with immediate effect from the close of business hours on February 16, 2026. The resignation is due to other professional commitments, as stated in his resignation letter. Mohapatra has served the company since his appointment and has confirmed that there are no other material reasons for his resignation beyond those mentioned in the letter.</p><ul><li>Amarendra Mohapatra resigns from Yash Trading &amp; Finance Ltd as a Non-Executive Independent Director.</li><li>The resignation is effective immediately from the close of business hours on February 16, 2026.</li><li>Mohapatra cites other professional commitments as the reason for his resignation.</li><li>Mohapatra has confirmed that there are no other material reasons for his resignation.</li><li>The company has acknowledged and recorded the resignation.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/53dba51e-7d72-43af-be77-6ab1529c7ad6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: YASH TRADING & FINANCE LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JAGRAN] Jagran Prakashan Ltd. Announces Disclosure under Regulation 30: Petitions Re-Notified for 24th February, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JAGRAN+PRAKASHAN+LTD.&title=Jagran+Prakashan+Ltd.+Announces+Disclosure+under+Regulation+30%3A+Petitions+Re-Notified+for+24th+February%2C+2026&newsId=a64ddcfc-8ae9-4ee2-8ef3-c4c6dcf3f9ea&token=YTY0ZGRjZmMtOGFl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a64ddcfc-8ae9-4ee2-8ef3-c4c6dcf3f9ea</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:04:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jagran Prakashan Ltd. has announced a disclosure under Regulation 30 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The petitions &apos;Mahendra Mohan Gupta and Ors. v. Devendra Mohan Gupta and Ors., C.P. No. 64 of 2023&apos; and &apos;Shailendra Mohan Gupta and Ors. v. Jagran Media Network Investment Private Limited, C.P. No. 57 of 2025&apos; were listed before the Hon’ble Bench of National Company Law Tribunal, Allahabad on 13th February, 2026. However, the Bench did not take up the matters and has re-notified them for 24th February, 2026 at 2:30 p.m. The company shall provide a disclosure/update when there is a material development in the proceedings.</p><ul><li>Jagran Prakashan Ltd. announces disclosure under Regulation 30 of SEBI regulations</li><li>Petitions listed before the Hon’ble Bench of National Company Law Tribunal, Allahabad on 13th February, 2026</li><li>Matters not taken up by the Bench and re-notified for 24th February, 2026 at 2:30 p.m.</li><li>Company to provide update when there is a material development in the proceedings</li><li>Disclosure to be uploaded on the corporate website of the Company, National Stock Exchange of India Limited and BSE Limited websites</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3529f855-76cf-44dc-82c7-55c54361bc45.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JAGRAN PRAKASHAN LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[YASTF] Akhil Nair Resigns from Yash Trading &amp; Finance Ltd due to Other Professional Commitments</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=YASH+TRADING+%26+FINANCE+LTD.&title=Akhil+Nair+Resigns+from+Yash+Trading+%26+Finance+Ltd+due+to+Other+Professional+Commitments&newsId=bf5b4c03-0ed5-40e5-8844-5462af581561&token=YmY1YjRjMDMtMGVk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf5b4c03-0ed5-40e5-8844-5462af581561</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Akhil Nair, a Non-Executive Independent Director of Yash Trading &amp; Finance Ltd, has resigned from his position with immediate effect from the close of business hours on February 16, 2026. The resignation is due to other professional commitments, as stated in his resignation letter. Nair has served the company since his appointment and has expressed gratitude for the opportunity to serve.</p><ul><li>Akhil Nair resigns from Yash Trading &amp; Finance Ltd.</li><li>Resignation is due to other professional commitments.</li><li>Nair has served the company since his appointment.</li><li>Nair expresses gratitude for the opportunity to serve.</li><li>Resignation takes effect from the close of business hours on February 16, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ec0d5310-fd86-4e64-9ce5-dfd6056a69b8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: YASH TRADING & FINANCE LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[YASTF] Yash Trading &amp; Finance Ltd: Vishvajitsinh Jadeja Resigns as Director &amp; Managing Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=YASH+TRADING+%26+FINANCE+LTD.&title=Yash+Trading+%26+Finance+Ltd%3A+Vishvajitsinh+Jadeja+Resigns+as+Director+%26+Managing+Director&newsId=946aa21c-e2f7-43ed-8adb-a6a7177f6114&token=OTQ2YWEyMWMtZTJm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">946aa21c-e2f7-43ed-8adb-a6a7177f6114</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Yash Trading &amp; Finance Ltd announced the resignation of Vishvajitsinh Dilipsinh Jadeja as Director and Managing Director, effective from the closing of business hours on 16 February 2026. The resignation is due to other professional engagements, as mentioned in the resignation letter.</p><ul><li>Vishvajitsinh Dilipsinh Jadeja resigns from Yash Trading &amp; Finance Ltd.</li><li>Resignation effective from the closing of business hours on 16 February 2026.</li><li>Resignation due to other professional engagements.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dfd1e2a8-a95d-4563-ae6d-100f981e9385.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: YASH TRADING & FINANCE LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHTL] Shining Tools Ltd Regularizes Appointments of Three Independent Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shining+Tools+Ltd&title=Shining+Tools+Ltd+Regularizes+Appointments+of+Three+Independent+Directors&newsId=53b5e27b-45b8-4628-afd7-afad340414a1&token=NTNiNWUyN2ItNDVi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53b5e27b-45b8-4628-afd7-afad340414a1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shining Tools Ltd, a company based in Rajkot, Gujarat, is regularizing the appointments of three Non-Executive Independent Directors: Mr. Shaileshbhai Durlabhjibhai Sagpariya, Mr. Jay Bharatbhai Pansuria, and Mr. Akshar Jagdish Patel. The appointments will be effective from December 11, 2025, and February 12, 2026, respectively, and will last for five years. The decision was made in accordance with the Companies Act, 2013, and the Companies (Appointment and Qualifications of Directors) Rules, 2014, and was based on the recommendation of the Nomination &amp; Remuneration Committee.</p><ul><li>Regularization of the appointments of three Non-Executive Independent Directors.</li><li>Appointments are effective from December 11, 2025, and February 12, 2026.</li><li>Each appointment will last for five years.</li><li>Decision is in accordance with the Companies Act, 2013, and the Companies (Appointment and Qualifications of Directors) Rules, 2014.</li><li>Appointments are based on the recommendation of the Nomination &amp; Remuneration Committee.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8fc864f7-5450-4fc9-a5d5-44a355944476.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shining Tools Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GSBFIN] GSB Finance Ltd Announces Changes in Management and Adoption of New MOA &amp; AOA</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GSB+FINANCE+LTD.&title=GSB+Finance+Ltd+Announces+Changes+in+Management+and+Adoption+of+New+MOA+%26+AOA&newsId=5d506840-290a-4d2a-a9b2-d9d006e3f290&token=NWQ1MDY4NDAtMjkw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d506840-290a-4d2a-a9b2-d9d006e3f290</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:53:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>GSB Finance Ltd has announced changes in management, including the appointment of Mr. Kshitij Agarwal as Non-Executive, Non-Independent Director, Mr. Vivek Kumar Singhal as Executive, Non-Independent, Managing Director, Mr. Hari Chand Mittal as Non-Executive, Independent Director, and Ms. Sweta Pareek as Non-Executive, Independent Director. The company has also adopted a new set of Memorandum of Association (MOA) and Articles of Association (AOA) as per the Companies Act, 2013.</p><ul><li>GSB Finance Ltd announces changes in management</li><li>Mr. Kshitij Agarwal appointed as Non-Executive, Non-Independent Director</li><li>Mr. Vivek Kumar Singhal appointed as Executive, Non-Independent, Managing Director</li><li>Mr. Hari Chand Mittal and Ms. Sweta Pareek appointed as Non-Executive, Independent Directors</li><li>New set of MOA and AOA adopted as per the Companies Act, 2013</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5ac5bb2d-14cf-4d35-b669-ea1eaed8240d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GSB FINANCE LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASMS] Bartronics India Ltd to Acquire 51% Stake in Shree Naganarasimha Private Limited for INR 3 Crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BARTRONICS+INDIA+LTD.&title=Bartronics+India+Ltd+to+Acquire+51%25+Stake+in+Shree+Naganarasimha+Private+Limited+for+INR+3+Crore&newsId=f2788287-b336-44e3-90a3-3780546cc875&token=ZjI3ODgyODctYjMz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f2788287-b336-44e3-90a3-3780546cc875</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:52:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Bartronics India Ltd (BIL) has entered into a Shareholders Agreement with Shree Naganarasimha Private Limited (SNN), Mr. Krishna Murthy Rama Gopal, and Mr. Anand Kumar Gangadhar Naik. BIL will acquire 10,408 equity shares of the SNN for 51% paid-up share capital. The agreement governs share allotment, rights and obligations of promoters and BIL, board composition, funding, governance, and operational matters. BIL will appoint one director and has the right to first subscription in future fund raises. The funds will be used for working capital and general business purposes.</p><ul><li>BIL to acquire 51% stake in SNN for INR 3 crore</li><li>BIL to appoint one director in SNN</li><li>BIL has right to first subscription in future fund raises</li><li>Funds to be used for working capital and general business purposes</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/be4b98e8-5605-4461-ab3f-67fc02b692fb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BARTRONICS INDIA LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KFINTECH] KFin Technologies Ltd Appoints Nazish Hussain Mir as Chief Technology Officer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KFin+Technologies+Ltd&title=KFin+Technologies+Ltd+Appoints+Nazish+Hussain+Mir+as+Chief+Technology+Officer&newsId=4b312457-d101-4d6f-9756-d3c562444a58&token=NGIzMTI0NTctZDEw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4b312457-d101-4d6f-9756-d3c562444a58</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:51:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>KFin Technologies Ltd has appointed Mr. Nazish Hussain Mir as the Chief Technology Officer (Senior Management Personnel) of the Company, with effect from April 01, 2026. Mr. Mir serves as the Head of WebileApps (India) Private Limited, a wholly owned subsidiary and the core digital transformation arm of KFin Technologies Limited. He has led its evolution from a specialized startup into a 400-person engineering organization supporting fintech, capital markets, and healthcare platforms across Indian and international markets. His role expanded to provide technical oversight of engineering capabilities, platform architecture, and delivery systems, with a focus on system reliability, high-concurrency scalability, and alignment with evolving regulatory frameworks.</p><ul><li>KFin Technologies Ltd has appointed Nazish Hussain Mir as the Chief Technology Officer.</li><li>Mr. Mir is currently the Head of WebileApps (India) Private Limited.</li><li>He has led WebileApps from a specialized startup to a 400-person engineering organization.</li><li>His role expanded to provide technical oversight of engineering capabilities and platform architecture.</li><li>He is currently directing the adoption of applied artificial intelligence across the software development lifecycle.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/45f6dfa7-3ff8-4c9e-a398-ea721cb3fbb5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KFin Technologies Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>