<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:26:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[PPLPHARMA] Piramal Pharma Ltd. Announces Q3 and 9M Unaudited Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Piramal+Pharma+Ltd&title=Piramal+Pharma+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+9M+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=37b29404-a82c-43ff-b05f-d47686b913b3&token=MzdiMjk0MDQtYTgy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37b29404-a82c-43ff-b05f-d47686b913b3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Piramal Pharma Ltd. has announced its unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s total expenses for the quarter were Rs. 347.06 crores, and for the nine months ended December 31, 2025, the total expenses were Rs. 1,107.77 crores. The company&apos;s earnings per equity share (EPS) for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, were not provided in the announcement. The company&apos;s total comprehensive income for the period was Rs. 696.90 crores. The company operates in only one segment, and the unaudited standalone financial results have been prepared in accordance with the Indian Accounting Standards as prescribed under section 133 of the Companies Act, 2013.</p><ul><li>Piramal Pharma Ltd. announced its unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>Total expenses for the quarter were Rs. 347.06 crores, and for the nine months ended December 31, 2025, the total expenses were Rs. 1,107.77 crores.</li><li>The company&apos;s earnings per equity share (EPS) for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, were not provided in the announcement.</li><li>The company&apos;s total comprehensive income for the period was Rs. 696.90 crores.</li><li>The unaudited standalone financial results have been prepared in accordance with the Indian Accounting Standards as prescribed under section 133 of the Companies Act, 2013.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fd285e0c-f6c7-4b38-af17-bf9df92c06a4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Piramal Pharma Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NDTV] New Delhi Television Ltd Reports Utilization of Rights Issue Proceeds for Q4 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NEW+DELHI+TELEVISION+LTD.&title=New+Delhi+Television+Ltd+Reports+Utilization+of+Rights+Issue+Proceeds+for+Q4+2025&newsId=c349cffb-20b9-489d-8859-8f6d1229f5b4&token=YzM0OWNmZmItMjBi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c349cffb-20b9-489d-8859-8f6d1229f5b4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>New Delhi Television Ltd, a TV Broadcasting and Software Production company, has utilized the proceeds from its Rights Issue of Rs. 396.50 crore as per the objects of the issue. The company has spent Rs. 71.00 crore on strategic initiatives, Rs. 229.00 crore on repayment of borrowings, and Rs. 94.31 crore on general corporate purposes. The remaining Rs. 2.19 crore, originally allocated for issue expenses, has been reallocated towards general corporate purposes. The utilization of funds is in line with the offer document and has been verified by the statutory auditor, S N Dhawan &amp; Co LLP.</p><ul><li>New Delhi Television Ltd has utilized the proceeds from its Rights Issue as per the objects of the issue.</li><li>Rs. 71.00 crore has been spent on strategic initiatives, Rs. 229.00 crore on repayment of borrowings, and Rs. 94.31 crore on general corporate purposes.</li><li>The remaining Rs. 2.19 crore, originally allocated for issue expenses, has been reallocated towards general corporate purposes.</li><li>The utilization of funds is in line with the offer document.</li><li>The utilization of funds has been verified by the statutory auditor, S N Dhawan &amp; Co LLP.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6ae1164b-e838-4a9a-80ee-b53a592f1bea.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NEW DELHI TELEVISION LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SURAJEST] Suraj Estate Developers Delivers Highest-Ever Q3 &amp; 9MFY26 Operational Performance, Backed by Commercial Launch</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Suraj+Estate+Developers+Ltd&title=Suraj+Estate+Developers+Delivers+Highest-Ever+Q3+%26+9MFY26+Operational+Performance%2C+Backed+by+Commercial+Launch&newsId=e55569cf-c872-4be5-a008-8a3cf66449f9&token=ZTU1NTY5Y2YtYzg3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e55569cf-c872-4be5-a008-8a3cf66449f9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Suraj Estate Developers Limited, a leading real estate player focused on the South-Central Mumbai (SCM) market, announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a significant increase in sales value, sales area, and collections for Q3FY26 and 9MFY26. The company also launched a new commercial project, Suraj One Business Bay, and acquired land parcels in Bandra West. These developments reflect sustained demand in the SCM market and reinforce the commercial segment as a key growth driver.</p><ul><li>Q3FY26 sales value increased by 137% y-o-y to Rs 253 Crores</li><li>Q3FY26 sales area increased by 211% y-o-y to 51,826 Sq ft</li><li>Q3FY26 collections increased by 48% y-o-y to Rs 124 Crores</li><li>Launched Suraj One Business Bay and achieved ~40,000 sq. ft. of sales within 45 days</li><li>Acquired two land parcels in Bandra West to enhance scale for residential project launches</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/202e8b6b-10f2-4b19-bff4-c0e99a528848.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Suraj Estate Developers Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GAYATRI] Gayatri Sugars Granted Trading Approval for 13,26,664 Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GAYATRI+SUGARS+LTD.&title=Gayatri+Sugars+Granted+Trading+Approval+for+13%2C26%2C664+Equity+Shares&newsId=29e6cdab-9a6e-413c-9672-e504e1a6b6c9&token=MjllNmNkYWItOWE2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29e6cdab-9a6e-413c-9672-e504e1a6b6c9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:31:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gayatri Sugars Ltd has received trading approval for 13,26,664 Equity Shares of Rs. 10/- each issued to Non-Promoters on a preferential basis pursuant to conversion of warrants. The approval was granted by BSE Limited on January 27, 2026. The shares, bearing distinctive numbers from 66200302 to 67526965, will be listed on the Exchange effective from January 28, 2026.</p><ul><li>Gayatri Sugars receives trading approval for 13,26,664 Equity Shares</li><li>Shares issued to Non-Promoters on a preferential basis pursuant to conversion of warrants</li><li>Shares listed on BSE Limited</li><li>Shares bear distinctive numbers from 66200302 to 67526965</li><li>Effective from January 28, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8f3e960b-8669-4c97-9f05-8515b05eacef.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GAYATRI SUGARS LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HGINFRA] H.G. Infra Engineering Chairman Granted Interim Protection by Court</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=H.G.+Infra+Engineering+Ltd&title=H.G.+Infra+Engineering+Chairman+Granted+Interim+Protection+by+Court&newsId=568c8f4a-2bc4-436a-82e6-9628b00ae5b4&token=NTY4YzhmNGEtMmJj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">568c8f4a-2bc4-436a-82e6-9628b00ae5b4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>H.G. Infra Engineering Ltd. announced that its Chairman and Managing Director, Mr. Harendra Singh, has been granted interim protection with no coercive steps by the Court of Spl. Judge, CBI-1, Patna. The order was given on January 27, 2026, and the certified copy was received on January 28, 2026. The company clarified that a copy of the FIR has not been formally served by the Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI), but based on the information available on the CBI’s official website, Mr. Harendra Singh has been named as a party in the FIR. The company and its officials have cooperated with the CBI and will continue to provide any clarification or information as required. The company&apos;s business is conducted in the normal course, and it remains committed to high standards of corporate governance and transparency. Any further developments will be promptly intimated to the Stock Exchanges.</p><ul><li>H.G. Infra Engineering Chairman, Mr. Harendra Singh, granted interim protection by the Court</li><li>Company continues to cooperate with the Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI)</li><li>Company&apos;s business operates as usual</li><li>Commitment to high standards of corporate governance and transparency</li><li>Further developments to be promptly informed to Stock Exchanges</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d223910e-6fc4-47a9-b2e4-36348b0a9a91.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: H.G. Infra Engineering Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PANAENERG] Panasonic Energy India Board Meeting Postponed: Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended December 31, 2025 Not Approved</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PANASONIC+ENERGY+INDIA+COMPANY+LTD.-%24&title=Panasonic+Energy+India+Board+Meeting+Postponed%3A+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+December+31%2C+2025+Not+Approved&newsId=09755f5d-4cbb-4d09-8b54-d5c027a348fd&token=MDk3NTVmNWQtNGNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09755f5d-4cbb-4d09-8b54-d5c027a348fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:31:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board Meeting of Panasonic Energy India Company Ltd., originally scheduled for January 29, 2026, to approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, has been cancelled due to unavoidable circumstances. A new date for the Board Meeting will be announced and shared with the Stock Exchange(s) as required under the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The updated information is also available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Panasonic Energy India Board Meeting postponed</li><li>Unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025 not approved</li><li>New date for the Board Meeting to be announced</li><li>Information to be shared with Stock Exchange(s) as required</li><li>Updated information available on the company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/03735b2d-19fe-4517-9136-0602ff67da26.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PANASONIC ENERGY INDIA COMPANY LTD.-$ | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[THREEMPAPE] Three M Paper Boards Ltd Reports Q4 2025 Investor Complaints Statement</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Three+M+Paper+Boards+Ltd&title=Three+M+Paper+Boards+Ltd+Reports+Q4+2025+Investor+Complaints+Statement&newsId=919bb5ff-dbf2-4606-bc66-5803308de739&token=OTE5YmI1ZmYtZGJm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">919bb5ff-dbf2-4606-bc66-5803308de739</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Three M Paper Boards Ltd has released its Statement of Investor Complaints as per Regulation 13(3) of SEBI LODR 2015 for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The report indicates the number of complaints received and resolved during the quarter.</p><ul><li>Three M Paper Boards Ltd has released its Statement of Investor Complaints for Q4 2025</li><li>The report is in accordance with Regulation 13(3) of SEBI LODR 2015</li><li>The statement provides the number of complaints received during the quarter</li><li>It also indicates the number of complaints resolved during the quarter</li><li>This report is for the quarter ended December 31, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/33db1085-3834-46db-bb43-2f0f9059c3a0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Three M Paper Boards Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PPLPHARMA] Piramal Pharma Ltd Subsidiary to Acquire Kenalog® from Bristol-Myers Squibb for Up to US$ 100 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Piramal+Pharma+Ltd&title=Piramal+Pharma+Ltd+Subsidiary+to+Acquire+Kenalog%C2%AE+from+Bristol-Myers+Squibb+for+Up+to+US%24+100+Million&newsId=6f280a41-1f02-41c5-9c40-7258fca7d65c&token=NmYyODBhNDEtMWYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f280a41-1f02-41c5-9c40-7258fca7d65c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Piramal Critical Care B.V., a step-down wholly owned subsidiary of Piramal Pharma Limited, has entered into a definitive agreement with Bristol-Myers Squibb Company (BMS) for the acquisition of Kenalog® and its associated brands for an upfront consideration of US$ 35 million and a contingent consideration of up to US$ 65 million. The transaction, which does not involve related parties and is expected to leverage the company&apos;s extensive distribution network and broaden its product portfolio, is subject to the fulfillment of certain closing conditions.</p><ul><li>Piramal Critical Care B.V. to acquire Kenalog® and its associated brands from Bristol-Myers Squibb Company for up to US$ 100 million</li><li>Transaction includes an upfront consideration of US$ 35 million and a contingent consideration of up to US$ 65 million</li><li>Kenalog® is a branded commercial injectable product containing Triamcinolone Acetonide, used as an adjunctive therapy in various inflammatory conditions</li><li>Transaction expected to leverage the company&apos;s extensive distribution network and broaden its product portfolio</li><li>Transaction does not involve related parties and is subject to the fulfillment of certain closing conditions</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/854dbadb-2a8b-4f89-a703-1d9d07a13626.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Piramal Pharma Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PPLPHARMA] Piramal Pharma Ltd Announces Changes in Senior Management and Key Managerial Personnel</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Piramal+Pharma+Ltd&title=Piramal+Pharma+Ltd+Announces+Changes+in+Senior+Management+and+Key+Managerial+Personnel&newsId=6c2946ee-bccf-4860-9fb3-54b0ad0e7b9d&token=NmMyOTQ2ZWUtYmNj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c2946ee-bccf-4860-9fb3-54b0ad0e7b9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 20:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Piramal Pharma Ltd has announced changes in its Senior Management Personnel (SMP) and Key Managerial Personnel (KMP) at its board meeting held on 28th January, 2026. The new SMP includes Ms. Rashida Najmi as Chief Quality Officer, Mr. Jatin Lal as President — Merger and Acquisitions, Mr. Sandeep Rathod as General Counsel, and Ms. Puneet Rajput as Chief Human Resource Officer. The KMP, Ms. Tanya Sanish, has resigned from her position as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer, to pursue career opportunities outside the organization. Ms. Pratibha Mishra has been appointed as the Interim Company Secretary and Compliance Officer with effect from 21st February, 2026.</p><ul><li>Piramal Pharma Ltd announces new Senior Management Personnel (SMP)</li><li>Ms. Tanya Sanish resigns from the position of Company Secretary and Compliance Officer</li><li>Ms. Pratibha Mishra appointed as Interim Company Secretary and Compliance Officer</li><li>New appointments are effective immediately</li><li>Resignation and new appointment to be effective from 20th and 21st February, 2026 respectively</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ec28cbac-d5a9-44a2-a46d-d91079af89c8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Piramal Pharma Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TEXELIN] Texel Industries Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on Feb 4, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TEXEL+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Texel+Industries+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+Feb+4%2C+2026&newsId=68bd3f98-7223-4734-938c-d9dc2c35a5af&token=NjhiZDNmOTgtNzIy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68bd3f98-7223-4734-938c-d9dc2c35a5af</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:54:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Texel Industries Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 4, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the third quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The meeting will also take on record the Limited Review Report of the Statutory Auditors.</p><ul><li>Texel Industries Ltd to approve Q3 and nine months financial results for the period ending December 31, 2025</li><li>The meeting will be held on February 4, 2026</li><li>The Board will consider and approve Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results</li><li>The Limited Review Report of the Statutory Auditors will be taken on record</li><li>The announcement is made in accordance with Regulation 29 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/10d7829d-b05c-48d4-9254-5fad187d79b4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TEXEL INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>