<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:31:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ASMS] Bartronics India Gets Board Nod to Acquire 51% Stake in Farm to Commerce Player AYOU</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BARTRONICS+INDIA+LTD.&title=Bartronics+India+Gets+Board+Nod+to+Acquire+51%25+Stake+in+Farm+to+Commerce+Player+AYOU&newsId=703ed29a-9616-4223-8349-509289167995&token=NzAzZWQyOWEtOTYx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">703ed29a-9616-4223-8349-509289167995</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:29:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Bartronics India Limited has received Board approval for a strategic 51% investment in AYOU, the fresh produce brand operated by Shree NagaNarasimha Pvt. Ltd. (SNN), a Bengaluru-based organised fresh produce aggregation and processing company. This move marks Bartronics’ formal entry into structured agri trade under Project Avio Agritech, and strengthens its presence across the fresh produce value chain. AYOU aggregates fruits and vegetables directly from farmers, FPOs, mandis and collection centres, undertakes grading and processing, and supplies leading quick commerce and modern retail platforms. The company currently works with Blinkit, Zepto, Swiggy Instamart, BigBasket, Ninjacart, More Retail and other organised retail partners, serving as a reliable supply partner in the fast-growing quick commerce ecosystem. Based in Bengaluru, AYOU operates a 6,000 sq. ft. processing and grading facility with capacity of up to 900 tonnes per month, supported by sourcing hubs and collection centres across multiple agri belts. Bartronics’ investment is expected to unlock expansion across aggregation volumes, processing capacity and trade cycles, enabling the addition of new SKUs and higher-margin processing-led categories. Beyond domestic growth, Bartronics and AYOU are jointly evaluating export-led opportunities, with Dubai being assessed as a strategic base for agri exports, particularly for premium fruits and vegetables. The companies are also exploring the possibility of selective imports of dry fruits and exotic produce into India, creating a two-way agri trade corridor. Singapore and other international markets are under evaluation as part of the longer-term roadmap.</p><ul><li>Bartronics India to acquire 51% stake in AYOU, a fresh produce brand operated by Shree NagaNarasimha Pvt. Ltd.</li><li>AYOU is a Bengaluru-based organised fresh produce aggregation and processing company.</li><li>Bartronics’ investment is expected to unlock expansion across aggregation volumes, processing capacity and trade cycles.</li><li>Bartronics and AYOU are jointly evaluating export-led opportunities, with Dubai being assessed as a strategic base for agri exports.</li><li>The companies are also exploring the possibility of selective imports of dry fruits and exotic produce into India.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0e3b0de8-1d76-4e0c-9921-4a82686d1f9f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BARTRONICS INDIA LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AJANTPHARM] Ajanta Pharma to Consider and Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on 30th January 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AJANTA+PHARMA+LTD.&title=Ajanta+Pharma+to+Consider+and+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+30th+January+2026&newsId=1f38a762-4647-4b08-ad52-e25b49aa44b2&token=MWYzOGE3NjItNDY0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f38a762-4647-4b08-ad52-e25b49aa44b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:28:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ajanta Pharma Ltd has informed the BSE that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on 30th January 2026. The agenda includes the consideration and approval of the unaudited consolidated and standalone financial results of the Company for the third quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. This is in accordance with Regulation 29 of the Listing Regulations.</p><ul><li>Ajanta Pharma to consider and approve Q3 and nine months financial results</li><li>Meeting of the Board of Directors scheduled on 30th January 2026</li><li>Unaudited consolidated and standalone financial results for the period ending 31st December 2025 will be considered</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d67c3689-de82-4978-ba41-93c313c2cda6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AJANTA PHARMA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GRSE] GRSE Promotes Four Officers to Executive Director, Chief General Manager, and General Manager Ranks</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Garden+Reach+Shipbuilders+%26+Engineers+Ltd&title=GRSE+Promotes+Four+Officers+to+Executive+Director%2C+Chief+General+Manager%2C+and+General+Manager+Ranks&newsId=93b85b04-0124-4f04-b486-526b55d7fc58&token=OTNiODViMDQtMDEy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93b85b04-0124-4f04-b486-526b55d7fc58</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:24:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Promotions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Garden Reach Shipbuilders &amp; Engineers Ltd. (GRSE) has approved the promotion of four officers to the grade of Executive Director, Chief General Manager, and General Manager. The promotions are effective from 01 Jan 2026. The officers and their brief profiles are as follows:</p><ul><li>Shri M Venkatesh Murthy, currently General Manager, has been promoted to Executive Director.</li><li>Cmde Rajat Manchanda, IN (Retd.), currently Chief General Manager, has been promoted to Executive Director.</li><li>Cdr Manoj Kumar Gupta, IN (Retd.), currently Deputy GM, has been promoted to Chief General Manager (CC, HP &amp; IP).</li><li>Lt Col Sanjay Anand (Retd.), currently GM (Security, FF &amp; OL), has been promoted to GM (Security, FF &amp; OL) from 01 Jan 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ead710a3-baf5-4e75-afc9-8b6b6684f06a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Garden Reach Shipbuilders & Engineers Ltd | Category: Promotions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AURIONPRO] Aurionpro Secures Order for Automated Fare Collection Systems in Bhopal and Indore Metro Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AURIONPRO+SOLUTIONS+LTD.&title=Aurionpro+Secures+Order+for+Automated+Fare+Collection+Systems+in+Bhopal+and+Indore+Metro+Projects&newsId=2df237f1-c6e3-4eec-8627-ce7cca5c5d0e&token=MmRmMjM3ZjEtYzZl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2df237f1-c6e3-4eec-8627-ce7cca5c5d0e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Aurionpro Solutions Limited has secured an order from Delhi Metro Rail Corporation Limited (DMRC) for the implementation of Automated Fare Collection (AFC) systems for the Bhopal and Indore Metro Rail projects. The project, valued at approximately INR 150 crore, aims to deploy standardized AFC systems to enhance commuter convenience, operational efficiency, and interoperability across the upcoming metro networks in Madhya Pradesh. Under this multi-year contract, Aurionpro will supply, implement, and maintain open-loop EMV card- and QR-code-based AFC solutions for both metro projects. The scope of work spans end-to-end implementation followed by comprehensive maintenance and support services over a five-year period.</p><ul><li>Aurionpro secures an order from DMRC for Bhopal and Indore Metro projects</li><li>Order valued at approximately INR 150 crore</li><li>Open-loop EMV card- and QR-code-based AFC solutions to be implemented</li><li>Five-year maintenance and support services contract</li><li>Reinforces Aurionpro’s leadership in smart mobility solutions</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d14c7c6a-db70-41ca-ae8b-4a0b7d42575f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AURIONPRO SOLUTIONS LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SIYARAM] Siyaram Recycling Secures Rs 4.05 Crore Order from Saanvi Metal Craft</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Siyaram+Recycling+Industries+Ltd&title=Siyaram+Recycling+Secures+Rs+4.05+Crore+Order+from+Saanvi+Metal+Craft&newsId=57b34a4b-cbe2-4036-adee-4d28425364f4&token=NTdiMzRhNGItY2Jl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57b34a4b-cbe2-4036-adee-4d28425364f4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Siyaram Recycling Industries Ltd has secured a significant order from Saanvi Metal Craft worth Rs 4,04,66,844. The order is for brass scrap honey as per ISRI and is to be executed within 6 months. The details of the order comply with the SEBI Listing Regulations, 2015 and SEBI Circular SEBI/HO/CFD/CFDPod-1/P/CIR/2023/123 dated July 13, 2023.</p><ul><li>Siyaram Recycling secures a noteworthy order from Saanvi Metal Craft</li><li>Order worth Rs. 4,04,66,844.00</li><li>To be executed within 6 months</li><li>Compliant with SEBI Listing Regulations, 2015 and SEBI Circular SEBI/HO/CFD/CFDPod-1/P/CIR/2023/123 dated July 13, 2023</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/86fcf5c4-e998-42cd-9ffa-f229366c1277.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Siyaram Recycling Industries Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CONCOR] CONCOR Reports 10.14% Increase in Physical Volume for Quarter Ended Dec-25</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CONTAINER+CORPORATION+OF+INDIA+LTD.&title=CONCOR+Reports+10.14%25+Increase+in+Physical+Volume+for+Quarter+Ended+Dec-25&newsId=c1287160-306f-4e2a-9e6a-afc39eb18751&token=YzEyODcxNjAtMzA2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c1287160-306f-4e2a-9e6a-afc39eb18751</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:13:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Container Corporation of India Ltd. (CONCOR) has disclosed the physical volume for the quarter and period ended on 31-Dec-25. The provisional figures show a 10.14% increase in the physical volume compared to the same quarter of the previous year. The throughput details are as follows: EXIM volumes are at 10,72,145 TEUs (Twenty Foot Equivalent Units) compared to 9,75,243 TEUs in the same quarter of the previous year, a 9.94% increase. DOM volumes are at 381,121 TEUs, a 13.43% increase compared to the same quarter of the previous year. The period ended figures show a 10.85% increase in EXIM volumes and a 10.78% increase in DOM volumes compared to the same period of the previous year. This information is provided in accordance with regulation 30 of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>CONCOR reports a 10.14% increase in physical volume for the quarter ended Dec-25</li><li>EXIM volumes are up by 9.94% compared to the same quarter of the previous year</li><li>DOM volumes show a 13.43% increase compared to the same quarter of the previous year</li><li>Period ended EXIM volumes are up by 10.85% compared to the same period of the previous year</li><li>Period ended DOM volumes show a 10.78% increase compared to the same period of the previous year</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ac4994d1-1ce0-424b-a10e-14d8c48f041d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CONTAINER CORPORATION OF INDIA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IDBI] IDBI Bank Ltd. to Approve Un-audited Financial Results for Q3 &amp; Nine Months Ended December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IDBI+BANK+LTD.&title=IDBI+Bank+Ltd.+to+Approve+Un-audited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Ended+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=fda1f4ee-6bc9-4db7-8670-1ca762cd5f8a&token=ZmRhMWY0ZWUtNmJj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fda1f4ee-6bc9-4db7-8670-1ca762cd5f8a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>IDBI Bank Ltd. has informed BSE that the meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on January 17, 2026, to consider and approve the Un-audited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, subject to a Limited Review by the Statutory Auditors. The trading window for dealing in securities of the Bank by the designated persons and their immediate relatives will remain closed until January 19, 2026, in accordance with the Bank&apos;s Code of Conduct for Prevention of Insider Trading and applicable SEBI regulations.</p><ul><li>IDBI Bank Ltd. to approve Un-audited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Meeting of the Board of Directors scheduled on January 17, 2026</li><li>Subject to Limited Review by the Statutory Auditors</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities to remain closed until January 19, 2026</li><li>In accordance with the Bank&apos;s Code of Conduct for Prevention of Insider Trading and SEBI regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/490a12cd-6cfb-4120-8637-8777feb81fe5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IDBI BANK LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GOACARBON] Goa Carbon Ltd to Consider and Approve Q4 Financial Results on 21st January, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GOA+CARBON+LTD.-%24&title=Goa+Carbon+Ltd+to+Consider+and+Approve+Q4+Financial+Results+on+21st+January%2C+2026&newsId=b732f6f1-fbf4-44f2-bfd1-e4773477ed80&token=YjczMmY2ZjEtZmJm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b732f6f1-fbf4-44f2-bfd1-e4773477ed80</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Goa Carbon Ltd has informed BSE that the meeting of the Board of Directors of the Company is scheduled on 21st January, 2026. The meeting will inter-alia consider and take on record the unaudited Financial Results of the Company for the Quarter ended on December 31, 2025. This notice is being submitted pursuant to Regulation 29 of the Securities &amp; Exchange Board of India (Listing Regulations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulation 2015.</p><ul><li>Goa Carbon Ltd to consider and approve Q4 financial results on 21st January, 2026</li><li>The meeting is pursuant to Regulation 29 of the Securities &amp; Exchange Board of India (Listing Regulations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulation 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bf7d43ac-4441-4d8c-933a-8fe4a6eb565c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GOA CARBON LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RDEL] Riddhi Display Equipments Ltd. Announces Unaudited Financial Results for H1 2025 with Approval from Board of Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Riddhi+Display+Equipments+Ltd&title=Riddhi+Display+Equipments+Ltd.+Announces+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+H1+2025+with+Approval+from+Board+of+Directors&newsId=ac17b11e-cff4-4457-a1a0-65d5cf0388c6&token=YWMxN2IxMWUtY2Zm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac17b11e-cff4-4457-a1a0-65d5cf0388c6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:09:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Riddhi Display Equipments Ltd. announced its unaudited financial results for the half year ended on September 30, 2025, during a board meeting held on January 05, 2026. The board approved the unaudited standalone financial results under IND AS for the aforementioned period. K M Chauhan &amp; Associates carried out a limited review of the financial results. The company&apos;s management prepared the statement in accordance with the generally accepted accounting principles in India and applicable accounting standards.</p><ul><li>Unaudited financial results for H1 2025 approved by the board of directors.</li><li>Limited review conducted by K M Chauhan &amp; Associates.</li><li>Financial statement prepared in accordance with GAAP and applicable accounting standards.</li><li>Riddhi Display Equipments Ltd. follows recognized accounting practices and policies.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/16b90eec-abf3-49f0-a96a-4b716f555158.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Riddhi Display Equipments Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MODRNSH] Modern Shares &amp; Stockbrokers Ltd to Approve Q3 Results on Jan 30, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MODERN+SHARES+%26+STOCKBROKERS+LTD.&title=Modern+Shares+%26+Stockbrokers+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+Results+on+Jan+30%2C+2026&newsId=dfbbce09-61fe-46fa-9c24-ef100623f9f0&token=ZGZiYmNlMDktNjFm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dfbbce09-61fe-46fa-9c24-ef100623f9f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Modern Shares &amp; Stockbrokers Ltd has announced a meeting of its Board of Directors on January 30, 2026, to consider and approve the estimated un-audited results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The notice for the meeting has been issued in accordance with Regulation 29(1) (a) &amp; 29(2) of the Listing Regulations. The trading window has been closed from January 2, 2026, and will open 48 hours after the outcome of the meeting is made public.</p><ul><li>Modern Shares &amp; Stockbrokers Ltd to consider and approve Q3 results on Jan 30, 2026</li><li>Trading window closed from Jan 2, 2026, and will open 48 hours after the meeting outcome is made public</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d059e3de-a986-4f78-a50d-21f465f13315.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MODERN SHARES & STOCKBROKERS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>