<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 18:46:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ANZEN] Anzen India Energy Yield Plus Trust Receives Unitholder Approval for Issuance of Units and Acquisition of Solar Power Assets</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Anzen+India+Energy+Yield+Plus+Trust&title=Anzen+India+Energy+Yield+Plus+Trust+Receives+Unitholder+Approval+for+Issuance+of+Units+and+Acquisition+of+Solar+Power+Assets&newsId=14e54c16-ac74-4824-ab6d-d2c9128fca42&token=MTRlNTRjMTYtYWM3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">14e54c16-ac74-4824-ab6d-d2c9128fca42</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:41:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Anzen India Energy Yield Plus Trust has received approval from unitholders for the issuance of units on a preferential basis for an aggregate consideration of up to ₹ 696.45 crores and the acquisition of 74% equity share capital and other securities in one or more tranches of ROFO assets. The approval was given during a postal ballot held on February 18, 2026, where unitholders voted in favor of the proposals with the requisite majority.</p><ul><li>Unitholders of Anzen India Energy Yield Plus Trust approved the issuance of units for up to ₹ 696.45 crores</li><li>Unitholders also approved the acquisition of 74% equity share capital and other securities in ROFO assets</li><li>The approval was given during a postal ballot held on February 18, 2026</li><li>The proposals received the requisite majority vote from unitholders</li><li>The scrutinizer&apos;s report and voting results have been made available on the Anzen website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fd806daf-6137-4bc8-9f09-52db23760eae.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Anzen India Energy Yield Plus Trust | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[APLLTD] Alembic Pharmaceuticals&apos; Injectable Facility Passes USFDA Inspection with Two Observations, None Data Integrity Related</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ALEMBIC+PHARMACEUTICALS+LTD.&title=Alembic+Pharmaceuticals%27+Injectable+Facility+Passes+USFDA+Inspection+with+Two+Observations%2C+None+Data+Integrity+Related&newsId=a6f00638-d006-433d-ad01-3d9171496ae6&token=YTZmMDA2MzgtZDAw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a6f00638-d006-433d-ad01-3d9171496ae6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:34:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>USFDA</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Alembic Pharmaceuticals Limited announced that the United States Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) has completed an unannounced cGMP inspection at its Injectable Facility (F-3) located at Karakhadi. The inspection took place from 9th to 18th February 2026, resulting in two observations, none of which are related to data integrity. The company will respond to these observations within the specified time. Alembic Pharmaceuticals remains committed to maintaining the highest quality standards and compliance.</p><ul><li>USFDA inspection completed at Alembic Pharmaceuticals&apos; Injectable Facility (F-3) at Karakhadi</li><li>Two observations reported, none related to data integrity</li><li>Company to respond to observations within stipulated time</li><li>Alembic Pharmaceuticals committed to highest quality standards and compliance</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/65d35813-aeb6-4d87-b948-6a7e34e9d76c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ALEMBIC PHARMACEUTICALS LTD. | Category: USFDA</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HILTON] Hilton Metal Forging Ltd Announces Rights Issue of 1,67,70,000 Equity Shares at Rs. 16.68 Each</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HILTON+METAL+FORGING+LTD.&title=Hilton+Metal+Forging+Ltd+Announces+Rights+Issue+of+1%2C67%2C70%2C000+Equity+Shares+at+Rs.+16.68+Each&newsId=bf3da381-5d47-4738-9d4b-24192d1d1bee&token=YmYzZGEzODEtNWQ0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf3da381-5d47-4738-9d4b-24192d1d1bee</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hilton Metal Forging Ltd, a company with CIN L-28900 MH 2005 PLC 154986, has announced a rights issue of 1,67,70,000 equity shares of Rs. 10 each at an issue price of Rs. 16.68 (including premium of Rs. 6.68) per equity share. The record date for determining the eligibility of equity shareholders for the rights issue is February 24, 2026. The company&apos;s authorized share capital will be increased from Rs. 55,00,00,000 to Rs. 85,00,00,000. The rights entitlement ratio is 29 (Twenty-nine) Rights Equity Shares for every 60 (Sixty) fully paid-up Equity Shares held by the eligible equity shareholders as on the Record Date.</p><ul><li>Hilton Metal Forging Ltd announces a rights issue of 1,67,70,000 equity shares</li><li>The issue price is Rs. 16.68 per equity share, including a premium of Rs. 6.68</li><li>The record date for eligibility is February 24, 2026</li><li>The company&apos;s authorized share capital will be increased to Rs. 85,00,00,000</li><li>The rights entitlement ratio is 29:60</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9b22a16a-462e-43fd-b117-c27b4f37e19b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HILTON METAL FORGING LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HILTON] Hilton Metal Forging Ltd Announces Record Date for Rights Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HILTON+METAL+FORGING+LTD.&title=Hilton+Metal+Forging+Ltd+Announces+Record+Date+for+Rights+Issue&newsId=dfa13614-36fb-42af-b0b8-502ef9f1dd88&token=ZGZhMTM2MTQtMzZm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dfa13614-36fb-42af-b0b8-502ef9f1dd88</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Right Issue</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hilton Metal Forging Ltd, a company based in Plot No. 1,2,3,15,16,17,20,21,25,26,28,29 &amp; 30, Shah &amp; Mehta Ind. Estate, Village Ghonsai, Tal. Wada, Dist. Palghar - 421 312, has fixed Tuesday, February 24, 2026, as the Record Date for the purpose of ascertaining the eligibility of shareholders entitled to receive 29 (Twenty-nine) Rights Equity Shares for every 60 (Sixty) fully paid-up Equity Shares held by the existing Equity Shareholders of the Company on a rights basis. This announcement was made pursuant to Regulation 42 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Hilton Metal Forging Ltd has fixed February 24, 2026, as the Record Date for Rights Issue</li><li>Eligible shareholders will receive 29 Rights Equity Shares for every 60 fully paid-up Equity Shares held</li><li>This announcement is pursuant to Regulation 42 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/445fe19d-d239-4e64-9830-34a8729c3d46.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HILTON METAL FORGING LTD. | Category: Right Issue</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CELEBRITY] Celebrity Fashions Ltd. Alters Capital Clause of MOA: Key Changes in Authorized Share Capital</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CELEBRITY+FASHIONS+LTD.&title=Celebrity+Fashions+Ltd.+Alters+Capital+Clause+of+MOA%3A+Key+Changes+in+Authorized+Share+Capital&newsId=0f155571-7932-45b6-abc2-cf01b743759b&token=MGYxNTU1NzEtNzkz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f155571-7932-45b6-abc2-cf01b743759b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>MoU</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Celebrity Fashions Ltd. has announced alterations to its Memorandum of Association (MOA) through a postal ballot dated 19th January 2026. The company sought approval for reclassification of authorized share capital and consequent amendments to the capital clause in the MOA. The resolutions were passed on 18th February 2026. The amendments include changes to the number of equity shares and preference shares. The company&apos;s authorized share capital will now comprise 7,00,00,000 equity shares and 2,00,00,000 1% cumulative redeemable preference shares. This development is expected to have significant implications for the company&apos;s financial structure and shareholding pattern.</p><ul><li>Celebrity Fashions Ltd. alters MOA through postal ballot</li><li>Reclassification of authorized share capital approved</li><li>Changes in the capital clause of the MOA</li><li>Issue of Equity Shares by way of Preferential issue on private placement basis</li><li>Significant implications for the company&apos;s financial structure and shareholding pattern</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/08eea17a-5737-413e-b876-01145e0b0c5b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CELEBRITY FASHIONS LTD. | Category: MoU</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KORE] Team24 Consumer Products Ltd Secures Contract with Milk Union at Ambala for Dairy Sweets Manufacturing Unit</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kore+Foods+Ltd&title=Team24+Consumer+Products+Ltd+Secures+Contract+with+Milk+Union+at+Ambala+for+Dairy+Sweets+Manufacturing+Unit&newsId=2b595d05-a34f-4986-9143-15866e47a43b&token=MmI1OTVkMDUtYTM0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b595d05-a34f-4986-9143-15866e47a43b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 17:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Team24 Consumer Products Limited, formerly known as Kore Foods Limited, has entered into a contract with Milk Union at Ambala for setting up machinery and equipment for manufacturing dairy sweets, namkeen products, and job work at plot no. 37, Industrial area phase-2 Panchkula. The contract also includes the supply, installation, and operation of a VITA display retail store at Panchkula.</p><ul><li>Team24 Consumer Products Limited has secured a contract with Milk Union at Ambala for setting up a dairy sweets and namkeen manufacturing unit.</li><li>The contract includes the supply, installation, and operation of a VITA display retail store at Panchkula.</li><li>The project is aimed at manufacturing and operating a diary sweets and namkeen manufacturing unit.</li><li>Team24 Consumer Products Limited, formerly known as Kore Foods Limited, is the company involved in this venture.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3e5d9986-1120-46e0-8fd2-3438759556fe.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kore Foods Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MEGACOR] Mega Corporation Ltd to Appoint New Non-Executive and Non-Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MEGA+CORPORATION+LTD.&title=Mega+Corporation+Ltd+to+Appoint+New+Non-Executive+and+Non-Independent+Director&newsId=43ef320c-30db-4146-acf8-7336cfb50381&token=NDNlZjMyMGMtMzBk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43ef320c-30db-4146-acf8-7336cfb50381</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:51:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mega Corporation Ltd has informed BSE that the company&apos;s Board of Directors will meet on 23/02/2026 to consider and approve the appointment of Mr. Kanishkkant Dubey as an Additional Director (Non-Executive and Non-Independent) of the Company. The meeting is in compliance with the provisions of Regulation 29(1) of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Mega Corporation Ltd to appoint Mr. Kanishkkant Dubey as an Additional Director (Non-Executive and Non-Independent)</li><li>The appointment is to be considered and approved in the Board Meeting scheduled on 23/02/2026</li><li>The meeting is in compliance with the provisions of Regulation 29(1) of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b545f31d-3f4e-4d20-8dca-b3085abe2097.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MEGA CORPORATION LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADITYA] Aditya Ispat Ltd Board Meeting Adjourned to February 20, 2026 for Clarification on Management Report</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADITYA+ISPAT+LTD.&title=Aditya+Ispat+Ltd+Board+Meeting+Adjourned+to+February+20%2C+2026+for+Clarification+on+Management+Report&newsId=50db944c-9995-44f0-93a3-39f15cb2273b&token=NTBkYjk0NGMtOTk5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50db944c-9995-44f0-93a3-39f15cb2273b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:51:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board Meeting of Aditya Ispat Ltd, scheduled for Wednesday, February 18, 2026, was adjourned to Friday, February 20, 2026, at the same venue. The decision was made during the meeting that commenced at 19:30 hours today and continued till 21:45 hours. The adjournment is to allow for clarification on the report submitted by the management. This information should be taken on record.</p><ul><li>Adjournment of Aditya Ispat Ltd Board Meeting to February 20, 2026</li><li>Meeting adjourned for clarification on management report</li><li>Meeting commenced at 19:30 hours and continued till 21:45 hours</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dabe4f6b-0277-433d-b5a1-dab83ecd485b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADITYA ISPAT LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[APIL] Avi Products India Ltd. Announces Extra Ordinary General Meeting for Director Appointments and Auditor Selection</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Avi+Products+India+Ltd&title=Avi+Products+India+Ltd.+Announces+Extra+Ordinary+General+Meeting+for+Director+Appointments+and+Auditor+Selection&newsId=776183c7-030f-4520-8b4a-ae50e8616fa0&token=Nzc2MTgzYzctMDMw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">776183c7-030f-4520-8b4a-ae50e8616fa0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Avi Products India Ltd. has announced an Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) to be held on Tuesday, 17 March, 2026 at 2:00 P.M. (IST) through Video Conferencing (VC) / Other Audio-Visual Means (OAVM). The EGM will transact the following businesses: Regularization/Appointment of Mr. Manas Ranjan Palo as an Independent Director for a term of five years, Regularization/Appointment of Mr. Saroj Kumar Choudhury as a Non-Executive Non-Independent Director, liable to retire by rotation, Appointment of Statutory Auditor M/S N K JALAN &amp; CO., Chartered Accountants, for a term of five financial years 2025-26 to 2029-30, and Appointment of Secretarial Auditor M/s. VKMG &amp; Associates LLP for a term of five financial years 2025-26 to 2029-30. The EGM will also consider an Enhancement of the Borrowing Limits of the Company.</p><ul><li>Regularization/Appointment of Mr. Manas Ranjan Palo as an Independent Director for a term of five years</li><li>Regularization/Appointment of Mr. Saroj Kumar Choudhury as a Non-Executive Non-Independent Director</li><li>Appointment of Statutory Auditor M/S N K JALAN &amp; CO., Chartered Accountants, for a term of five financial years 2025-26 to 2029-30</li><li>Appointment of Secretarial Auditor M/s. VKMG &amp; Associates LLP for a term of five financial years 2025-26 to 2029-30</li><li>Enhancement of the Borrowing Limits of the Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a87e4e84-e829-4b2c-974e-956d05c769c3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Avi Products India Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ANGELONE] Angel One Ltd. Sets Record Date for Equity Shares Sub-Division</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Angel+One+Ltd&title=Angel+One+Ltd.+Sets+Record+Date+for+Equity+Shares+Sub-Division&newsId=c723cf0e-8d22-4018-8d3b-f579c11264b2&token=YzcyM2NmMGUtOGQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c723cf0e-8d22-4018-8d3b-f579c11264b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 16:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Split</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Angel One Ltd. has fixed February 26, 2026 as the Record Date for the purpose of determining the eligible equity shareholders whose shares will be sub-divided, following the sub-division/split of the existing equity shares of the Company. The information is available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Angel One Ltd. sets Record Date for equity shares sub-division</li><li>The Record Date is fixed as February 26, 2026</li><li>The decision follows the sub-division/split of the existing equity shares of the Company</li><li>The information is available on the company&apos;s website: www.angelone.in</li><li>Angel One Ltd. is a SEBI registered Stock Broker with the registration number INZ000161534</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b7d5848f-1da8-4ae7-99c5-f449ec20818d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Angel One Ltd | Category: Split</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>