<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:47:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[INDAG] Indag Rubber Ltd. Reports Q3 and FY 2025 Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDAG+RUBBER+LTD.-%24&title=Indag+Rubber+Ltd.+Reports+Q3+and+FY+2025+Financial+Results&newsId=baa8d792-ea31-44dc-8983-4cd949b6698f&token=YmFhOGQ3OTItZWEz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">baa8d792-ea31-44dc-8983-4cd949b6698f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:46:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indag Rubber Ltd. has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and period ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 5,611.83 lakh rupees for the quarter and 22,481.65 lakh rupees for the period. The net profit after tax for the quarter is 676.93 lakh rupees. The company&apos;s total income and expenses for the quarter and period ended are also provided in the statement. The statement also includes other comprehensive income and earnings per share information.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for Q3 2025: 5,611.83 lakh rupees</li><li>Revenue from operations for FY 2025: 22,481.65 lakh rupees</li><li>Net profit after tax for Q3 2025: 676.93 lakh rupees</li><li>Total income and expenses details provided</li><li>Other comprehensive income and earnings per share information included</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f33f9136-b200-4cbf-943b-19cc362c534a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDAG RUBBER LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AKASHDEEP] Kalyan Capitals Ltd Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results, Reports Net Loss</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Akashdeep+Metal+Industries+Ltd&title=Kalyan+Capitals+Ltd+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results%2C+Reports+Net+Loss&newsId=78322144-9a72-429d-a1cb-81592e94f933&token=NzgzMjIxNDQtOWE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78322144-9a72-429d-a1cb-81592e94f933</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kalyan Capitals Ltd, formerly known as Akashdeep Metal Industries Ltd, announced the outcome of their Board Meeting held on 12th February 2026. The company reported the un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December 2025. The Board discussed and approved the financial results, which showed a net loss for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December 2025.</p><ul><li>Kalyan Capitals Ltd reported a net loss for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December 2025.</li><li>The company announced the un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December 2025.</li><li>The announcement was made following the Board Meeting held on 12th February 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a0d817f9-a18f-4358-884f-20ff324b665d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Akashdeep Metal Industries Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WATERBASE] Waterbase Ltd Announces Q3 2025 Financial Results and Leadership Realignment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=WATERBASE+LTD.&title=Waterbase+Ltd+Announces+Q3+2025+Financial+Results+and+Leadership+Realignment&newsId=463aba85-50cb-4366-8512-04a81365956a&token=NDYzYWJhODUtNTBj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">463aba85-50cb-4366-8512-04a81365956a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Waterbase Ltd has announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s Board of Directors approved the financial results, which will be published in English and Telegu newspapers and on the company&apos;s website. In addition, the board approved a leadership realignment effective April 1, 2026, with Ramakanth V. Akula continuing as Managing Director and Chola Varma Alluri being elevated to Chief Executive Officer.</p><ul><li>Waterbase Ltd announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s financial results were approved by the Board of Directors and will be published in newspapers and on the company&apos;s website.</li><li>A leadership realignment was approved, with Ramakanth V. Akula continuing as Managing Director and Chola Varma Alluri being appointed as Chief Executive Officer.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b32d9550-9e6f-4d93-bc65-89076e477dfe.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: WATERBASE LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SPICEJET] Spicejet Ltd Announces Q3 Results for 2025, Reports Net Loss</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SPICEJET+LTD.&title=Spicejet+Ltd+Announces+Q3+Results+for+2025%2C+Reports+Net+Loss&newsId=b6297441-d7e9-4751-9265-8aaa4e849374&token=YjYyOTc0NDEtZDdl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6297441-d7e9-4751-9265-8aaa4e849374</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:34:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Spicejet Ltd, a leading airline company, announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the third quarter ended on December 31, 2025. The company reported a net loss of Rs. 2,674.72 million for the quarter and Rs. 11,405.57 million for the nine months period. The accumulated losses as of December 31, 2025, amounted to Rs. 89,053.73 million, with current liabilities exceeding current assets by Rs. 42,139.31 million. The company is facing material uncertainties that may cast significant doubt about its ability to continue as a going concern. However, the management is optimistic about future business projections and mitigating factors.</p><ul><li>Spicejet Ltd reported a net loss of Rs. 2,674.72 million for Q3 2025</li><li>The company&apos;s accumulated losses as of December 31, 2025, amounted to Rs. 89,053.73 million</li><li>Current liabilities exceed current assets by Rs. 42,139.31 million as of December 31, 2025</li><li>Material uncertainties exist that may cast significant doubt about the company&apos;s ability to continue as a going concern</li><li>Management is optimistic about future business projections and mitigating factors</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d10a15e0-7111-414a-9694-8fa57aff4e9a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SPICEJET LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[3IINFOTECH] Corrigendum: Inadvertent Typo in 3i Infotech Stock Option Plan 2023 Disclosure</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=3I+INFOTECH+LTD.&title=Corrigendum%3A+Inadvertent+Typo+in+3i+Infotech+Stock+Option+Plan+2023+Disclosure&newsId=fcf15d47-9a25-4738-8ad3-ae4fdf98bd89&token=ZmNmMTVkNDctOWEy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fcf15d47-9a25-4738-8ad3-ae4fdf98bd89</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:34:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Corrigendum</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>3i Infotech Ltd has submitted a corrigendum to the stock exchanges regarding a typographical error in their previous disclosure related to the Grant of Stock Options under the 3i Infotech Stock Option Plan 2023. The error was on the first page where the number of stock options was incorrectly stated as 89,000, while the correct number, as stated in the annexure on the second page, is 83,000. The company sincerely regrets the oversight and requests that this corrigendum be taken on record.</p><ul><li>3i Infotech Ltd has submitted a corrigendum to the stock exchanges</li><li>Typographical error in the disclosure related to the Grant of Stock Options under the 3i Infotech Stock Option Plan 2023</li><li>The number of stock options was incorrectly stated as 89,000, the correct number is 83,000</li><li>The error was on the first page of the disclosure</li><li>The company regrets the oversight and requests the corrigendum be taken on record</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c5689a7f-ecd2-4b9e-ab97-9a987a092886.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: 3I INFOTECH LTD. | Category: Corrigendum</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GSTL] Globalspace Technologies Ltd Announces Q3 2025 Financial Results with a Net Loss of INR 234.37 Lakhs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Globalspace+Technologies+Ltd&title=Globalspace+Technologies+Ltd+Announces+Q3+2025+Financial+Results+with+a+Net+Loss+of+INR+234.37+Lakhs&newsId=29bb7e15-f20f-4ca2-b3ef-86db257c96b8&token=MjliYjdlMTUtZjIw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29bb7e15-f20f-4ca2-b3ef-86db257c96b8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:33:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Globalspace Technologies Ltd has announced its financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a net loss of INR 234.37 lakhs, with revenue from operations at INR 1,256.85 lakhs. The company&apos;s total expenses stood at INR 2,374.06 lakhs. The Board of Directors also approved a corporate guarantee for Innopharm Healthcare Private Limited, a subsidiary of the company. The trading window for dealing in the company&apos;s shares has been closed until 48 hours after the announcement of the un-audited financial results.</p><ul><li>Globalspace Technologies Ltd reported a net loss of INR 234.37 lakhs for Q3 2025</li><li>Revenue from operations stood at INR 1,256.85 lakhs</li><li>Total expenses were INR 2,374.06 lakhs</li><li>The Board approved a corporate guarantee for Innopharm Healthcare Private Limited</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the company&apos;s shares is closed</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6959d232-9202-4710-9031-bab85b471b3d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Globalspace Technologies Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ELEMARB] Elegant Marbles &amp; Grani Industries Ltd Reports Un-Audited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended on December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ELEGANT+MARBLES+%26+GRANI+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Elegant+Marbles+%26+Grani+Industries+Ltd+Reports+Un-Audited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+on+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=f4e2ecb9-412f-4f00-9bde-650261f187d3&token=ZjRlMmVjYjktNDEy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4e2ecb9-412f-4f00-9bde-650261f187d3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:33:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Elegant Marbles &amp; Grani Industries Ltd has announced its un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The results were reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors. The company has reported a net profit of INR 3.347 Crores for the period. The results are prepared in accordance with the Companies (Indian Accounting Standards) Rules, 2015. The company has recognized a one-time increase in provision for employee benefits of INR 23.03 Lakhs due to changes from the New Labour Codes.</p><ul><li>Net profit of INR 3.347 Crores for the period</li><li>Recognition of one-time increase in provision for employee benefits of INR 23.03 Lakhs due to changes from the New Labour Codes</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b975ad1b-9400-4d20-bc2b-562d901cb742.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ELEGANT MARBLES & GRANI INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NIBE] NIBE Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025: Revenue Up by 28.5%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NIBE+Ltd&title=NIBE+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025%3A+Revenue+Up+by+28.5%25&newsId=76424145-c940-49cc-a28a-60c68c336c0f&token=NzY0MjQxNDUtYzk0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76424145-c940-49cc-a28a-60c68c336c0f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>NIBE Ltd, a leading company in the industry, has reported its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue for the quarter increased by 28.5% compared to the same period last year. The total income for the nine months ended December 31, 2025, stands at INR 18,473.42 Lakhs. The company&apos;s net profit after tax for the quarter is INR 1,449.75 Lakhs.</p><ul><li>Revenue for the quarter increased by 28.5%</li><li>Total income for the nine months ended at INR 18,473.42 Lakhs</li><li>Net profit after tax for the quarter is INR 1,449.75 Lakhs</li><li>Unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results approved by the Board of Directors</li><li>Limited Review Reports of the Statutory Auditors submitted</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b12e60cc-bbc5-47af-94a9-e0f5c1f097ab.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NIBE Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TRITONV] Triton Valves Ltd. Announces Q3 and 9M Results, Capital Clause Alteration, Bonus Issue, and New Director Appointment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TRITON+VALVES+LTD.&title=Triton+Valves+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+9M+Results%2C+Capital+Clause+Alteration%2C+Bonus+Issue%2C+and+New+Director+Appointment&newsId=ed7afda3-9a00-4f8f-8144-8251d63e6af0&token=ZWQ3YWZkYTMtOWEw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed7afda3-9a00-4f8f-8144-8251d63e6af0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Triton Valves Ltd. announced the outcome of their Board meeting held on February 12, 2026. The Board approved the Unaudited Financial Results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. They proposed to alter the Capital Clause of the Memorandum of Association to increase the Authorised Share Capital. The Board also approved a bonus equity share issue in the ratio of 3:1 and appointed Mr. Ashok Kumar Dash as an Additional (Non-executive, Independent) Director.</p><ul><li>Approval of Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and 9M ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Proposal to alter the Capital Clause of the Memorandum of Association</li><li>Bonus equity share issue in the ratio of 3:1</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Ashok Kumar Dash as an Additional (Non-executive, Independent) Director</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0298bcea-d4cd-47cc-9c83-a1e711561cd3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TRITON VALVES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PANIDPR] Panther Industrial Products Ltd. Approves Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PANTHER+INDUSTRIAL+PRODUCTS+LTD.&title=Panther+Industrial+Products+Ltd.+Approves+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=6a9be7fa-6576-49aa-b423-23797a4bc830&token=NmE5YmU3ZmEtNjU3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a9be7fa-6576-49aa-b423-23797a4bc830</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Panther Industrial Products Ltd. met on 12th February, 2026 to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December, 2025. The company reported no revenue for the first nine months of the current financial year, but expects to generate revenue by the end of the financial year.</p><ul><li>The Board approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December, 2025.</li><li>The company reported no revenue for the first nine months of the current financial year.</li><li>Management has provided written confirmation indicating that revenue is expected to be generated by the end of the financial year.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/599d5ac3-650c-4fe6-b8d1-cb0e59609b59.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PANTHER INDUSTRIAL PRODUCTS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>