<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 12:38:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ICICIGI] ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Ltd Approves Audited Financial Statements for Q3 and Nine Months Ended December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ICICI+Lombard+General+Insurance+Company+Ltd&title=ICICI+Lombard+General+Insurance+Company+Ltd+Approves+Audited+Financial+Statements+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=0e5af37d-8a5b-4df9-b0dd-182e9777dfd0&token=MGU1YWYzN2QtOGE1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e5af37d-8a5b-4df9-b0dd-182e9777dfd0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 12:38:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Ltd has approved the audited financial statements for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The statements were approved at a Board Meeting held on January 13, 2026. The company&apos;s net profit and other financial information for the quarter and year to date were also approved.</p><ul><li>ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Ltd has approved the audited financial statements for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The approval was given at a Board Meeting held on January 13, 2026.</li><li>The statements include the net profit and other financial information for the quarter and year to date.</li><li>The audit was conducted in accordance with the auditing standards generally accepted in India.</li><li>The actuarial valuation of liabilities in respect of Claims Incurred But Not Reported (IBNR), Claims Incurred But Not Enough Reported (IBNER) and Premium Deficiency Reserve (PDR) has been duly certified by the Appointed Actuary.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f303dc10-9f69-412e-b84c-2b50c7b4e0c0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ALPSINDUS] Alps Industries Ltd Appoints Mr. Nishant Sharma as Whole-Time Director, Mr. Vinod Kumar Resigns</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ALPS+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Alps+Industries+Ltd+Appoints+Mr.+Nishant+Sharma+as+Whole-Time+Director%2C+Mr.+Vinod+Kumar+Resigns&newsId=fb7338fe-0518-459e-a4bf-da16795d410a&token=ZmI3MzM4ZmUtMDUx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fb7338fe-0518-459e-a4bf-da16795d410a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 12:34:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Alps Industries Ltd has appointed Mr. Nishant Sharma as a Whole-Time Director and Mr. Vinod Kumar has resigned from his position as a Whole-Time Director due to some unavoidable reasons. The appointment and resignation are subject to the approval of the shareholders of the Company. The meeting of the Board of Directors was held on Tuesday, January 13, 2026, and the Board approved the Notice of Postal Ballot and considered other matters.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Nishant Sharma as a Whole-Time Director of Alps Industries Ltd.</li><li>Resignation of Mr. Vinod Kumar as a Whole-Time Director of Alps Industries Ltd.</li><li>Approval of the Notice of Postal Ballot by the Board of Directors.</li><li>Consideration of other matters by the Board of Directors.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/eb9f461f-3c66-41f4-ae24-2bff8127072c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ALPS INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TRISHAKT] Trishakti Industries Ltd to Approve Q3 FY2025-26 Financial Results on Jan 19, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TRISHAKTI+ELECTRONICS+%26+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Trishakti+Industries+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+FY2025-26+Financial+Results+on+Jan+19%2C+2026&newsId=9be4d85a-96ef-4894-8085-f6fdb7b7066e&token=OWJlNGQ4NWEtOTZl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9be4d85a-96ef-4894-8085-f6fdb7b7066e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 12:34:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Trishakti Industries Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 19, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The meeting is in accordance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations &amp; Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The &apos;Trading Window&apos; for dealing in securities of the Company will remain closed for &apos;Designated Persons and their immediate relatives&apos; till the expiry of 48 hours after the declaration of the results.</p><ul><li>Trishakti Industries Ltd to approve Q3 FY2025-26 financial results on Jan 19, 2026</li><li>The results are for the quarter ended December 31, 2025</li><li>The meeting is in accordance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations &amp; Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Trading Window to remain closed for Designated Persons and their immediate relatives till 48 hours after the declaration of results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e3da14b7-88b6-49c7-856d-c08c291b8ee9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TRISHAKTI ELECTRONICS & INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ARSSBL] Anand Rathi Share And Stock Brokers Ltd Subsidiary, Anand Rathi International Ventures, to Enter Investment Banking and Advisory Business in GIFT City</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Anand+Rathi+Share+And+Stock+Brokers+Ltd&title=Anand+Rathi+Share+And+Stock+Brokers+Ltd+Subsidiary%2C+Anand+Rathi+International+Ventures%2C+to+Enter+Investment+Banking+and+Advisory+Business+in+GIFT+City&newsId=b3d3f3c3-302e-4fa0-8288-b5550bad4d3e&token=YjNkM2YzYzMtMzAy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3d3f3c3-302e-4fa0-8288-b5550bad4d3e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 12:32:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Anand Rathi Share And Stock Brokers Ltd has announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, Anand Rathi International Ventures (IFSC) Private Limited, will enter into new lines of business. These include Investment Banking / Merchant Banking business in GIFT City under the International Financial Services Centres Authority (‘IFSCA’) Listing framework and Investment Advisory business in GIFT City. This decision was made at a Board of Directors meeting held on January 13, 2026. The disclosure was made in accordance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015 and will be uploaded on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Anand Rathi International Ventures (IFSC) Private Limited to enter Investment Banking / Merchant Banking business in GIFT City under IFSCA Listing framework</li><li>The subsidiary will also carry out Investment Advisory business in GIFT City</li><li>This decision was made at a Board of Directors meeting held on January 13, 2026</li><li>The disclosure is in accordance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015</li><li>The disclosure will be uploaded on the company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1eb1a514-3d62-4c58-97e4-4df134f11efc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Anand Rathi Share And Stock Brokers Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BURNPUR] Burnpur Cement Ltd to Approve Q4 2025 Financial Results on January 19, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BURNPUR+CEMENT+LTD.&title=Burnpur+Cement+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+2025+Financial+Results+on+January+19%2C+2026&newsId=b9246402-8353-4e60-a208-aaf516785cee&token=YjkyNDY0MDItODM1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b9246402-8353-4e60-a208-aaf516785cee</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 12:31:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Burnpur Cement Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 19, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in shares of the company was closed from January 1, 2026, and will remain closed till 48 hours after the announcement of the un-audited financial results.</p><ul><li>Burnpur Cement Ltd to approve Q4 2025 financial results on January 19, 2026</li><li>The meeting will be held under Regulation 29(1)(a) of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Trading window for dealing in shares of the company was closed from January 1, 2026</li><li>Trading window to remain closed till 48 hours after the announcement of un-audited financial results</li><li>Un-Audited Standalone Financial Results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025 to be considered</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fb556b77-3cbf-48fa-b467-586946b09826.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BURNPUR CEMENT LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BIGBLOC] Bigbloc Construction Ltd to Approve Q3 &amp; Period Ended Dec 2025 Results on Jan 20, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Bigbloc+Construction+Ltd&title=Bigbloc+Construction+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+%26+Period+Ended+Dec+2025+Results+on+Jan+20%2C+2026&newsId=01e1630a-87c9-4f52-a7d3-fe1e525f3061&token=MDFlMTYzMGEtODdj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01e1630a-87c9-4f52-a7d3-fe1e525f3061</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 12:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bigbloc Construction Ltd has scheduled a Board Meeting on 20th January 2026 to consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and period ended 31st December 2025. The trading window for dealing in shares of the company by designated persons will remain closed from 1st January 2026 until 48 hours after the declaration of financial results. The Board Meeting will be preceded by an Audit Committee Meeting on the same day.</p><ul><li>Bigbloc Construction Ltd to approve Q3 &amp; period ended Dec 2025 results on Jan 20, 2026</li><li>Trading window for designated persons to remain closed from Jan 1, 2026 until 48 hours after results declaration</li><li>Board Meeting to be held on 20th Jan 2026, preceded by Audit Committee Meeting</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/958e956e-0953-40b9-9248-5b36cbc851db.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Bigbloc Construction Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAGARSYST] Sagar Systech Ltd. Reports No Activity in Re-lodgement of Transfer Requests of Physical Shares for December 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SAGAR+SYSTECH+LTD.&title=Sagar+Systech+Ltd.+Reports+No+Activity+in+Re-lodgement+of+Transfer+Requests+of+Physical+Shares+for+December+2025&newsId=e2ed438a-5577-4cdc-acae-f252212c5bd7&token=ZTJlZDQzOGEtNTU3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e2ed438a-5577-4cdc-acae-f252212c5bd7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 12:31:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sagar Systech Ltd. has released a report on the re-lodgement of transfer requests of physical shares for the period ending December 31, 2025, in accordance with SEBI regulations and circulars. The report indicates no activity in terms of received, processed, approved, or rejected transfer requests during December 2025. The company encourages shareholders to check their records and ensure compliance with the specified time frame for re-lodgement of transfer requests.</p><ul><li>Sagar Systech Ltd. releases report on re-lodgement of transfer requests of physical shares for the period ending December 31, 2025.</li><li>No activity in received, processed, approved, or rejected transfer requests during December 2025.</li><li>Report is in accordance with SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, and SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2a3ff10b-b86d-4c03-8530-4c443e43d332.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SAGAR SYSTECH LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DREDGECORP] Dredging Corporation of India&apos;s Credit Rating Reaffirmed with Stable Outlook</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DREDGING+CORPORATION+OF+INDIA+LTD.&title=Dredging+Corporation+of+India%27s+Credit+Rating+Reaffirmed+with+Stable+Outlook&newsId=e883503b-cfcb-4029-b953-d2fbb35178ed&token=ZTg4MzUwM2ItY2Zj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e883503b-cfcb-4029-b953-d2fbb35178ed</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 12:31:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Rating Action</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dredging Corporation of India Limited (DCIL) had its long term and short term bank facilities reaffirmed by Care Edge Rating with a rating of CARE BBB+ and CARE A3+ respectively. The rating is supported by DCIL&apos;s established presence in domestic and overseas dredging services, strong parentage with shareholding held by major ports, and a growing order book providing medium-term revenue visibility. However, the rating is tempered by the ageing fleet of dredgers, vulnerability to foreign exchange risk, volatility in margins due to fluctuation in fuel prices, and increased competition from domestic and global private players.</p><ul><li>DCIL&apos;s long term bank facilities reaffirmed at CARE BBB+ with stable outlook</li><li>Short term bank facilities reaffirmed at CARE A3+</li><li>Rating strength from established presence and strong parentage</li><li>Rating tempered by ageing fleet, foreign exchange risk, and competition</li><li>Growing order book provides medium-term revenue visibility</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dffc1b81-f3ae-4671-8d84-02d15d289e2c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DREDGING CORPORATION OF INDIA LTD. | Category: Rating Action</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ANDHRACEMT] Andhra Cements Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on 21st January, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ANDHRA+CEMENTS+LTD.&title=Andhra+Cements+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+21st+January%2C+2026&newsId=58d56a86-6695-4b6c-9ebe-76c17abd44f1&token=NThkNTZhODYtNjY5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58d56a86-6695-4b6c-9ebe-76c17abd44f1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 12:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Andhra Cements Ltd has announced a Board Meeting on 21st January, 2026 to consider and approve the un-audited standalone financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The trading window will remain closed 48 hours after the announcement of the financial results.</p><ul><li>Andhra Cements Ltd scheduled a Board Meeting on 21st January, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the un-audited standalone financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025</li><li>The trading window will be closed 48 hours after the financial results announcement</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ee064abb-3f3d-425f-912d-c9b1a26e5e4b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ANDHRA CEMENTS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GRAVITA] Gravita India Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results on 21st January 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GRAVITA+INDIA+LTD.&title=Gravita+India+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+on+21st+January+2026&newsId=36b216b1-2285-48be-8c2c-d0fdd86d428c&token=MzZiMjE2YjEtMjI4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">36b216b1-2285-48be-8c2c-d0fdd86d428c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 12:26:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gravita India Ltd has scheduled a Board of Directors meeting on 21st January 2026 to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The trading window for designated persons and their immediate relatives has been closed since 1st January 2026, in accordance with SEBI regulations, and will reopen after 48 hours from the declaration of the results.</p><ul><li>Gravita India Ltd to consider and approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December 2025</li><li>Board of Directors meeting scheduled on 21st January 2026</li><li>Trading window for designated persons and their immediate relatives closed since 1st January 2026</li><li>Trading window to reopen after 48 hours from the declaration of results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/82189b8f-d97a-46ed-8262-9ee2bf159857.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GRAVITA INDIA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>