<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:26:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[JUSTO] Promoter Puspamitra Das Acquires 4,000 Equity Shares of Justo Realfintech Ltd Through Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Justo+Realfintech+Ltd&title=Promoter+Puspamitra+Das+Acquires+4%2C000+Equity+Shares+of+Justo+Realfintech+Ltd+Through+Open+Market&newsId=698b72d0-7c3d-4cc7-83c7-d795427b1844&token=Njk4YjcyZDAtN2Mz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">698b72d0-7c3d-4cc7-83c7-d795427b1844</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:20:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Puspamitra Das, a promoter of Justo Realfintech Ltd, has acquired 4,000 equity shares of the company through the open market. The acquisition was made on 3rd February 2026. Before the acquisition, the promoter held 38.52% of the total share capital and voting rights. Post-acquisition, the holding has increased to 38.52%. The total equity share capital of the company remains at INR 18,79,81,420 consisting of 1,87,98,142 equity shares of Rs. 10 each.</p><ul><li>Puspamitra Das, a promoter of Justo Realfintech Ltd, has acquired 4,000 equity shares of the company.</li><li>The acquisition was made through the open market on 3rd February 2026.</li><li>Before the acquisition, the promoter held 38.52% of the total share capital and voting rights.</li><li>Post-acquisition, the holding of the promoter has increased to 38.52%.</li><li>The total equity share capital of the company remains at INR 18,79,81,420 consisting of 1,87,98,142 equity shares of Rs. 10 each.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/CC398FD3_9632_4F27_8F6C_73DC25E2008D_094258.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Justo Realfintech Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CSL] Vachi Commercial LLP Acquires 7,00,000 Equity Shares of Continental Securities Limited via Preferential Allotment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Continental+Securities+Ltd&title=Vachi+Commercial+LLP+Acquires+7%2C00%2C000+Equity+Shares+of+Continental+Securities+Limited+via+Preferential+Allotment&newsId=00bd42fb-8cda-4f9c-af75-f756ef367e16&token=MDBiZDQyZmItOGNk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00bd42fb-8cda-4f9c-af75-f756ef367e16</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vachi Commercial LLP, a Partner of Vachi Commercial LLP, has acquired 7,00,000 equity shares of Continental Securities Limited through a preferential allotment. This acquisition increases Vachi Commercial LLP&apos;s holding to 8.85% of the total share capital diluted. The equity shares have a face value of Rs. 2/- each and amount to Rs. 5,99,06,000/-. The acquisition was made on 31st January 2026.</p><ul><li>Vachi Commercial LLP acquires 7,00,000 equity shares of Continental Securities Limited.</li><li>The acquisition was made through a preferential allotment.</li><li>Vachi Commercial LLP&apos;s holding increases to 8.85% of the total share capital diluted.</li><li>The equity shares have a face value of Rs. 2/- each and amount to Rs. 5,99,06,000/-.</li><li>The acquisition was made on 31st January 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/59BF9947_A998_47C9_AF90_9434B780A8D4_094100.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Continental Securities Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AXISCADES] AXISCADES Announces Significant Wins from US Customers Post Indo-US Trade Deal</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Axiscades+Technologies+Ltd&title=AXISCADES+Announces+Significant+Wins+from+US+Customers+Post+Indo-US+Trade+Deal&newsId=1b99779e-bd99-45bb-adb1-3de8402dee72&token=MWI5OTc3OWUtYmQ5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b99779e-bd99-45bb-adb1-3de8402dee72</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:12:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>AXISCADES Technologies Limited, a chip to product company and a pioneer in Aerospace, Defence, Electronics, Semiconductor and Artificial Intelligence applications, announces new wins from its US customers division by its subsidiary Mistral Solutions. The orders, valued at approximately 13.5 crores, are with two leading US companies, one in homeland security and the other in marketing and audience engagement products. This is the first &apos;Make in India&apos; production engagement between these companies, reinforcing AXISCADES’ position as a trusted global engineering and manufacturing partner.</p><ul><li>AXISCADES announces significant wins from its US customers post the Indo-US trade deal.</li><li>The wins are with two leading US companies, one in homeland security and the other in marketing and audience engagement products.</li><li>The orders are the first &apos;Make in India&apos; production engagement between these companies.</li><li>The deals reinforce AXISCADES’ position as a trusted global engineering and manufacturing partner.</li><li>The deals enhance long-term revenue visibility and underscore AXISCADES’ ability to capitalise on the evolving US-India strategic and industrial alignment.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/70438b25-e237-4974-9886-bd08e4cdd65b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Axiscades Technologies Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MAXINDIA] Max India&apos;s Antara Senior Care &amp; Star Union Dai-ichi Life Insurance Join Hands for Senior Care Awareness in India</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Max+India+Ltd&title=Max+India%27s+Antara+Senior+Care+%26+Star+Union+Dai-ichi+Life+Insurance+Join+Hands+for+Senior+Care+Awareness+in+India&newsId=64920be8-cb52-4f6f-a684-d6b7a36c782d&token=NjQ5MjBiZTgtY2I1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">64920be8-cb52-4f6f-a684-d6b7a36c782d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:12:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Partnership</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Antara Senior Care, a fully integrated senior care ecosystem and subsidiary of Max India Ltd, has collaborated with Star Union Dai-ichi Life Insurance (SUD Life) to spread awareness about senior care and financial literacy in India. The partnership aims to launch specialized financial products for seniors, addressing the lack of awareness and access to age-care services. According to The Longitudinal Ageing Study of India 2021 report, only 28% of seniors are aware of available concessions, schemes, or benefits, and 78% live without pension cover. The Antara-SUD Life partnership intends to bridge this gap by integrating financial security with overall wellness and offering information-rich communication and webinars for SUD Life’s customers and employees.</p><ul><li>Antara Senior Care, a fully integrated senior care ecosystem, collaborates with Star Union Dai-ichi Life Insurance (SUD Life).</li><li>The partnership aims to launch specialized financial products for seniors and improve awareness about senior care services.</li><li>Only 28% of seniors are aware of available concessions, schemes, or benefits, and 78% live without pension cover according to The Longitudinal Ageing Study of India 2021 report.</li><li>Antara and SUD Life will offer digital-first, information-rich communication and webinars for SUD Life’s customers and employees.</li><li>India is experiencing a significant demographic shift, with the senior population poised to more than double by 2050.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a039704d-93a6-4d49-9b0c-ebf5cace3d2e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Max India Ltd | Category: Partnership</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AXISCADES] Axiscades&apos; Subsidiary, Mistral Solutions, Secures Contracts for Design, Development, and Production from Axon Enterprise Inc and Stratacache Inc</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Axiscades+Technologies+Ltd&title=Axiscades%27+Subsidiary%2C+Mistral+Solutions%2C+Secures+Contracts+for+Design%2C+Development%2C+and+Production+from+Axon+Enterprise+Inc+and+Stratacache+Inc&newsId=57d82e04-4071-498b-b24a-a462c2de4ae0&token=NTdkODJlMDQtNDA3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57d82e04-4071-498b-b24a-a462c2de4ae0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:10:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Axiscades Technologies Ltd announced that its subsidiary, Mistral Solutions Private Limited, has been awarded contracts for design, development, and production by Axon Enterprise Inc and Stratacache Inc. The contracts have a time period of over one year for execution, with a broad consideration of around USDA Whitten. The contracts do not involve any interest from the promoter/promoter group/group companies, and are not related party transactions. The announcement was made in compliance with the Awarding of Contracts Requirements) Regulations, 2015 and the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Axiscades&apos; subsidiary, Mistral Solutions, secures contracts from Axon Enterprise Inc and Stratacache Inc</li><li>Contracts are for design, development, and production</li><li>Time period for execution is over one year</li><li>Broad consideration is around USDA Whitten</li><li>No involvement of promoter/promoter group/group companies in the contracts</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6acc72a1-aaf1-4d38-9ebd-3b63940e9e09.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Axiscades Technologies Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KAYPOWR] Statutory Auditor M/s. R Y Kulkarni &amp; Associates Resigns from Kay Power and Paper Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KAY+POWER+AND+PAPER+LTD.&title=Statutory+Auditor+M%2Fs.+R+Y+Kulkarni+%26+Associates+Resigns+from+Kay+Power+and+Paper+Ltd&newsId=8f0537e7-aaad-4f73-bd2c-203438431137&token=OGYwNTM3ZTctYWFh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f0537e7-aaad-4f73-bd2c-203438431137</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 04:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kay Power and Paper Ltd announced the resignation of its Statutory Auditor, M/s. R Y Kulkarni &amp; Associates, due to the expiry of their Peer Review Certificate and health issues of the proprietor. The resignation will be effective from the closing business hours of February 03, 2026. The company will issue a limited review report for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025.</p><ul><li>M/s. R Y Kulkarni &amp; Associates resigns as Statutory Auditor of Kay Power and Paper Ltd</li><li>Resignation due to expiry of Peer Review Certificate and health issues</li><li>Effective from closing business hours of February 03, 2026</li><li>Company to issue limited review report for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5491f459-a8a9-438c-aea7-5dc5bcab1e2a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KAY POWER AND PAPER LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GARMNTMNTR] Global Trade Developments Boost Indian Textile and Apparel Export Industry: Garment Mantra Lifestyle Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Garment+Mantra+Lifestyle+Ltd&title=Global+Trade+Developments+Boost+Indian+Textile+and+Apparel+Export+Industry%3A+Garment+Mantra+Lifestyle+Ltd&newsId=4e03ecff-8add-4b5e-9ce9-fdcf7ce47a44&token=NGUwM2VjZmYtOGFk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4e03ecff-8add-4b5e-9ce9-fdcf7ce47a44</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 03:52:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Garment Mantra Lifestyle Ltd has announced that recent global trade developments, including the conclusion of the India—EU Free Trade Agreement and improved clarity on US tariff structures, are expected to have a positive impact on the Indian textile and apparel export industry. These developments are expected to enhance the global competitiveness of Indian textile and apparel manufacturers, improve market access, reduce tariff and non-tariff barriers, and provide greater predictability and stability for exporters. The Company, which has already achieved a significant milestone of export sales exceeding ~100 crore, is well-positioned to capitalize on these opportunities and remains committed to leveraging technology, process optimization, and prudent capital deployment to support scalable growth.</p><ul><li>India—EU Free Trade Agreement concluded</li><li>Improved clarity on US tariff structures</li><li>Enhanced global competitiveness of Indian textile and apparel manufacturers</li><li>Improved market access and reduced tariff barriers</li><li>Garment Mantra Lifestyle Ltd well-positioned to capitalize on opportunities</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9b520ccd-cccb-4058-9980-6ec781966246.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Garment Mantra Lifestyle Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ACMESOLAR] ACME Solar Appoints Rahul Kaushik as Head of Process Transformation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ACME+Solar+Holdings+Ltd&title=ACME+Solar+Appoints+Rahul+Kaushik+as+Head+of+Process+Transformation&newsId=ab0537e2-d6e9-4a45-bc1c-a604efaee319&token=YWIwNTM3ZTItZDZl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab0537e2-d6e9-4a45-bc1c-a604efaee319</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 03:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>ACME Solar Holdings Ltd (ACME Solar) has appointed Rahul Kaushik as Head of Process Transformation to strengthen the company’s focus on building robust, future-ready processes and governance frameworks. Rahul, with nearly two decades of experience, will work closely with the leadership team to drive optimization of business processes. His rich experience in internal audit, risk and process transformation, especially in the renewable energy sector, will be significant as ACME Solar continues to scale and institutionalise robust governance.</p><ul><li>ACME Solar appoints Rahul Kaushik as Head of Process Transformation</li><li>Rahul to focus on risk management, internal controls and operational excellence</li><li>Rahul brings nearly two decades of internal audit and risk advisory experience</li><li>Rahul&apos;s experience in renewable energy sector will be significant for ACME Solar&apos;s growth</li><li>Appointment reiterates ACME Solar&apos;s commitment to institutionalising strong governance</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0eed68dc-6b9f-4f13-a332-14bd5c5fbd37.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ACME Solar Holdings Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TIMETECHNO] Time Technoplast&apos;s Subsidiary, Power Build Batteries, Enters Business Collaboration with Monbat AD</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TIME+TECHNOPLAST+LTD.&title=Time+Technoplast%27s+Subsidiary%2C+Power+Build+Batteries%2C+Enters+Business+Collaboration+with+Monbat+AD&newsId=8431b357-106a-4b3f-ac1d-3770995e6365&token=ODQzMWIzNTctMTA2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8431b357-106a-4b3f-ac1d-3770995e6365</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 03:28:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Power Build Batteries Private Limited, a subsidiary of Time Technoplast Limited, has entered into a business collaboration and exclusive distribution agreement with Monbat AD, a leading European battery manufacturer. This collaboration aims to cater to the rapidly expanding requirements of Data Centres, IT infrastructure, BFSI institutions, and other mission-critical industrial applications in India. The agreement establishes a multi-year commercial collaboration, supporting the Government of India’s Make in India initiative.</p><ul><li>PowerBuild will exclusively distribute Monbat&apos;s maintenance-free, advanced Valve Regulated Lead-Acid (VRLA) stationary and reserve power battery solutions in India.</li><li>This collaboration is expected to generate local employment, develop technical support ecosystem, and enhance service network capabilities for advanced battery solutions in India.</li><li>India is witnessing a structural expansion in digital infrastructure, creating a market opportunity for advanced VRLA batteries of approximately INR 3,500-4,000 crore over the next decade.</li><li>PowerBuild gains access to Monbat’s complete portfolio of Eurobat-compliant, high-reliability batteries engineered for mission-critical environments.</li><li>This collaboration is uniquely positioned to participate in India’s next phase of digital infrastructure growth.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e3cb2175-048d-4191-a7d7-1b70e888aeef.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TIME TECHNOPLAST LTD. | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[3IINFOTECH] 3i Infotech Ltd. Files Complaint Against eMudhra Limited for Large-Scale Financial Fraud</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=3I+INFOTECH+LTD.&title=3i+Infotech+Ltd.+Files+Complaint+Against+eMudhra+Limited+for+Large-Scale+Financial+Fraud&newsId=8f6fd6ce-6f4d-424c-9c32-2f528a2a9285&token=OGY2ZmQ2Y2UtNmY0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f6fd6ce-6f4d-424c-9c32-2f528a2a9285</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 03:07:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>3i Infotech Ltd. has filed a complaint with the Additional Commissioner of Police, Economic Offence Wing, Navi Mumbai Police Commissionerate, against eMudhra Limited (originally incorporated as 3i Infotech Consumer Services Limited) for a large-scale corporate financial fraud, criminal breach of trust, cheating, dishonest misappropriation, and criminal conspiracy. The fraud is estimated to have caused a loss of over Rupees 128 crores (Rupees One Hundred Twenty-Eight crores only) plus interest and damages to the listed entity from December 2010 to January 2021. The complaint also involves two individuals, Mr. Venkatraman Srinivasan and Mr. Ravi Jagannathan. 3i Infotech Ltd. is also in the process of submitting a complaint with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI).</p><ul><li>3i Infotech Ltd. files complaint against eMudhra Limited for large-scale financial fraud</li><li>Fraud estimated to have caused a loss of over Rupees 128 crores plus interest and damages</li><li>Involvement of two individuals, Mr. Venkatraman Srinivasan and Mr. Ravi Jagannathan</li><li>Complaint filed with the Additional Commissioner of Police, Economic Offence Wing, Navi Mumbai Police Commissionerate</li><li>3i Infotech Ltd. also in process of submitting a complaint with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ca94f66b-9ab3-4269-ab82-84bdc6e4772f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: 3I INFOTECH LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>