<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:36:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[INSECTICID] Insecticides (India) Ltd Declares Interim Dividend of Rs. 2.00 per Share for FY 2025-2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INSECTICIDES+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Insecticides+%28India%29+Ltd+Declares+Interim+Dividend+of+Rs.+2.00+per+Share+for+FY+2025-2026&newsId=67a35240-f6c8-4bff-807f-09f02bd75777&token=NjdhMzUyNDAtZjZj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67a35240-f6c8-4bff-807f-09f02bd75777</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:35:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Insecticides (India) Ltd announced an interim dividend of Rs. 2.00 per equity share for the financial year 2025-2026. The record date for the dividend is February 6, 2026. The dividend will be paid within the prescribed time under law, on or after February 11, 2026. The announcement came after the company&apos;s board meeting held on January 30, 2026, where they also reviewed and approved the un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</p><ul><li>Insecticides (India) Ltd declares an interim dividend of Rs. 2.00 per equity share for FY 2025-2026.</li><li>The record date for the dividend is February 6, 2026.</li><li>The dividend will be paid within the prescribed time under law, on or after February 11, 2026.</li><li>The declaration came after the company&apos;s board meeting held on January 30, 2026.</li><li>The board also reviewed and approved the un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/535d4c58-81f1-4b67-82b5-990d1f2d499e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INSECTICIDES (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AJANTPHARM] Ajanta Pharma Reports 20% Revenue Growth &amp; 18% PAT Growth in Q3 FY 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AJANTA+PHARMA+LTD.&title=Ajanta+Pharma+Reports+20%25+Revenue+Growth+%26+18%25+PAT+Growth+in+Q3+FY+2026&newsId=3e5aff04-f1fc-4744-9ca1-a92a593b51d3&token=M2U1YWZmMDQtZjFm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e5aff04-f1fc-4744-9ca1-a92a593b51d3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Ajanta Pharma Ltd., a specialty pharmaceutical formulation company, reported its excellent performance for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations for Q3 FY 2026 stood at Rs. 1,375 cr., up 20% from Q3 FY 2025. The profit after tax for the same period was Rs. 274 cr., showing a growth of 18%. The 9M FY 2026 performance highlights include a 16% increase in revenue from operations and a 14% growth in profit after tax.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations up by 20% in Q3 FY 2026</li><li>Profit after tax up by 18% in Q3 FY 2026</li><li>16% increase in revenue from operations in 9M FY 2026</li><li>14% growth in profit after tax in 9M FY 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/62f9a571-200b-4472-bb3f-3a7a1cd649cc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AJANTA PHARMA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HEIDELBERG] HeidelbergCement India Ltd Receives Three Transfer Requests in December 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HEIDELBERGCEMENT+INDIA+LTD.&title=HeidelbergCement+India+Ltd+Receives+Three+Transfer+Requests+in+December+2025&newsId=0ef4d091-2db4-4337-97da-fadcbab6b9c1&token=MGVmNGQwOTEtMmRi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ef4d091-2db4-4337-97da-fadcbab6b9c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:35:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>HeidelbergCement India Ltd has confirmed receiving three transfer requests during the month of December 2025. This confirmation comes pursuant to the SEBI circular SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97 dated July 02, 2025, which established a special window for re-lodgement of transfer requests of physical form. The registrar and share transfer agent (RTA) of the company, M/s. Integrated Registry Management Services Private Limited, has provided this information.</p><ul><li>HeidelbergCement India Ltd received three transfer requests in December 2025.</li><li>The receipt of these requests is confirmed by M/s. Integrated Registry Management Services Private Limited, the company&apos;s RTA.</li><li>This confirmation is pursuant to the SEBI circular SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97 dated July 02, 2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/12ffa2bc-df8a-4443-af7f-d2e775e7cb52.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HEIDELBERGCEMENT INDIA LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ARCHIDPLY] Archidply Industries Ltd. Announces Q3 2025 Results with Profit for the Period from Continuing Operations at 172.64 Lakhs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ARCHIDPLY+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Archidply+Industries+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+2025+Results+with+Profit+for+the+Period+from+Continuing+Operations+at+172.64+Lakhs&newsId=8424f461-ea7c-40a8-88f9-6bc52e47e17b&token=ODQyNGY0NjEtZWE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8424f461-ea7c-40a8-88f9-6bc52e47e17b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:34:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Archidply Industries Ltd. has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company has reported a revenue from operations of 12,146.05 Lakhs and a total income of 12,160.09 Lakhs. The total expenditure stands at 14,790.69 Lakhs, resulting in a profit before exceptional items and tax of 369.41 Lakhs. The profit for the period from continuing operations is 172.64 Lakhs. The company has also reported an impact of Labour Codes, which has resulted in an increase in gratuity liability and leave liability by 138.86 Lakhs.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations at 12,146.05 Lakhs</li><li>Total income of 12,160.09 Lakhs</li><li>Profit before exceptional items and tax at 369.41 Lakhs</li><li>Profit for the period from continuing operations at 172.64 Lakhs</li><li>Impact of Labour Codes resulting in an increase in gratuity liability and leave liability by 138.86 Lakhs</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/db04969f-0587-4c53-86ad-33769c65264e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ARCHIDPLY INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INSECTICID] Insecticides (India) Ltd Declares Interim Dividend of Rs. 2.00 per Share for FY 2025-2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INSECTICIDES+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Insecticides+%28India%29+Ltd+Declares+Interim+Dividend+of+Rs.+2.00+per+Share+for+FY+2025-2026&newsId=d0cf4002-414d-4cf7-9b19-2214e32ee75f&token=ZDBjZjQwMDItNDE0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d0cf4002-414d-4cf7-9b19-2214e32ee75f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Insecticides (India) Limited approved the Un-audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company declared an interim dividend of Rs. 2.00 per equity share for financial year 2025-2026, which will be paid on or after February 11, 2026. The company has estimated that there is no incremental liability due to implications of the New Labour Codes to the standalone or consolidated financial statements.</p><ul><li>Insecticides (India) Ltd declares an interim dividend of Rs. 2.00 per equity share for FY 2025-2026</li><li>The dividend will be paid on or after February 11, 2026</li><li>The Board approved the Un-audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>The company has estimated no incremental liability due to the New Labour Codes</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/02c1d60f-cb38-457d-91a0-41e89a1cdb93.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INSECTICIDES (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NATIONALUM] National Aluminium Company Ltd Declares 2nd Interim Dividend @ Rs. 4.50 per share</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NATIONAL+ALUMINIUM+CO.LTD.&title=National+Aluminium+Company+Ltd+Declares+2nd+Interim+Dividend+%40+Rs.+4.50+per+share&newsId=427b7954-8c13-4ae7-be14-cd72fb53026a&token=NDI3Yjc5NTQtOGMx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">427b7954-8c13-4ae7-be14-cd72fb53026a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:33:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>National Aluminium Company Ltd (NALCO) has declared a 2nd interim dividend of Rs. 4.50 per share for the financial year 2025-26. The record date for payment of the dividend is 06th February, 2026. The dividend will be paid to all eligible shareholders whose names appear in the Register of Members and the beneficial owners position as downloaded by NSDL &amp; CDSL as on Record Date. The company will make the dividend payment only through electronic modes as per the SEBI regulations.</p><ul><li>NALCO declares 2nd interim dividend @ Rs. 4.50 per share for the financial year 2025-26</li><li>The record date for payment of the dividend is 06th February, 2026</li><li>Dividend payment will be made only through electronic modes</li><li>The company has fixed Friday, the 06th February, 2026 as Record Date for payment of the dividend</li><li>The payment of the dividend shall be made on or before 01.03.2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9e8909ff-a3f4-4f6f-9320-f782f17ff8f4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NATIONAL ALUMINIUM CO.LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FIBERWEB] Fiberweb India Ltd. Approves Q3 &amp; 9M Results for FY2025-26, Announces Expansion Project</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=FIBERWEB+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Fiberweb+India+Ltd.+Approves+Q3+%26+9M+Results+for+FY2025-26%2C+Announces+Expansion+Project&newsId=358844a2-0cce-43f0-b71b-e935b9d289b4&token=MzU4ODQ0YTItMGNj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">358844a2-0cce-43f0-b71b-e935b9d289b4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Fiberweb India Ltd. has approved the Unaudited Standalone Financial Results for the 3rd quarter and 9 months ended 31st December, 2025. The company is setting up a new project with a total project cost of Rs. 168 crores, for which funding has been tied up with State Bank of India who have sanctioned a term loan of Rs. 115 crores and working capital of Rs. 20 crores. The balance is being funded from equity and internal accruals. Once the expansion is complete, the top line of the company will go up from Rs. 100 crores to approximately Rs. 350 crores at 80% capacity utilization on an annualized basis, and the EBIDTA margin will go up from 16% to 30% approximately.</p><ul><li>Fiberweb India Ltd. approved the Unaudited Standalone Financial Results for Q3 and 9M ended 31st December, 2025.</li><li>The company is setting up a new project with a total project cost of Rs. 168 crores.</li><li>State Bank of India sanctioned a term loan of Rs. 115 crores and working capital of Rs. 20 crores.</li><li>Once the expansion is complete, the top line will go up from Rs. 100 crores to approximately Rs. 350 crores.</li><li>The EBIDTA margin will go up from 16% to 30% approximately.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/35700639-6b0f-42d2-a548-4c2c8c3eb0d5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: FIBERWEB (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAGAR] Sagar Diamonds Ltd Assures Timely Submission of Financial Results After Delay</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sagar+Diamonds+Ltd&title=Sagar+Diamonds+Ltd+Assures+Timely+Submission+of+Financial+Results+After+Delay&newsId=3e3ab154-31bb-4783-a2d0-391b85257035&token=M2UzYWIxNTQtMzFi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e3ab154-31bb-4783-a2d0-391b85257035</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sagar Diamonds Ltd, a company registered in Surat, Gujarat, has issued a declaration regarding the delay in filing their annual audited standalone financial results for the year ended 31st March, 2024. The delay was due to unforeseen circumstances and technical issues beyond their control. The company has assured that necessary follow-ups and corrective actions have been taken and utmost care will be taken to ensure timely submission in the future. The audit report by the statutory auditor, M/s. Manish K Ramawati And Company &amp; Co, Chartered Accounts, has been issued with an unmodified opinion and no qualifications.</p><ul><li>Sagar Diamonds Ltd delays filing of annual audited standalone financial results for the year ended 31st March, 2024</li><li>The delay was due to unforeseen circumstances and technical issues</li><li>Necessary follow-ups and corrective actions have been taken</li><li>The company assures timely submission in the future</li><li>Audit report issued with unmodified opinion and no qualifications</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/552dfe9b-56d6-441e-92eb-aedf390a400e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sagar Diamonds Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MFL] Epigral Ltd&apos;s Q3FY26 Revenue Stands at ¥ 603 Crore, Despite Temporary Marginal Pressures</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Meghmani+Finechem+Ltd&title=Epigral+Ltd%27s+Q3FY26+Revenue+Stands+at+%C2%A5+603+Crore%2C+Despite+Temporary+Marginal+Pressures&newsId=7bba144e-2b37-412c-b7df-816d78a7f99b&token=N2JiYTE0NGUtMmIz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7bba144e-2b37-412c-b7df-816d78a7f99b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Epigral Limited, a leading integrated chemical manufacturer in India, announced its financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company posted a revenue of ¥ 603 Crore for Q3FY26, a decrease from ¥ 649 Crore in Q3FY25. The Profit After Tax (PAT) stood at ¥ 39 Crore compared to ¥ 104 Crore in Q3FY25. The company&apos;s plant utilization stood at 78%, similar to the previous quarter. The EBITDA margin dropped to 17% due to lower realizations and increased raw material costs. The company is optimistic about the improving market scenario and anticipates positive outcomes from Q4FY26. Epigral&apos;s capacity expansion projects are progressing smoothly and are expected to drive growth from FY27 onwards.</p><ul><li>Q3FY26 Revenue stood at ¥ 603 Crore</li><li>Plant utilization at 78%</li><li>EBITDA margin at 17% due to drop in realizations and increase in cost of raw materials</li><li>PAT at ¥ 39 Crore</li><li>Capacity expansion projects progressing smoothly</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/79507c1d-e691-4e86-ac59-7b363ab1dcb9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Meghmani Finechem Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AMBUJACEM] Ambuja Cements Ltd Confirms No Deviations in Preferential Issue of Equity Shares for Q4 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AMBUJA+CEMENTS+LTD.&title=Ambuja+Cements+Ltd+Confirms+No+Deviations+in+Preferential+Issue+of+Equity+Shares+for+Q4+2025&newsId=ce999de2-a861-42fb-a5c5-2cc6ecbdf63d&token=Y2U5OTlkZTItYTg2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce999de2-a861-42fb-a5c5-2cc6ecbdf63d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 09:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ambuja Cements Ltd has submitted a Statement of Deviation for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025, stating that there are no deviations or variations in the use of proceeds of preferential issue of equity shares. The funds, raised in two tranches, were used for capital expenditures, de-bottlenecking, logistics, infrastructure, digitizing logistics, optimizing plants to accelerate ESG compliance, acquisitions, consolidation, working capital requirements, investment in technology and for general corporate purpose.</p><ul><li>Ambuja Cements Ltd confirms no deviations in the use of proceeds of preferential issue of equity shares for Q4 2025</li><li>Funds raised in two tranches and used for various purposes including capital expenditures, de-bottlenecking, logistics, and ESG compliance</li><li>Total funds utilized till December 31, 2025, amounted to Rs. 14895.1 crores out of Rs. 15000.046 crores raised</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e86f2fdb-0aa3-498e-af07-8dc035716930.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AMBUJA CEMENTS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>