<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:39:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ETT] Laddu Gopal Online Services Ltd. Board Meeting Postponed to 29th January, 2026: Key Discussions on Funds Raising, Share Capital Increase, and E-Voting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ETT+Ltd&title=Laddu+Gopal+Online+Services+Ltd.+Board+Meeting+Postponed+to+29th+January%2C+2026%3A+Key+Discussions+on+Funds+Raising%2C+Share+Capital+Increase%2C+and+E-Voting&newsId=af5cb8be-a94c-4025-8246-4986de21dec0&token=YWY1Y2I4YmUtYTk0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">af5cb8be-a94c-4025-8246-4986de21dec0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:37:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Laddu Gopal Online Services Ltd. (formerly ETT Limited) has informed the BSE about the postponement of their Board Meeting, originally scheduled for 27th January, 2026. The meeting will now take place on 29th January, 2026 due to the unavailability of key board members. The primary agenda of the meeting includes considering and approving the intimation for funds raising through various methods such as preferential allotment, right issue, QIP’s, ADR GDR, FCCB or any other method or combination thereof. Additionally, the board will discuss increasing the authorized share capital of the company and amending the memorandum accordingly. A postal ballot by means of E-voting will be conducted to obtain approval from the members of the company for rescinding the resolution passed in the Annual General Meeting on 22nd September 2025 and approving the increase in the authorized share capital.</p><ul><li>Postponement of Board Meeting to 29th January, 2026</li><li>Consideration of funds raising by various methods</li><li>Increase in the authorized share capital of the company</li><li>E-voting for obtaining approval of the members for rescinding and approving the increase in share capital</li><li>Trading Window closure for designated persons and their immediate relatives</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c5116613-accb-4c52-b433-056cf131cc93.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ETT Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUERYAAKNI] Sueryaa Knitwear Ltd Approves Unaudited Standalone Financial Results for Q3 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sueryaa+Knitwear+Ltd&title=Sueryaa+Knitwear+Ltd+Approves+Unaudited+Standalone+Financial+Results+for+Q3+2025&newsId=b6d6a2c2-693f-475d-aa52-d6808dba0cae&token=YjZkNmEyYzItNjkz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6d6a2c2-693f-475d-aa52-d6808dba0cae</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:35:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sueryaa Knitwear Ltd has announced the approval of its unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The board of directors convened a meeting on January 27, 2026, where they considered and took on record the financial results and the limited review report submitted by the statutory auditor. The company&apos;s revenue from operations for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, was INR 0.39 Crore, and the total income stood at the same amount. The company&apos;s total expenses for the quarter amounted to INR 0.00 Crore, resulting in a profit before exceptional items and tax of -INR 0.05 Crore. The company reported a loss for the period from continuing operations of -INR 0.05 Crore.</p><ul><li>Sueryaa Knitwear Ltd approved the unaudited standalone financial results for Q3 2025.</li><li>The board considered and took on record the limited review report submitted by the statutory auditor.</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue from operations for Q3 2025 was INR 0.39 Crore.</li><li>Total expenses for the quarter amounted to INR 0.00 Crore.</li><li>The company reported a loss for the period from continuing operations of -INR 0.05 Crore.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6f459c74-d841-4847-8121-9ecfb3aaebfb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sueryaa Knitwear Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TAJGVK] Taj Gvk Hotels &amp; Resorts Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on Feb 9, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TAJGVK+HOTELS+%26+RESORTS+LTD.&title=Taj+Gvk+Hotels+%26+Resorts+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+Feb+9%2C+2026&newsId=a1d013da-7081-4025-a21f-e3065b02eb1e&token=YTFkMDEzZGEtNzA4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a1d013da-7081-4025-a21f-e3065b02eb1e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:34:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Taj Gvk Hotels &amp; Resorts Ltd has announced a Board Meeting on February 9, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Limited Reviewed Financial Results for the 3rd Quarter and Nine months period ended 31st December, 2025. The trading window for dealing in securities of the company will remain closed till the completion of 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results.</p><ul><li>Taj Gvk Hotels &amp; Resorts Ltd to hold a Board Meeting on February 9, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Limited Reviewed Financial Results for the 3rd Quarter and Nine months period ended 31st December, 2025</li><li>The trading window for dealing in securities of the company will remain closed till the completion of 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8fe19d2a-d8e6-449a-b2d9-404ee730d7ef.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TAJGVK HOTELS & RESORTS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHARPLINE] Sharpline Broadcast Ltd Holds EGM for Conversion of Outstanding Loans, Majority Votes in Favor</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sharpline+Broadcast+Ltd&title=Sharpline+Broadcast+Ltd+Holds+EGM+for+Conversion+of+Outstanding+Loans%2C+Majority+Votes+in+Favor&newsId=39e35bcf-c921-4662-a9f1-3b31f5bddecc&token=MzllMzViY2YtYzky</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">39e35bcf-c921-4662-a9f1-3b31f5bddecc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sharpline Broadcast Ltd, a company based in New Delhi, held an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) on Thursday, 22nd January, 2026, to discuss the conversion of outstanding unsecured inter corporate loans. The meeting was conducted through Video Conferencing (VC) and Other Audio Visual Means (OAVM). The e-voting facility was provided by National Securities Depositories Limited and remained open from Monday, 19th January, 2026, to Wednesday, 21st January, 2026. The results of the remote e-voting together with e-voting conducted during the EGM are as under: SPECIAL BUSINESS: RESOLUTION NO. 1- As a Special Resolution Issue_of Equity Shares to the Creditors towards Conversion of Outstanding Unsecured Inter Corporate Loans (i) Voted in favour of the resolution: 98.2072%</p><ul><li>Sharpline Broadcast Ltd held an EGM to discuss the conversion of outstanding unsecured inter corporate loans.</li><li>The meeting was conducted through Video Conferencing (VC) and Other Audio Visual Means (OAVM).</li><li>The e-voting facility was provided by National Securities Depositories Limited.</li><li>98.2072% of the votes were cast in favor of the resolution.</li><li>The results of the voting by ballot and remote E-voting have been declared.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/450d4a3d-8358-493d-a140-faa8a568d281.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sharpline Broadcast Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ORICON] Oricon Enterprises Ltd: Appointment of New Directors and Resignation of Executive Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ORICON+ENTERPRISES+LTD.-%24&title=Oricon+Enterprises+Ltd%3A+Appointment+of+New+Directors+and+Resignation+of+Executive+Director&newsId=ef6a7aad-f391-47f5-9070-6bc391b0fae4&token=ZWY2YTdhYWQtZjM5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef6a7aad-f391-47f5-9070-6bc391b0fae4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Oricon Enterprises Ltd has announced the appointment of Mr. Ramkishore Singhi and Mr. Prashant Mantri as Additional Directors, and Mr. Bal Mukand Gaggar as Joint Managing Director-cum- Chief Financial Officer and Executive Director. The appointments are effective from February 01, 2026, for a term of five years. The company also accepted the resignation of Mr. Balkishan Udairam Toshniwal as Executive Director, with effect from February 01, 2026. Mr. Toshniwal will also cease to be a member of the Audit Committee, Stakeholders Relationship Committee, and Executive Committee.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Ramkishore Singhi as Additional Director (Independent)</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Bal Mukand Gaggar as Joint Managing Director-cum- Chief Financial Officer and Executive Director</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Prashant Mantri as Additional Director and Executive Director</li><li>Resignation of Mr. Balkishan Udairam Toshniwal as Executive Director</li><li>Mr. Toshniwal to cease membership in Audit Committee, Stakeholders Relationship Committee, and Executive Committee</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/58267aa1-67ff-4f4f-ada0-1164cae925dd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ORICON ENTERPRISES LTD.-$ | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KOVAI] Kovai Medical Center &amp; Hospital Ltd Receives Show Cause Notice from GST and Central Excise</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KOVAI+MEDICAL+CENTER+%26+HOSPITAL+LTD.&title=Kovai+Medical+Center+%26+Hospital+Ltd+Receives+Show+Cause+Notice+from+GST+and+Central+Excise&newsId=a4b4bbed-9742-4d5e-aeb4-ab5d6c08d3c8&token=YTRiNGJiZWQtOTc0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a4b4bbed-9742-4d5e-aeb4-ab5d6c08d3c8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:32:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kovai Medical Center &amp; Hospital Ltd, a healthcare and education services provider, has received a Show Cause Notice from the Office of the Assistant Commissioner, GST and Central Excise, Coimbatore. The notice is in relation to contravention of provisions of Sections 7, 9(1) of the CGST Act, 2017 and rules made thereunder. The company is liable for demand under Section 73 of the CGST Act, 2017 along with appropriate interest and penalty. The notice pertains to non-payment of GST under RCM on rent a cab/taxi service, room rent above 5000, water charges collected, wrong availment of ITC on blocked credits under Section 17(5) of CGST Act, 2017, non-payment of interest on belated payment of tax in GSTR-3B, and non-payment of GST on charges collected in the name of UK Visa Package. The company has paid tax with interest in respect of Paras 1 to 6, but has not paid tax with interest in respect of Para 7.</p><ul><li>Show Cause Notice received from GST and Central Excise</li><li>Contravention of provisions of Sections 7, 9(1) of the CGST Act, 2017</li><li>Liability for demand under Section 73 of the CGST Act, 2017</li><li>Non-payment of GST under RCM on rent a cab/taxi service, room rent above 5000, water charges collected, and UK Visa Package</li><li>Non-payment of interest on belated payment of tax in GSTR-3B</li><li>Wrong availment of ITC on blocked credits under Section 17(5) of CGST Act, 2017</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/18882f1c-745e-46b6-868f-175d2f603c76.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KOVAI MEDICAL CENTER & HOSPITAL LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TCI] Transport Corporation of India Ltd Subsidiary Acquired by TCI Express Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TRANSPORT+CORPORATION+OF+INDIA+LTD.&title=Transport+Corporation+of+India+Ltd+Subsidiary+Acquired+by+TCI+Express+Limited&newsId=65c6c3c2-484e-4912-82a2-b49d49842d95&token=NjVjNmMzYzItNDg0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65c6c3c2-484e-4912-82a2-b49d49842d95</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Transport Corporation of India Ltd has announced the sale of 100% equity shares of its stepdown wholly owned subsidiary, TCI Global (Singapore) Pte. Ltd., to TCI Express Pte. Ltd., a subsidiary of TCI Express Limited. The transaction was executed through a Share Purchase Agreement dated January 26, 2026. This has resulted in TCI Global (Singapore) Pte. Ltd. becoming a step-down wholly owned subsidiary of TCI Express Limited.</p><ul><li>Transport Corporation of India Ltd has sold 100% equity shares of its stepdown wholly owned subsidiary, TCI Global (Singapore) Pte. Ltd., to TCI Express Pte. Ltd., a subsidiary of TCI Express Limited.</li><li>The transaction was executed through a Share Purchase Agreement dated January 26, 2026.</li><li>TCI Global (Singapore) Pte. Ltd. has ceased to be a step-down wholly owned subsidiary of Transport Corporation of India Limited and has become a step-down wholly owned subsidiary of TCI Express Limited.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0b3feed4-828c-4feb-9a3e-25bf6bb60612.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TRANSPORT CORPORATION OF INDIA LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RRECL] Vinod Dugar&apos;s Share-holding in RDB Real Estate Constructions Ltd Decreases to 60.67%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RDB+Real+Estate+Constructions+Ltd&title=Vinod+Dugar%27s+Share-holding+in+RDB+Real+Estate+Constructions+Ltd+Decreases+to+60.67%25&newsId=fafe4708-fefc-4552-9f3f-56cfd075fec5&token=ZmFmZTQ3MDgtZmVm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fafe4708-fefc-4552-9f3f-56cfd075fec5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>RDB Real Estate Constructions Ltd has received a disclosure under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011 from Vinod Dugar &amp; PACs. Due to the allotment dated 22.01.2026, Vinod Dugar&apos;s share-holding percentage has decreased to 60.67% upon conversion of 27,75,000 share warrants into Equity Shares of the company. The details of the acquisition and the company&apos;s share capital before and after the acquisition are provided in the disclosure.</p><ul><li>Vinod Dugar&apos;s share-holding in RDB Real Estate Constructions Ltd has decreased to 60.67%</li><li>Decrease due to the conversion of 27,75,000 share warrants into Equity Shares</li><li>The acquisition was made on 22.01.2026</li><li>RDB Real Estate Constructions Ltd equity share capital has increased to Rs. 20,05,84,000/-</li><li>Total diluted share/voting capital of the TC after the acquisition is Rs. 35,11,34,000</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/071C850A_BA8D_4FAC_999F_A5B01E27B727_175038.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RDB Real Estate Constructions Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ABCAPITAL] Aditya Birla Capital Ltd Allots Non-Convertible Debentures Worth Rs. 325 Crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Aditya+Birla+Capital+Ltd&title=Aditya+Birla+Capital+Ltd+Allots+Non-Convertible+Debentures+Worth+Rs.+325+Crore&newsId=acd5d57f-13b4-4ebf-81e9-b1ecc03f7845&token=YWNkNWQ1N2YtMTNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">acd5d57f-13b4-4ebf-81e9-b1ecc03f7845</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Aditya Birla Capital Limited has allotted 32,500 Unsecured, Rated, Listed, Taxable, Redeemable Non-Convertible Subordinate Debentures (&apos;NCDs&apos;) worth Rs. 325 Crore on a private placement basis to identified investors. The NCDs have a face value of Rs. 1,00,000 per Debenture and will mature in 3,650 days from the date of allotment, which is January 27, 2026. The coupon rate for these NCDs is 8.0300% per annum, with semi-annual payments starting from May 6, 2026, and the final payment, including the principal, on May 4, 2035.</p><ul><li>Aditya Birla Capital Ltd has allotted Non-Convertible Debentures worth Rs. 325 Crore.</li><li>32,500 Unsecured, Rated, Listed, Taxable, Redeemable Non-Convertible Subordinate Debentures (&apos;NCDs&apos;) have been allotted.</li><li>The face value of each Debenture is Rs. 1,00,000 and the coupon rate is 8.0300% per annum.</li><li>The NCDs will mature in 3,650 days from the date of allotment, i.e., January 27, 2026.</li><li>Semi-annual payments will start from May 6, 2026, with the final payment, including the principal, on May 4, 2035.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2739463c-e2c1-45aa-bf3e-3b77f9182cb3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Aditya Birla Capital Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PANACHE] Panabyte Technologies Receives Work Order from Mahindra &amp; Mahindra for Face Recognition Devices Worth Rs. 11,62,742.5</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Panache+Innovations+Ltd&title=Panabyte+Technologies+Receives+Work+Order+from+Mahindra+%26+Mahindra+for+Face+Recognition+Devices+Worth+Rs.+11%2C62%2C742.5&newsId=bceaa760-24e8-4988-a7ee-d85eda3bf47c&token=YmNlYWE3NjAtMjRl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bceaa760-24e8-4988-a7ee-d85eda3bf47c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 12:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Panabyte Technologies Ltd has announced that it has received a work order from Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Limited for the Supply, Installation, Testing and Commissioning (SITC) of Face recognition devices for Access Control and Time Attendance System. The order is worth Rs. 11,62,742.5 (Rupees Eleven lakh sixty-two thousand seven hundred forty-two and fifty paise only) and will be executed within a one-month period.</p><ul><li>Work order received from Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Limited for SITC of face recognition devices.</li><li>Order worth Rs. 11,62,742.5 including taxes.</li><li>To be executed within a one-month period.</li><li>Order from a renowned domestic entity.</li><li>Deal falls under the Supply, Installation, Testing and Commissioning (SITC) category.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e70871f1-fc2a-4276-9efc-1045d11f689e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Panache Innovations Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>