<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:33:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[POLYCHMP] Polymechplast Machines Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=POLYMECHPLAST+MACHINES+LTD.&title=Polymechplast+Machines+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025&newsId=859e4ad6-c07e-4397-8c09-08ee6be25cf8&token=ODU5ZTRhZDYtYzA3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">859e4ad6-c07e-4397-8c09-08ee6be25cf8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:33:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Polymechplast Machines Ltd, a manufacturer of plastic processing machines, has reported its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The results were approved by the Board of Directors at their meeting on 28th January, 2026. The company&apos;s activities relate to only one segment and the figures for the corresponding previous year/periods have been regrouped/reclassified to confirm to the figures represented in the current year/period, following the consolidation of 29 labor laws into four comprehensive Labour Codes by the Government of India. The review report by CNK &amp; Associates LLP, the independent auditor, indicates that the financial results are free of material misstatement.</p><ul><li>Polymechplast Machines Ltd reports its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December, 2025.</li><li>The results were approved by the Board of Directors at their meeting on 28th January, 2026.</li><li>The company&apos;s activities relate to only one segment: manufacturing of plastic processing machines.</li><li>The Government of India has consolidated 29 labor laws into four comprehensive Labour Codes, which became effective from 21st April, 2021.</li><li>CNK &amp; Associates LLP, the independent auditor, has issued a review report indicating that the financial results are free of material misstatement.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bb30e7e7-a791-4938-bc18-cc11b47cc049.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: POLYMECHPLAST MACHINES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TCPLPACK] TCPL Packaging Ltd to Approve Q3 and Q9 Results on Feb 9, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TCPL+PACKAGING+LTD.-%24&title=TCPL+Packaging+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Q9+Results+on+Feb+9%2C+2026&newsId=5c360b78-5c50-4745-8342-8cdb1b14c63c&token=NWMzNjBiNzgtNWM1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c360b78-5c50-4745-8342-8cdb1b14c63c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>TCPL Packaging Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 9, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results (standalone and consolidated) for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window will be closed from January 1, 2026, and will open 48 hours after the declaration of the unaudited financial results. This decision is in line with the company&apos;s code of conduct for prevention of Insider Trading in Securities.</p><ul><li>TCPL Packaging Ltd to consider and approve Q3 and Q9 results on Feb 9, 2026</li><li>The trading window will be closed from January 1, 2026, and will open 48 hours after the declaration of the results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4de9aeb0-879c-4995-bc9a-286438481503.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TCPL PACKAGING LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SBILIFE] SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd Reports Q3 2025 Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SBI+Life+Insurance+Company+Ltd&title=SBI+Life+Insurance+Company+Ltd+Reports+Q3+2025+Financial+Results&newsId=1896bdcf-b14e-4396-ac81-8f48ade7fba6&token=MTg5NmJkY2YtYjE0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1896bdcf-b14e-4396-ac81-8f48ade7fba6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd has announced its financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s Board of Directors approved the Audited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The gross premium income for the quarter is INR 7,91,934 Lakhs, and the net premium income is INR 30,24,532 Lakhs. The company&apos;s investment income stands at INR 15,53,101 Lakhs.</p><ul><li>SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd reported a gross premium income of INR 7,91,934 Lakhs for Q3 2025.</li><li>The net premium income for the quarter is INR 30,24,532 Lakhs.</li><li>The company&apos;s investment income stands at INR 15,53,101 Lakhs for Q3 2025.</li><li>The Board of Directors approved the Audited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The trading window to deal in securities of the Company will be re-opened from Saturday, January 31, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8b917eda-1673-4c3e-bce9-9110b2f2c52e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SBI Life Insurance Company Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAVERA] Savera Industries Ltd to Consider and Approve Unaudited Financial Results on Feb 12, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SAVERA+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Savera+Industries+Ltd+to+Consider+and+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+on+Feb+12%2C+2026&newsId=ed586304-9c83-4ebe-ae94-a5bc51d9b546&token=ZWQ1ODYzMDQtOWM4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed586304-9c83-4ebe-ae94-a5bc51d9b546</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Savera Industries Ltd has announced that a meeting of the Board of Directors will be held on February 12, 2026. The agenda includes the consideration and approval of the unaudited financial results for the period ending December 31, 2025. This is in accordance with Regulation 29 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Savera Industries Ltd board meeting scheduled on February 12, 2026</li><li>Meeting to consider and approve unaudited financial results for the period ending December 31, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/35363b36-e3b4-4827-9216-c2b74e3b8e34.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SAVERA INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VINCOFE] Vintage Coffee and Beverages Ltd: Approval of Un-Audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vintage+Coffee+And+Beverages+Ltd&title=Vintage+Coffee+and+Beverages+Ltd%3A+Approval+of+Un-Audited+Standalone+and+Consolidated+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=7135a476-d760-4df1-a011-ed3220af9503&token=NzEzNWE0NzYtZDc2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7135a476-d760-4df1-a011-ed3220af9503</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:29:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vintage Coffee and Beverages Limited held a Board meeting on January 28, 2026, where they approved the Un-Audited Standalone and Consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company operates in the Manufacturing and Export of Instant Coffee and Instant Chicory Products segment. The financial results have been prepared in accordance with the Ind AS and reviewed by the Audit Committee.</p><ul><li>Approval of Un-Audited Standalone and Consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors</li><li>Prepared in accordance with the Ind AS</li><li>Vintage Coffee and Beverages Limited now has two Material Subsidiaries: Vintage Coffee Private Limited and Delecto Foods Private Limited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5291f312-0a38-4219-9abb-d382b72b5462.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vintage Coffee And Beverages Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RAMCOIND] Ramco Industries Ltd Announces Trading Window Closure and Q3 Results for FY2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RAMCO+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Ramco+Industries+Ltd+Announces+Trading+Window+Closure+and+Q3+Results+for+FY2025-26&newsId=5d5e30f0-44f0-4f4b-9211-ac9eb6e921dd&token=NWQ1ZTMwZjAtNDRm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d5e30f0-44f0-4f4b-9211-ac9eb6e921dd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:29:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ramco Industries Ltd has announced that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled to consider the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. In accordance with the company&apos;s code of conduct, the trading window for dealing in the securities of the company will be closed for the company&apos;s directors and other designated persons (including their immediate relatives) till 13th February 2026.</p><ul><li>Ramco Industries Ltd to consider unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December 2025.</li><li>Trading window closure for company&apos;s directors and designated persons from 11th February to 13th February 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b089a98c-3c81-41de-936d-1a51fb875958.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RAMCO INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HARRMALAYA] Harrisons Malayalam Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results for FY2025-26 on Feb 9, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HARRISONS+MALAYALAM+LTD.&title=Harrisons+Malayalam+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+FY2025-26+on+Feb+9%2C+2026&newsId=499bc3f5-5085-4528-a603-19680acef0a4&token=NDk5YmMzZjUtNTA4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">499bc3f5-5085-4528-a603-19680acef0a4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Harrisons Malayalam Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 9, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window will remain closed until 48 hours after the declaration of results and will reopen on February 12, 2026, unless communicated otherwise.</p><ul><li>Harrisons Malayalam Ltd to consider and approve unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>Trading window to remain closed till 48 hours after the declaration of results.</li><li>Trading window to reopen on February 12, 2026, unless communicated otherwise.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b58d89b2-6463-47c3-8d85-c22901a96616.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HARRISONS MALAYALAM LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AMIORG] Acutaas Chemicals Ltd Approves Q3 &amp; Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ami+Organics+Ltd&title=Acutaas+Chemicals+Ltd+Approves+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=47f91484-594d-4df1-8f10-9fb54cc3b5bd&token=NDdmOTE0ODQtNTk0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47f91484-594d-4df1-8f10-9fb54cc3b5bd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:29:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Acutaas Chemicals Ltd, at their meeting on January 28, 2026, considered and approved the Unaudited Standalone &amp; Consolidated Financial Results for the third quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The Audit Committee reviewed and recommended these results, and the Limited Review Report was issued by the Statutory Auditors of the Company, M/s Maheshwari &amp; Co., Chartered Accountants.</p><ul><li>Acutaas Chemicals Ltd has approved the Unaudited Standalone &amp; Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 and nine months of 2025.</li><li>The Audit Committee has reviewed and recommended the financial results.</li><li>The Limited Review Report was issued by the Statutory Auditors, M/s Maheshwari &amp; Co., Chartered Accountants.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/84c506ea-c5b6-4b1f-bfa2-03ac9bdeabcb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ami Organics Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PRINCEPIPE] Prince Pipes And Fittings Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025 on February 10, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Prince+Pipes+and+Fittings+Ltd&title=Prince+Pipes+And+Fittings+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025+on+February+10%2C+2026&newsId=0326b946-102c-421e-baf8-f51ba761ba49&token=MDMyNmI5NDYtMTAy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0326b946-102c-421e-baf8-f51ba761ba49</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Prince Pipes And Fittings Ltd has informed the BSE that their Board of Directors will meet on February 10, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will also take on record the Limited Review Report of the Auditors. The trading window for dealing in securities of the Company will be closed from January 01, 2026, to February 12, 2026 (both days inclusive) under the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Prince Pipes And Fittings Ltd to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>The meeting will take on record the Limited Review Report of the Auditors</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities of the Company will be closed from January 01, 2026, to February 12, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2e75d502-3cf6-457a-8e03-50fe7d60c630.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Prince Pipes and Fittings Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CSBBANK] CSB Bank Reports 21% YoY Growth in Total Deposits in Q3 FY26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CSB+Bank+Ltd&title=CSB+Bank+Reports+21%25+YoY+Growth+in+Total+Deposits+in+Q3+FY26&newsId=b39618b8-58ee-4f01-9837-7464ddb123f4&token=YjM5NjE4YjgtNThl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b39618b8-58ee-4f01-9837-7464ddb123f4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 09:28:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>CSB Bank Ltd, one of the oldest private sector banks in India, reported a 21% year-over-year (YoY) growth in total deposits for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The bank&apos;s total deposits grew from INR 33,407 crore as on 31.12.2024 to INR 40,460 crore as on 31.12.2025. The bank&apos;s net interest income (NII) also increased by 21% YoY to INR 453 crore for Q3 FY26. The bank&apos;s asset quality is within the guided range, but the elevated level of asset quality parameters will be a key monitorable going forward.</p><ul><li>Total Deposits grew by 21% YoY from INR 33,407 crore as on 31.12.2024 to INR 40,460 crore as on 31.12.2025.</li><li>Net Interest Income (NII) up by 21% YoY from INR 375 crore for Q3 FY25 to INR 453 crore for Q3 FY26.</li><li>Cost Income Ratio improved to 60% for Q3 FY26 compared to 63% for Q3 FY25.</li><li>Operating Profit up by 32% YoY from INR 221 crore for Q3 FY25 to INR 292 crore for Q3 FY26.</li><li>Profit after Tax (PAT) stood at INR 153 crore for Q3 FY26 as against INR 152 crore for Q3 FY25.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/01573bcc-937a-49fc-8d06-08ea9b5a148a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CSB Bank Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>