<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:36:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ECLERX] eClerx Services Ltd Completes Buy Back of 625,000 Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ECLERX+SERVICES+LTD.&title=eClerx+Services+Ltd+Completes+Buy+Back+of+625%2C000+Equity+Shares&newsId=d672d5c9-aa9b-447d-a3ee-870a9e1464ce&token=ZDY3MmQ1YzktYWE5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d672d5c9-aa9b-447d-a3ee-870a9e1464ce</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:34:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Buyback</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>eClerx Services Ltd has completed the buy back of 625,000 equity shares of the face value of Rs. 10/- each through the tender offer route. The buy back was conducted at a price of Rs. 4,800/- per Equity Share. The company has extinguished these shares, leading to a change in the capital structure and shareholding pattern.</p><ul><li>eClerx Services Ltd has bought back 625,000 equity shares at a price of Rs. 4,800/- per share.</li><li>The buy back was conducted through the tender offer route.</li><li>The company has extinguished the bought back shares, leading to a change in the capital structure.</li><li>The shareholding pattern of the company has also changed post the buy back.</li><li>The buy back was conducted in compliance with the Companies Act, 2013, SEBI Buy Back Regulations, and other applicable provisions.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c0118784-9063-4637-bd71-3450f6f08781.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ECLERX SERVICES LTD. | Category: Buyback</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DMART] Avenue Supermarts Ltd Allots Unsecured Commercial Paper Worth Rs. 100 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Avenue+Supermarts+Ltd&title=Avenue+Supermarts+Ltd+Allots+Unsecured+Commercial+Paper+Worth+Rs.+100+Crores&newsId=26b3da6b-7a35-4682-aae7-2dafc9603692&token=MjZiM2RhNmItN2Ez</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26b3da6b-7a35-4682-aae7-2dafc9603692</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Avenue Supermarts Ltd, the company behind the popular retail chain D-Mart, has allotted Commercial Paper (CP) worth Rs. 100 crores. The CP, which is unsecured, has a tenure of 80 days, with the date of allotment being 9th January, 2026 and the date of maturity being 30th March, 2026. The coupon/interest offered is 6.00%, which will be paid at maturity. The CP is proposed to be listed on the BSE Limited.</p><ul><li>Avenue Supermarts Ltd allots Commercial Paper worth Rs. 100 crores</li><li>The CP is unsecured</li><li>The tenure of the CP is 80 days</li><li>The coupon/interest offered is 6.00%</li><li>The CP is proposed to be listed on the BSE Limited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b185e1af-9136-45d6-be1e-1ed232c6434a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Avenue Supermarts Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EMMVEE] Emmvee Photovoltaic Power Ltd to Approve Q4 2025 Financial Results on Jan 15, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Emmvee+Photovoltaic+Power+Ltd&title=Emmvee+Photovoltaic+Power+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+2025+Financial+Results+on+Jan+15%2C+2026&newsId=ded19ff3-2b44-4be0-90a8-397fa7a0c800&token=ZGVkMTlmZjMtMmI0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ded19ff3-2b44-4be0-90a8-397fa7a0c800</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Emmvee Photovoltaic Power Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 15, 2026, to consider and approve the standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the company will remain closed until 48 hours after the results are intimated to the stock exchanges.</p><ul><li>Emmvee Photovoltaic Power Ltd to consider and approve Q4 2025 financial results</li><li>Board meeting scheduled for January 15, 2026</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities to remain closed until 48 hours after results are intimated</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/81fcac06-d50d-4f6c-ab26-79af0f986df7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Emmvee Photovoltaic Power Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VEERHEALTH] Veerhealth Care Ltd. Secures Order from India&apos;s Leading FMCG Company for Face Care Products Manufacturing</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Veerhealth+Care+Limited&title=Veerhealth+Care+Ltd.+Secures+Order+from+India%27s+Leading+FMCG+Company+for+Face+Care+Products+Manufacturing&newsId=9b85fe0a-0e86-4d23-8c5e-0dd359b5dff9&token=OWI4NWZlMGEtMGU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b85fe0a-0e86-4d23-8c5e-0dd359b5dff9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Veerhealth Care Ltd. has announced receiving an order from one of India&apos;s leading FMCG companies for manufacturing and supplying their product line under the private label category. The product falls under the face care range category and is for one of India&apos;s leading consumer supply companies. This new order is expected to significantly contribute to the company&apos;s growth in turnover.</p><ul><li>Order from a leading FMCG company in India</li><li>Manufacturing and supplying face care products</li><li>Private label category order</li><li>Significant growth in turnover expected</li><li>Order execution within 30 days</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9d82d1b5-6e58-42fe-bca7-7a8d7e15c15b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Veerhealth Care Limited | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GGENG] G G Engineering Ltd Announces Q3 Results with Board Meeting Approval</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=G+G+Engineering+Ltd&title=G+G+Engineering+Ltd+Announces+Q3+Results+with+Board+Meeting+Approval&newsId=1afc7351-5513-4c05-85fc-397c97205b9f&token=MWFmYzczNTEtNTUx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1afc7351-5513-4c05-85fc-397c97205b9f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:22:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>G G Engineering Ltd announced the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December, 2025. The announcement was made during a Board Meeting held on 9th January, 2026. The results were reviewed by the independent auditor A K Bhargav &amp; Co. and found to be in compliance with the applicable Ind AS 34 and other recognized accounting practices.</p><ul><li>Unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended on 31st December, 2025 approved by the Board of Directors.</li><li>Results reviewed by the independent auditor A K Bhargav &amp; Co.</li><li>Compliance with applicable Ind AS 34 and other recognized accounting practices confirmed.</li><li>Board Meeting held on 9th January, 2026 to discuss and approve the results.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b36b39a5-7c17-4d47-b697-cc74ce859ca8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: G G Engineering Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GGENG] G G Engineering Ltd Announces Q3 Results with Board Approval</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=G+G+Engineering+Ltd&title=G+G+Engineering+Ltd+Announces+Q3+Results+with+Board+Approval&newsId=e25f25b8-a892-447d-817e-1d8eef5b78fa&token=ZTI1ZjI1YjgtYTg5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e25f25b8-a892-447d-817e-1d8eef5b78fa</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:22:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>G G Engineering Ltd announced the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The announcement was made during a Board Meeting held on 9th January, 2026. The results were approved by the Board and were submitted in compliance with Regulation 33 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December, 2025 approved by the Board of Directors.</li><li>The results were submitted in compliance with Regulation 33 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li><li>The Board Meeting was held on 9th January, 2026.</li><li>The review of the financial results was conducted by A K BHARGAV &amp; CO., Chartered Accountants.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d0cbfdcd-9c0d-46b4-ba28-9a0935935767.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: G G Engineering Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MASTEK] Mastek Ltd to Announce Q3FY26 Results on January 20, 2026; Trading Window Closed</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MASTEK+LTD.&title=Mastek+Ltd+to+Announce+Q3FY26+Results+on+January+20%2C+2026%3B+Trading+Window+Closed&newsId=00f0f0ad-9e4a-421d-8e21-ccf839ccbdc2&token=MDBmMGYwYWQtOWU0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00f0f0ad-9e4a-421d-8e21-ccf839ccbdc2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mastek Ltd has informed BSE that the meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on January 20, 2026, to consider and approve the Intimation of Board Meeting to consider the Company for the Third quarter and nine months period ended December 31, 2025. The trading window of the Company has been closed since January 01, 2026, and will remain closed till January 23, 2026. The Company will hold an Earnings Conference Call on January 21, 2026, for investors/analysts to discuss the financial results and business outlook.</p><ul><li>Mastek Ltd to announce Q3FY26 results on January 20, 2026</li><li>Trading window closed from January 01, 2026, to January 23, 2026</li><li>Earnings Conference Call scheduled on January 21, 2026, for investors/analysts</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f115579f-eb91-4cc3-8aa4-1771476ff90e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MASTEK LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[YUG] Mayadevi Darji Acquires 0.06% Stake in Yug Decor Ltd via Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Yug+Decor+Ltd&title=Mayadevi+Darji+Acquires+0.06%25+Stake+in+Yug+Decor+Ltd+via+Open+Market&newsId=93f5eabc-725c-4a92-b72d-24a4ca51bf1e&token=OTNmNWVhYmMtNzI1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93f5eabc-725c-4a92-b72d-24a4ca51bf1e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:21:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mayadevi Laxminarayan Darji, also known as Mayadevi Darji, has purchased 6900 shares of Yug Decor Ltd, representing 0.06% of the total issued and paid-up equity share capital of the company. The acquisition took place on the Bombay Stock Exchange (SME Platform) on 8th and 9th January 2026. This acquisition makes Darji an immediate relative employee of Yug Decor Ltd. The total equity share capital of the company stands at Rs. 10,78,92,690 (1,07,89,269 shares of Rs. 10 each) before and after the acquisition.</p><ul><li>Mayadevi Darji acquires 0.06% stake in Yug Decor Ltd</li><li>Acquisition of 6900 shares through open market</li><li>Transaction took place on the Bombay Stock Exchange (SME Platform)</li><li>Darji becomes an immediate relative employee of Yug Decor Ltd</li><li>Total equity share capital remains unchanged at Rs. 10,78,92,690</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7D6A829F_6838_44EC_A447_732727E8F3EF_174051.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Yug Decor Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AADHARHFC] Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd Reports Asset Liability Management Statements as of December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Aadhar+Housing+Finance+Ltd&title=Aadhar+Housing+Finance+Ltd+Reports+Asset+Liability+Management+Statements+as+of+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=0eb380d4-9280-4866-9346-176c223bab76&token=MGViMzgwZDQtOTI4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0eb380d4-9280-4866-9346-176c223bab76</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:21:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd. has released its Asset Liability Management (ALM) statements as of December 31, 2025. The statements disclose various financial aspects, including outflows, returns, and short-term dynamic liquidity. The company&apos;s total outflows stand at 10451.19, with a significant increase in loans and advances. The statements also show a net increase in investments, borrowings from various sources, and market lending. The short-term dynamic liquidity is calculated for different periods, with the 15 days to 30/31 days period showing the highest liquidity of 576447.6.</p><ul><li>Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd. releases ALM statements as of December 31, 2025</li><li>Total outflows stand at 10451.19</li><li>Significant increase in loans and advances</li><li>Net increase in investments, borrowings, and market lending</li><li>Short-term dynamic liquidity calculated for different periods</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/14b19bf9-a824-43a5-b325-315ab7787f5b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HITTCO] Hittco Tools Ltd Postpones Board Meeting to 19th January, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HITTCO+TOOLS+LTD.&title=Hittco+Tools+Ltd+Postpones+Board+Meeting+to+19th+January%2C+2026&newsId=49b7ddcc-fedc-41f1-bba0-75ce6343e2c2&token=NDliN2RkY2MtZmVk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">49b7ddcc-fedc-41f1-bba0-75ce6343e2c2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hittco Tools Ltd, a company with CIN L28939KA1995PLC0O16888, has postponed its board meeting initially scheduled for 9th January, 2026. The meeting will now take place on 19th January, 2026. The agenda includes consideration and approval of preferential allotment of shares, noting the valuation report from a registered valuer, approving forfeiture of shares, and any other items with the permission of the chair.</p><ul><li>Hittco Tools Ltd postpones board meeting to 19th January, 2026</li><li>Meeting was originally scheduled for 9th January, 2026</li><li>Agenda includes preferential allotment of shares, valuation report, and forfeiture of shares</li><li>Company has CIN L28939KA1995PLC0O16888</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b1b07791-d3b4-475b-ba7f-5cf74b966db7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HITTCO TOOLS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>