<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:59:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SMLISUZU] SML Mahindra Ltd Reports January 2026 Production, Sales, and Export Figures</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SML+ISUZU+LIMITED&title=SML+Mahindra+Ltd+Reports+January+2026+Production%2C+Sales%2C+and+Export+Figures&newsId=de6cc6af-9ca4-4158-b396-1f01ec623a25&token=ZGU2Y2M2YWYtOWNh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de6cc6af-9ca4-4158-b396-1f01ec623a25</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 04:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>SML Mahindra Ltd has released its production, sales, and export figures for January 2026. The company produced 4597 vehicles in January 2026 compared to 1681 vehicles in January 2025, marking a significant increase. In terms of sales, 925 vehicles were sold in January 2026, up from 1220 vehicles in January 2025. Export figures also saw a change, with 100 vehicles exported in January 2026 compared to 117 vehicles in January 2025. These figures are requested to be taken on record.</p><ul><li>Production increased from 1681 vehicles in Jan&apos;25 to 4597 vehicles in Jan&apos;26</li><li>Sales decreased from 1220 vehicles in Jan&apos;25 to 925 vehicles in Jan&apos;26</li><li>Export figures decreased from 117 vehicles in Jan&apos;25 to 100 vehicles in Jan&apos;26</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0ce9ef57-1be3-4037-ab79-45eb9fa405f6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SML ISUZU LIMITED | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LWSKNIT] LWS Knitwear Ltd to Consider and Approve Q4 Results on Feb 13, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LWS+KNITWEAR+LTD.&title=LWS+Knitwear+Ltd+to+Consider+and+Approve+Q4+Results+on+Feb+13%2C+2026&newsId=d66fc72c-6b93-4ef2-8b9e-9a1625b3fc50&token=ZDY2ZmM3MmMtNmI5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d66fc72c-6b93-4ef2-8b9e-9a1625b3fc50</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>LWS Knitwear Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 13, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter ended 31.12.2025. The meeting will also consider the Limited Review Report on Un-Audited Financial Results by the Statutory Auditor. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the company will remain closed for all insiders from January 1, 2026, till the end of 48 hours after the declaration of financial results for the Quarter Ended 31%t December, 2025.</p><ul><li>LWS Knitwear Ltd to consider and approve Q4 results on Feb 13, 2026</li><li>Un-Audited financial results for the quarter ended 31.12.2025 will be considered</li><li>Limited Review Report on Un-Audited Financial Results by the Statutory Auditor will be taken on record</li><li>Trading Window for dealing in the securities of the Company will remain closed for all insiders from Jan 1, 2026</li><li>Trading Window to open 48 hours after the declaration of financial results for the Quarter Ended 31%t December, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9bf6f01a-5c73-4705-a44d-7acda9e54c78.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LWS KNITWEAR LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PACEDIGITK] Pace Digitek Ltd Announces Q3 2025 Financial Results with 670.80 Profit and 2,333.77 Total Comprehensive Income</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Pace+Digitek+Ltd&title=Pace+Digitek+Ltd+Announces+Q3+2025+Financial+Results+with+670.80+Profit+and+2%2C333.77+Total+Comprehensive+Income&newsId=69a5988c-645d-4ab6-8a70-9942773e2eb8&token=NjlhNTk4OGMtNjQ1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69a5988c-645d-4ab6-8a70-9942773e2eb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pace Digitek Ltd, formerly known as Pace Digitek Private Limited and Pace Digitek Infra Private Limited, has announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 12,538.38 million, with a total income of 14,547.51 million. The profit before tax for the period is 5,293.32 million, and the profit after tax is 670.80 million. The total comprehensive income for the period is 2,333.77 million. The company&apos;s earnings per share (EPS) is not annualized and stands at 3.35 (Rupee) for basic and 3.35 (Rupee) for diluted.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations stands at 12,538.38 million</li><li>Profit before tax for the period is 5,293.32 million</li><li>Profit after tax is 670.80 million</li><li>Total comprehensive income for the period is 2,333.77 million</li><li>EPS is 3.35 (Rupee) for basic and diluted</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/61ae864a-7c72-4fa9-b1a8-d0936c2a8fad.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Pace Digitek Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JKIPL] Jinkushal Industries Announces Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jinkushal+Industries+Ltd&title=Jinkushal+Industries+Announces+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=b8e319c5-620e-4dc1-8896-d39dc1d1a66b&token=YjhlMzE5YzUtNjIw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8e319c5-620e-4dc1-8896-d39dc1d1a66b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jinkushal Industries Limited has announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a 27% year-on-year increase in standalone turnover, driven by export-led growth. A strategic inventory build-up was also undertaken at the overseas subsidiary to strengthen market access and increase the share of higher-margin used and refurbished machines. The company also balanced sales momentum by increasing focus on other international markets in response to temporary demand deferrals in Mexico.</p><ul><li>Standalone turnover increased by approximately 27% year-on-year, driven by export-led growth</li><li>Strategic inventory positioning undertaken at overseas subsidiary to strengthen market access</li><li>Continued focus on higher-margin refurbished and value-added equipment</li><li>Balanced geographic execution across multiple international markets</li><li>Expected progression as inventory is monetised</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e7081089-ddbb-4de6-b88d-ac84300665e4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jinkushal Industries Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JKIPL] Jinkushal Industries Ltd Submits Statement of No Deviation in IPO Fund Utilization</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jinkushal+Industries+Ltd&title=Jinkushal+Industries+Ltd+Submits+Statement+of+No+Deviation+in+IPO+Fund+Utilization&newsId=caf38068-f25a-4f3a-af51-f329fec0bd64&token=Y2FmMzgwNjgtZjI1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">caf38068-f25a-4f3a-af51-f329fec0bd64</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jinkushal Industries Ltd, a machinery, mining, and logistics company, has submitted a statement of no deviation in the utilization of funds raised from their Initial Public Offer (IPO). The IPO proceeds, totaling Rs. 11615.45 Lakhs, were raised through a public issue that closed on 29th September 2025. The funds were utilized for long-term applicable cable working capital requirements and general corporate purposes. The utilization of funds was reviewed by the Audit Committee and found to be in line with the objects stated in the prospectus.</p><ul><li>Jinkushal Industries Ltd submits Statement of Deviation as per Regulation 32 of SEBI</li><li>No deviation in the utilization of IPO funds during the quarter ended 31st December 2025</li><li>Funds utilized for long-term applicable cable working capital requirements and general corporate purposes</li><li>The Audit Committee has reviewed and taken the statement on record</li><li>Total funds raised through IPO: Rs. 11615.45 Lakhs</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d0410855-ffc8-4380-9677-f2243996ff40.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jinkushal Industries Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PACEDIGITK] Pace Digitek Ltd Announces Q3 and 9M Financial Results for 2025, Reveals IPO Proceeds Utilization</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Pace+Digitek+Ltd&title=Pace+Digitek+Ltd+Announces+Q3+and+9M+Financial+Results+for+2025%2C+Reveals+IPO+Proceeds+Utilization&newsId=4b4021e5-a571-48dd-9ee6-265894ea7c8b&token=NGI0MDIxZTUtYTU3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4b4021e5-a571-48dd-9ee6-265894ea7c8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pace Digitek Ltd, formerly known as Pace Digitek Private Limited and Pace Digitek Infra Private Limited, announced its unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 5,419.95 million for Q3 and 16,511.09 million for the nine-month period. The profit before tax for the period is 1,247.66 million, while the profit after tax is 932.94 million. The company has completed its Initial Public Offer (IPO) of Rs. 8,191.48 million, listing its equity shares on the National Stock Exchange (NSE) and Bombay Stock Exchange (BSE) on 06 October 2025. The total proceeds from the issue consisted of IPO proceeds of Rs. 8,191.48 million, with offer expenses estimated at Rs. 733.14 million. The objects of the issue included funding capital expenditure requirements, general corporate purposes, and share issue expenses.</p><ul><li>Pace Digitek Ltd announced its unaudited standalone financial results for Q3 and 9M 2025</li><li>Revenue from operations stands at 5,419.95 million for Q3 and 16,511.09 million for 9M</li><li>Profit before tax for the period is 1,247.66 million, while the profit after tax is 932.94 million</li><li>Completed IPO of Rs. 8,191.48 million, listing equity shares on NSE and BSE on 06 October 2025</li><li>IPO proceeds utilized for capital expenditure requirements, general corporate purposes, and share issue expenses</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1d4d41d5-12ea-4902-9947-c78e90be95eb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Pace Digitek Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CSURGSU] Centenial Surgical Suture Ltd. to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results on Feb 12, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CENTENIAL+SURGICAL+SUTURE+LTD.&title=Centenial+Surgical+Suture+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+on+Feb+12%2C+2026&newsId=b25f93aa-49cc-45d8-bd4f-1c2bd0d57392&token=YjI1ZjkzYWEtNDlj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b25f93aa-49cc-45d8-bd4f-1c2bd0d57392</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 22:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Centenial Surgical Suture Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 12, 2026, to consider and approve the Standalone Un-Audited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in securities of the company is closed from January 1, 2026, until 48 hours after the declaration of the results.</p><ul><li>Centenial Surgical Suture Ltd. to hold a Board Meeting on February 12, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the Standalone Un-Audited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Trading Window for dealing in securities of the company is closed from January 1, 2026, until 48 hours after the declaration of the results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a3cec2ae-e0d5-42f7-8ca3-970ed4aaf369.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CENTENIAL SURGICAL SUTURE LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TVSMOTOR] TVS Motor Strengthens its presence in Egypt with TVS RONIN and TVS NTORQ RACE EDITION Launch</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TVS+MOTOR+COMPANY+LTD.&title=TVS+Motor+Strengthens+its+presence+in+Egypt+with+TVS+RONIN+and+TVS+NTORQ+RACE+EDITION+Launch&newsId=68020361-2da8-4825-b22a-6cab2743a2ac&token=NjgwMjAzNjEtMmRh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68020361-2da8-4825-b22a-6cab2743a2ac</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>TVS Motor Company, a global leader in two and three-wheeler manufacturing, unveiled two new products, the TVS Ronin Top and TVS Ntorg RE, in Egypt. The launch ceremony was attended by key stakeholders, dealers, influencers, and senior representatives from TVS Motor Company and Ezz LCV, TVS’s authorized distributor in Egypt. This step marks a significant move in TVS Motor Company’s long-term strategic focus to deepen its presence in Egypt. The TVS Ronin Top, available in Nimbus Grey and Midnight Blue, offers a unique modern-retro design philosophy, cutting-edge engineering, optimized performance, and everyday versatility. The TVS Ntorg RE, available in Marine Blue and Red, enhances the brand’s presence in the performance scooter category with its sporty design, responsive acceleration, and advanced features. This launch strengthens TVS Motor Company’s commitment to delivering well-engineered products and expanding its global portfolio.</p><ul><li>TVS Motor Company launched two new products, the TVS Ronin Top and TVS Ntorg RE, in Egypt.</li><li>The launch was attended by key stakeholders, dealers, influencers, and senior representatives from TVS Motor Company and Ezz LCV.</li><li>The TVS Ronin Top offers a unique modern-retro design philosophy, cutting-edge engineering, optimized performance, and everyday versatility.</li><li>The TVS Ntorg RE enhances the brand’s presence in the performance scooter category with its sporty design, responsive acceleration, and advanced features.</li><li>This launch marks a significant step in TVS Motor Company’s long-term strategic focus to deepen its presence in Egypt.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/43fc5f3e-d50f-4587-8cab-8dfa4c5eff28.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TVS MOTOR COMPANY LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ACMESOLAR] ACME Solar Subsidiary Commissions 4 MW of 100 MW Wind Power Project in Gujarat</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ACME+Solar+Holdings+Ltd&title=ACME+Solar+Subsidiary+Commissions+4+MW+of+100+MW+Wind+Power+Project+in+Gujarat&newsId=5f2fe746-8a94-4726-815d-24226670121f&token=NWYyZmU3NDYtOGE5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f2fe746-8a94-4726-815d-24226670121f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:51:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>ACME Solar Holdings Limited has announced that its subsidiary, ACME Eco Clean Energy Private Limited, has successfully commissioned an additional 4 MW out of the 100 MW wind power project located at Village: Titoda, Taluka: Sayla, Dist: Surendaranagar, Gujarat. This achievement brings the total commissioned capacity to 76 MW out of 100 MW. The commissioning has been confirmed by officials from Gujarat Energy Development Agency (GEDA) and Paschim Gujarat Vij Company Limited (PGVCL), with formal certificates expected to be issued shortly.</p><ul><li>ACME Solar&apos;s subsidiary commissions 4 MW of a 100 MW wind power project in Gujarat</li><li>Total commissioned capacity now stands at 76 MW out of 100 MW</li><li>Commissioning confirmed by GEDA and PGVCL officials</li><li>Formal certificates awaited</li><li>Location: Village: Titoda, Taluka: Sayla, Dist: Surendaranagar, Gujarat</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ca569d14-d26b-44d4-88a2-2aa2bef82487.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ACME Solar Holdings Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BEML] BEML Ltd Approves Rs 1500 Crores Investment for Greenfield Rail Manufacturing Facility - BRAHMA</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BEML+LTD.&title=BEML+Ltd+Approves+Rs+1500+Crores+Investment+for+Greenfield+Rail+Manufacturing+Facility+-+BRAHMA&newsId=ff262570-7423-451f-b8bc-4a92aa5574a4&token=ZmYyNjI1NzAtNzQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff262570-7423-451f-b8bc-4a92aa5574a4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:51:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>BEML Ltd board has approved an estimated investment of approximately Rs 1500 crores for a greenfield rail manufacturing facility named BRAHMA. The facility will be set up at Umariya, near Bhopal, Madhya Pradesh. The project is expected to be completed in a phase-wise manner over five years. The investment is aimed at enhancing the Company’s manufacturing capabilities.</p><ul><li>BEML Ltd has approved an estimated investment of approximately Rs 1500 crores for a greenfield rail manufacturing facility named BRAHMA.</li><li>The facility will be located at Umariya, near Bhopal, Madhya Pradesh.</li><li>The project is expected to be completed in a phase-wise manner over five years.</li><li>The investment is aimed at enhancing the Company’s manufacturing capabilities.</li><li>The mode of financing for the project is long-term debt.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/60b99224-198e-4509-942f-db7489d0cfd4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BEML LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>