<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:43:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[BIZOTIC] Bizotic Commercial Ltd Appoints M/s. Shweta Jain &amp; Co. LLP Chartered Accountants as New Statutory Auditors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Bizotic+Commercial+Ltd&title=Bizotic+Commercial+Ltd+Appoints+M%2Fs.+Shweta+Jain+%26+Co.+LLP+Chartered+Accountants+as+New+Statutory+Auditors&newsId=baee3cb2-d807-4329-8c2c-80b1a16cb852&token=YmFlZTNjYjItZDgw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">baee3cb2-d807-4329-8c2c-80b1a16cb852</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bizotic Commercial Ltd has appointed M/s. Shweta Jain &amp; Co. LLP Chartered Accountants as new Statutory Auditors following the resignation of M/s J Singh &amp; Associates Chartered Accountants. The new auditors will hold office from 19th February, 2026 till the conclusion of the Annual General Meeting pertaining to the Financial Year 2025-26. They will conduct the Statutory Audit for the Financial Year ending 31st March, 2026. The appointment is in compliance with the provisions of Section 139 of the Companies Act, 2013 read with the Companies (Audit and Auditors) Rules, 2014 and the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The company also announced the resignation of Ms. Inderpreet Kaur Gulati from the post of Chief Financial Officer (CFO) &amp; Executive Director with effect from the Closing of Business hours 13th February, 2026.</p><ul><li>Bizotic Commercial Ltd appoints M/s. Shweta Jain &amp; Co. LLP Chartered Accountants as new Statutory Auditors.</li><li>The new auditors will conduct the Statutory Audit for the Financial Year ending 31st March, 2026.</li><li>The appointment is in compliance with the Companies Act, 2013, Companies (Audit and Auditors) Rules, 2014 and the SEBI Regulations, 2015.</li><li>Ms. Inderpreet Kaur Gulati resigns from the post of Chief Financial Officer (CFO) &amp; Executive Director.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/87a17add-3501-46c1-9793-9278acf52ef8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Bizotic Commercial Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LANCER] Lancer Container Lines Ltd Allots 10.29 Crore Shares on Preferential Basis for PKMGT Acquisition</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Lancer+Container+Lines+Ltd&title=Lancer+Container+Lines+Ltd+Allots+10.29+Crore+Shares+on+Preferential+Basis+for+PKMGT+Acquisition&newsId=a31ce484-95ec-47b0-9f2d-d147e8adf757&token=YTMxY2U0ODQtOTVl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a31ce484-95ec-47b0-9f2d-d147e8adf757</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Lancer Container Lines Ltd has allotted 10,28,69,409 fully paid-up equity shares on a preferential basis to several individuals for a consideration other than cash. This allotment is towards the discharge of the total consideration payable for the acquisition of the entire fully paid-up equity share capital of P K M General Trading L.L.C. (PKMGT). Consequently, PKMGT has become a wholly owned subsidiary of the Company and PT Map Trans Logistic, a subsidiary of PKMGT, has become a step-down subsidiary of the Company. The paid-up equity share capital of the Company stands increased from Rs. 1,25,19,71,545/- to Rs. 1,76,63,18,590/-. The allotment was made in compliance with Regulation 30 of Listing Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Lancer Container Lines Ltd allotted 10,28,69,409 equity shares on a preferential basis.</li><li>The allotment was made for the acquisition of PKMGT for a non-cash consideration.</li><li>PKMGT became a wholly owned subsidiary of Lancer Container Lines Ltd post allotment.</li><li>PT Map Trans Logistic, a subsidiary of PKMGT, became a step-down subsidiary of Lancer Container Lines Ltd.</li><li>The paid-up equity share capital of the Company increased from Rs. 1,25,19,71,545/- to Rs. 1,76,63,18,590/-.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a165c012-72be-4688-9829-43e69f8534af.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Lancer Container Lines Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MAHINDCIE] CIE Automotive India Ltd Appoints Protiviti India Member Private Limited as Internal Auditor</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Mahindra+CIE+Automotive+Limited&title=CIE+Automotive+India+Ltd+Appoints+Protiviti+India+Member+Private+Limited+as+Internal+Auditor&newsId=f0f21290-3378-4270-a06a-2ade82cc5567&token=ZjBmMjEyOTAtMzM3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0f21290-3378-4270-a06a-2ade82cc5567</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>CIE Automotive India Ltd has announced the appointment of Protiviti India Member Private Limited as their Internal Auditor. The decision was made at the Board of Directors meeting held on 19th February, 2026. The appointment is in accordance with Section 138 of the Companies Act, 2013 and the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. Protiviti is a global consulting firm that delivers expertise in various fields including finance, technology, operations, data, digital, legal, HR, risk and internal audit.</p><ul><li>CIE Automotive India Ltd appoints Protiviti India Member Private Limited as Internal Auditor</li><li>Appointment made at the Board of Directors meeting held on 19th February, 2026</li><li>Appointment in accordance with Section 138 of the Companies Act, 2013 and the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Protiviti is a global consulting firm with expertise in various fields</li><li>Appointment term is for the financial year ending 31 December, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ea465609-51b5-4cd0-b297-f2b60e65bb4b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Mahindra CIE Automotive Limited | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZYDUSLIFE] USFDA Inspection Closed at Zydus Injectable Plant with No Observations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Zydus+Lifesciences+Ltd&title=USFDA+Inspection+Closed+at+Zydus+Injectable+Plant+with+No+Observations&newsId=747a618c-9f1e-4fa8-b5e8-a8594d2b5f71&token=NzQ3YTYxOGMtOWYx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">747a618c-9f1e-4fa8-b5e8-a8594d2b5f71</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:17:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>USFDA</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>The US Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) conducted a Pre Approval Inspection (PAI) for Injectable Medical Devices at Zydus Lifesciences Ltd.’s Unit 9 facility located at Zydus Biotech Park, Changodar, Ahmedabad from 16th to 19th February, 2026. The inspection closed with NIL observations. This disclosure is pursuant to Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>USFDA conducted PAI for Injectable Medical Devices at Zydus Lifesciences Ltd.’s Unit 9 facility in Ahmedabad</li><li>The inspection was conducted from 16th to 19th February, 2026</li><li>The inspection closed with NIL observations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a074bf07-11ab-43df-8f63-e5f9aa979d6c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Zydus Lifesciences Ltd | Category: USFDA</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BALRAMCHIN*] Balrampur Chini Mills Ltd Fails to Credit Interim Dividend to Some Shareholders Due to Incorrect Bank Details</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BALRAMPUR+CHINI+MILLS+LTD.&title=Balrampur+Chini+Mills+Ltd+Fails+to+Credit+Interim+Dividend+to+Some+Shareholders+Due+to+Incorrect+Bank+Details&newsId=49641fd7-b5ec-4dba-bd76-2b29a1106f48&token=NDk2NDFmZDctYjVl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">49641fd7-b5ec-4dba-bd76-2b29a1106f48</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Balrampur Chini Mills Ltd has failed to credit the interim dividend for the Financial Year 2025-26 to some shareholders due to incorrect and/or incomplete bank account details. The company is requesting these shareholders to update their bank details and KYC information along with submission of requisite documents with the Company’s Registrar and Share Transfer Agent to release their dividend payable against their holding which has been lying unpaid with the Company.</p><ul><li>Balrampur Chini Mills Ltd could not credit interim dividend to some shareholders due to incorrect bank details.</li><li>Shareholders are requested to update their bank details and KYC information with the Company’s Registrar and Share Transfer Agent.</li><li>The unpaid dividend amount will be released immediately upon receipt and verification of the requisite documents.</li><li>Dividends on shares are payable only through electronic mode for shareholders with unpaid or unclaimed dividends.</li><li>The company is encouraging shareholders to update their PAN, KYC, Choice of Nomination &amp; Signature with Company&apos;s RTA to avoid any inconvenience.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/83430222-132d-4738-a18f-0f8719680d9d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BALRAMPUR CHINI MILLS LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ARIHANT] Arihant Foundations &amp; Housing Ltd. Approves Issuance of Non-Convertible Debentures Worth Up to INR 180 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ARIHANT+FOUNDATIONS+%26+HOUSING+LTD.-%24&title=Arihant+Foundations+%26+Housing+Ltd.+Approves+Issuance+of+Non-Convertible+Debentures+Worth+Up+to+INR+180+Crores&newsId=def25672-19ad-4ed1-893c-80f04b8d9e76&token=ZGVmMjU2NzItMTlh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">def25672-19ad-4ed1-893c-80f04b8d9e76</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Arihant Foundations &amp; Housing Ltd. announced that their Board of Directors approved the issuance of Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs) at a private placement, amounting to a total issue size of up to INR 180 Crores. The NCDs will be unlisted, unsecured, and redeemable. The decision was made during a meeting held on 19th February 2026, which commenced at 06.00 PM and concluded at 06.30 PM.</p><ul><li>Arihant Foundations &amp; Housing Ltd. to issue Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs) worth up to INR 180 Crores.</li><li>The NCDs will be unlisted, unsecured, and redeemable.</li><li>The issuance is on a private placement basis and will be in one or more tranches.</li><li>The decision was approved during a Board of Directors meeting on 19th February 2026.</li><li>The NCDs will be subject to statutory and regulatory approvals.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/98725d77-3eb1-4a09-b845-131f1c58d139.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ARIHANT FOUNDATIONS & HOUSING LTD.-$ | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BIZOTIC] Bizotic Commercial Ltd Appoints New Statutory Auditors and Announces CFO Resignation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Bizotic+Commercial+Ltd&title=Bizotic+Commercial+Ltd+Appoints+New+Statutory+Auditors+and+Announces+CFO+Resignation&newsId=b86998fe-8130-43e2-a809-c036f056b714&token=Yjg2OTk4ZmUtODEz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b86998fe-8130-43e2-a809-c036f056b714</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:08:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bizotic Commercial Ltd has appointed M/s. Shweta Jain &amp; Co LLP Chartered Accountants as new Statutory Auditors following the resignation of M/s J Singh &amp; Associates. The new auditors will hold office from 19th February, 2026 till the conclusion of the Annual General Meeting pertaining to the Financial Year 2025-26. The company will conduct the Statutory Audit for the Financial Year ending 31st March, 2026. The Board has also recommended the said appointment for approval of shareholders at the ensuing Extraordinary General Meeting (EGM). Furthermore, Ms. Inderpreet Kaur Gulati, the Chief Financial Officer (CFO) &amp; Executive Director of the company, has resigned from her post with effect from the closing of business hours 13th February, 2026.</p><ul><li>Appointment of M/s. Shweta Jain &amp; Co LLP Chartered Accountants as new Statutory Auditors</li><li>Resignation of Ms. Inderpreet Kaur Gulati as Chief Financial Officer (CFO) &amp; Executive Director</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0bb40d5c-cb8c-448b-b343-7cd67600e1ba.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Bizotic Commercial Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MAHINDCIE] CIE Automotive India Ltd Recommends Final Dividend of Rs. 7/- per Share for FY 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Mahindra+CIE+Automotive+Limited&title=CIE+Automotive+India+Ltd+Recommends+Final+Dividend+of+Rs.+7%2F-+per+Share+for+FY+2025&newsId=cdeb0265-7996-4a33-9ae1-d6b531b6c239&token=Y2RlYjAyNjUtNzk5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cdeb0265-7996-4a33-9ae1-d6b531b6c239</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:51:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>The Board of Directors of CIE Automotive India Ltd has recommended a final dividend of Rs. 7/- per equity share of face value of Rs. 10/- each for the financial year ended 31st December 2025. The 27th Annual General Meeting (AGM) of the company will be held on Wednesday, 29th April 2026, at 3:30 P.M.(IST) through Video Conferencing (VC)/ Other Audio Visual Mechanism (OAVM). The Record Date for the purpose of the AGM and determining the shareholders entitled for Final Dividend is fixed as Wednesday, 22nd April, 2026.</p><ul><li>The Board of Directors has recommended a final dividend of Rs. 7/- per equity share for FY 2025.</li><li>The 27th AGM of the company will be held on 29th April 2026 through VC/OAVM.</li><li>The Record Date for the purpose of the AGM and determining the shareholders entitled for Final Dividend is fixed as 22nd April, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/895f3e1f-0a7c-4aee-9a86-4de9376af11e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Mahindra CIE Automotive Limited | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MAHINDCIE] CIE Automotive India Ltd Recommends Final Dividend of Rs. 7/- per Share for FY 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Mahindra+CIE+Automotive+Limited&title=CIE+Automotive+India+Ltd+Recommends+Final+Dividend+of+Rs.+7%2F-+per+Share+for+FY+2025&newsId=d606282b-693d-4c77-8fd8-25aaa035b6f4&token=ZDYwNjI4MmItNjkz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d606282b-693d-4c77-8fd8-25aaa035b6f4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:50:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>The Board of Directors of CIE Automotive India Ltd has recommended a final dividend of Rs. 7/- per equity share of face value of Rs. 10/- for the financial year ended 31st December 2025. The dividend will be paid within 30 days from the date of the Annual General Meeting (AGM) to shareholders or their mandates, whose names appear as Beneficial Owners or Members in respect of shares held in electronic or physical form, as per the data made available by National Securities Depository Limited, Central Depository Services (India) Limited and the Register of Members of the Company on the close of business hours Wednesday, 22nd April, 2026. The AGM will be held on Wednesday, 29th April, 2026 at 3:30 P.M.(IST) through Video Conferencing (VC)/ Other Audio Visual Mechanism (OAVM) in accordance with the provisions of the Companies Act, 2013 and SEBI Regulations. The Record Date for the purpose of the AGM and determining the shareholders entitled for Final Dividend is fixed as Wednesday, 22nd April, 2026.</p><ul><li>CIE Automotive India Ltd recommends a final dividend of Rs. 7/- per equity share for FY 2025.</li><li>The dividend will be paid within 30 days from the date of the AGM to eligible shareholders.</li><li>The AGM will be held on Wednesday, 29th April, 2026 through Video Conferencing (VC)/ Other Audio Visual Mechanism (OAVM).</li><li>The Record Date for the purpose of the AGM and determining the shareholders entitled for Final Dividend is fixed as Wednesday, 22nd April, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/755f3fe0-ea7a-4b6c-b492-2085e5eaeb56.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Mahindra CIE Automotive Limited | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AVI] AVI Polymers Ltd. Extends Rights Issue Closing Date to March 17, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AVI+Polymers+Ltd&title=AVI+Polymers+Ltd.+Extends+Rights+Issue+Closing+Date+to+March+17%2C+2026&newsId=f9ebc98c-445e-4b18-a885-71ea37988038&token=ZjllYmM5OGMtNDQ1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9ebc98c-445e-4b18-a885-71ea37988038</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:48:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Right Issue</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>AVI Polymers Ltd. has announced an extension of the Rights Issue closing date from March 16, 2026, to March 17, 2026. The decision was made during a board meeting on February 19, 2026, to provide shareholders with an opportunity to exercise their rights in the Rights Issue. The last date for submitting the duly filled CAF along with the application amount is now March 16, 2026. The revised issue schedule is as follows: Issue Opening Date - February 23, 2026; Issue Closing Date - March 17, 2026; Finalizing the basis of allotment - March 24, 2026; Date of Allotment - March 25, 2026; Date of credit - March 31, 2026; and Date of listing - April 01, 2026.</p><ul><li>AVI Polymers Ltd. extends Rights Issue closing date to March 17, 2026</li><li>Last date for CAF submission is now March 16, 2026</li><li>Revised issue schedule: Issue Opening Date - February 23, 2026; Issue Closing Date - March 17, 2026</li><li>Finalizing the basis of allotment on March 24, 2026</li><li>Date of Allotment - March 25, 2026; Date of credit - March 31, 2026; and Date of listing - April 01, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/76fde61b-2fc1-4716-9323-3c89d50a333c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AVI Polymers Ltd | Category: Right Issue</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>