<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:36:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[APEX] Apex Frozen Foods Ltd to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 2025 on Feb 11, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Apex+Frozen+Foods+Ltd&title=Apex+Frozen+Foods+Ltd+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+2025+on+Feb+11%2C+2026&newsId=46a60197-f927-4264-b3e9-2d9e764bde3f&token=NDZhNjAxOTctZjky</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">46a60197-f927-4264-b3e9-2d9e764bde3f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:34:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Apex Frozen Foods Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 11, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the third quarter ended 31st December 2025. The meeting is scheduled in accordance with Regulation 33 and Regulation 29 of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015. The trading window for dealing in equity shares of the company has been closed for all promoters, directors, designated employees, insiders, and their relatives from January 1, 2026, until 48 hours after the declaration of the unaudited financial results.</p><ul><li>Apex Frozen Foods Ltd to approve unaudited financial results for Q3 2025 on Feb 11, 2026</li><li>Meeting scheduled in accordance with Regulation 33 and Regulation 29 of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Trading window for dealing in equity shares closed for promoters, directors, designated employees, insiders, and their relatives from Jan 1, 2026, to 48 hours after the declaration of results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3afad0f6-467e-4878-9765-b9853f03d0f2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Apex Frozen Foods Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UNIVPHOTO] Universus Photo Imagings Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results on Feb 11, 2026; Trading Window Closed</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Universus+Photo+Imagings+Ltd&title=Universus+Photo+Imagings+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+on+Feb+11%2C+2026%3B+Trading+Window+Closed&newsId=2e9f44c1-ca5f-49c8-993d-a5c70f43587a&token=MmU5ZjQ0YzEtY2E1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e9f44c1-ca5f-49c8-993d-a5c70f43587a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:34:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Universus Photo Imagings Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 11, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited Financial Results (Standalone &amp; Consolidated) for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. In accordance with the Company&apos;s Code of Conduct for prevention of Insider Trading, the trading window for dealing in shares of the Company will remain closed for all the designated persons of the Company and their immediate relatives until February 13, 2026. This information is also available on the Company&apos;s website and at the websites of Stock Exchanges.</p><ul><li>Universus Photo Imagings Ltd to consider and approve Q3 and nine months results on Feb 11, 2026</li><li>Trading window closed for all designated persons and their immediate relatives until Feb 13, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cc1c0a03-ffba-472d-b2c0-883f082636f6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Universus Photo Imagings Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SASKEN] Sasken Technologies Ltd Receives Intimation Order from Income Tax - Centralized Processing Centre (CPC) with No Material Impact</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sasken+Technologies+Ltd&title=Sasken+Technologies+Ltd+Receives+Intimation+Order+from+Income+Tax+-+Centralized+Processing+Centre+%28CPC%29+with+No+Material+Impact&newsId=6265f5e6-8bf8-4ae1-964d-506cced91338&token=NjI2NWY1ZTYtOGJm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6265f5e6-8bf8-4ae1-964d-506cced91338</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sasken Technologies Ltd has received an intimation order under section 143(1) from Income Tax - Centralized Processing Centre (CPC) for the Assessment Year 2025-26. The order, which includes a surcharge added to the tax payable, has created a tax demand of Rs. 1,45,100. However, the company has stated that there is no material impact on financial, operational, or other activities due to the passing of this intimation order. The order is currently appealable, and the company intends to exercise its right to appeal before CIT - Appeals.</p><ul><li>Sasken Technologies Ltd has received an intimation order under section 143(1) from Income Tax - Centralized Processing Centre (CPC).</li><li>The intimation order has created a tax demand of Rs. 1,45,100 for the Assessment Year 2025-26.</li><li>The company has stated that there is no material impact on financial, operational, or other activities due to the passing of this intimation order.</li><li>The order is currently appealable, and the company intends to exercise its right to appeal before CIT - Appeals.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2bb3193f-94c0-487f-9df5-22185f3ffbca.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sasken Technologies Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ISCITRUST] Intelligent Supply Chain Infrastructure Trust Approves Unaudited Standalone Financial Information for Q3 &amp; Nine Months Ended December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Intelligent+Supply+Chain+Infrastructure+Trust&title=Intelligent+Supply+Chain+Infrastructure+Trust+Approves+Unaudited+Standalone+Financial+Information+for+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Ended+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=6b383a22-eef2-4292-9474-838f3951e08f&token=NmIzODNhMjItZWVm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6b383a22-eef2-4292-9474-838f3951e08f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:33:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Intelligent Supply Chain Infrastructure Trust has informed the Exchange about the disclosure of material issues in the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The Board of Directors of Infinite India Investment Management Limited, the Investment Manager of the Trust, has approved the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial information of the Trust for the same period. The financial information, reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors, is being uploaded on the Trust&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>The Board of Directors of Infinite India Investment Management Limited approved the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial information for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The financial information is reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</li><li>The financial information is being uploaded on the Trust&apos;s website: https://www.intelsupplychaininfra.com/FinancialResultsAndValuationReport.html.</li><li>Deloitte Haskins &amp; Sells LLP provided a limited review report with an unmodified opinion on the financial information.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0072b772-caa4-4cde-b83e-4dcf5b1adb8d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Intelligent Supply Chain Infrastructure Trust | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BROOKS] Brooks Laboratories Ltd: Unaudited Financial Results for Quarter and Nine Months Ended 31st December 2025 Approved in Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BROOKS+LABORATORIES+LTD.&title=Brooks+Laboratories+Ltd%3A+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Quarter+and+Nine+Months+Ended+31st+December+2025+Approved+in+Board+Meeting&newsId=f0f4a03c-e2b1-4820-9bda-efd58d24e49f&token=ZjBmNGEwM2MtZTJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0f4a03c-e2b1-4820-9bda-efd58d24e49f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:32:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Brooks Laboratories Ltd, in a meeting held on Friday, 6th February 2026, approved and took on record the unaudited financial results (standalone and consolidated) for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The special resolution passed by the members of the company for alteration of the Object Clause of the Memorandum of Association has not taken effect. The financial results will be published in newspapers and will be available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025 approved</li><li>Special resolution for alteration of the Object Clause of the Memorandum of Association not taken effect</li><li>Financial results to be published in newspapers and available on the company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/49205f08-17bf-4147-a308-126097e1db1b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BROOKS LABORATORIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FUSION] Fusion Finance Ltd Reports No Deviation in Rights Issue Fund Utilization for Q4 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Fusion+Micro+Finance+Ltd&title=Fusion+Finance+Ltd+Reports+No+Deviation+in+Rights+Issue+Fund+Utilization+for+Q4+2025&newsId=7539e31d-7173-4145-91da-e783fe6284a7&token=NzUzOWUzMWQtNzE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7539e31d-7173-4145-91da-e783fe6284a7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Fusion Finance Ltd (Formerly known as Fusion Micro Finance Limited) has reported no deviation or variation in the use of proceeds of the Rights Issue of equity shares from the objects stated in the Letter of Offer dated March 29, 2025. The company raised INR 795.23 Crore through the Rights Issue, all of which has been utilized towards augmenting the capital base of the Company to meet future capital requirements.</p><ul><li>Fusion Finance Ltd reports no deviation in Rights Issue fund utilization for Q4 2025</li><li>INR 795.23 Crore raised through Rights Issue</li><li>Funds utilized towards augmenting the capital base of the Company</li><li>No deviation or variation in the use of proceeds of the Rights Issue</li><li>Reviewed by the Audit Committee of the Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5a885b18-225c-4d84-9f49-365c7f73b1a1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Fusion Micro Finance Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BROOKS] Brooks Laboratories Ltd: Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 &amp; Nine Months Ended 31st December 2025 Approved in Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BROOKS+LABORATORIES+LTD.&title=Brooks+Laboratories+Ltd%3A+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Ended+31st+December+2025+Approved+in+Board+Meeting&newsId=919d5297-ae2d-4fd0-970a-3956990d1e8b&token=OTE5ZDUyOTctYWUy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">919d5297-ae2d-4fd0-970a-3956990d1e8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Brooks Laboratories Ltd held a Board Meeting on 6th February 2026, where they considered, approved, and took on record the Unaudited Financial Results (Standalone and Consolidated) for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The Limited Review Reports were issued by the Statutory Auditors of the Company. The Special Resolution passed by the Members of the Company at the Annual General Meeting held on 26th September 2025 for alteration of the Object Clause of the Memorandum of Association has not taken effect. The financial results will be published in newspapers and will be available on the Company’s website.</p><ul><li>Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 &amp; Nine Months Ended 31st December 2025 approved in Board Meeting.</li><li>Limited Review Reports issued by the Statutory Auditors of the Company.</li><li>Special Resolution passed by the Members of the Company at the Annual General Meeting held on 26th September 2025 for alteration of the Object Clause of the Memorandum of Association has not taken effect.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/95c0f090-6837-4a9c-914a-86460fc68d82.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BROOKS LABORATORIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZOMATO] Deepinder Goyal Steps Down as Eternal&apos;s CEO, Albinder Dhindsa Takes Over</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Zomato+Ltd&title=Deepinder+Goyal+Steps+Down+as+Eternal%27s+CEO%2C+Albinder+Dhindsa+Takes+Over&newsId=17d4070d-614e-4942-bb9d-f07ac85ac312&token=MTdkNDA3MGQtNjE0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17d4070d-614e-4942-bb9d-f07ac85ac312</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Deepinder Goyal, the CEO of Eternal Ltd (Formerly known as Zomato Limited), has resigned from his position as Director, MD &amp; CEO and various committees, effective from the close of business hours on February 1, 2026. Albinder Dhindsa will be the new Group CEO, subject to shareholders’ approval. Goyal will remain on the board of directors as Vice Chairman. Goyal is stepping down to explore new ideas that involve higher-risk exploration and experimentation, which do not fit Eternal’s risk profile. The change allows Eternal to remain focused and disciplined while giving Goyal the space to explore these new ideas. Goyal&apos;s financial future remains tied to Eternal, and his incentives remain aligned with long-term shareholder value creation.</p><ul><li>Deepinder Goyal resigns as CEO of Eternal Ltd</li><li>Albinder Dhindsa to take over as new Group CEO</li><li>Goyal to explore new ideas outside Eternal&apos;s risk profile</li><li>Goyal to remain on the board of directors as Vice Chairman</li><li>Goyal&apos;s financial future remains tied to Eternal</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/851a0ab6-2469-476e-86f4-b9fef5a2b695.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Zomato Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JAYAGROGN] Jayant Agro Organics Ltd: Un-Audited Financial Results for Q3 &amp; Nine Months Ended Dec 31, 2025 &amp; Re-Appointment of Mr. Sanjay J. Mariwala as Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JAYANT+AGRO-ORGANICS+LTD.&title=Jayant+Agro+Organics+Ltd%3A+Un-Audited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Ended+Dec+31%2C+2025+%26+Re-Appointment+of+Mr.+Sanjay+J.+Mariwala+as+Independent+Director&newsId=17a8850b-6338-4931-b292-a5b090076cf9&token=MTdhODg1MGItNjMz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17a8850b-6338-4931-b292-a5b090076cf9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:23:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jayant Agro Organics Ltd. has announced its un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 24,164.70 lakhs for the quarter and 82,632.82 lakhs for the nine months. The Board has also approved the re-appointment of Mr. Sanjay J. Mariwala as an Independent Director for a second term of 5 years.</p><ul><li>Jayant Agro Organics Ltd. announced un-audited financial results for Q3 &amp; nine months ended Dec 31, 2025</li><li>Revenue from operations stands at 24,164.70 lakhs for the quarter and 82,632.82 lakhs for the nine months</li><li>The Board approved the re-appointment of Mr. Sanjay J. Mariwala as an Independent Director for a second term of 5 years</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f057aff7-6126-4541-983b-b7e2cced1268.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JAYANT AGRO-ORGANICS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JAYBARMARU] Jay Bharat Maruti to Invest Rs. 170 Crores in Phase II of Plant J7</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JAY+BHARAT+MARUTI+LTD.&title=Jay+Bharat+Maruti+to+Invest+Rs.+170+Crores+in+Phase+II+of+Plant+J7&newsId=c28d0c74-f515-47cc-9478-3ce6e507aff4&token=YzI4ZDBjNzQtZjUx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c28d0c74-f515-47cc-9478-3ce6e507aff4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 15:21:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Jay Bharat Maruti Limited, the flagship company of the US$3.3 bn JBM Group, has approved a capex of Rs. 170 Crores for Phase II of Plant J7 at Kharkhoda, Sonipat, Haryana. This investment is part of the earlier approved capex of Rs. 350 Crores for setting up 2 new manufacturing plants in Haryana and Gujarat. The company is known for its quality-delivery, frugal engineering, low time-to-market, and art-to-part philosophy, providing it an indomitable position in the automotive industry.</p><ul><li>Jay Bharat Maruti Limited to invest Rs. 170 crores in Phase II of Plant J7 (Kharkhoda).</li><li>This investment is part of the earlier approved capex of Rs. 350 Crores for setting up 2 new manufacturing plants in Haryana and Gujarat.</li><li>Jay Bharat Maruti Limited is a leading manufacturer of key auto systems and assemblies for Maruti Suzuki India Limited.</li><li>JBM Group has a diversified portfolio in the field of automotive, buses &amp; electric vehicles, EV charging Infra, engineering &amp; design services and renewables.</li><li>JBM Group has an infrastructure of 70+ manufacturing plants and 5 engineering &amp; design centers with presence in over 37+ countries.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/702cdc7b-f769-44e9-bed3-3a481216f8fa.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JAY BHARAT MARUTI LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>