<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 01:23:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[AXISCADES] AXISCADES secures 100 Cr Defence Radar Subsystem Contract, bolstering high-margin Embedded Systems Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Axiscades+Technologies+Ltd&title=AXISCADES+secures+100+Cr+Defence+Radar+Subsystem+Contract%2C+bolstering+high-margin+Embedded+Systems+Growth&newsId=f6534a47-c8bc-495f-884d-03651a115f54&token=ZjY1MzRhNDctYzhi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6534a47-c8bc-495f-884d-03651a115f54</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 01:04:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>AXISCADES Technologies Limited, a chip to product company and a pioneer in Aerospace, Defence, Electronics, Semiconductor and Artificial Intelligence applications, announced that its subsidiary Mistral Solutions has secured a contract worth around 100 Crores from the LLTR Ashwini programme. This programme is India’s indigenous Low-Level Transportable Radar system developed by DRDO and BEL. The contract is for the supply of Signal and Data Processing Units (SDPU), including associated spares, with deliveries over 2 years for steady revenue visibility. This win reflects Mistral’s continued commitment to supporting India’s defence indigenisation initiatives and contributing critical technologies to next-generation military systems. It also positions Mistral to capture the expanding DRDO/BEL pipeline in indigenous defence electronics.</p><ul><li>Around 100 Crores contract for state-of-the-art Signal and Data Processing Units (SDPU) and associated spares</li><li>Deliveries over 2 years for steady revenue visibility</li><li>Critical role in enhancing low-altitude surveillance against UAVs, helicopters, and fighter jets</li><li>Liquid-cooled SDPU meets extreme operational demands, showcasing proprietary expertise in embedded computing for next-gen radar platforms</li><li>Positions Mistral to capture expanding DRDO/BEL pipeline in indigenous defence electronics</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3362371a-e714-463f-8208-7f471e43928f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Axiscades Technologies Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AXISCADES] Axiscades Technologies&apos; Subsidiary Secures Supply Order from Bharat Electronics Ltd for Signal and Data Processing Units</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Axiscades+Technologies+Ltd&title=Axiscades+Technologies%27+Subsidiary+Secures+Supply+Order+from+Bharat+Electronics+Ltd+for+Signal+and+Data+Processing+Units&newsId=90940940-dd47-41e8-ada9-45589a54a5e3&token=OTA5NDA5NDAtZGQ0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90940940-dd47-41e8-ada9-45589a54a5e3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 00:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Axiscades Technologies Ltd announced that its subsidiary, Mistral Solutions Private Limited, has secured a supply order from Bharat Electronics Ltd (BEL), Ministry of Defence, for supply of Signal and Data Processing Units along with associated spares. The order is worth approximately 100 Crores INR and is to be executed over a period of two years.</p><ul><li>Axiscades Technologies&apos; subsidiary, Mistral Solutions Private Limited, has secured a supply order from Bharat Electronics Ltd (BEL), Ministry of Defence.</li><li>The order is for the supply of Signal and Data Processing Units along with associated spares.</li><li>The estimated value of the order is 100 Crores INR.</li><li>The order is to be executed over a period of two years.</li><li>Bharat Electronics Ltd (BEL) is a domestic entity.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/22447165-67df-4e75-a7c3-650971ed5855.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Axiscades Technologies Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WAKEFIT] Wakefit Innovations Ltd. Announces Amendments to Memorandum and Articles of Association</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Wakefit+Innovations+Ltd&title=Wakefit+Innovations+Ltd.+Announces+Amendments+to+Memorandum+and+Articles+of+Association&newsId=730798a8-6284-4fde-8607-f8cb78aa9113&token=NzMwNzk4YTgtNjI4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">730798a8-6284-4fde-8607-f8cb78aa9113</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 00:02:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Wakefit Innovations Ltd. has announced amendments to its Memorandum and Articles of Association. The amendments include reclassification of authorized share capital, alteration to the Capital Clause, approval for upside arrangement under the Shareholders’ Agreement, and amendment in the Articles of Association. The reclassification of authorized share capital will result in the conversion of compulsorily convertible preference shares into equity shares. The upside arrangement under the Shareholders’ Agreement has been approved, which relates to the right of promoters to receive upside sharing from investors. The Articles of Association have been amended to insert a new article relating to the right to upside arrangement. These amendments are subject to approval from shareholders as required under SEBI regulations.</p><ul><li>Reclassification of authorized share capital and alteration to the Capital Clause of the Memorandum of Association</li><li>Approval for the upside arrangement under the Shareholders’ Agreement</li><li>Amendment in the Articles of Association</li><li>Subject to approval from shareholders as required under SEBI regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/32ce02fc-4da4-4e6b-baf0-31a3d0fb4bda.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Wakefit Innovations Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WAKEFIT] Wakefit Innovations Ltd. Announces Capital Reclassification, Upside Arrangement Approval, and AOA Amendment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Wakefit+Innovations+Ltd&title=Wakefit+Innovations+Ltd.+Announces+Capital+Reclassification%2C+Upside+Arrangement+Approval%2C+and+AOA+Amendment&newsId=5f8024fb-23df-48ab-ac5a-9835477d83b0&token=NWY4MDI0ZmItMjNk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f8024fb-23df-48ab-ac5a-9835477d83b0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 00:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Wakefit Innovations Ltd. has announced several key decisions made through a postal ballot by remote e-voting process. The decisions include the reclassification of authorized share capital, approval for an upside arrangement under the Shareholders’ Agreement, and an amendment in the Articles of Association. The reclassification of authorized share capital involves the conversion of compulsorily convertible preference shares into equity shares. The upside arrangement under the Shareholders’ Agreement, which originally stood terminated upon the listing of the company, will now continue in force post-listing. The amendment in the Articles of Association includes the insertion of Article 168 relating to the right to upside arrangement. These decisions are subject to compliance with applicable laws and approval from shareholders.</p><ul><li>Reclassification of authorized share capital and alteration to the Capital Clause of the Memorandum of Association</li><li>Approval for the upside arrangement under the Shareholders’ Agreement</li><li>Amendment in the Articles of Association of the Company</li><li>Subject to compliance with applicable laws and approval from shareholders</li><li>Continuation of the upside arrangement post-listing</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9e77370f-d76d-4342-9f50-0abcdc4768f1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Wakefit Innovations Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STANCAP] Standard Capital Markets Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on January 21, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=STANDARD+CAPITAL+MARKETS+LTD.&title=Standard+Capital+Markets+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+January+21%2C+2026&newsId=02517152-2ff2-4b1d-9f5d-1c7c734a3674&token=MDI1MTcxNTItMmZm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02517152-2ff2-4b1d-9f5d-1c7c734a3674</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 20:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Standard Capital Markets Ltd has announced a Board of Directors meeting on January 21, 2026, to consider and approve the Standalone and Consolidated Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31 December, 2025. The trading window for all designated persons and their immediate relatives has been closed from January 01, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of the Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Standard Capital Markets Ltd scheduled a Board of Directors meeting on January 21, 2026</li><li>The meeting aims to consider and approve the Standalone and Consolidated Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31 December, 2025</li><li>Trading window for all designated persons and their immediate relatives is closed from January 01, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of the Financial Results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4e5feec1-169e-4dc0-8f30-e2d7fc5c89bc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: STANDARD CAPITAL MARKETS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FORTISMLR] Fortis Malar Hospitals Ltd Announces Changes in Board Composition: Appointment of Mr. Bidesh Chandra Paul and Resignation of Mr. Chandrasekar Ramaswamy</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Fortis+Malar+Hospitals+Limited&title=Fortis+Malar+Hospitals+Ltd+Announces+Changes+in+Board+Composition%3A+Appointment+of+Mr.+Bidesh+Chandra+Paul+and+Resignation+of+Mr.+Chandrasekar+Ramaswamy&newsId=c5d1e08b-8246-4114-86e3-2a6099a2284f&token=YzVkMWUwOGItODI0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5d1e08b-8246-4114-86e3-2a6099a2284f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Fortis Malar Hospitals Ltd has announced changes in its Board of Directors. Mr. Bidesh Chandra Paul has been appointed as an Additional Director (Non-Independent) effective from January 18, 2026. Mr. Paul is a healthcare and operations leader with over 15 years of experience in manufacturing, R&amp;D, healthcare operations, and supply chain management. On the other hand, Mr. Chandrasekar Ramaswamy has resigned from his position as Whole Time Director and Key Managerial Personnel due to other commitments and responsibilities, effective from the same date.</p><ul><li>Mr. Bidesh Chandra Paul appointed as Additional Director (Non-Independent) of Fortis Malar Hospitals Ltd</li><li>Mr. Paul is a healthcare and operations leader with over 15 years of experience</li><li>Mr. Chandrasekar Ramaswamy has resigned from his position as Whole Time Director and Key Managerial Personnel</li><li>Mr. Ramaswamy&apos;s resignation is due to other commitments and responsibilities</li><li>Both changes are effective from January 18, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ffaa6617-5476-43be-8dc4-b3f623ffaff2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Fortis Malar Hospitals Limited | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DESCO] Desco Infratech Ltd Pays Fine of Rs. 5,900 for Late Submission of Related Party Transactions</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Desco+Infratech+Ltd&title=Desco+Infratech+Ltd+Pays+Fine+of+Rs.+5%2C900+for+Late+Submission+of+Related+Party+Transactions&newsId=355e9252-9b75-46ae-ac69-8a5fd591ca18&token=MzU1ZTkyNTItOWI3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">355e9252-9b75-46ae-ac69-8a5fd591ca18</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 14:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Desco Infratech Ltd has paid a fine of Rs. 5,900 (inclusive of GST) for late submission of related party transactions in the format as specified and within the prescribed timeline under Regulation 23(9) of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015 for the half year ended September 2025. The delay was inadvertent and has since been rectified. The fine was paid within the stipulated time and the matter was placed before the Board of Directors. The Company has advised to strengthen internal compliance monitoring systems to avoid recurrence of such instances in future.</p><ul><li>Desco Infratech Ltd pays fine of Rs. 5,900 for late submission of related party transactions.</li><li>The delay was inadvertent and has since been rectified.</li><li>The fine was paid within the stipulated time.</li><li>The matter was placed before the Board of Directors.</li><li>Company advised to strengthen internal compliance monitoring systems.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/17aa17c4-b2f7-4589-8931-560828539cff.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Desco Infratech Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JCTLTD] JCT Ltd Announces 8th Meeting of CoC on January 19, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JCT+LTD.&title=JCT+Ltd+Announces+8th+Meeting+of+CoC+on+January+19%2C+2026&newsId=d7e4875a-e26c-486a-91e9-edb145d9f77f&token=ZDdlNDg3NWEtZTI2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7e4875a-e26c-486a-91e9-edb145d9f77f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 14:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>JCT Ltd has announced the 8th meeting of its Committee of Creditors (CoC) to be held on Monday, the 19th day of January, 2026 at 3.00 P.M. The meeting is scheduled to take place at The Park Hotel, Parliament Street, New Delhi-110001.</p><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/96890b00-cacf-49cf-a41c-97f5ca653b33.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JCT LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CHMBBRW] Chambal Breweries &amp; Distilleries Ltd: Major Board Resignations and Appointment of New Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CHAMBAL+BREWERIES+%26+DISTILLERIES+LTD.&title=Chambal+Breweries+%26+Distilleries+Ltd%3A+Major+Board+Resignations+and+Appointment+of+New+Independent+Director&newsId=20a9bc35-dcb4-4618-8fb8-3473f1b82056&token=MjBhOWJjMzUtZGNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">20a9bc35-dcb4-4618-8fb8-3473f1b82056</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 13:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Chambal Breweries &amp; Distilleries Ltd has announced significant changes in its Board of Directors. Mr. Parasram Jhamnani, Mrs. Amrita Modi, Mr. Rinku Goyal, and Mr. Anmol Jindal have resigned from their positions, effective from 18/01/2026, due to a change in management by takeover. Additionally, Mr. Gaurav Sharma has been appointed as an Additional Independent Director on the same date. Mr. Sharma brings over 22 years of experience in HR leadership across diverse organizations and holds relevant qualifications in ESG and AI leadership.</p><ul><li>Resignation of Mr. Parasram Jhamnani as Managing Director and Chairman</li><li>Resignation of Mrs. Amrita Modi as Director</li><li>Resignation of Mr. Rinku Goyal as an Independent Director</li><li>Resignation of Mr. Anmol Jindal as an Independent Director</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Gaurav Sharma as an Additional Independent Director</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5f4f8665-2098-4c4d-81f9-ef9d0e36f1b8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CHAMBAL BREWERIES & DISTILLERIES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CHMBBRW] Chambal Breweries &amp; Distilleries Ltd: Mass Resignation of Directors and Appointment of New Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CHAMBAL+BREWERIES+%26+DISTILLERIES+LTD.&title=Chambal+Breweries+%26+Distilleries+Ltd%3A+Mass+Resignation+of+Directors+and+Appointment+of+New+Independent+Director&newsId=9e70564f-a621-4e7f-a514-52cbbb46d716&token=OWU3MDU2NGYtYTYy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e70564f-a621-4e7f-a514-52cbbb46d716</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 13:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Chambal Breweries &amp; Distilleries Ltd has announced the resignation of several directors due to a change in management by takeover. The resigning directors include Parasram Jhamnani as Managing Director and Chairman, Amrita Modi as Director, Rinku Goyal and Anmol Jindal as Independent Directors. The resignations are effective from 18/01/2026. Following this, Mr. Gaurav Sharma has been appointed as an Additional Independent Director on the Board of the Company from the same date.</p><ul><li>Parasram Jhamnani, Amrita Modi, Rinku Goyal, and Anmol Jindal have resigned from their positions in Chambal Breweries &amp; Distilleries Ltd.</li><li>The resignations are a result of a change in management by takeover.</li><li>The resignations are effective from 18/01/2026.</li><li>Mr. Gaurav Sharma has been appointed as an Additional Independent Director on the Board of the Company from 18/01/2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f6e6d630-dd82-4d2e-8270-6c23b9179c37.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CHAMBAL BREWERIES & DISTILLERIES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>