<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:56:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[KFINTECH] KFin Technologies Ltd CTO, Mr. Venkatagiri Vonkayala, Resigns Effective February 15, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KFin+Technologies+Ltd&title=KFin+Technologies+Ltd+CTO%2C+Mr.+Venkatagiri+Vonkayala%2C+Resigns+Effective+February+15%2C+2026&newsId=9c0b697b-6d19-4c2c-a3df-0ebffc0004ee&token=OWMwYjY5N2ItNmQx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c0b697b-6d19-4c2c-a3df-0ebffc0004ee</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:47:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>KFin Technologies Ltd has announced the resignation of its Chief Technology Officer, Mr. Venkatagiri Vonkayala, with his last working day being February 15, 2026. The resignation comes as Mr. Vonkayala is pursuing better opportunities elsewhere. He expressed gratitude towards the Board of Directors and management for their support during his tenure.</p><ul><li>Mr. Venkatagiri Vonkayala resigns as the Chief Technology Officer of KFin Technologies Ltd.</li><li>His last working day at the company is February 15, 2026.</li><li>Mr. Vonkayala is leaving to pursue better opportunities.</li><li>He thanked the Board of Directors and management for their support during his tenure.</li><li>The resignation is in compliance with LODR Regulations and SEBI Master Circular No. HO/49/14/14(7)2025-CFD-POD2/1/3762/2026 dated January 30, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/73226ff3-ef0a-49bb-94a5-c312306e56a9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KFin Technologies Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RMDRIP] R M Drip and Sprinklers Systems Ltd Forays into Smart Irrigation Automation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=R+M+Drip+and+Sprinklers+Systems+Ltd&title=R+M+Drip+and+Sprinklers+Systems+Ltd+Forays+into+Smart+Irrigation+Automation&newsId=01ccead8-80e3-4e75-801a-187bcb4975be&token=MDFjY2VhZDgtODBl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01ccead8-80e3-4e75-801a-187bcb4975be</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:36:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>R M Drip and Sprinklers Systems Ltd, a leading manufacturer of micro-irrigation systems, has announced a strategic technology partnership with an advanced farm automation technology company. This initiative marks the company&apos;s entry into loT-based smart irrigation and digital agriculture, representing a key milestone in its transition toward technology-led growth, recurring revenue generation, and expansion into next-generation agriculture solutions.</p><ul><li>Strategic entry into next-generation irrigation automation</li><li>Expansion from hardware-led products to integrated hardware + software platform</li><li>New revenue streams from hardware, mobile apps, analytics and subscriptions</li><li>Expected contribution of ~5% of revenue in FY27, ~30% growth expected in this segment from FY27 onwards</li><li>Leverage of 1,000+ dealer and retail touchpoints for nationwide rollout, supported by favourable government initiatives, subsidies adoption driving faster farmer adoption</li><li>Strong alignment with water conservation, solar irrigation and digital agriculture initiatives</li><li>Enhances long-term revenue visibility, margin profile and business scalability</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/04c27b34-2144-4497-9c6c-c054ba823c68.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: R M Drip and Sprinklers Systems Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HFIL] Himalaya Food International: Q3 Performance &amp; Strategic Roadmap Amidst Tariff Challenges</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Himalaya+Food+International+Ltd&title=Himalaya+Food+International%3A+Q3+Performance+%26+Strategic+Roadmap+Amidst+Tariff+Challenges&newsId=d02d3e45-dde5-4942-b59f-d8507c35acab&token=ZDAyZDNlNDUtZGRl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d02d3e45-dde5-4942-b59f-d8507c35acab</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:35:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Himalaya Food International&apos;s Q3 results showed resilience despite steep U.S. tariffs. The company is optimistic about a potential 18% tariff reduction and has shifted to an aggressive operational stance. A One-Time Settlement (OTS) has been successfully concluded, and the company is pursuing strategic asset monetization and investor engagement for future growth.</p><ul><li>Q3 results reflect resilience amidst U.S. tariffs</li><li>Optimism about potential 18% tariff reduction</li><li>Aggressive operational stance to regain order book momentum</li><li>Successful conclusion of One-Time Settlement (OTS)</li><li>Strategic asset monetization and investor engagement for future growth</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/467b2d2c-df5b-444a-bd7b-a5d35dcd9fdd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Himalaya Food International Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PRITIKAUTO] Pritika Auto Industries Reports 40.64% YoY Increase in Q3 FY26 Total Revenue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Pritika+Auto+Industries+Ltd&title=Pritika+Auto+Industries+Reports+40.64%25+YoY+Increase+in+Q3+FY26+Total+Revenue&newsId=23dfdbb6-1353-4b3e-9d24-e8bd05bc1b93&token=MjNkZmRiYjYtMTM1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23dfdbb6-1353-4b3e-9d24-e8bd05bc1b93</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Pritika Auto Industries Ltd, a leading manufacturer of tractor components in India, announced its unaudited results for the third quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company reported a 40.64% YoY increase in total revenue to Rs. 113.43 crore. The production volume also increased by 41.10% YoY to 13,160 tons. The company&apos;s EBITDA and PAT also saw a significant YoY growth of 37.01% and 29.43% respectively. The company is planning a strategic capital expenditure program aimed at capacity expansion, product enhancement, and operational efficiency improvements.</p><ul><li>Q3 FY26 Total Revenue increased by 40.64% YoY to Rs. 113.43 crore</li><li>Production volume for Q3 FY26 was at 13,160 tons, up 41.10% YoY</li><li>EBITDA for Q3 FY26 was Rs. 18.34 crore, up 37.01% YoY</li><li>Profit after Tax for Q3 FY26 was Rs. 5.73 crore, up 29.43% YoY</li><li>Company is planning a strategic capital expenditure program for capacity expansion and operational efficiency improvements</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3391c0aa-28c6-4c17-8df1-918f4d9df638.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Pritika Auto Industries Ltd | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PEIL] Premier Energy and Infrastructure Ltd Changes Statutory Auditor&apos;s Name</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Premier+Energy+and+Infrastructure+Ltd&title=Premier+Energy+and+Infrastructure+Ltd+Changes+Statutory+Auditor%27s+Name&newsId=2637c06d-5395-49cc-8141-208596d1e948&token=MjYzN2MwNmQtNTM5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2637c06d-5395-49cc-8141-208596d1e948</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 04:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Other</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Premier Energy and Infrastructure Ltd has announced a change in the name of its Statutory Auditor. The name of the Statutory Auditors has been changed from R. Sundararajan &amp; Associates to M/s N Raghavan &amp; Associates. This change does not affect the firm&apos;s constitution, ownership, management, scope of services, or professional responsibilities.</p><ul><li>Premier Energy and Infrastructure Ltd has changed the name of its Statutory Auditors</li><li>The new name of the Statutory Auditors is M/s N Raghavan &amp; Associates</li><li>The change does not affect the firm&apos;s constitution, ownership, management, scope of services, or professional responsibilities</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b57ca8b2-baa8-4ba8-ae68-d371004e147e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Premier Energy and Infrastructure Ltd | Category: Other</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SARVESHWAR] Sarveshwar Foods Delivers Robust 9M FY26 Performance; Revenue at £966.43 Crore, Net Profit Jumps 33.44%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sarveshwar+Foods+Ltd&title=Sarveshwar+Foods+Delivers+Robust+9M+FY26+Performance%3B+Revenue+at+%C2%A3966.43+Crore%2C+Net+Profit+Jumps+33.44%25&newsId=e39385d9-35a3-467e-9824-8b9286ca89d9&token=ZTM5Mzg1ZDktMzVh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e39385d9-35a3-467e-9824-8b9286ca89d9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 03:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Sarveshwar Foods Limited, one of India’s leading agro and organic FMCG companies, has announced its Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 &amp; 9M FY26. The company reported a revenue of £966.43 Crore and a net profit jump of 33.44% for the nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s EBITDA margin stands at 5.67%.</p><ul><li>Revenue from Operations: £966.43 Crore (22.45% YoY growth)</li><li>EBITDA: £254.42 Crore (4.96% YoY growth)</li><li>Net Profit: £224.47 Crore (33.44% YoY growth)</li><li>EBITDA Margin: 5.67%</li><li>Net Profit Margin: 21 bps YoY growth</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f69fe96b-c746-4fc9-a4e2-0823b789b413.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sarveshwar Foods Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RUSTOMJEE] Keystone Realtors Ltd. Selected for Large Society Redevelopment Project in Mumbai</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Keystone+Realtors+Ltd&title=Keystone+Realtors+Ltd.+Selected+for+Large+Society+Redevelopment+Project+in+Mumbai&newsId=48d62e79-7268-4965-a102-1409ca64053b&token=NDhkNjJlNzktNzI2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48d62e79-7268-4965-a102-1409ca64053b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 03:46:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Keystone Realtors Limited has been chosen as the developer for the redevelopment project of Om Nagar Co-operative Housing Society Federation Limited, comprising of 8 housing societies. The project will be developed on a land of approximately 20,569.90 square meters in Andheri (East), Mumbai, Maharashtra. The acquisition does not fall under related party transactions and does not require any governmental or regulatory approvals. The cost of acquisition and/or the price at which the shares are acquired is not applicable.</p><ul><li>Keystone Realtors Ltd. selected for large society redevelopment project</li><li>Project to redevelop Om Nagar Co-operative Housing Society Federation Limited&apos;s plot and premises</li><li>Project located in Andheri (East), Mumbai, Maharashtra</li><li>No related party transactions involved</li><li>No governmental or regulatory approvals required</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1e7b65ce-96eb-4784-aff7-6adc9cedf5c7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Keystone Realtors Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RUSTOMJEE] Keystone Realtors Selected as Developer for Large Society Redevelopment Project in Mumbai with GDV of ~Rs. 1,775 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Keystone+Realtors+Ltd&title=Keystone+Realtors+Selected+as+Developer+for+Large+Society+Redevelopment+Project+in+Mumbai+with+GDV+of+~Rs.+1%2C775+Crores&newsId=0b488cd0-f055-4601-aa2f-abecd9d37bca&token=MGI0ODhjZDAtZjA1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b488cd0-f055-4601-aa2f-abecd9d37bca</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 03:44:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Keystone Realtors Limited, a leading real estate developer in Mumbai, has been appointed as the Developer for a large society redevelopment project of Om Nagar Co-operative Housing Society Federation Limited. The project involves the redevelopment of eight housing societies located on a 20,569.90 square meter land parcel in Andheri (East), Mumbai. The proposed redevelopment will result in the rehousing of 637 existing members and is expected to unlock a significant free sale potential of ~5 Lakhs sq. ft. of RERA carpet area, with an estimated Gross Development Value (GDV) of ~Rs. 1,775 crores. This project aligns with Rustomjee’s strategy to build a diversified portfolio across ticket sizes and further deepens its footprint in Mumbai’s high-growth western suburbs.</p><ul><li>Keystone Realtors Limited selected as the Developer for the redevelopment project of Om Nagar Co-operative Housing Society Federation Limited.</li><li>The project involves the redevelopment of eight housing societies in Andheri (East), Mumbai, Maharashtra.</li><li>The proposed redevelopment will result in the rehousing of 637 existing members and is expected to unlock a significant free sale potential of ~5 Lakhs sq. ft. of RERA carpet area.</li><li>The estimated Gross Development Value (GDV) of the project is ~Rs. 1,775 crores.</li><li>This project aligns with Rustomjee’s strategy to build a diversified portfolio across ticket sizes and further deepen its footprint in Mumbai’s high-growth western suburbs.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/563ab3b9-0063-4930-9826-379621528d43.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Keystone Realtors Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EASEMYTRIP] EaseMyTrip Plans Strategic Capital Raise Up to 500 Cr to Strengthen Growth Momentum and Expand High-Potential Segments</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Easy+Trip+Planners+Ltd&title=EaseMyTrip+Plans+Strategic+Capital+Raise+Up+to+500+Cr+to+Strengthen+Growth+Momentum+and+Expand+High-Potential+Segments&newsId=9d71f5fb-f3ad-4d5f-91c2-17d446f04970&token=OWQ3MWY1ZmItZjNh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d71f5fb-f3ad-4d5f-91c2-17d446f04970</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 03:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>EaseMyTrip, one of India’s leading online travel-tech platforms, has announced plans to raise capital up to 500 Cr. The proposed capital raise is intended to support EaseMyTrip’s expansion across high-potential segments, particularly in hotels and holidays, while also enabling continued investments in technology, platform enhancement, and strategic opportunities aligned with its long-term business priorities. The move is aimed at providing additional flexibility to execute growth initiatives while maintaining a disciplined approach to capital allocation.</p><ul><li>EaseMyTrip plans to raise capital up to 500 Cr for growth and expansion</li><li>Funds to support expansion in high-potential segments like hotels and holidays</li><li>Continued investments in technology and platform enhancement</li><li>Funds to be raised through various modes including rights issue, QIP, preferential issue, private placement</li><li>EaseMyTrip is a leading online travel-tech platform in India, delivering consistent profitability and industry-leading EBITDA margins</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1eb710c4-6132-4ae6-a4b8-d5506d8636fe.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Easy Trip Planners Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HYUNDAI] Hyundai Motor India Announces Changes in Senior Management Personnel</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Hyundai+Motor+India+Ltd&title=Hyundai+Motor+India+Announces+Changes+in+Senior+Management+Personnel&newsId=72ab09cd-15a0-478e-83c9-6c2614221baf&token=NzJhYjA5Y2QtMTVh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72ab09cd-15a0-478e-83c9-6c2614221baf</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 03:32:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hyundai Motor India Ltd. has announced changes in its senior management personnel in accordance with the Change in Management Regulations, 2015 (SEBI LODR). The changes include the appointment of Mr. Madhurendra Malu as Senior Management Personnel and the exclusion of Mr. Anuraag Singh from the list of Senior Management Personnel, both effective from February 16, 2026. Mr. Malu brings over two decades of experience in the automobile industry and holds an MDI Gurgaon alumnus. His expertise in data-driven strategy and luxury mindset will accelerate the premium positioning and launch of Genesis in India.</p><ul><li>Hyundai Motor India announces changes in senior management personnel</li><li>Mr. Madhurendra Malu appointed as Senior Management Personnel</li><li>Mr. Malu has over two decades of experience in the automobile industry</li><li>Mr. Malu is an MDI Gurgaon alumnus</li><li>Mr. Malu&apos;s expertise in data-driven strategy and luxury mindset will accelerate the premium positioning and launch of Genesis in India</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b6540ae6-49db-40f1-8d7e-df815279494b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Hyundai Motor India Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>