<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:22:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SHARDA] ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund Acquires 0.26% Stake in Sharda Motor Industries Ltd.</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sharda+Motor+Industries+Ltd&title=ICICI+Prudential+Mutual+Fund+Acquires+0.26%25+Stake+in+Sharda+Motor+Industries+Ltd.&newsId=57feb933-f507-4dcc-85cd-a1e59967414e&token=NTdmZWI5MzMtZjUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57feb933-f507-4dcc-85cd-a1e59967414e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:21:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund has acquired 1,50,000 shares of Sharda Motor Industries Ltd., exceeding 5% of the paid-up capital of the company. This acquisition is for investment purposes and not for controlling interest. The schemes of the Fund hold these shares, which are listed on the BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange of India Limited.</p><ul><li>ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund acquires 1,50,000 shares of Sharda Motor Industries Ltd.</li><li>The acquisition exceeds 5% of the paid-up capital of the company.</li><li>The acquisition is for investment purposes and not for controlling interest.</li><li>The shares are held by schemes of the Fund.</li><li>The shares are listed on the BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange of India Limited.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/50227EF8_CF40_463F_8E26_5D10C1804B0B_204444.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sharda Motor Industries Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WENDT] Wendt (India) Ltd. to Consider Unaudited Financial Results and Interim Dividend Proposal for Q4 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=WENDT+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Wendt+%28India%29+Ltd.+to+Consider+Unaudited+Financial+Results+and+Interim+Dividend+Proposal+for+Q4+2025&newsId=92fe2c54-45a6-4fbf-a890-f13811fc1bc4&token=OTJmZTJjNTQtNDVh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">92fe2c54-45a6-4fbf-a890-f13811fc1bc4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:11:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Wendt (India) Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 21st January 2026 to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter/period ended 31st December 2025. The meeting will also discuss an Interim Dividend proposal for the financial year 2025-26, adhering to the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Wendt (India) Ltd. to consider and approve unaudited financial results for Q4 2025</li><li>Interim Dividend proposal for the financial year 2025-26 to be discussed</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b8a1cdab-51f3-463c-9f36-f33acd6e246e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: WENDT (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WAAREERTL] Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd. Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025, Reports 15.94 Crore Profit Before Tax</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Waaree+Renewable+Technologies+Ltd&title=Waaree+Renewable+Technologies+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Reports+15.94+Crore+Profit+Before+Tax&newsId=34fdd32a-9f7c-492b-b9d1-4cfd2c1c5a9c&token=MzRmZGQzMmEtOWY3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">34fdd32a-9f7c-492b-b9d1-4cfd2c1c5a9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:11:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd. has announced its un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s profit before tax stands at 15.94 crore. The Board of Directors has also approved the setting up of a new 80 MWac/120 MWp Solar Power Park at Buldhana, Maharashtra.</p><ul><li>Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd. reported a profit before tax of 15.94 crore for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 222.90 crore for the quarter and 4321.90 crore for the nine months period.</li><li>The Board of Directors has approved the setting up of a new 80 MWac/120 MWp Solar Power Park at Buldhana, Maharashtra.</li><li>The financial results include the results of four subsidiaries which have not been reviewed by their auditors.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d62c1065-ec85-40db-9873-f8624cd0df0f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Waaree Renewable Technologies Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SVPHOUSING] Ganesha Ecoverse Ltd to Merge with Associate Company GESL Spinners, Resulting Entity to be Listed on BSE-SME Platform</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SVP+Housing+Ltd&title=Ganesha+Ecoverse+Ltd+to+Merge+with+Associate+Company+GESL+Spinners%2C+Resulting+Entity+to+be+Listed+on+BSE-SME+Platform&newsId=895da473-4f23-43ee-9cb6-681543de6ad0&token=ODk1ZGE0NzMtNGYy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">895da473-4f23-43ee-9cb6-681543de6ad0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:57:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Merger</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ganesha Ecoverse Ltd, a company dealing with plastic and textile products, has announced that its Board of Directors has accorded in-principle approval for the merger of the Company into GESL Spinners Private Limited (GSPL), an associate company. The merger is deemed more appropriate as it would facilitate the merged entity to continue to avail the existing taxation and financial benefits available to GSPL and is in the best interest of the Company and its shareholders. The resulting entity shall be listed on the BSE-SME platform and there shall be no dilution of shareholders’ rights.</p><ul><li>Ganesha Ecoverse Ltd to merge with associate company GESL Spinners Private Limited</li><li>Merger to facilitate the merged entity to continue to avail existing taxation and financial benefits</li><li>Resulting entity to be listed on the BSE-SME platform</li><li>No dilution of shareholders’ rights</li><li>Merger in line with the Companies Act, 2013 and applicable SEBI Regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/19551868-c400-4398-aae9-b84c90ee3433.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SVP Housing Ltd | Category: Merger</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RAYMOND] Raymond Ltd: J.K. Investors (Bombay) Ltd Creates Pledge on Shares Worth 29.83%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RAYMOND+LTD.&title=Raymond+Ltd%3A+J.K.+Investors+%28Bombay%29+Ltd+Creates+Pledge+on+Shares+Worth+29.83%25&newsId=7eaeacfb-04b3-477a-9179-dccdd037079f&token=N2VhZWFjZmItMDRi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7eaeacfb-04b3-477a-9179-dccdd037079f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>On January 14, 2026, Raymond Ltd, a company listed on the National Stock Exchange of India Limited and BSE Limited, received a disclosure from J.K. Investors (Bombay) Ltd. The disclosure was regarding the creation of encumbrances on the shares of Raymond Limited. J.K. Investors (Bombay) Ltd, a promoter of Raymond Ltd, created a pledge on 19,861,793 shares, which is 29.83% of the total share capital. This pledge was made as collateral for a loan taken by J.K. Investors (Bombay) Ltd from Bajaj Finance Limited. The encumbered shares represent a significant portion of the total share capital, which could potentially impact the company&apos;s shareholding pattern and financial status.</p><ul><li>J.K. Investors (Bombay) Ltd creates pledge on 19,861,793 shares of Raymond Ltd, equivalent to 29.83% of the total share capital.</li><li>Pledge made as collateral for a loan taken by J.K. Investors (Bombay) Ltd from Bajaj Finance Limited.</li><li>This encumbrance could potentially impact the company&apos;s shareholding pattern and financial status.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/18498C5E_7AD9_4FCB_8D0C_DDA04363CD05_201434.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RAYMOND LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RAYMONDREL] J.K. Investors (Bombay) Ltd Encumbers Shares of Raymond Realty Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Raymond+Realty+Ltd&title=J.K.+Investors+%28Bombay%29+Ltd+Encumbers+Shares+of+Raymond+Realty+Ltd&newsId=f16ef3de-53a5-41e6-b9b8-b903d9d9e824&token=ZjE2ZWYzZGUtNTNh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f16ef3de-53a5-41e6-b9b8-b903d9d9e824</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:51:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Pledge</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>J.K. Investors (Bombay) Ltd has encumbered a significant portion of its shares in Raymond Realty Ltd, as per a disclosure made under Regulation 31(1) and 31(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. The total encumbered shares amount to 29.83% of the total shares of Raymond Realty Ltd. The encumbrance is primarily in the form of a pledge, serving as collateral for loans taken by the company.</p><ul><li>J.K. Investors (Bombay) Ltd encumbers 29.83% shares of Raymond Realty Ltd</li><li>Encumbrance in the form of pledge for loans taken by the company</li><li>14,37,471 shares already encumbered before the event</li><li>5,00,000 shares encumbered on 08/01/2026</li><li>Bajaj Finance Limited is the lender and trustee for the encumbered shares</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/DCC6B6FC_39D0_4034_94BB_1C20557928D6_201755.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Raymond Realty Ltd | Category: Pledge</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RAYMONDLSL] J.K. Investors (Bombay) Ltd Creates Encumbrances on Raymond Lifestyle Ltd Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Raymond+Lifestyle+Ltd&title=J.K.+Investors+%28Bombay%29+Ltd+Creates+Encumbrances+on+Raymond+Lifestyle+Ltd+Shares&newsId=ba1d8a32-c5cc-4f69-a1f5-c2d313061b49&token=YmExZDhhMzItYzVj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba1d8a32-c5cc-4f69-a1f5-c2d313061b49</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:47:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Encumbrances</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>J.K. Investors (Bombay) Ltd has created encumbrances on 38.02% of the total shares of Raymond Lifestyle Ltd. The encumbrances are primarily for collateral for loans taken by the company and group companies. The shares have been pledged to various entities including Bajaj Finance Limited, Helene Curtis Limited, and Sunitidevi Singhania Hospital Trust.</p><ul><li>J.K. Investors (Bombay) Ltd has created encumbrances on 38.02% of Raymond Lifestyle Ltd shares</li><li>The encumbrances are mainly for collateral for loans taken by the company and group companies</li><li>The shares have been pledged to various entities including Bajaj Finance Limited, Helene Curtis Limited, and Sunitidevi Singhania Hospital Trust</li><li>The total number of encumbered shares is 23,165,400</li><li>The encumbrance is in the form of a pledge</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9E1E9397_9E3B_439E_A139_1B40B432D128_200401.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Raymond Lifestyle Ltd | Category: Encumbrances</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PACEDIGITK] Pace Digitek Secures $3,757.25 Million Solar EPC Order from Bondada Engineering</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Pace+Digitek+Ltd&title=Pace+Digitek+Secures+%243%2C757.25+Million+Solar+EPC+Order+from+Bondada+Engineering&newsId=e48ce0bb-a50e-4447-a9d2-ff6944bfde36&token=ZTQ4Y2UwYmItYTUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e48ce0bb-a50e-4447-a9d2-ff6944bfde36</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:41:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Award</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Pace Digitek Limited, a leading provider of integrated power and passive telecom infrastructure solutions, has announced a significant domestic order for solar infrastructure development valued at $3,757.25 Million from Bondada Engineering Limited (BEL). The project scope includes engineering &amp; design, EPC services, and O&amp;M support for a 300 MW AC Solar Power Project. The project is scheduled for completion within 15 months from the receipt of the Letter of Award (LOA). This win will reinforce Pace Digitek&apos;s position in the renewable energy segment and support its strategic focus on expanding its footprint across solar and energy infrastructure projects in India.</p><ul><li>Pace Digitek secured a $3,757.25 Million order from Bondada Engineering for a 300 MW AC Solar Power Project</li><li>The project includes engineering, design, EPC services, and O&amp;M support</li><li>The project is scheduled for completion within 15 months from the receipt of the LOA</li><li>This win reinforces Pace Digitek&apos;s position in the renewable energy segment</li><li>The company is focused on expanding its footprint across solar and energy infrastructure projects in India</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/32fbac1e-fd71-4683-8d71-d25d2b0f129d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Pace Digitek Ltd | Category: Award</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JSL] Jindal Stainless Ltd. to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results for FY 2025-26 and Consider Interim Dividend</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JINDAL+STAINLESS+LTD.&title=Jindal+Stainless+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+FY+2025-26+and+Consider+Interim+Dividend&newsId=2ecc4ea6-4eac-47c5-a300-fd28da4af106&token=MmVjYzRlYTYtNGVh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ecc4ea6-4eac-47c5-a300-fd28da4af106</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jindal Stainless Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 21st January, 2026 to consider and approve unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The meeting will also discuss the potential declaration of an interim dividend for the financial year 2025-26. The trading window for dealing in securities of the Company, which was closed since 1st January, 2026, will reopen on 24th January, 2026.</p><ul><li>Jindal Stainless Ltd. to consider and approve unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December, 2025</li><li>Potential declaration of interim dividend for the financial year 2025-26</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities to reopen on 24th January, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/10a79a91-1887-4d71-bc76-c06b38ee480d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JINDAL STAINLESS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GAYATRI] Gayatri Sugars Granted Trading Approval for 13,99,996 Equity Shares Issued to Non-Promoters</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GAYATRI+SUGARS+LTD.&title=Gayatri+Sugars+Granted+Trading+Approval+for+13%2C99%2C996+Equity+Shares+Issued+to+Non-Promoters&newsId=64cfa72f-e93c-42fe-b1d3-6419f4bfac72&token=NjRjZmE3MmYtZTkz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">64cfa72f-e93c-42fe-b1d3-6419f4bfac72</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gayatri Sugars Ltd has received trading approval for 13,99,996 equity shares of Rs. 10/- each issued to non-promoters on a preferential basis. This approval is pursuant to the conversion of warrants issued on preferential basis. The trading of these securities will commence on the BSE Limited from January 16, 2026.</p><ul><li>Gayatri Sugars Ltd has received trading approval for 13,99,996 equity shares issued to non-promoters.</li><li>The approval is pursuant to the conversion of warrants issued on a preferential basis.</li><li>The trading of these securities will start on the BSE Limited from January 16, 2026.</li><li>The warrants are of Rs. 10/- each and will be issued at par.</li><li>The distinctive numbers of these shares will range from 64800306 to 66200301.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/277b971c-3b70-4e9e-a59f-e381aa7d0d6e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GAYATRI SUGARS LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>