<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:21:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[CENTUM] Centum Electronics Ltd Redesignates Dr. Vinod Chippalkatti as Chief Technology Officer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CENTUM+ELECTRONICS+LTD.&title=Centum+Electronics+Ltd+Redesignates+Dr.+Vinod+Chippalkatti+as+Chief+Technology+Officer&newsId=f926dc6c-ee97-473b-836d-b566fd84eb5c&token=ZjkyNmRjNmMtZWU5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f926dc6c-ee97-473b-836d-b566fd84eb5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:21:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Centum Electronics Ltd has redesignated Dr. Vinod Chippalkatti from his previous role as President - Strategic Electronics Business Unit (SEBU) to Chief Technology Officer (CTO) - Centum Group with immediate effect. He continues to be a part of the Senior Management of the Company. Dr. Chippalkatti has been with Centum for over 25 years, holding multiple leadership roles including heading the design and engineering function. He has contributed to India’s first series of communication satellites at ISRO before joining Centum. He holds a BE (ECE) from NITK Suratkal, a Master’s in Engineering from IISc Bangalore, a PhD, and a PG Diploma in IP Law from NLSIU, Bangalore. He is also a member of the Executive Committee of Indian Space Association (ISPA).</p><ul><li>Dr. Vinod Chippalkatti redesignated as Chief Technology Officer (CTO) - Centum Group</li><li>Over 25 years of experience at Centum Electronics Ltd</li><li>Previously held multiple leadership roles at Centum</li><li>Contributed to India’s first series of communication satellites at ISRO</li><li>Holds BE (ECE), Master’s in Engineering, PhD, and a PG Diploma in IP Law</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9ba2cf3a-7e14-48e3-bec8-124cf64523ac.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CENTUM ELECTRONICS LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HCLTECH] HCL Technologies Grants RSUs to Employees Under 2021 and 2024 Plans</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HCL+TECHNOLOGIES+LTD.&title=HCL+Technologies+Grants+RSUs+to+Employees+Under+2021+and+2024+Plans&newsId=0e952d88-382d-43c2-8a2f-7850dccd0af4&token=MGU5NTJkODgtMzgy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e952d88-382d-43c2-8a2f-7850dccd0af4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>HCL Technologies Ltd. has granted Restricted Stock Units (RSUs) to eligible employees under the HCL Technologies Limited - Restricted Stock Unit Plan 2021 (&apos;RSU Plan 2021&apos;) and HCL Technologies Limited - Restricted Stock Unit Plan 2024 (&apos;RSU Plan 2024&apos;). A total of 601 RSUs have been granted to one eligible employee under the RSU Plan 2021, while 24,659 RSUs have been granted to 5 eligible employees under the RSU Plan 2024. Each RSU, upon vesting and exercise, will entitle the holder to one fully paid-up equity share of INR 2/- each of the company. The RSU Plans are implemented through a trust mechanism, with the trust acquiring shares from the secondary market. No fresh shares will be issued by the company for these plans. The vesting period and exercise period for the RSUs vary for each plan, with the vested RSUs to be exercised within a maximum period of 6 months from the date of vesting. The exercise price is set at INR 2/- per RSU, which is the par value of the equity share. The grant of 23,925 RSUs under the RSU Plan 2024, which were previously approved, has been cancelled.</p><ul><li>HCL Technologies has granted RSUs to eligible employees under the RSU Plan 2021 and RSU Plan 2024.</li><li>601 RSUs granted to one eligible employee under the RSU Plan 2021.</li><li>24,659 RSUs granted to 5 eligible employees under the RSU Plan 2024.</li><li>RSUs to be exercised within 6 months from the date of vesting.</li><li>No fresh shares to be issued by the company for these plans.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/63c8597c-14c2-44ad-bda9-372110aab903.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HCL TECHNOLOGIES LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FIRSTCRY] Brainbees Solutions Completes Acquisition of Solis Hygiene, Increasing Indirect Stake to 76.59%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Brainbees+Solutions+Ltd&title=Brainbees+Solutions+Completes+Acquisition+of+Solis+Hygiene%2C+Increasing+Indirect+Stake+to+76.59%25&newsId=38668e12-e2bd-4493-b418-495a477401c8&token=Mzg2NjhlMTItZTJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">38668e12-e2bd-4493-b418-495a477401c8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 15:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Brainbees Solutions Limited has completed the acquisition of Solis Hygiene Private Limited through its subsidiary, Swara Baby Products Private Limited. The acquisition was made in consideration of 52,890 Series A1 Equity Shares held by Brainbees Solutions in Solis Hygiene. Post-acquisition, Swara Baby has become the wholly-owned subsidiary of Brainbees Solutions, and Solis Hygiene has become a step-down subsidiary. Consequently, the indirect control of Brainbees Solutions in Solis Hygiene has increased from 75.92% to 76.59%.</p><ul><li>Brainbees Solutions Limited has completed the acquisition of Solis Hygiene Private Limited.</li><li>The acquisition was made through its subsidiary, Swara Baby Products Private Limited.</li><li>Swara Baby has become the wholly-owned subsidiary of Brainbees Solutions.</li><li>Solis Hygiene has become a step-down subsidiary of Brainbees Solutions.</li><li>The indirect control of Brainbees Solutions in Solis Hygiene has increased to 76.59%.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3aa2b1d1-d519-4484-9e19-39a15145b2d1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Brainbees Solutions Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TRL] Taylormade Renewables Ltd. fails to receive subscription for proposed preferential issue of 3,00,000 Convertible Warrants</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Taylormade+Renewables+Ltd&title=Taylormade+Renewables+Ltd.+fails+to+receive+subscription+for+proposed+preferential+issue+of+3%2C00%2C000+Convertible+Warrants&newsId=eeb5bf5e-05ae-4ceb-92b5-e81148ed7c46&token=ZWViNWJmNWUtMDVh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eeb5bf5e-05ae-4ceb-92b5-e81148ed7c46</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:57:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Other</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Taylormade Renewables Ltd. has announced that the proposed preferential issue of 3,00,000 Convertible Warrants, approved by BSE Limited and shareholders, did not materialize due to non-receipt of subscription money from the proposed allottees within the stipulated time. Consequently, no warrants were allotted and no equity shares will arise against these warrants.</p><ul><li>Taylormade Renewables Ltd. did not receive subscription for proposed preferential issue of 3,00,000 Convertible Warrants</li><li>The proposed allottees belonged to the Non-Promoter category</li><li>The issue price was 3222.5 per equity share</li><li>The approval was from BSE Limited and shareholders</li><li>No warrants were allotted and no equity shares will arise against these warrants</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9418b6e1-096c-4b46-a143-e3e273a46363.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Taylormade Renewables Ltd | Category: Other</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DEVYANI] Devyani International Completes Sale of 51% Stake in Peanutbutter</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Devyani+International+Ltd&title=Devyani+International+Completes+Sale+of+51%25+Stake+in+Peanutbutter&newsId=287aef99-ab5c-418e-a7e4-f2f2db59b2e7&token=Mjg3YWVmOTktYWI1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">287aef99-ab5c-418e-a7e4-f2f2db59b2e7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Devyani International Ltd has announced the completion of the sale of its entire 51% equity stake held in Peanutbutter and Jelly Private Limited. This announcement comes after the company&apos;s earlier intimation on December 30, 2025, where it was informed that Sky Gate Hospitality Private Limited, a subsidiary company, had executed a Share Purchase Agreement with Heritage Foods Limited for the sale of its entire 51% equity stake held in Peanutbutter. As a result, Peanutbutter has ceased to be a subsidiary of Sky Gate and a step-down subsidiary of Devyani International Ltd with immediate effect.</p><ul><li>Devyani International Ltd has completed the sale of its 51% equity stake in Peanutbutter and Jelly Private Limited.</li><li>The sale was initially announced on December 30, 2025, and has now been finalized.</li><li>Peanutbutter was a subsidiary of Sky Gate Hospitality Private Limited and a step-down subsidiary of Devyani International Ltd.</li><li>Following the sale, Peanutbutter has ceased to be a subsidiary of Sky Gate and a step-down subsidiary of Devyani International Ltd.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0e69298a-d4ef-418f-ac02-19ee3f6b16db.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Devyani International Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RELIANCE] Reliance Industries Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RELIANCE+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Reliance+Industries+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025&newsId=47140d82-6b4e-464a-9699-8d43582b14ea&token=NDcxNDBkODItNmI0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47140d82-6b4e-464a-9699-8d43582b14ea</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:47:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Reliance Industries Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 16, 2026, to consider and approve the standalone and consolidated unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company will also hold an analyst meet after the Board Meeting to discuss the financial results.</p><ul><li>Reliance Industries Ltd&apos;s Board of Directors to meet on January 16, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the standalone and consolidated unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>The company will hold an analyst meet after the Board Meeting to discuss the financial results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f0a88c04-40b7-4697-a903-d8671e912d17.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RELIANCE INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZOMATO] Eternal Ltd Receives GST Demand of INR 16.72 Crore from West Bengal Authority</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Zomato+Ltd&title=Eternal+Ltd+Receives+GST+Demand+of+INR+16.72+Crore+from+West+Bengal+Authority&newsId=54df7e8d-4fa1-431d-93bf-8029e3ddcabf&token=NTRkZjdlOGQtNGZh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54df7e8d-4fa1-431d-93bf-8029e3ddcabf</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:41:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Eternal Limited has informed the exchange about two orders received from the Additional Commissioner of State Tax (Appeals), West Bengal. The orders, received on 08 January 2026, confirm a total demand of GST of INR 16,72,34,030/- (Rupees Sixteen Crore Seventy Two Lakh Thirty Four Thousand and Thirty only) with interest of INR 9,16,48,814/- (Rupees Nine Crore Sixteen Lakh Forty Eight Thousand Eight Hundred and Fourteen only) and penalty of INR 1,67,23,404/- (Rupees One Crore Sixty Seven Lakh Twenty Three Thousand Four Hundred and Four only) for the period April 2020 to March 2022. The Company believes it has a strong case and will file appeals against the orders before the appropriate authority.</p><ul><li>Eternal Limited received two orders from Additional Commissioner of State Tax (Appeals), West Bengal</li><li>Orders confirm total demand of GST of INR 16,72,34,030/-</li><li>Demand includes interest of INR 9,16,48,814/- and penalty of INR 1,67,23,404/-</li><li>Orders are for the period April 2020 to March 2022</li><li>Company believes it has a strong case and will file appeals</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7b36bc80-362d-4683-8e07-8659593dcfbe.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Zomato Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HINDUNILVR] Hindustan Unilever Faces INR 1559.69 Cr Demand in Income Tax Assessment Order</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HINDUSTAN+UNILEVER+LTD.&title=Hindustan+Unilever+Faces+INR+1559.69+Cr+Demand+in+Income+Tax+Assessment+Order&newsId=f34b183a-27f7-4af6-9baf-e8901a24d754&token=ZjM0YjE4M2EtMjdm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f34b183a-27f7-4af6-9baf-e8901a24d754</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:41:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Taxation</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hindustan Unilever Ltd has received an Assessment Order under section 143(3) read with Sec. 144C(13) of the Income Tax Act, 1961, along with a notice of demand of INR 1559.69 crs under section 156 of the ITA. The order pertains to the disallowance of payments to related parties and challenges the pricing. The order was received on 7th January 2026 from the Assistant Commissioner of Income-Tax, Central Circle 5(2), Mumbai. The company is expected to take necessary actions in response to this communication.</p><ul><li>Hindustan Unilever received an Assessment Order under section 143(3) read with Sec. 144C(13) of the Income Tax Act, 1961</li><li>Notice of demand of INR 1559.69 crs under section 156 of the ITA</li><li>Order pertains to the disallowance of payments to related parties</li><li>Order received on 7th January 2026</li><li>Company expected to take necessary actions</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c2cf9a4b-1490-43d5-88c6-5d44610bd383.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HINDUSTAN UNILEVER LTD. | Category: Taxation</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RECLTD] REC Ltd Achieves &apos;Excellent&apos; Rating in MOU Performance for Financial Year 2024-25</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=REC+Ltd&title=REC+Ltd+Achieves+%27Excellent%27+Rating+in+MOU+Performance+for+Financial+Year+2024-25&newsId=208ecb6d-53ef-4895-b62c-6f05b4a29354&token=MjA4ZWNiNmQtNTNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">208ecb6d-53ef-4895-b62c-6f05b4a29354</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>MoU</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>REC Ltd, named in the text, has achieved an &apos;Excellent&apos; rating in the Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) Performance for the financial year 2024-25 with the Holding company, Power Finance Corporation Limited. This rating is awarded by the Department of Public Enterprises (DPE), Ministry of Finance, as per their guidelines. REC has maintained this &apos;Excellent&apos; rating for three consecutive financial years, highlighting its consistent operational and financial performance.</p><ul><li>REC Ltd achieved an &apos;Excellent&apos; rating in the MoU Performance for the financial year 2024-25</li><li>This is the third consecutive year REC has received this rating</li><li>The rating was awarded by the Department of Public Enterprises (DPE), Ministry of Finance</li><li>The MoU was signed with the Holding company, Power Finance Corporation Limited</li><li>This rating reflects REC&apos;s consistent operational and financial performance</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1ebc1d5a-d038-49c8-a3d9-4b00586e6700.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: REC Ltd | Category: MoU</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PREMIERENE] Premier Energies Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Premier+Energies+Ltd&title=Premier+Energies+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=bfd8a955-555f-49ab-ae3a-d00d2427e641&token=YmZkOGE5NTUtNTU1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bfd8a955-555f-49ab-ae3a-d00d2427e641</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:37:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Premier Energies Ltd has informed the BSE that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on 22/01/2026. The meeting will consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results of the Company for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company will be closed for all the Directors, Key Managerial Persons, Designated Persons, and their Immediate Relatives from January 01, 2026 till 48 hours after the declaration of the Unaudited Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Premier Energies Ltd scheduled a Board Meeting on 22/01/2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company will be closed for all the Directors, Key Managerial Persons, Designated Persons, and their Immediate Relatives from January 01, 2026 till 48 hours after the declaration of the Unaudited Financial Results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3199a150-a3bd-4dcc-a34d-3de8cf241e27.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Premier Energies Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>