<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:52:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[GLAXO] GlaxoSmithKline Pharmaceuticals Ltd Appoints Mr. Ronojit Biswas as Whole-Time Director &amp; CFO</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GLAXOSMITHKLINE+PHARMACEUTICALS+LTD.&title=GlaxoSmithKline+Pharmaceuticals+Ltd+Appoints+Mr.+Ronojit+Biswas+as+Whole-Time+Director+%26+CFO&newsId=82f9158e-35ab-439a-a07b-64e1cf9984ca&token=ODJmOTE1OGUtMzVh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">82f9158e-35ab-439a-a07b-64e1cf9984ca</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:47:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>GlaxoSmithKline Pharmaceuticals Ltd has announced the appointment of Mr. Ronojit Biswas as the Whole-Time Director &amp; Chief Financial Officer (CFO) for a term of three years starting from 15th April 2026. Mr. Biswas, who has over 25 years of experience with GSK across international markets, will take over from Mr. Juby Chandy, the current CFO, who will transition into a new role in the GSK Group. Mr. Biswas has previously served as CFO for GSK&apos;s Brazil and its Vietnam Businesses, and has completed a Post Graduate Program in Management (Finance) from the Management Development Institute, Gurgaon.</p><ul><li>Mr. Ronojit Biswas appointed as Whole-Time Director &amp; CFO of GlaxoSmithKline Pharmaceuticals Ltd for a term of three years starting from 15th April 2026.</li><li>Mr. Biswas has over 25 years of experience with GSK across international markets.</li><li>Mr. Juby Chandy, the current CFO, will transition into a new role in the GSK Group.</li><li>Mr. Biswas has previously served as CFO for GSK&apos;s Brazil and its Vietnam Businesses.</li><li>Mr. Biswas has completed a Post Graduate Program in Management (Finance) from the Management Development Institute, Gurgaon.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/56ec471a-ae8c-4153-bbf4-36ed54804dba.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GLAXOSMITHKLINE PHARMACEUTICALS LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PICCADIL] Piccadily Agro Industries to Approve Allotment of Equity Shares to Eligible Employees</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PICCADILY+AGRO+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Piccadily+Agro+Industries+to+Approve+Allotment+of+Equity+Shares+to+Eligible+Employees&newsId=315a6507-f3d3-4816-be77-d0caa968f723&token=MzE1YTY1MDctZjNk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">315a6507-f3d3-4816-be77-d0caa968f723</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:47:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>ESOP</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Piccadily Agro Industries Ltd has announced that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on 06/03/2026. The meeting will consider and approve the allotment of 2092 equity shares of Rs.10/-each to the Eligible Employees/Grantees. This is pursuant to the exercise of Options granted under Piccadily Agro Employee Stock Option Plan 2024, as per Regulation 29 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015 and other applicable Regulations.</p><ul><li>Piccadily Agro Industries Ltd to consider and approve allotment of equity shares to eligible employees</li><li>Allotment pursuant to the exercise of Options granted under Piccadily Agro Employee Stock Option Plan 2024</li><li>Meeting of the Board of Directors scheduled on 06/03/2026</li><li>Allotment as per Regulation 29 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>2092 equity shares of Rs.10/-each to be allotted</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/46cb6acb-daa2-490c-882c-4a7f350b367d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PICCADILY AGRO INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: ESOP</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SURAKSHA] Suraksha Diagnostic Ltd Announces Resignation of Group Chief Financial Officer (CFO) Mr. K S Ravindra</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Suraksha+Diagnostic+Ltd&title=Suraksha+Diagnostic+Ltd+Announces+Resignation+of+Group+Chief+Financial+Officer+%28CFO%29+Mr.+K+S+Ravindra&newsId=bc030b68-97df-4057-8a6e-6484859492ab&token=YmMwMzBiNjgtOTdk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc030b68-97df-4057-8a6e-6484859492ab</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:41:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Suraksha Diagnostic Ltd has announced the resignation of its Group Chief Financial Officer (CFO), Mr. K S Ravindra, who is designated as Key Managerial Personnel (KMP) of the Company. Mr. Ravindra tendered his resignation on 02 March 2026, citing personal reasons. His last working day with the Company will be on or before 31 May 2026. The Company has expressed its appreciation for Mr. Ravindra&apos;s services and his contributions during his tenure.</p><ul><li>Suraksha Diagnostic Ltd announces the resignation of its Group Chief Financial Officer (CFO), Mr. K S Ravindra.</li><li>Mr. Ravindra tendered his resignation on 02 March 2026 due to personal reasons.</li><li>His last working day with the Company will be on or before 31 May 2026.</li><li>The Company has expressed its appreciation for Mr. Ravindra&apos;s services and his contributions.</li><li>The resignation has been made in compliance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d772ea72-6c86-4898-af9a-d667c0e995a2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Suraksha Diagnostic Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IRFC] Indian Railway Finance Corporation Ltd: President of India Proposes to Sell 2% Equity Shares via Offer for Sale</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Indian+Railway+Finance+Corporation+Ltd&title=Indian+Railway+Finance+Corporation+Ltd%3A+President+of+India+Proposes+to+Sell+2%25+Equity+Shares+via+Offer+for+Sale&newsId=40444ecc-eca8-47c6-8c99-bd024af3e066&token=NDA0NDRlY2MtZWNh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40444ecc-eca8-47c6-8c99-bd024af3e066</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:39:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Sale</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>The President of India, acting through the Ministry of Railways, Government of India, proposed to sell up to 26,13,70,120 Equity Shares (representing 2% of the total paid up equity share capital of the Company) on February 25, 2026, for non-Retail Investors and on February 26, 2026, for Retail Investors, Employees and for non-Retail Investors who choose to carry forward their un-allotted bids from T day. This was done in accordance with the SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011, as amended. Additionally, 25,000 Equity Shares were offered to eligible employees of the Company.</p><ul><li>President of India proposes to sell 2% equity shares of Indian Railway Finance Corporation Ltd.</li><li>Sale to occur in two phases: February 25, 2026, for non-Retail Investors and February 26, 2026, for Retail Investors, Employees and for non-Retail Investors who choose to carry forward their un-allotted bids from T day.</li><li>Additional 25,000 Equity Shares offered to eligible employees of the Company.</li><li>Sale conducted in accordance with the SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011, as amended.</li><li>Offer for Sale commenced on February 25, 2026, and ended on February 26, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9412983B_536B_4444_8034_FE55ED6F8613_120616.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Indian Railway Finance Corporation Ltd | Category: Sale</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EDELWEISS] Edelweiss Financial Services Limited Announces 33,500 Million Public Issue of Secured Redeemable Non-Convertible Debentures</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Edelweiss+Financial+Services+Ltd.&title=Edelweiss+Financial+Services+Limited+Announces+33%2C500+Million+Public+Issue+of+Secured+Redeemable+Non-Convertible+Debentures&newsId=065b048e-cfc7-4c4c-a293-67024bde3896&token=MDY1YjA0OGUtY2Zj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">065b048e-cfc7-4c4c-a293-67024bde3896</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:35:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Edelweiss Financial Services Limited (EFSL) announced the public issue of Secured Redeemable Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs) of the face value of 21,000 each for an amount up to 1,750 million with a green shoe option of up to 1,750 million, cumulatively aggregating up to 33,500 million. The Issue has 10 series of NCDs carrying fixed coupons and having a tenure of 24 months, 36 months, 60 months, and 120 months with annual, monthly and cumulative interest options. The effective annual interest yield on the NCDs ranges from 8.64% p.a. to 10.01% p.a. The Issue is scheduled to open on March 2, 2026 and will close on March 16, 2026. At least 75% of the funds raised through this Issue will be used for the purpose of repayment/prepayment of interest and principal of existing borrowings of the Company and the balance is proposed to be utilised for general corporate purposes.</p><ul><li>Edelweiss Financial Services Limited announces a public issue of Secured Redeemable Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs) worth up to 33,500 million</li><li>The NCDs have a fixed coupon rate and varying tenures from 24 months to 120 months</li><li>The effective annual interest yield on the NCDs ranges from 8.64% p.a. to 10.01% p.a.</li><li>The Issue will open on March 2, 2026 and close on March 16, 2026</li><li>At least 75% of the funds raised will be used for repayment/prepayment of existing borrowings</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/49b9254d-7eec-4cf8-b42f-22be6c2d7a35.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Edelweiss Financial Services Ltd. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MAYURUNIQ] Mayur Uniquoters Ltd. Appoints Mrs. Puja Poddar as President- HR and Administration and SMP</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MAYUR+UNIQUOTERS+LTD.-%24&title=Mayur+Uniquoters+Ltd.+Appoints+Mrs.+Puja+Poddar+as+President-+HR+and+Administration+and+SMP&newsId=d6fa9b1f-d843-4c77-9684-03746921a8e9&token=ZDZmYTliMWYtZDg0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6fa9b1f-d843-4c77-9684-03746921a8e9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mayur Uniquoters Ltd. has approved the appointment of Mrs. Puja Poddar as President- HR and Administration and Senior Management Personnel (SMP) of the Company. The appointment was made during the Board of Directors meeting held on March 02, 2026 through Video Conferencing (VC)/Other Audio Visual Means (OAVM). Mrs. Puja Poddar has around five years of work experience in Mayur Uniquoters Limited and has expertise in formulating premium grade materials aligned with international quality standards and specifications. She has represented the organization at international levels including technical engagements with globally known companies like Mercedes Benz. Her academic qualification is Bachelor of Commerce (B.Com) from Sydenham College of Commerce &amp; Economics, Mumbai. She is also a Certified Health Coach from the Institute for Integrative Nutrition (IIN), New York, USA and an Access Consciousness (USA) Practioner.</p><ul><li>Mrs. Puja Poddar appointed as President- HR and Administration and SMP of Mayur Uniquoters Ltd.</li><li>Mrs. Poddar has around five years of work experience in Mayur Uniquoters Limited.</li><li>She has expertise in formulating premium grade materials aligned with international quality standards and specifications.</li><li>Mrs. Poddar has represented the organization at international levels including technical engagements with globally known companies like Mercedes Benz.</li><li>Mrs. Poddar is a Certified Health Coach from the Institute for Integrative Nutrition (IIN), New York, USA and an Access Consciousness (USA) Practioner.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4296b04f-9725-4a56-88b0-ff92ebff0ae8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MAYUR UNIQUOTERS LTD.-$ | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ATULAUTO] Atul Auto Ltd. Reports 14.2% YoY Increase in Total Sales for February 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ATUL+AUTO+LTD.-%24&title=Atul+Auto+Ltd.+Reports+14.2%25+YoY+Increase+in+Total+Sales+for+February+2026&newsId=ec0156ce-0752-47af-a19c-ed1d1450bee5&token=ZWMwMTU2Y2UtMDc1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ec0156ce-0752-47af-a19c-ed1d1450bee5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Atul Auto Ltd. has reported its sales performance for the month of February 2026. The company&apos;s total sales for the month stood at 3,429 units, representing a 14.2% year-over-year increase from 2,900 units in February 2025. The domestic sales saw a growth of 7.79% YoY, while exports increased by 20.72%. The 3W - IC Engine segment showed a significant increase of 26.96%, while the EV segment saw a decline of 10.97% and 58.24% for the L5 category.</p><ul><li>Atul Auto Ltd. reports a 14.2% YoY increase in total sales for February 2026</li><li>Domestic sales grow by 7.79% YoY</li><li>Exports increase by 20.72% YoY</li><li>3W - IC Engine sales surge by 26.96%</li><li>EV segment experiences a decline of 10.97% and 58.24% for the L5 category</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b17e9762-343f-434e-bb62-6c44c44ab1ce.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ATUL AUTO LTD.-$ | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[POLYPLEX] Polyplex Corporation Ltd Clarifies on Volume Movement, Confirms Compliance with SEBI Regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=POLYPLEX+CORPORATION+LTD.&title=Polyplex+Corporation+Ltd+Clarifies+on+Volume+Movement%2C+Confirms+Compliance+with+SEBI+Regulations&newsId=328abd34-7a71-4b49-b6b1-d553db8b2ef9&token=MzI4YWJkMzQtN2E3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">328abd34-7a71-4b49-b6b1-d553db8b2ef9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Polyplex Corporation Ltd, in response to an email from the Exchange, confirmed that they have been timely informing the Exchange of all price sensitive information as required by Regulation 30 of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015. The company stated that there is no additional information or pending furnishing required as of now.</p><ul><li>Polyplex Corporation Ltd confirms timely compliance with SEBI regulations</li><li>Company has been informing Exchange of all price sensitive information as required</li><li>No additional information or pending furnishing required as of now</li><li>Clarification comes in response to an email from the Exchange</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/895c5488-40d7-4abc-961e-7e10c4386e40.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: POLYPLEX CORPORATION LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GAUDIUMIVF] Gaudium IVF and Women Health Ltd Announces Trading Window Closure</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Gaudium+IVF+and+Women+Health+Ltd&title=Gaudium+IVF+and+Women+Health+Ltd+Announces+Trading+Window+Closure&newsId=fba4e950-c48e-4173-9e4a-1d977ec3e242&token=ZmJhNGU5NTAtYzQ4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fba4e950-c48e-4173-9e4a-1d977ec3e242</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:27:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gaudium IVF and Women Health Ltd has announced the closure of its trading window for designated persons and their immediate relatives. The closure is in compliance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, and the Company’s ‘Code of conduct for regulating, monitoring and reporting of trading by Insiders&apos; and ‘Code of practices and procedures for fair disclosure of unpublished price sensitive information’. The trading window will remain closed from Friday, February 27, 2026, till the expiry of 48 hours after the announcement of un-audited financial results of the Company for the quarter and nine months period ended December 31, 2025. The date of the meeting of the Board of Directors of the Company to approve the financial results will be intimated separately.</p><ul><li>Gaudium IVF and Women Health Ltd closes trading window for designated persons and their immediate relatives</li><li>Closure in compliance with Securities and Exchange Board of India (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Trading window to remain closed till the expiry of 48 hours after the announcement of un-audited financial results for Q3 2025</li><li>The date of the Board of Directors&apos; meeting to approve the financial results will be intimated separately</li><li>Announcement made to ensure compliance with the Company’s ‘Code of conduct for regulating, monitoring and reporting of trading by Insiders&apos; and ‘Code of practices and procedures for fair disclosure of unpublished price sensitive information’</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4d93e082-e5c4-4b65-bb76-c7c8f66bbf65.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Gaudium IVF and Women Health Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UTKARSHBNK] Completion of Term for Non-Executive Non-Independent Director at Utkarsh Small Finance Bank Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Utkarsh+Small+Finance+Bank+Ltd&title=Completion+of+Term+for+Non-Executive+Non-Independent+Director+at+Utkarsh+Small+Finance+Bank+Ltd&newsId=c5db6f93-4fb7-4cd1-944e-94b94a09ba6b&token=YzVkYjZmOTMtNGZi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5db6f93-4fb7-4cd1-944e-94b94a09ba6b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:25:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Utkarsh Small Finance Bank Ltd has announced the completion of the first term of Mr. Muralidharan Rajamani as a Non-Executive Non-Independent Director. He ceased to be a Director of the Bank on March 2, 2026, after completing his five-year term on March 1, 2026. The Bank has expressed gratitude for his contributions during his tenure.</p><ul><li>Completion of Mr. Muralidharan Rajamani&apos;s first term as Non-Executive Non-Independent Director at Utkarsh Small Finance Bank Ltd.</li><li>Mr. Rajamani ceased to be a Director of the Bank on March 2, 2026.</li><li>The Bank has appreciated Mr. Rajamani&apos;s contributions during his tenure.</li><li>Mr. Rajamani has decided not to offer himself for reappointment.</li><li>The announcement was made in accordance with SEBI Listing Regulations and SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/CFD/PoD2/CIR/P/0155 dated November 11, 2024.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/79158247-4fca-4a95-b8ae-a7026805e7b0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Utkarsh Small Finance Bank Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>