<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 18:56:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SANCODE] Sancode Technologies Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Discuss Fund Raising</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sancode+Technologies+Ltd&title=Sancode+Technologies+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Discuss+Fund+Raising&newsId=4dd0cdf4-dce7-41ed-a917-c9c89e4c6e20&token=NGRkMGNkZjQtZGNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4dd0cdf4-dce7-41ed-a917-c9c89e4c6e20</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:54:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sancode Technologies Ltd has informed the BSE that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on 26/02/2026. The agenda includes considering a proposal for fund raising through preferential allotment of equity shares, convertible warrants, or other instruments for cash or other than cash. The proposal is subject to approval from shareholders and compliance with applicable laws. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the company is closed for all connected persons, officers, designated employees, insiders, directors, and their immediate relatives until the end of 48 hours from the conclusion of the Board Meeting.</p><ul><li>Sancode Technologies Ltd schedules Board Meeting on 26/02/2026</li><li>Fund raising through preferential allotment of equity shares, convertible warrants, or other instruments</li><li>Fund raising to consider cash or other than cash</li><li>Subject to approval from shareholders and compliance with applicable laws</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the securities of the company is closed</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/46f08163-28e9-4723-97d4-ca065d27b815.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sancode Technologies Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MOBIKWIK] Mobikwik Securities Broking Private Limited Approved as Trading Member on BSE Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=One+Mobikwik+Systems+Ltd&title=Mobikwik+Securities+Broking+Private+Limited+Approved+as+Trading+Member+on+BSE+Limited&newsId=3cb595f7-989d-4eff-b109-26a30439b6ae&token=M2NiNTk1ZjctOTg5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3cb595f7-989d-4eff-b109-26a30439b6ae</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:51:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Mobikwik Securities Broking Private Limited, a wholly owned subsidiary of One Mobikwik Systems Ltd, has received approval for commencement of business as a trading member on BSE Limited. This approval comes after the company received the Certificate of Registration as a stock broker/clearing member under the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Stock-Brokers) Regulations, 1992. The approval was received on February 23, 2026.</p><ul><li>Mobikwik Securities Broking Private Limited received approval for commencement of business as a trading member on BSE Limited</li><li>The approval was received after obtaining the Certificate of Registration as a stock broker/clearing member under the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Stock-Brokers) Regulations, 1992</li><li>Mobikwik Securities Broking Private Limited is a wholly owned subsidiary of One Mobikwik Systems Ltd</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/65a82c03-b583-4899-871d-d48ca4e3cc77.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: One Mobikwik Systems Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FUSION] Fusion Finance Ltd Proposes Reclassification of Mr. Devesh Sachdev &amp; Family from Promoter to Public Category Shareholders</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Fusion+Micro+Finance+Ltd&title=Fusion+Finance+Ltd+Proposes+Reclassification+of+Mr.+Devesh+Sachdev+%26+Family+from+Promoter+to+Public+Category+Shareholders&newsId=b79ee272-6f71-43f7-89f2-b6fa27a34977&token=Yjc5ZWUyNzItNmY3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b79ee272-6f71-43f7-89f2-b6fa27a34977</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 17:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Fusion Finance Ltd has announced a proposal to reclassify Mr. Devesh Sachdev and his family members from the &apos;Promoter &amp; Promoter Group&apos; category to the &apos;Public&apos; category of shareholders. This decision follows a structured leadership and governance transition, with Mr. Sachdev resigning as Managing Director in September 2025 and stepping down from the Board of Directors in November 2025. He has not been involved in the management or day-to-day affairs of the Company since then. The Company had kept stakeholders informed of these developments through timely stock exchange disclosures and formal communications with lenders. The proposed reclassification is a natural progression of the governance transition already effected, ensuring that shareholding classification accurately reflects the Company’s evolved management and control structure. The reclassification request will be placed before the Board of Directors, followed by an application with the Stock Exchanges for their no-objection/ approval, and then shareholders’ approval. The other promoter entities will continue to remain classified as promoters and will continue to hold majority shareholding in the Company.</p><ul><li>Fusion Finance Ltd proposes reclassification of Mr. Devesh Sachdev and his family members from &apos;Promoter &amp; Promoter Group&apos; to &apos;Public&apos; category shareholders.</li><li>Mr. Sachdev resigned as Managing Director in September 2025 and stepped down from the Board of Directors in November 2025.</li><li>The Company had kept stakeholders informed of these developments through timely stock exchange disclosures and formal communications with lenders.</li><li>The proposed reclassification is a natural progression of the governance transition already effected.</li><li>The reclassification request will be placed before the Board of Directors, followed by an application with the Stock Exchanges for their no-objection/ approval, and then shareholders’ approval.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/482d41e4-8ff0-4d4e-88e3-9ee5daa897a0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Fusion Micro Finance Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LANCER] Lancer Container Lines Ltd Receives Disclosures Under SEBI Regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Lancer+Container+Lines+Ltd&title=Lancer+Container+Lines+Ltd+Receives+Disclosures+Under+SEBI+Regulations&newsId=b78b9e75-4560-48f6-ac57-a3b0318fe910&token=Yjc4YjllNzUtNDU2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b78b9e75-4560-48f6-ac57-a3b0318fe910</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:52:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Lancer Container Lines Ltd has received disclosures from several persons pursuant to Regulation 29(1) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. The disclosures were made by Mr. Miju Kattukaran Antony Kattukaran Vareed Antony, Mr. Prafulla Kumar Jha Someshwar Jha, Mr. Muhammad Noufal Balliyod Master Abdullakunhi, and Ms. Naeema Cheruvanthan Kandy Mahin Kottikkulum Moola. The acquirers have acquired a significant number of shares, resulting in a change in the company&apos;s shareholding pattern.</p><ul><li>Lancer Container Lines Ltd has received disclosures from several persons under SEBI regulations.</li><li>The disclosures were made by Mr. Miju Kattukaran Antony Kattukaran Vareed Antony, Mr. Prafulla Kumar Jha Someshwar Jha, Mr. Muhammad Noufal Balliyod Master Abdullakunhi, and Ms. Naeema Cheruvanthan Kandy Mahin Kottikkulum Moola.</li><li>The acquirers have acquired a significant number of shares, leading to a change in the company&apos;s shareholding pattern.</li><li>The total shares acquired by the first acquirer are 2,46,88,658, which is 6.99% of the total voting rights.</li><li>The total shares acquired by the second acquirer are also 2,46,88,658, which is also 6.99% of the total voting rights.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/11dcc740-b6b3-4aff-a7ff-599ff8e2d067.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Lancer Container Lines Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZELIO] Zelio E Mobility Boosts Production Capacity by 150% and Commences New Manufacturing Plant in Odisha</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Zelio+E+Mobility+Ltd&title=Zelio+E+Mobility+Boosts+Production+Capacity+by+150%25+and+Commences+New+Manufacturing+Plant+in+Odisha&newsId=7e26b324-9f85-49c1-ad27-ca5dd978c92f&token=N2UyNmIzMjQtOWY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7e26b324-9f85-49c1-ad27-ca5dd978c92f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Expansion</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Zelio E-Mobility Limited has significantly increased its overall installed production capacity for electric vehicles from 72,000 units per annum to 1,80,000 units per annum. This enhancement is a result of process-level optimization at the existing manufacturing facility in Ladwa, Hisar, Haryana, and the commissioning of a new manufacturing plant in Odisha. The new facility contributes an additional 60,000 units to the company&apos;s annual capacity. This expansion aligns with Zelio&apos;s strategic objective to strengthen its manufacturing footprint, enhance supply chain efficiencies, and cater to the growing demand for sustainable mobility solutions across India.</p><ul><li>Overall capacity enhancement from 72,000 units per annum to 1,80,000 units per annum</li><li>Capacity increase at existing facility in Ladwa, Hisar, Haryana: 72,000 to 1,20,000 units per annum</li><li>New manufacturing plant in Odisha with a capacity of 60,000 units per annum</li><li>Expansion aligns with the company’s strategic objective to strengthen its manufacturing footprint and supply chain efficiencies</li><li>Expected to contribute positively to the Company’s operational performance</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9b883d0a-19e8-459b-ac21-9c82b07ba72c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Zelio E Mobility Ltd | Category: Expansion</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GGDANDE] G. G. Dandekar Properties Ltd Receives Order to Withdraw Appeals Before ITAT Nagpur Bench</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=G.G.DANDEKAR+MACHINE+WORKS+LTD.&title=G.+G.+Dandekar+Properties+Ltd+Receives+Order+to+Withdraw+Appeals+Before+ITAT+Nagpur+Bench&newsId=e99ab9ee-df9c-4647-9fba-de7f2599f723&token=ZTk5YWI5ZWUtZGY5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e99ab9ee-df9c-4647-9fba-de7f2599f723</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>G. G. Dandekar Properties Ltd has received an order from the Hon&apos;ble ITAT Nagpur Bench allowing the Company to withdraw the appeals filed for the assessment years 2011-12 &amp; 2013-14. The decision comes after the Company filed an application under the Direct Tax Vivad se Viswas Scheme, 2024 (&apos;DTVSV&apos; Scheme) for the same assessment years, which is currently under processing by the Income Tax department. The Company will keep the stock exchange updated on further developments under the DTVSV scheme.</p><ul><li>G. G. Dandekar Properties Ltd receives order to withdraw appeals before ITAT Nagpur Bench</li><li>Order allows withdrawal due to application under Direct Tax Vivad se Viswas Scheme, 2024 for the same assessment years</li><li>Income Tax department is currently processing the DTVSV scheme application</li><li>Company to keep stock exchange updated on further developments under the DTVSV scheme</li><li>Appeals filed for assessment years 2011-12 &amp; 2013-14 are dismissed as withdrawn</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4263f694-b6a0-47a4-b18e-79dd28549284.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: G.G.DANDEKAR MACHINE WORKS LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RNITAI] RNIT AI Solutions Ltd Successfully Launches AI-based Facial Recognition Attendance System in Lakshadweep&apos;s Schools</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Rnit+Ai+Solutions+Ltd&title=RNIT+AI+Solutions+Ltd+Successfully+Launches+AI-based+Facial+Recognition+Attendance+System+in+Lakshadweep%27s+Schools&newsId=d3c57958-af34-4900-aebe-d04abfd2fbd5&token=ZDNjNTc5NTgtYWYz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3c57958-af34-4900-aebe-d04abfd2fbd5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:51:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>RNIT AI Solutions Limited has successfully rolled out an AI-based Facial Recognition Attendance Management System (FRS) for the Department of Education in the Union Territory of Lakshadweep. This is the first implementation of such an AI-based attendance system in Lakshadweep, deployed in all schools under the Department of Education to facilitate daily attendance capture of students and teachers, including reporting functions. The platform is currently operational, enabling secure, technology-driven attendance recording and reporting for students and teachers across schools under the Department of Education in Lakshadweep.</p><ul><li>RNIT AI Solutions Limited launches AI-based Facial Recognition Attendance Management System in Lakshadweep&apos;s schools.</li><li>First implementation of an AI-based attendance system in Lakshadweep.</li><li>System deployed in all schools under the Department of Education, Lakshadweep.</li><li>Facilitates daily attendance capture of students and teachers with reporting functions.</li><li>Secure, technology-driven attendance recording and reporting platform.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/670bc326-5a3b-4f9e-9fca-fd64ad251b70.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Rnit Ai Solutions Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DEEPAKNI] Deepak Nitrite Ltd. to Participate in IIFL 17 Entrepreneurial Mumbai One on One India Conference 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DEEPAK+NITRITE+LTD.-%24&title=Deepak+Nitrite+Ltd.+to+Participate+in+IIFL+17+Entrepreneurial+Mumbai+One+on+One+India+Conference+2026&newsId=0de2fbf3-aa26-4f60-9441-39bf7f838278&token=MGRlMmZiZjMtYWEy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0de2fbf3-aa26-4f60-9441-39bf7f838278</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:51:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Deepak Nitrite Ltd. is set to participate in the IIFL 17 Entrepreneurial Mumbai One on One India Conference 2026 and Group Meeting, scheduled for February 26, 2026. The event will take place in Mumbai, India. The company will be represented by its Management Representatives. It&apos;s important to note that the schedule of the event is subject to change and no Unpublished Price Sensitive Information will be shared during the meetings. The company has also stated that no presentation is proposed to be made.</p><ul><li>Deepak Nitrite Ltd. to participate in IIFL 17 Entrepreneurial Mumbai One on One India Conference 2026</li><li>Event scheduled for February 26, 2026</li><li>To be held in Mumbai, India</li><li>Company representatives will be present</li><li>No Unpublished Price Sensitive Information or presentations will be shared</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7c2b6fc5-3e35-45a9-a2ed-5531096eb96a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DEEPAK NITRITE LTD.-$ | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SMLISUZU] SML Mahindra Ltd Changes Corporate Office Address Effective from 23 February, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SML+ISUZU+LIMITED&title=SML+Mahindra+Ltd+Changes+Corporate+Office+Address+Effective+from+23+February%2C+2026&newsId=6aa1f5a1-4343-4562-8c05-798a10606c8a&token=NmFhMWY1YTEtNDM0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6aa1f5a1-4343-4562-8c05-798a10606c8a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SML Mahindra Ltd, a well-known entity in the industry, has announced a change in its corporate office address. The new address is SML Mahindra Limited 1st Floor, T7 Tech Park C-119, Industrial Area, Phase-7, Sector 73 Mohali, SAS Nagar Punjab — 160055, effective from 23 February, 2026. The registered office address remains unchanged. This shift is in compliance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>SML Mahindra Ltd has changed its corporate office address.</li><li>The new address is SML Mahindra Limited 1st Floor, T7 Tech Park C-119, Industrial Area, Phase-7, Sector 73 Mohali, SAS Nagar Punjab — 160055.</li><li>The change is effective from 23 February, 2026.</li><li>The registered office address remains the same.</li><li>This change is in compliance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0a997be7-d3ca-4598-b005-803a434e45ce.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SML ISUZU LIMITED | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STOVACQ] Stovec Industries Ltd. Declares 120% Dividend for FY 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=STOVEC+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Stovec+Industries+Ltd.+Declares+120%25+Dividend+for+FY+2025&newsId=3bcc9d9e-b28f-4dea-9217-3fb5d5c29c74&token=M2JjYzlkOWUtYjI4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3bcc9d9e-b28f-4dea-9217-3fb5d5c29c74</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 16:12:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Stovec Industries Ltd., a subsidiary of SPGPrints B.V., The Netherlands, has declared a dividend of Rs. 12 per equity share of Rs. 10/- each (i.e. 120%) for the financial year ended December 31, 2025. The dividend will be paid to the eligible members on or before its due date, if approved by the shareholders at the ensuing Annual General Meeting. The audited financial results for the quarter and financial year ended on December 31, 2025 have been approved by the Board of Directors and will be submitted to the stock exchange.</p><ul><li>Stovec Industries Ltd. declares a dividend of 120% for FY 2025</li><li>The dividend is subject to approval by shareholders at the AGM</li><li>The audited financial results for the quarter and financial year ended on December 31, 2025 have been approved by the Board of Directors</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ac90b85c-81bd-4655-bf95-4b33652394f4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: STOVEC INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>