<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:35:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[RITES] RITES &amp; SAIL sign MoU for loco leasing &amp; maintenance services</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RITES+Ltd&title=RITES+%26+SAIL+sign+MoU+for+loco+leasing+%26+maintenance+services&newsId=8e70a5c3-7592-41f6-a7ed-2a90e21dbdf1&token=OGU3MGE1YzMtNzU5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8e70a5c3-7592-41f6-a7ed-2a90e21dbdf1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>MoU</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>RITES Limited, a leading Transport Infrastructure Consultancy and Engineering firm, has signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) with Steel Authority of India Limited (SAIL). The MoU provides a framework for collaboration to support SAIL’s plants and mines through specialised railway services, including wet leasing of locomotives and higher schedule maintenance of SAIL-owned diesel-electric locomotives. The collaboration aims at enhancing efficiency, reliability, and safety of SAIL’s in-house railway systems, while enabling SAIL to focus on its core steel production operations. RITES has been supporting SAIL plants for over two decades and the MoU formalises a long-term engagement to strengthen rail-based logistics critical to SAIL’s expanding steel production capacity.</p><ul><li>RITES &amp; SAIL sign MoU for loco leasing &amp; maintenance services</li><li>MoU provides a framework for collaboration to support SAIL’s plants and mines through specialised railway services</li><li>RITES to leverage its expertise to provide locomotive leasing with operation and maintenance (O&amp;M) support</li><li>Collaboration aims at enhancing efficiency, reliability, and safety of SAIL’s in-house railway systems</li><li>MoU formalises a long-term engagement to strengthen rail-based logistics critical to SAIL’s expanding steel production capacity</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/30dc9981-4fc1-4ae5-b828-b66e67935e25.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RITES Ltd | Category: MoU</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[3IINFOTECH] 3i Infotech Ltd. to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on Feb 13, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=3I+INFOTECH+LTD.&title=3i+Infotech+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+Feb+13%2C+2026&newsId=f7ef5cb2-9cfa-4e82-8627-493e6eb2c8d6&token=ZjdlZjVjYjItOWNm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7ef5cb2-9cfa-4e82-8627-493e6eb2c8d6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>3i Infotech Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 13, 2026, to consider and approve the Statements of Unaudited Financial Results (Standalone &amp; Consolidated) for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for all designated persons and their immediate relatives will remain closed from December 29, 2025, to February 15, 2026, in accordance with the Code of Conduct for Prevention of Insider Trading.</p><ul><li>3i Infotech Ltd. to consider and approve Q3 and nine months financial results for 2025</li><li>Trading window to remain closed for designated persons and their immediate relatives from Dec 29, 2025, to Feb 15, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ca0975fb-3458-48b1-bf66-444383a22591.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: 3I INFOTECH LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RAINBOWDQ] Rainbow Denim Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q3 Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RAINBOW+DENIM+LTD.&title=Rainbow+Denim+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+Results+for+2025&newsId=fa18e4df-eb92-48f7-b9e9-8aac0537aa06&token=ZmExOGU0ZGYtZWI5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa18e4df-eb92-48f7-b9e9-8aac0537aa06</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:24:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rainbow Denim Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 05/02/2026 to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. This meeting is in accordance with Regulation 29(1) of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Rainbow Denim Ltd has scheduled a Board Meeting for 05/02/2026</li><li>The meeting aims to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for Q3 2025</li><li>The announcement is in compliance with Regulation 29(1) of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/eba180dc-0fc2-4460-8e4a-f145edba2123.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RAINBOW DENIM LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[COALINDIA] Coal India Upgrades Pay Scale for Middle Level Executives: Estimated Rs. 3400 Crores Financial Impact by 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=COAL+INDIA+LTD.&title=Coal+India+Upgrades+Pay+Scale+for+Middle+Level+Executives%3A+Estimated+Rs.+3400+Crores+Financial+Impact+by+2026&newsId=1b57550f-ff17-42bb-9683-5aa8c354b413&token=MWI1NzU1MGYtZmYx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b57550f-ff17-42bb-9683-5aa8c354b413</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:24:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Coal India Ltd. has upgraded the pay scale of its middle level executives, effective from 01.01.2017. The financial impact of this upgradation, amounting to approximately Rs. 3400 Crores, will be payable from 23.08.2023. This disclosure is in accordance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations 2015.</p><ul><li>Coal India has upgraded the pay scale of its middle level executives as of 01.01.2017</li><li>The financial impact of this upgradation is estimated to be approximately Rs. 3400 Crores</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/07b968fd-872b-4ca9-a211-d6ac50e5f78d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: COAL INDIA LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PRATIKSH] Pratiksha Chemicals Ltd Announces Changes in Board of Directors and Key Appointments</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PRATIKSHA+CHEMICALS+LTD.&title=Pratiksha+Chemicals+Ltd+Announces+Changes+in+Board+of+Directors+and+Key+Appointments&newsId=65bbec71-a089-4540-9b4b-81b13f6551af&token=NjViYmVjNzEtYTA4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65bbec71-a089-4540-9b4b-81b13f6551af</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:22:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pratiksha Chemicals Ltd has announced changes in its Board of Directors, including the resignation of two directors and the appointment of a new Additional Non-Executive Independent Director and a Chief Financial Officer. The company has also provided details of the resignations and the new appointments as per SEBI regulations. The resignations are not due to any material reasons other than those mentioned in the resignation letters.</p><ul><li>Harishbhai Bhatt has resigned from the post of Director of the company.</li><li>Jayesh Kantilal Patel has resigned from the posts of Director and Chief Financial Officer of the company.</li><li>Ms. Aastha Jain has been appointed as an Additional Non-Executive Independent Director and Independent Director for a period of 5 years.</li><li>Mr. Chirag Vallabhbhai Pansuriya has been appointed as the new Chief Financial Officer.</li><li>The company has provided detailed disclosures as per SEBI regulations regarding the resignations and appointments.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cacc3a91-8026-48a6-ac7d-ec072a73482b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PRATIKSHA CHEMICALS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BRIGHOTEL] Brigade Hotel Ventures to Invest ₹ 1,100 Crore in Chennai, Adding 500+ Keys Across Three New Hotels</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Brigade+Hotel+Ventures+Ltd&title=Brigade+Hotel+Ventures+to+Invest+%E2%82%B9+1%2C100+Crore+in+Chennai%2C+Adding+500%2B+Keys+Across+Three+New+Hotels&newsId=bcd447d8-b228-47ba-966d-d33d43e13979&token=YmNkNDQ3ZDgtYjIy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bcd447d8-b228-47ba-966d-d33d43e13979</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:21:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Brigade Hotel Ventures Limited (BHVL) has signed an MoU with the Government of Tamil Nadu to invest ₹  1,100 crore in Chennai. This investment aims to significantly bolster the state’s tourism infrastructure and create high-value employment opportunities for over 1000 people. The new properties include Courtyard by Marriott at Chennai World Trade Center, Grand Hyatt Chennai ECR and JW Marriott Chennai OMR.</p><ul><li>BHVL to invest ₹  1,100 crore in Chennai&apos;s hospitality sector.</li><li>Three new hotels to be added: Courtyard by Marriott at Chennai World Trade Center, Grand Hyatt Chennai ECR and JW Marriott Chennai OMR.</li><li>Over 500 new keys to be added across the three properties.</li><li>The initiative aligns with the Tamil Nadu Global Tourism Summit 2026&apos;s core objective of exploring and developing new opportunities in the hospitality and leisure sectors.</li><li>The new hotels are expected to create high-value employment opportunities for over 1000 people.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8d885e3d-f8a2-4664-b73a-231e9862dbb5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Brigade Hotel Ventures Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STALLION] Stallion India Fluorochemicals Ltd Clarifies Financial Communication Inconsistencies in Q3 &amp; Nine Months FY26 Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Stallion+India+Fluorochemicals+Ltd&title=Stallion+India+Fluorochemicals+Ltd+Clarifies+Financial+Communication+Inconsistencies+in+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+FY26+Results&newsId=d9923832-e1a9-48c5-9561-a92f9169ee06&token=ZDk5MjM4MzItZTFh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d9923832-e1a9-48c5-9561-a92f9169ee06</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:21:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Stallion India Fluorochemicals Ltd (SIFL) submitted a clarification and apology addressing inadvertent inconsistencies in external market communications regarding its Q3 &amp; Nine Months FY26 earnings release. The clarification aims to provide accurate and verified financial performance, approved by the management and already disclosed to stock exchanges. The company regrets any inconvenience and reaffirms its commitment to transparency and timely disclosures. SIFL&apos;s Q3 FY25-26 financial highlights include a 23.17% increase in total revenue, 4.52% decrease in EBITDA, and 12.42% growth in PAT compared to Q3 FY24-25. The 9M FY25-26 financials show a 41.69% increase in total revenue, 48.57% growth in EBITDA, and 72.81% rise in PAT compared to 9M FY24-25. SIFL continues to target FY26 revenue of INR 43,000 Lakhs and PAT of INR 4,000 Lakhs, with a 30-35% CAGR over the next three years. The management is taking steps to strengthen internal communication controls to prevent future discrepancies.</p><ul><li>Stallion India Fluorochemicals Ltd acknowledges inadvertent communication lapses in external market communications regarding Q3 &amp; Nine Months FY26 financial performance.</li><li>The company issued a clarification to address inconsistencies and place accurate and verified financial performance on record.</li><li>SIFL&apos;s Q3 FY25-26 total revenue increased by 23.17%, EBITDA decreased by 4.52%, and PAT grew by 12.42% compared to Q3 FY24-25.</li><li>SIFL&apos;s 9M FY25-26 total revenue, EBITDA, and PAT showed significant growth compared to 9M FY24-25.</li><li>SIFL remains committed to targets for FY26 revenue and PAT, with a 30-35% CAGR over the next three years.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3447130c-372f-4a32-b306-fd1ee7e65ba3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Stallion India Fluorochemicals Ltd | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PARADEEP] Paradeep Phosphates Ltd Reports 15% YoY Revenue Growth in Q3 &amp; 34% YoY in 9M FY26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Paradeep+Phosphates+Ltd&title=Paradeep+Phosphates+Ltd+Reports+15%25+YoY+Revenue+Growth+in+Q3+%26+34%25+YoY+in+9M+FY26&newsId=be3192ea-ff5f-4c66-b659-9841e7613f64&token=YmUzMTkyZWEtZmY1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be3192ea-ff5f-4c66-b659-9841e7613f64</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Paradeep Phosphates Ltd, one of India&apos;s largest private-sector fertilizer companies, has announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a 15% YoY increase in revenue from operations for Q3 FY26, reaching INR 5,749 crore. EBITDA for the quarter stood at INR 503 crore, up 5% YoY. For 9M FY26, revenue from operations increased by 34% YoY to INR 17,124 crore, and EBITDA rose by 45% YoY to INR 1,817 crore. Profit After Tax (PAT) for the 9M stood at INR 841 crore, up 71% YoY. The company&apos;s production and sales volumes also saw significant growth.</p><ul><li>Revenue from Operations: INR 5,749 crore in Q3 FY26 (15% YoY); INR 17,124 crore in 9M FY26 (34% YoY)</li><li>EBITDA: INR 503 crore in Q3 (5% YoY), INR 1,817 crore in 9M FY 26 (45% YoY)</li><li>PAT: INR 182 crore in Q3; INR 841 crore in 9M FY 26 (71% YoY)</li><li>Production volumes: 10.00 lakh tonnes in Q3 (13% YoY), 28.60 lakh tonnes in 9M (15% YoY)</li><li>Sales volumes: 10.70 lakh tonnes in Q3 ; 33.66 lakh tonnes in 9M (16.9% YoY)</li><li>NPK sales: 17.51 in 9M (30% YoY); TSP: 2.43 (107% YoY)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2a5ea97c-7923-43c7-bbcd-bdb29fc20f1c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Paradeep Phosphates Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AKZOINDIA] Akzo Nobel India Ltd Announces Q3 &amp; 9M 2025 Financial Results with Exceptional Items</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Akzo+Nobel+India+Limited&title=Akzo+Nobel+India+Ltd+Announces+Q3+%26+9M+2025+Financial+Results+with+Exceptional+Items&newsId=55932fe6-5645-48b9-8b2f-828c853a607f&token=NTU5MzJmZTYtNTY0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55932fe6-5645-48b9-8b2f-828c853a607f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:12:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Akzo Nobel India Ltd has announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company reported a profit before tax of INR 3,207 million for the quarter and INR 4,321 million for the nine-month period. The Board approved the financial results, which include exceptional items such as profits from the slump sale of the Powder Coatings business division and the International Research Center division, as well as provisions for impairment and reimbursements. The company has also recognized a financial impact of INR 316 million due to the implementation of new Labour Codes.</p><ul><li>Akzo Nobel India Ltd announced its Q3 &amp; 9M 2025 financial results</li><li>The results include exceptional items related to the slump sale of the Powder Coatings business division and the International Research Center division</li><li>Provision for impairment of property, plant and equipment was made</li><li>Reimbursement towards additional costs incurred due to the slump sale was recognized</li><li>The company recognized a financial impact of INR 316 million due to the implementation of new Labour Codes</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7038db60-75d3-4b31-936f-34930b95ddf1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Akzo Nobel India Limited | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AARTIIND] Aarti Industries Delivers Robust Sequential Growth in Q3 FY26 Amid Global Volatility</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AARTI+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Aarti+Industries+Delivers+Robust+Sequential+Growth+in+Q3+FY26+Amid+Global+Volatility&newsId=e8c3cdda-7446-44b0-b668-7ed612cacae8&token=ZThjM2NkZGEtNzQ0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e8c3cdda-7446-44b0-b668-7ed612cacae8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:11:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Aarti Industries Limited, a leading global speciality chemicals company, announced its unaudited consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. Despite a challenging global operating environment, the company reported an 11% Q-o-Q increase in revenue, driven by volume growth across various value chains. EBITDA surged to Rs. 323 crore, and Profit After Tax for the quarter increased by 25% Q-o-Q to Rs. 133 crore. The energy portfolio, led by MMA, remained a key growth driver, while Agrochemicals, Dyes, Pigments and Printing Inks, and Polymers showed varying performance.</p><ul><li>Revenue stood at Rs. 2,492 crore, an increase of 11% Q-o-Q</li><li>EBITDA surged to Rs. 323 crore, marking a 11% Q-o-Q increase</li><li>Profit After Tax surged to Rs. 133 crore, an increase of 25% Q-o-Q</li><li>Energy Business, led by MMA, remained a key growth driver</li><li>Company expects to commission various process blocks including the multipurpose plant (MPP) at Zone IV in a phased manner starting from Q4FY26</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7ee561b5-5de3-47e3-9bb1-212fba8cdfa9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AARTI INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>