<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 15:16:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[TLL] Trident Lifeline Ltd Approves Un-Audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended 31st December, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Trident+Lifeline+Ltd&title=Trident+Lifeline+Ltd+Approves+Un-Audited+Standalone+and+Consolidated+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+31st+December%2C+2025&newsId=69f90d46-ec1a-4191-8128-48ab2847b44e&token=NjlmOTBkNDYtZWMx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69f90d46-ec1a-4191-8128-48ab2847b44e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Trident Lifeline Ltd announced the outcome of its Board Meeting held on 17th January, 2026. The Board approved and took on record the Un-Audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations for the nine months ended 31st December, 2025, stands at INR 7,246.47 crores. The company&apos;s net profit for the same period is INR 500.40 crores. The company&apos;s earnings per equity share (basic and diluted) for the nine months ended 31st December, 2025, is INR 2.63.</p><ul><li>Trident Lifeline Ltd approved Un-Audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue from operations for the nine months ended 31st December, 2025, stands at INR 7,246.47 crores.</li><li>The company&apos;s net profit for the same period is INR 500.40 crores.</li><li>The company&apos;s earnings per equity share (basic and diluted) for the nine months ended 31st December, 2025, is INR 2.63.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2ab3831c-6ef6-405a-82d2-ff058ae78e87.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Trident Lifeline Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LGEINDIA] LG Electronics India Faces Rs. 11 Crore Differential Duty Demand from Customs Authority</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LG+Electronics+India+Ltd&title=LG+Electronics+India+Faces+Rs.+11+Crore+Differential+Duty+Demand+from+Customs+Authority&newsId=f4da3818-5448-499a-8aad-23d44e68c721&token=ZjRkYTM4MTgtNTQ0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4da3818-5448-499a-8aad-23d44e68c721</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:51:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>LG Electronics India Ltd. has received an order from the Office of Commissioner of Customs (NS-V), Jawaharlal Nehru, Customs House Nhava sheva — Mumbai (Maharashtra) dated 08/01/2026, demanding a differential duty amount of Rs. 11,91,51,910/- (Rupees Eleven Crore Ninety-One Lakh Fifty-One Thousand Nine Hundred Ten only) along with applicable interest and penalty. The demand is due to a gap in assessable value of imported goods. The management of LG Electronics India does not expect this order to have a material impact on the financials, operations, or other activities of the company and plans to file an appeal against the matter.</p><ul><li>LG Electronics India Ltd. has received an order from the Office of Commissioner of Customs (NS-V), Jawaharlal Nehru, Customs House Nhava sheva — Mumbai (Maharashtra) demanding a differential duty amount of Rs. 11,91,51,910/-</li><li>The demand is due to a gap in assessable value of imported goods</li><li>The management of LG Electronics India does not expect this order to have a material impact on the financials, operations, or other activities of the company</li><li>LG Electronics India plans to file an appeal against the matter</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c894781f-4fb3-474e-b344-850710c413d7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LG Electronics India Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TLL] Trident Lifeline Ltd. Approves and Takes on Record Un-Audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended 31st December, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Trident+Lifeline+Ltd&title=Trident+Lifeline+Ltd.+Approves+and+Takes+on+Record+Un-Audited+Standalone+and+Consolidated+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+31st+December%2C+2025&newsId=7a8fd57c-6833-4164-b2fa-3363075d9c28&token=N2E4ZmQ1N2MtNjgz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7a8fd57c-6833-4164-b2fa-3363075d9c28</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Trident Lifeline Ltd. has approved and taken on record the Un-Audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations for the nine months ended 31st December, 2025, stands at INR 7,246.47 Lacs. The company&apos;s earning per equity share for the same period is INR 2.63 (Not Annualized). The financial results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Trident Lifeline Ltd. has approved and taken on record the Un-Audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue from operations for the nine months ended 31st December, 2025, stands at INR 7,246.47 Lacs.</li><li>The company&apos;s earning per equity share for the same period is INR 2.63 (Not Annualized).</li><li>The financial results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee.</li><li>The financial results have been approved by the Board of Directors.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dbbab78d-678a-41bd-bedc-9e9f47598a37.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Trident Lifeline Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CANFINHOME] Can Fin Homes Ltd Reports 25% Increase in Q3 Net Profit for FY26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CAN+FIN+HOMES+LTD.&title=Can+Fin+Homes+Ltd+Reports+25%25+Increase+in+Q3+Net+Profit+for+FY26&newsId=5595ff76-7119-40fe-bc8b-fd4b9413faae&token=NTU5NWZmNzYtNzEx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5595ff76-7119-40fe-bc8b-fd4b9413faae</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:24:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Can Fin Homes Ltd (CFHL) has reported a 25% increase in net profit for the third quarter of the current fiscal, which ended on December 31, 2025. The net profit for the quarter stood at Rs. 265 crore, compared to Rs. 212 crores for the corresponding previous period.</p><ul><li>Net profit for Q3 FY26 increased by 25% compared to Q3 FY25</li><li>Loan assets stood at Rs. 40693 crores, a 10% growth from December 2024</li><li>Housing loan constitutes 73% of the loan book, non-housing loans constitute 27%</li><li>Loan disbursements for the nine months ended December 31, 2025, stood at Rs. 7287 crores, a 19% growth Year-on-Year</li><li>CFHL is required to carry provisions of Rs. 400 crores towards expected credit losses as per Ind AS 109</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/379e2d87-29e4-44c5-8404-5cdfa601b639.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CAN FIN HOMES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DBOL] Dhampur Bio Organics Ltd to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months of FY 2025-2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Dhampur+Bio+Organics+Ltd&title=Dhampur+Bio+Organics+Ltd+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+of+FY+2025-2026&newsId=2ecca0dd-66c5-4ad9-968b-6edc5201cabe&token=MmVjY2EwZGQtNjZj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ecca0dd-66c5-4ad9-968b-6edc5201cabe</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:11:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dhampur Bio Organics Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 21, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. This meeting is pursuant to Regulation 29 of the Securities &amp; Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The trading window for trading in the company’s securities will remain closed till January 23, 2026, for those to whom the company’s &apos;Code of Conduct’ for Prevention of Insider Trading is applicable. However, the trading window will be open for general investors.</p><ul><li>Dhampur Bio Organics Ltd to consider and approve unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>Board Meeting scheduled on January 21, 2026.</li><li>Trading window to remain closed till January 23, 2026, for insiders.</li><li>Trading window to remain open for general investors.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b7e6c136-d20a-44cb-9e2c-d2e860183d59.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Dhampur Bio Organics Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KPITTECH] KPIT Technologies Ltd. Receives Request for Promoter to Public Category Reclassification</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KPIT+Technologies+Ltd&title=KPIT+Technologies+Ltd.+Receives+Request+for+Promoter+to+Public+Category+Reclassification&newsId=e3bc7125-f6bb-4ad5-ad46-3a7f821dfe2a&token=ZTNiYzcxMjUtZjZi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3bc7125-f6bb-4ad5-ad46-3a7f821dfe2a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Promoter to Public Reclassification</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>KPIT Technologies Ltd. has received a request from two promoters, Mr. Ajay Bhagwat and Ms. Ashwini Bhagwat, for reclassification from &apos;Promoter&apos; to &apos;Public&apos; category. The reclassification involves 2,24,68,839 shares, which is 0.82% of the total share capital of the company. The reclassification is subject to the approval of the Board of Directors and both the stock exchanges, BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange of India Limited. The outgoing promoters have confirmed that they are not associated with the business of the company and do not exercise any control or influence over the business and policy decisions of the company.</p><ul><li>KPIT Technologies Ltd. received a request for reclassification from two promoters.</li><li>The reclassification involves 2,24,68,839 shares, which is 0.82% of the total share capital of the company.</li><li>The reclassification is subject to the approval of the Board of Directors and both the stock exchanges.</li><li>The outgoing promoters have confirmed that they are not associated with the business of the company.</li><li>The outgoing promoters do not exercise any control or influence over the business and policy decisions of the company.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8f93c892-c3af-41a4-b6be-5926e069f098.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KPIT Technologies Ltd | Category: Promoter to Public Reclassification</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CANFINHOME] Can Fin Homes Ltd Approves Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and 9 Months Ended December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CAN+FIN+HOMES+LTD.&title=Can+Fin+Homes+Ltd+Approves+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+9+Months+Ended+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=270d82ff-f7d1-4160-93f4-388b53fbc308&token=MjcwZDgyZmYtZjdk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">270d82ff-f7d1-4160-93f4-388b53fbc308</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Can Fin Homes Ltd has approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter and 9 months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting of the Board of Directors commenced at 04.40 p.m. and concluded at 5.40 p.m. The financial results have been prepared in accordance with the recognition and measurement principles laid down in Indian Accounting Standard 34 Interim Financial Reporting. The main business of the company is to provide loans against /for purchase, construction, renovation of houses/flats/commercial properties. The company has maintained 100% Asset Cover on its secured redeemable non-convertible debentures as on December 31, 2025. The above financial results for the quarter and Nine months ended December 31, 2025 have been reviewed and recommended by the Audit Committee of the Board and subsequently approved by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Can Fin Homes Ltd has approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter and 9 months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The financial results have been prepared in accordance with the recognition and measurement principles laid down in Indian Accounting Standard 34 Interim Financial Reporting.</li><li>The main business of the company is to provide loans against /for purchase, construction, renovation of houses/flats/commercial properties.</li><li>The company has maintained 100% Asset Cover on its secured redeemable non-convertible debentures as on December 31, 2025.</li><li>The above financial results for the quarter and Nine months ended December 31, 2025 have been reviewed and recommended by the Audit Committee of the Board and subsequently approved by the Board of Directors.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/46cb258e-4caa-4ee6-8fb7-45476c5a8d29.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CAN FIN HOMES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ORIENTTR] Orient Tradelink Ltd Allots 3,55,683 Equity Shares at INR 22 Each, Increasing Paid-up Equity Share Capital</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ORIENT+TRADELINK+LTD.&title=Orient+Tradelink+Ltd+Allots+3%2C55%2C683+Equity+Shares+at+INR+22+Each%2C+Increasing+Paid-up+Equity+Share+Capital&newsId=94197d05-36ae-4491-b894-5314ccb7e081&token=OTQxOTdkMDUtMzZh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">94197d05-36ae-4491-b894-5314ccb7e081</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:47:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Orient Tradelink Ltd has allotted 3,55,683 equity shares of INR 10 each at a price of INR 22 per share, comprising of a premium of INR 12 per share. The allotment was made to Tejinder Singh, Hemlata Sharma, Sanjay Sinha, Rudrakshi Sharma, and Shikha. The allotment increased the company&apos;s paid-up equity share capital from INR 37,60,67,690 divided into 3,76,06,769 Equity Shares of INR 10/-each to INR 37,96,24,520 divided into 3,79,62,452 Equity Shares of INR 10/-each.</p><ul><li>Orient Tradelink Ltd allotted 3,55,683 equity shares at INR 22 per share with a premium of INR 12 per share.</li><li>The allotment increased the company&apos;s paid-up equity share capital from INR 37,60,67,690 to INR 37,96,24,520.</li><li>The allottees include Tejinder Singh, Hemlata Sharma, Sanjay Sinha, Rudrakshi Sharma, and Shikha.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fe73bae8-b919-4592-a6c5-063c58ae98c2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ORIENT TRADELINK LTD. | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PPARIVAH] Paradeep Parivahan Limited Honoured with Prestigious ‘Times Business Award’</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Paradeep+Parivahan+Ltd&title=Paradeep+Parivahan+Limited+Honoured+with+Prestigious+%E2%80%98Times+Business+Award%E2%80%99&newsId=8a74f0c8-a7cc-4a9d-8573-2b389a39c4af&token=OGE3NGYwYzgtYTdj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a74f0c8-a7cc-4a9d-8573-2b389a39c4af</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Award</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Paradeep Parivahan Limited, a BSE SME-listed company, has been conferred the prestigious ‘Transformational Growth &amp; Strategic Innovation in Port Logistics &amp; Transportation’ award at the Times Business Awards. The award ceremony was held in Bhubaneswar and was graced by several eminent dignitaries. The award was received by Ms. Bushra Khan, Director, Paradeep Parivahan Limited. This recognition is a testament to the company&apos;s unwavering dedication, operational excellence, and consistent service quality delivered over the years.</p><ul><li>Paradeep Parivahan Limited has been honoured with the prestigious ‘Times Business Award’ for Transformational Growth &amp; Strategic Innovation in Port Logistics &amp; Transportation.</li><li>The award was presented at a ceremony in Bhubaneswar graced by several eminent dignitaries.</li><li>The award was received by Ms. Bushra Khan, Director, Paradeep Parivahan Limited.</li><li>This recognition is a testament to the company&apos;s unwavering dedication, operational excellence, and consistent service quality.</li><li>Paradeep Parivahan Limited is a leading provider of integrated logistics, supply chain solutions, and port services.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/79e5a2a2-6a3a-42a6-a0b2-7db392b078eb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Paradeep Parivahan Ltd | Category: Award</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ORIENTTR] Orient Tradelink Ltd Allots 3,55,683 Equity Shares at INR 22 Each, Increasing Paid-up Equity Share Capital</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ORIENT+TRADELINK+LTD.&title=Orient+Tradelink+Ltd+Allots+3%2C55%2C683+Equity+Shares+at+INR+22+Each%2C+Increasing+Paid-up+Equity+Share+Capital&newsId=14fd0446-a570-4343-94c1-adef52acf951&token=MTRmZDA0NDYtYTU3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">14fd0446-a570-4343-94c1-adef52acf951</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Orient Tradelink Ltd has allotted 3,55,683 equity shares of INR 10 each at a price of INR 22 per share, comprising of a premium of INR 12 per share. The allotment was made to Tejinder Singh, Hemlata Sharma, Sanjay Sinha, Rudrakshi Sharma, and Shikha. The paid-up equity share capital of the company has increased from INR 37,60,67,690 to INR 37,96,24,520 after the allotment.</p><ul><li>Allotment of 3,55,683 equity shares at INR 22 per share with a premium of INR 12 per share</li><li>Payment received from allottees Tejinder Singh, Hemlata Sharma, Sanjay Sinha, Rudrakshi Sharma, and Shikha</li><li>Paid-up equity share capital increased from INR 37,60,67,690 to INR 37,96,24,520</li><li>50,000 equity shares allotted to Tejinder Singh</li><li>72,727 equity shares allotted to Hemlata Sharma</li><li>190,909 equity shares allotted to Sanjay Sinha</li><li>17,047 equity shares allotted to Rudrakshi Sharma</li><li>25,000 equity shares allotted to Shikha</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/32b51249-600f-414b-9dbd-13c9c02b8023.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ORIENT TRADELINK LTD. | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>