<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:37:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[TTIENT] Kanakavally Prathapan Sells 25,04,101 Shares of TTI Enterprise Ltd, Reducing Stake to 0%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TTI+Enterprise+Ltd&title=Kanakavally+Prathapan+Sells+25%2C04%2C101+Shares+of+TTI+Enterprise+Ltd%2C+Reducing+Stake+to+0%25&newsId=c63e8030-9e47-4f75-9d31-da04da3da076&token=YzYzZTgwMzAtOWU0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c63e8030-9e47-4f75-9d31-da04da3da076</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 05:54:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kanakavally Prathapan, a promoter of TTI Enterprise Ltd, has sold 25,04,101 shares of the company on 04.02.2026, reducing his stake to 0%. This sale has resulted in a significant change in the shareholding pattern of the company. The sold shares represent 9.86% of the total voting rights and total capital of the company. The shares were sold through an off-market encumbrance. This sale has led to a dilution in the share and voting capital of the company.</p><ul><li>Kanakavally Prathapan sells 25,04,101 shares of TTI Enterprise Ltd</li><li>Sale represents 9.86% of the total voting rights and total capital</li><li>Sale conducted through off-market encumbrance</li><li>Resulted in a significant dilution in share and voting capital</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/F19EEC21_2CF7_4BF8_BA3C_545EDDD0AA5B_111603.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TTI Enterprise Ltd | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GMRINFRA] GMR Airports Ltd: GQG Partners Emerging Markets Equity Fund Acquires 7.57% Stake</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GMR+Airports+Infrastructure+Ltd&title=GMR+Airports+Ltd%3A+GQG+Partners+Emerging+Markets+Equity+Fund+Acquires+7.57%25+Stake&newsId=f3429191-c50d-440f-9f4f-59d660932fca&token=ZjM0MjkxOTEtYzUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3429191-c50d-440f-9f4f-59d660932fca</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 05:51:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>GQG Partners Emerging Markets Equity Fund A has acquired 7.57% stake in GMR Airports Ltd. The acquisition was made in several phases, with the initial acquisition of 7.66% in December 2023, followed by a reduction to below 5% due to corporate actions, and then an increase to 5.17% in August 2024. The final acquisition of 7.57% was made on February 4, 2026. GQG Partners LLC, the investment manager, made the investment decision on behalf of the fund. The shares were acquired through the stock exchange settlement issue.</p><ul><li>GQG Partners Emerging Markets Equity Fund A acquires 7.57% stake in GMR Airports Ltd</li><li>The acquisition was made in several phases over a period of time</li><li>GQG Partners LLC, the investment manager, made the investment decision</li><li>The shares were acquired through the stock exchange settlement issue</li><li>The acquisition increased the fund&apos;s holding from 0.49% to 7.57%</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/D226E449_5E73_441A_8673_14E0BFD275C3_111022.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GMR Airports Infrastructure Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[OASISEC] Sodhani Capital Acquires 43,150 Shares of Oasis Securities Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=OASIS+SECURITIES+LTD.&title=Sodhani+Capital+Acquires+43%2C150+Shares+of+Oasis+Securities+Ltd&newsId=f1423a3f-725d-4ef1-b3a0-44c82ff3f88c&token=ZjE0MjNhM2YtNzI1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f1423a3f-725d-4ef1-b3a0-44c82ff3f88c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 05:41:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sodhani Capital Ltd has acquired 43,150 equity shares of Oasis Securities Ltd on 5th February 2026. This acquisition increases Sodhani Capital&apos;s holding to 70.30% of the total voting rights and diluted capital of Oasis Securities Ltd.</p><ul><li>Sodhani Capital Ltd has acquired 43,150 equity shares of Oasis Securities Ltd.</li><li>This acquisition increases Sodhani Capital&apos;s holding to 70.30% of the total voting rights and diluted capital of Oasis Securities Ltd.</li><li>The acquisition was made on 5th February 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/B85A11AE_D38D_41C3_A85F_42049BE3775D_110315.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: OASIS SECURITIES LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUNSHIEL] Swarna Malhotra Acquires Shares of Sunshield Chemicals Ltd Through Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SUNSHIELD+CHEMICALS+LTD.&title=Swarna+Malhotra+Acquires+Shares+of+Sunshield+Chemicals+Ltd+Through+Open+Market&newsId=9c8abb5a-7073-499c-9563-befad7439067&token=OWM4YWJiNWEtNzA3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c8abb5a-7073-499c-9563-befad7439067</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 05:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Swarna Malhotra, through open market, has acquired shares of Sunshield Chemicals Ltd. The total equity share capital of the company before the acquisition was Rs. 8,79,48,360, which remains the same after the acquisition. The total diluted share/voting capital of the company after the acquisition is also Rs. 8,79,48,360. The acquisition was made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</p><ul><li>Swarna Malhotra acquires shares of Sunshield Chemicals Ltd through open market</li><li>The acquisition was made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011</li><li>The total equity share capital of the company before and after the acquisition is Rs. 8,79,48,360</li><li>The total diluted share/voting capital of the company after the acquisition is also Rs. 8,79,48,360</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/285C5834_0B09_4B7D_ABBA_C5D26F154436_110546.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SUNSHIELD CHEMICALS LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MRO-TEK] Umiya Holding Pvt Ltd Acquires 37.97% Stake in Umiya Buildcon Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MRO-TEK+Realty+Ltd&title=Umiya+Holding+Pvt+Ltd+Acquires+37.97%25+Stake+in+Umiya+Buildcon+Ltd&newsId=7dcde2ff-2b1e-4394-b7c3-bfb719761abf&token=N2RjZGUyZmYtMmIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7dcde2ff-2b1e-4394-b7c3-bfb719761abf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 05:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Umiya Holding Pvt Ltd has acquired a significant stake in Umiya Buildcon Ltd (formerly MRO-TEK Realty Limited). The acquisition includes 70,95,416 shares, 70,95,416 voting rights (VR) otherwise than by equity shares, and warrants/convertible securities. The total holding after the acquisition is 71,02,916 shares, 71,02,916 VRs, and warrants/convertible securities. The mode of acquisition was open market. The acquisition was made by Umiya Holding Pvt Ltd, represented by Aniruddha Bhanuprasad Mehta, Director.</p><ul><li>Umiya Holding Pvt Ltd acquires 37.97% stake in Umiya Buildcon Ltd</li><li>Acquisition includes 70,95,416 shares, 70,95,416 VRs, and warrants/convertible securities</li><li>Total holding after acquisition is 71,02,916 shares, 71,02,916 VRs, and warrants/convertible securities</li><li>Mode of acquisition was open market</li><li>Acquisition represented by Aniruddha Bhanuprasad Mehta, Director of Umiya Holding Pvt Ltd</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2E0F97E8_CC8D_4742_8201_018BABFB0F37_104124.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MRO-TEK Realty Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AGARWALEYE] Promoter Group of Dr. Agarwal&apos;s Health Care Ltd Proposes Inter-se Transfer of Shares by Way of Gift</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Dr.+Agarwals+Health+Care+Ltd&title=Promoter+Group+of+Dr.+Agarwal%27s+Health+Care+Ltd+Proposes+Inter-se+Transfer+of+Shares+by+Way+of+Gift&newsId=227e464b-8a54-455d-8c1e-9e4ecfc159cc&token=MjI3ZTQ2NGItOGE1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">227e464b-8a54-455d-8c1e-9e4ecfc159cc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 05:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Promoter Group of Dr. Agarwal&apos;s Health Care Ltd, a listed company, has disclosed its intention to transfer shares by way of gift amongst immediate relatives. The proposed acquisition involves 14,85,822 shares (0.47%) of the company. The transferor and transferee have complied with applicable disclosure requirements in Chapter V of the Takeover Regulations, 2011. The proposed acquisition is a private transfer family arrangement and no consideration is involved.</p><ul><li>The proposed acquisition involves 14,85,822 shares (0.47%) of Dr. Agarwal&apos;s Health Care Ltd.</li><li>The shares are proposed to be transferred by way of &apos;Gift&apos; amongst immediate relatives.</li><li>The proposed acquisition is a private transfer family arrangement and no consideration is involved.</li><li>The transferor and transferee have complied with applicable disclosure requirements in Chapter V of the Takeover Regulations, 2011.</li><li>There will be no change in the Total Shareholding of the Promoter and Promoter Group after such inter-se transfer of shares.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9B2D2BB4_AF2C_4C78_8503_84802C590A11_104319.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Dr. Agarwals Health Care Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MAGNAELQ] Magna Electro Castings: No Material Information Withheld, Price Movement Market-Driven</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MAGNA+ELECTRO+CASTINGS+LTD.-%24&title=Magna+Electro+Castings%3A+No+Material+Information+Withheld%2C+Price+Movement+Market-Driven&newsId=2c1aaf27-7610-4614-8309-20b94812c2f2&token=MmMxYWFmMjctNzYx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2c1aaf27-7610-4614-8309-20b94812c2f2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:51:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Magna Electro Castings Ltd. has clarified that it has been making timely disclosures of all material information as required by the SEBI regulations. The company confirmed that it has not withheld any material information that could affect the price behavior of its shares. Therefore, the significant movement in the price of the company&apos;s shares is understood to be due to market conditions.</p><ul><li>Magna Electro Castings has been making timely disclosures of all material information as per SEBI regulations.</li><li>The company has not withheld any material information that could affect the price behavior of its shares.</li><li>The price movement of the company&apos;s shares is attributed to market conditions.</li><li>The company has no control over the market-driven price behavior.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/26ecf686-e84a-4cef-a9f5-e81145aef70a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MAGNA ELECTRO CASTINGS LTD.-$ | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PURPLEFIN] Purple Finance Raises ₹69 Crore through Equity Warrants</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Purple+Finance+Ltd&title=Purple+Finance+Raises+%E2%82%B969+Crore+through+Equity+Warrants&newsId=604a2082-3be4-4e7b-a4d1-15d94c004e9a&token=NjA0YTIwODItM2Jl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">604a2082-3be4-4e7b-a4d1-15d94c004e9a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Purple Finance Ltd. approved an equity raise of ₹69.30 crore through equity warrants, comprising 1.26 crore warrants issued at ₹55 per warrant. The company has raised a total of ₹183 crore since its listing in June 2024. Purple Finance has expanded to 45 branches, with Assets Under Management (AUM) of ~ ₹210 crore as of January 2026 and a team of approximately 430 employees. The company remains focused on responsible growth in the SME and retail lending ecosystem.</p><ul><li>Purple Finance raises ₹69.30 crore through equity warrants</li><li>1.26 crore warrants issued at ₹55 per warrant</li><li>Company has raised a total of ₹183 crore since its listing in June 2024</li><li>Expanded to 45 branches, with Assets Under Management (AUM) of ~ ₹210 crore as of January 2026</li><li>Focused on responsible growth in the SME and retail lending ecosystem</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/364a408b-e7fb-497b-bf91-6fa9d8ba842d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Purple Finance Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[QUADRANT] Quadrant Televentures Ltd. to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and H1 of FY2025-2026 on Feb 11, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Quadrant+Televentures+Limited-%24&title=Quadrant+Televentures+Ltd.+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+H1+of+FY2025-2026+on+Feb+11%2C+2026&newsId=3b9c3320-adf3-4b4a-a210-7b229b2b37a1&token=M2I5YzMzMjAtYWRm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b9c3320-adf3-4b4a-a210-7b229b2b37a1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Quadrant Televentures Ltd. has informed the BSE that its Board of Directors will meet on February 11, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and half year ended September 30, 2025. The company is under Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process as per the Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code. The unaudited standalone financial results for the same period were submitted earlier. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the company remains closed till the financial results are declared.</p><ul><li>Quadrant Televentures Ltd. to consider and approve unaudited financial results for Q3 and H1 of FY2025-2026 on Feb 11, 2026</li><li>Company is under Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process as per the Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code</li><li>Unaudited standalone financial results for Q3 and H1 of FY2025-2026 were submitted earlier</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the securities of the company remains closed till the financial results are declared</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/602e5a30-72f8-4c2a-82c0-5999c5d14f13.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Quadrant Televentures Limited-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PURPLEFIN] Purple Finance Raises ₹69 Crore Through Equity Warrants</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Purple+Finance+Ltd&title=Purple+Finance+Raises+%E2%82%B969+Crore+Through+Equity+Warrants&newsId=fac55470-9de5-43bc-8e14-a3085908dbf9&token=ZmFjNTU0NzAtOWRl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fac55470-9de5-43bc-8e14-a3085908dbf9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 04:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Purple Finance Ltd. has approved an equity raise of ₹69.30 crore through equity warrants, comprising 1.26 crore warrants issued at ₹55 per warrant. The company has been following a disciplined, phased approach to capital raising since its successful listing in June 2024. With the recent fundraising, Purple Finance has raised a total of ₹232 crore. The company has expanded to 45 branches, with Assets Under Management (AUM) of ~ €210 crore as of January 2026 and a team of approximately 430 employees. Purple Finance remains focused on responsible growth in the SME and retail lending ecosystem, creating long-term value for its 3,800+ equity shareholders and 4,000+ NCD holders.</p><ul><li>Purple Finance raises ₹69.30 crore through equity warrants.</li><li>The company has raised a total of ₹232 crore since its listing in June 2024.</li><li>Purple Finance has expanded to 45 branches and has a team of approximately 430 employees.</li><li>As of January 2026, the company&apos;s Assets Under Management (AUM) is ~ €210 crore.</li><li>The company aims to create long-term value for its 3,800+ equity shareholders and 4,000+ NCD holders.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4c79f3fb-0230-4cab-994e-be86afd965bc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Purple Finance Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>