<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:28:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SCI] Shipping Corporation Of India Ltd. to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025 and Consider Interim Dividend</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHIPPING+CORPORATION+OF+INDIA+LTD.&title=Shipping+Corporation+Of+India+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025+and+Consider+Interim+Dividend&newsId=481ef107-a3d8-4c98-8bcd-874cb420d386&token=NDgxZWYxMDctYTNk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">481ef107-a3d8-4c98-8bcd-874cb420d386</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 04:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shipping Corporation Of India Ltd. has announced a Board of Directors meeting on 06/02/2026 to consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31.12.2025. The company will also consider declaring an interim dividend. The trading window for insider trading has been closed from 01.01.2026 and will remain closed up to forty eight (48) hours after the declaration of the financial results and interim dividend, if declared. The interim dividend, if declared, will be paid within 30 days from the date of declaration electronically to those Shareholders holding shares in dematerialised mode and who have updated bank account details. Shareholders are requested to update their bank account details at the earliest to avoid delay in receiving the dividend.</p><ul><li>Shipping Corporation Of India Ltd. to approve Q3 and nine months financial results for 2025</li><li>Consideration of interim dividend declaration</li><li>Trading window for insider trading closed from 01.01.2026</li><li>Interim dividend, if declared, to be paid within 30 days from the date of declaration</li><li>Shareholders holding shares in dematerialised mode and with updated bank account details to receive dividend electronically</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/773b0d07-7454-4e88-b665-108202308ed5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHIPPING CORPORATION OF INDIA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BHARATFORG] Bharat Forge Invests € 10 Million in Wholly Owned Subsidiary Bharat Forge Global Holding GmbH</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BHARAT+FORGE+LTD.&title=Bharat+Forge+Invests+%E2%82%AC+10+Million+in+Wholly+Owned+Subsidiary+Bharat+Forge+Global+Holding+GmbH&newsId=e621d9dc-e0f6-44a6-a308-daea0c00daa3&token=ZTYyMWQ5ZGMtZTBm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e621d9dc-e0f6-44a6-a308-daea0c00daa3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 03:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Bharat Forge Ltd has made an investment in Bharat Forge Global Holding GmbH (BFGH), a wholly owned subsidiary based in Germany. The investment, amounting to Rs. 1,100.45 million / € 10 million, is in the form of equity capital infusion. BFGH, incorporated on December 15, 2003, is the holding company for overseas investments undertaken by Bharat Forge Limited. It had a turnover of € 6.50 million for the period January 2024 — December 2024.</p><ul><li>Bharat Forge Ltd invests € 10 million in its wholly owned subsidiary Bharat Forge Global Holding GmbH.</li><li>The investment is in the form of equity capital infusion, maintaining the Company&apos;s 100% stake in BFGH.</li><li>BFGH is a holding company for overseas investments undertaken by Bharat Forge Limited.</li><li>BFGH had a turnover of € 6.50 million for the period January 2024 — December 2024.</li><li>The transaction is in line with Bharat Forge&apos;s strategic growth plans.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cb89fe22-0f8c-4186-84af-edb0872b4ba8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BHARAT FORGE LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADANIGREEN] Adani Companies Secure Landmark Japanese Credit Ratings - JCR Ratings</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Adani+Green+Energy+Ltd&title=Adani+Companies+Secure+Landmark+Japanese+Credit+Ratings+-+JCR+Ratings&newsId=ef4b283b-19ba-4885-a4b1-ec7714f364f5&token=ZWY0YjI4M2ItMTli</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef4b283b-19ba-4885-a4b1-ec7714f364f5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 03:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Japan Credit Rating Agency (JCR) has assigned long-term foreign currency credit ratings with a Stable outlook to three Adani Portfolio companies: Adani Ports &amp; SEZ (APSEZ), Adani Green Energy Ltd. (AGEL), and Adani Energy Solutions Ltd. (AESL). This is a significant milestone in the Group&apos;s global credit journey and reinforces its underlying credit strength. APSEZ has been rated &apos;A-&apos;, AGEL and AESL have each been rated &apos;BBB+&apos;. These ratings are at par with India’s sovereign rating of BBB+. The ratings underline the strong credit profile, diversified asset base, and resilient cash-flow generation of APSEZ, and mark one of the first instances of Indian infrastructure platforms being assessed by JCR at these levels.</p><ul><li>Adani Ports &amp; SEZ (APSEZ) has been rated &apos;A-&apos; with Stable outlook by JCR, a notch above India’s sovereign rating</li><li>Adani Green Energy Ltd. (AGEL) and Adani Energy Solutions Ltd. (AESL) have each been rated &apos;BBB+&apos; with Stable Outlook at Par with India’s sovereign rating</li><li>APSEZ’s strong rating underlines its strong credit profile, diversified asset base, and resilient cash-flow generation</li><li>APSEZ is among a select group of Indian infrastructure companies to achieve an above-sovereign rating from a leading international rating agency</li><li>JCR has assigned ratings to three Adani Portfolio companies, marking one of the first instances of Indian infrastructure platforms being assessed by JCR at these levels</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/61fd8d81-2549-4eaa-9272-d53cf966d410.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Adani Green Energy Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RMDRIP] R M Drip and Sprinklers Systems Limited Delivers 55% YoY Revenue Growth and 139% QoQ Surge in Q3 FY26; EBITDA Jumps 169% QoQ</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=R+M+Drip+and+Sprinklers+Systems+Ltd&title=R+M+Drip+and+Sprinklers+Systems+Limited+Delivers+55%25+YoY+Revenue+Growth+and+139%25+QoQ+Surge+in+Q3+FY26%3B+EBITDA+Jumps+169%25+QoQ&newsId=3c761240-b365-4d60-904e-67689f8dada9&token=M2M3NjEyNDAtYjM2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3c761240-b365-4d60-904e-67689f8dada9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 03:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>R M Drip and Sprinklers Systems Limited announced its financial results for the third quarter ended December 31, 2025 (Q3 FY26). The company confirmed the successful completion of the acquisition of its wholly-owned subsidiary, Brahmanand Pipes Private Limited (BPPL). Q3 FY26 highlights include a 55.05% YoY and 139% QoQ increase in revenue from operations, a 51.71% YoY and 169% QoQ rise in EBITDA, and a 36.50% YoY and 145% QoQ growth in Profit After Tax (PAT). The acquisition of BPPL is expected to increase overall production capacity by approximately 50% and enhance manufacturing flexibility, improve supply-chain reliability, and support sustained revenue growth and operating leverage.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations increased 55.05% YoY and 139% QoQ to 27,463.50 lakh</li><li>EBITDA rose 51.71% YoY and 169% QoQ to 2,257.04 lakh</li><li>Profit After Tax (PAT) grew 36.50% YoY and 145% QoQ to 21,401.62 lakh</li><li>Completion of the acquisition of 100% equity shareholding in Brahmanand Pipes Private Limited</li><li>Expected to increase overall production capacity by approximately 50%</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b8e09e87-5d5f-480c-a5f6-9243c811c851.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: R M Drip and Sprinklers Systems Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ACMESOLAR] ACME Solar Signs PPA for 250 MW ISTS-Connected FDRE Project with NHPC Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ACME+Solar+Holdings+Ltd&title=ACME+Solar+Signs+PPA+for+250+MW+ISTS-Connected+FDRE+Project+with+NHPC+Ltd&newsId=3ed0852a-8cb4-41bb-bc4a-1285bb250237&token=M2VkMDg1MmEtOGNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ed0852a-8cb4-41bb-bc4a-1285bb250237</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 03:23:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>ACME Solar Holdings Limited, through its subsidiary ACME Urja One Private Limited, has signed a 25-year Power Purchase Agreement (PPA) with NHPC Limited for its 250 MW Firm and Dispatchable Renewable Energy (FDRE) Tranche VI Project. The project will be connected to ISTS substations and is expected to have a CUF of more than 60%. ACME Solar will invest approximately Rs 3,700 crore and has already acquired 40% of the land requirement. This PPA increases ACME Solar&apos;s total PPA-signed portfolio to 5,630 MW.</p><ul><li>ACME Solar signs PPA with NHPC Ltd for 250 MW FDRE Tranche VI Project</li><li>Project to be connected to ISTS substations with approvals already in place</li><li>Expected CUF of the project is more than 60%</li><li>ACME Solar to invest approximately Rs 3,700 crore in the project</li><li>ACME Solar&apos;s total PPA-signed portfolio now stands at 5,630 MW</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/93e56cd5-0e25-4141-ab4f-77b019816eb1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ACME Solar Holdings Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LUCENT] Mobavenue AI Tech Ltd to Approve Q3 and Q9 Results for FY 2025-26 and Consider Interim Dividend</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Lucent+Industries+Ltd&title=Mobavenue+AI+Tech+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Q9+Results+for+FY+2025-26+and+Consider+Interim+Dividend&newsId=53feb904-4d60-41d6-945b-806994451b26&token=NTNmZWI5MDQtNGQ2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53feb904-4d60-41d6-945b-806994451b26</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 03:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mobavenue AI Tech Ltd (formerly Lucent Industries Limited) has informed the BSE that their Board of Directors will meet on 11th February 2026 to consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The meeting will also consider declaring an interim dividend for the financial year 2025-26. In accordance with the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, the trading window for dealing in the securities of the company by designated persons and their immediate relatives has been closed and will remain closed till 48 hours after the declaration of the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended on 31st December 2025.</p><ul><li>Mobavenue AI Tech Ltd to approve Q3 and Q9 results for FY 2025-26</li><li>Consideration of interim dividend for FY 2025-26</li><li>Trading window closed for designated persons and their immediate relatives</li><li>Window to remain closed till 48 hours after Q3 and Q9 results declaration</li><li>Formerly known as Lucent Industries Limited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7193741c-5ffb-4c29-939e-1daa3b43d892.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Lucent Industries Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GODREJPROP] Godrej Properties Acquires 8.5-Acre Land Parcel in Pune&apos;s Mahalunge Micro-Market with Estimated Revenue Potential of INR 2,000 Crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Godrej+Properties+Ltd&title=Godrej+Properties+Acquires+8.5-Acre+Land+Parcel+in+Pune%27s+Mahalunge+Micro-Market+with+Estimated+Revenue+Potential+of+INR+2%2C000+Crore&newsId=1b1aef85-3870-412a-8888-01ae92a15048&token=MWIxYWVmODUtMzg3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b1aef85-3870-412a-8888-01ae92a15048</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 00:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Godrej Properties Ltd. (GPL) has acquired an 8.5-acre land parcel in Mahalunge, Pune, through outright purchase. The proposed development will primarily comprise group housing and is expected to offer a developable potential of approximately 2.1 million square feet, with an estimated revenue potential of INR 2,000 crore. The land is strategically located in the Mahalunge-Maan-Nande belt, part of the Mahalunge - Hinjewadi micro-market, and benefits from proximity to the upcoming Pune Inner Ring Road and the city&apos;s fast-growing Hinjewadi—Balewadi corridor. The location offers convenient access to major IT and BFSI hubs in Pune and benefits from a well-developed social infrastructure.</p><ul><li>Godrej Properties acquires 8.5-acre land parcel in Mahalunge, Pune</li><li>Proposed development to offer approximately 2.1 million square feet of developable potential</li><li>Estimated revenue potential of INR 2,000 crore</li><li>Strategically located with proximity to the upcoming Pune Inner Ring Road and Hinjewadi—Balewadi corridor</li><li>Well-developed social infrastructure with convenient access to major IT and BFSI hubs in Pune</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/45fb0400-30a2-4193-a1e8-bdf3775cc948.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Godrej Properties Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MODIPON] Modipon Ltd Reports Zero Investor Complaints for Q4 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MODIPON+LTD.&title=Modipon+Ltd+Reports+Zero+Investor+Complaints+for+Q4+2025&newsId=56a35f72-c6ff-4435-bb16-b88358520cec&token=NTZhMzVmNzItYzZm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56a35f72-c6ff-4435-bb16-b88358520cec</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 00:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Modipon Ltd, as per the enclosed document, has reported zero investor complaints for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The report, in accordance with SEBI regulations, states that there were no pending complaints at the beginning of the quarter, no new complaints received during the quarter, and no complaints left unresolved at the end of the quarter. This report includes various categories of complaints such as non-receipt of refund allotment, non-receipt of dividend on shares, and non-receipt of interest on debentures, among others. All such complaints were reported as &apos;disposed of&apos; during the quarter.</p><ul><li>Modipon Ltd reported zero investor complaints for Q4 2025</li><li>No pending complaints at the beginning of the quarter</li><li>No new complaints received during the quarter</li><li>No complaints left unresolved at the end of the quarter</li><li>All categories of complaints reported as &apos;disposed of&apos; during the quarter</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0a7c5085-e6d0-4016-a4e8-1dcf2a8aba03.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MODIPON LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ACMESOLAR] ACME Solar Subsidiary Signs 250 MW Power Purchase Agreement with NHPC Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ACME+Solar+Holdings+Ltd&title=ACME+Solar+Subsidiary+Signs+250+MW+Power+Purchase+Agreement+with+NHPC+Limited&newsId=9ad30e2c-fdb3-4844-a120-4928af3e3128&token=OWFkMzBlMmMtZmRi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ad30e2c-fdb3-4844-a120-4928af3e3128</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:44:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>ACME Urja One Private Limited, a wholly owned subsidiary of ACME Solar Holdings Ltd, has executed a Power Purchase Agreement (PPA) with NHPC Limited to set up a 250 MW FDRE Project. The project has a scheduled commercial operation date of 30th June 2027 and a project tenure of 25 years from the date of signing of the PPA. The tariff for the project is set at Rs. 4.33 per unit.</p><ul><li>ACME Urja One Private Limited has signed a PPA with NHPC Limited for a 250 MW FDRE project</li><li>The project has a scheduled commercial operation date of 30th June 2027</li><li>The project tenure is 25 years from the date of signing of the PPA</li><li>The tariff for the project is set at Rs. 4.33 per unit</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/29201877-3ee9-4734-b989-a7ec86f46768.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ACME Solar Holdings Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KOTAKBANK] Kotak Mahindra Bank Allots 1,33,400 Equity Shares After Judicial Clearance</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KOTAK+MAHINDRA+BANK+LTD.&title=Kotak+Mahindra+Bank+Allots+1%2C33%2C400+Equity+Shares+After+Judicial+Clearance&newsId=35481a68-ecec-453f-8fff-c898feafb287&token=MzU0ODFhNjgtZWNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">35481a68-ecec-453f-8fff-c898feafb287</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd has allotted 1,33,400 equity shares of Re. 1/- each to eligible equity shareholders. This allotment is in respect of the rights shares and subsequent corporate benefits which had been kept in abeyance, pending judicial clearance. The allotment has been made in line with the order passed by the competent authority.</p><ul><li>Kotak Mahindra Bank allots 1,33,400 equity shares</li><li>Allotment made in respect of rights shares and subsequent corporate benefits</li><li>Allotment made after judicial clearance</li><li>Allotment in line with the order passed by the competent authority</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/98523991-b298-420e-b6b9-ae16e37992ce.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KOTAK MAHINDRA BANK LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>