<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:57:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[POWERMECH] Power Mech Projects Secures Over ₹1,000 Crores in Large-Scale Orders</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Power+Mech+Projects+Ltd&title=Power+Mech+Projects+Secures+Over+%E2%82%B91%2C000+Crores+in+Large-Scale+Orders&newsId=41487351-de35-4323-a5b7-fb46bc2040b5&token=NDE0ODczNTEtZGUz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41487351-de35-4323-a5b7-fb46bc2040b5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:56:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Power Mech Projects Ltd has announced that it has secured large-scale orders aggregating to over ₹1,000 Crores (excluding GST, other applicable taxes and cess, if any). The orders have been awarded by the subsidiaries of Adani Power Limited, namely Mirzapur Thermal Energy (UP) Private Limited and Mahan Energen Limited. The scope of work includes onsite contract services for Erection, Testing, Commissioning and manpower assistance for Performance Guarantee Test of Steam Generator (SG) &amp; Steam Turbine Generator (STG) and its Auxiliaries for 2x800 MW Mirzapur and Mahan Phase-l Ultra Supercritical Thermal Power Project.</p><ul><li>Power Mech Projects secures large-scale orders worth over ₹1,000 Crores.</li><li>Orders awarded by the subsidiaries of Adani Power Limited: Mirzapur Thermal Energy (UP) Private Limited and Mahan Energen Limited.</li><li>Scope of work includes onsite contract services for Erection, Testing, Commissioning and manpower assistance.</li><li>Work to be done for 2x800 MW Mirzapur and Mahan Phase-l Ultra Supercritical Thermal Power Project.</li><li>Orders to be executed within 36 months from the required Erection start date as notified in Notice To Proceed - NTP.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5d912834-3bcf-4eed-8ce6-75f3ad14f6b5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Power Mech Projects Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STYLEBAAZA] Baazar Style Retail Ltd Opens New Store in Gonda, Uttar Pradesh</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Baazar+Style+Retail+Ltd&title=Baazar+Style+Retail+Ltd+Opens+New+Store+in+Gonda%2C+Uttar+Pradesh&newsId=c9ce1d8c-817b-406a-9c6d-4355a1e07423&token=YzljZTFkOGMtODE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9ce1d8c-817b-406a-9c6d-4355a1e07423</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:55:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Baazar Style Retail Ltd, formerly known as Baazar Style Retail Pvt. Ltd., has announced the opening of a new Style Baazar store in Gonda, Uttar Pradesh. This brings the total number of stores to 256 as of the date of this announcement. The company is committed to expanding its retail presence and providing its products to a wider audience.</p><ul><li>Baazar Style Retail Ltd has opened a new Style Baazar store in Gonda, Uttar Pradesh.</li><li>This brings the total number of stores to 256.</li><li>The company is expanding its retail presence in Uttar Pradesh.</li><li>The announcement was made in accordance with Regulation 30 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/587c6476-cf01-4419-9858-4fe37105d48e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Baazar Style Retail Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SOUTHBANK] South Indian Bank Ltd Revises Marginal Cost of Funds Lending Rates (MCLR) for Multiple Tenors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SOUTH+INDIAN+BANK+LTD.&title=South+Indian+Bank+Ltd+Revises+Marginal+Cost+of+Funds+Lending+Rates+%28MCLR%29+for+Multiple+Tenors&newsId=754c2c0e-33f3-4195-b238-c20e04f8767f&token=NzU0YzJjMGUtMzNm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">754c2c0e-33f3-4195-b238-c20e04f8767f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:53:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>South Indian Bank Ltd has revised its Marginal Cost of Funds Based Lending Rates (MCLR) for various tenors with effect from 20th February, 2026. The revised MCLR rates for Tenor, Overnight, One-month, Three-month, Six month, and One year are provided in the document.</p><ul><li>South Indian Bank Ltd revises MCLR for multiple tenors</li><li>Revision effective from 20th February, 2026</li><li>New MCLR rates provided for Overnight, One-month, Three-month, Six month, and One year tenors</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3a2640a6-2a35-413b-ad71-66734fbaf6e8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SOUTH INDIAN BANK LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KPIGREEN] KPI Green Energy Allots 1 Crore Equity Warrants to Promoter Entity Quyosh Energia</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KPI+Green+Energy+Ltd&title=KPI+Green+Energy+Allots+1+Crore+Equity+Warrants+to+Promoter+Entity+Quyosh+Energia&newsId=fe5ec6b1-5703-4dc2-b0f8-c9e3e3d121b8&token=ZmU1ZWM2YjEtNTcw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe5ec6b1-5703-4dc2-b0f8-c9e3e3d121b8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>KPI Green Energy Limited has allotted 1,01,00,000 fully convertible equity warrants to Quyosh Energia Private Limited, an entity belonging to the Promoter group. The warrants have an exercise price of 470.30 with a premium of 7465.30 per warrant. Each warrant is convertible into one fully paid-up Equity Share of Rs. 5/- each on payment of the balance 75% of the total consideration. The securities allotted on a preferential basis shall be subject to lock-in restriction as prescribed under the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Issue of Capital and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2018.</p><ul><li>KPI Green Energy allotted 1,01,00,000 fully convertible equity warrants to Quyosh Energia</li><li>The warrants have an exercise price of 470.30 with a premium of 7465.30 per warrant</li><li>Each warrant is convertible into one fully paid-up Equity Share of Rs. 5/- each</li><li>The securities allotted on a preferential basis are subject to lock-in restriction</li><li>The allotment was approved by the Members of the Company and in-principle approval received from NSE and BSE</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/597bb88a-516d-4c92-9908-a693ecf1a71d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KPI Green Energy Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BELLACASA] Independent Director, Mrs. Nivedita Ravindra Sarda, Resigns from Bella Casa Fashion &amp; Retail Ltd.</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Bella+Casa+Fashion+%26+Retail+Ltd&title=Independent+Director%2C+Mrs.+Nivedita+Ravindra+Sarda%2C+Resigns+from+Bella+Casa+Fashion+%26+Retail+Ltd.&newsId=143b3d84-63e6-481b-9599-87609c359ed2&token=MTQzYjNkODQtNjNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">143b3d84-63e6-481b-9599-87609c359ed2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bella Casa Fashion &amp; Retail Ltd. announced the resignation of Mrs. Nivedita Ravindra Sarda as an Independent Director, citing professional and personal commitments. The resignation will be effective from close of business hours on February 24, 2026. Mrs. Sarda also resigned from her positions as chairperson of the Nomination and Remuneration committee and member of the Shareholder’s / Investors Grievance Committee. She holds directorships in Mayur Uniquoters Limited and Electrotherm (India) Limited.</p><ul><li>Mrs. Nivedita Ravindra Sarda resigns as Independent Director from Bella Casa Fashion &amp; Retail Ltd.</li><li>Resignation effective from close of business hours on February 24, 2026.</li><li>Mrs. Sarda also resigns from her positions as chairperson of the Nomination and Remuneration committee and member of the Shareholder’s / Investors Grievance Committee.</li><li>Mrs. Sarda holds directorships in Mayur Uniquoters Limited and Electrotherm (India) Limited.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/888fb36a-e10e-4b75-83eb-d6e5423ec053.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Bella Casa Fashion & Retail Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CEIGALL] Ceigall India Ltd Incorporates Subsidiary &apos;Ceigall Sahebganj Bettiah Highway Limited&apos;</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ceigall+India+Ltd&title=Ceigall+India+Ltd+Incorporates+Subsidiary+%27Ceigall+Sahebganj+Bettiah+Highway+Limited%27&newsId=2dd1b7f3-ca29-4363-8f53-7da568c79377&token=MmRkMWI3ZjMtY2Ey</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2dd1b7f3-ca29-4363-8f53-7da568c79377</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Ceigall India Ltd has incorporated a new subsidiary, &apos;Ceigall Sahebganj Bettiah Highway Limited&apos;, on February 17, 2026, in India. The new subsidiary is a Special Purpose Vehicle (SPV) established to undertake the project of &apos;Construction of 4 laning of Sahebganj Areraj Bettiah of NH 139W&apos; in the State of Bihar on Hybrid Annuity Mode. The project is awarded by the National Highways Authority of India.</p><ul><li>Ceigall India Ltd incorporates a new subsidiary, &apos;Ceigall Sahebganj Bettiah Highway Limited&apos;</li><li>The new subsidiary is a Special Purpose Vehicle (SPV) for the project &apos;Construction of 4 laning of Sahebganj Areraj Bettiah of NH 139W&apos;</li><li>The project is awarded by the National Highways Authority of India</li><li>The project is in the Infrastructure Development Industry</li><li>Ceigall India Ltd holds 100% shareholding in the new subsidiary</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bb5e725c-9c61-4564-842f-c25493a68b6a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ceigall India Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GLAND] Gland Pharma Appoints Dr. Jitendra Gangwal as Vice President (R&amp;D) from Feb 18, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Gland+Pharma+Ltd&title=Gland+Pharma+Appoints+Dr.+Jitendra+Gangwal+as+Vice+President+%28R%26D%29+from+Feb+18%2C+2026&newsId=83b7233a-f266-4a90-88ac-f7db1179078d&token=ODNiNzIzM2EtZjI2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">83b7233a-f266-4a90-88ac-f7db1179078d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gland Pharma Ltd. has appointed Dr. Jitendra Gangwal as Vice President (Research and Development) with effect from February 18, 2026. Dr. Gangwal is a seasoned pharmaceutical R&amp;D leader with 24 years of experience across premier research institutions and leading Indian pharmaceutical organizations. He has developed 55 products, filed 10 patents, and led multiple 505(b)(2) and ANDA filings. His expertise includes complex parenterals, nano-crystals, liposomes, microspheres, depot systems, peptides, metal complexes, and advanced polymer-based delivery systems. Dr. Gangwal holds a PhD from National Chemical Laboratory, Pune.</p><ul><li>Dr. Jitendra Gangwal appointed as Vice President (R&amp;D) of Gland Pharma Ltd.</li><li>Dr. Gangwal has 24 years of experience in pharmaceutical R&amp;D.</li><li>He has developed 55 products and filed 10 patents.</li><li>His expertise includes complex parenterals, nano-crystals, and liposomes.</li><li>Dr. Gangwal holds a PhD from National Chemical Laboratory, Pune.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2bc9ed01-fb1a-4057-90e4-fce313c31d96.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Gland Pharma Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ELNET] Elnet Technologies Ltd Independent Director, Mr. AP Radhakrishnan, Passes Away</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ELNET+TECHNOLOGIES+LTD.-%24&title=Elnet+Technologies+Ltd+Independent+Director%2C+Mr.+AP+Radhakrishnan%2C+Passes+Away&newsId=2630f3a7-a708-4b93-af36-1c0c0af42274&token=MjYzMGYzYTctYTcw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2630f3a7-a708-4b93-af36-1c0c0af42274</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Elnet Technologies Ltd has announced the unfortunate demise of its Independent Director, Mr. AP Radhakrishnan, due to illness and old age on 17th February 2026. Mr. Radhakrishnan was a part of the company&apos;s board since 2nd March 2019 and his contributions and rich experience were highly beneficial to the company. The board and employees express their deep sympathy, sorrow, and condolences to his family.</p><ul><li>Elnet Technologies Ltd Independent Director, Mr. AP Radhakrishnan, has passed away due to illness and old age.</li><li>Mr. Radhakrishnan was a board member since 2nd March 2019.</li><li>His contributions and rich experience significantly benefited the company during his tenure.</li><li>The board and employees express their deep sympathy, sorrow, and condolences to his family.</li><li>The company has made the necessary disclosures as required by the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c0f383b8-3332-4dfd-b0a7-0c236f7abbae.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ELNET TECHNOLOGIES LTD.-$ | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GLOBECIVIL] Globe Civil Projects India Limited Announces Q3 &amp; 9M FY26 Financial Results: Steady Execution Reflects Operational Discipline and Order-Led Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Globe+Civil+Projects+Ltd&title=Globe+Civil+Projects+India+Limited+Announces+Q3+%26+9M+FY26+Financial+Results%3A+Steady+Execution+Reflects+Operational+Discipline+and+Order-Led+Growth&newsId=666b7d00-2a0d-4f45-b0ef-48c738b5ae01&token=NjY2YjdkMDAtMmEw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">666b7d00-2a0d-4f45-b0ef-48c738b5ae01</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:39:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Globe Civil Projects India Limited, an EPC-focused infrastructure company, has announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The Company demonstrated stable operational execution during the period, supported by progress across ongoing projects and disciplined cost management within its Engineering, Procurement and Construction (EPC) operations. The key financial highlights for the nine months ended December 31, 2025, include a total income of 2481.37 million, a net profit of 175.67 million, and a net profit margin of ~7.07%. For the third quarter of the financial year 2026, the Company reported a total income of 937.57 million, a net profit of 65.28 million, and a net profit margin of ~6.96%. The consolidated financial highlights for the nine months ended December 31, 2025, include a total income of 2645.70 million, a net profit of 3175.41 million, and a net profit margin of 6.63%.</p><ul><li>Steady execution across EPC projects reflects operational discipline and order-led growth.</li><li>Total income for 9M FY26 stands at 2481.37 million with a net profit of 175.67 million.</li><li>Total income for Q3 FY26 is 937.57 million with a net profit of 65.28 million.</li><li>Consolidated total income for 9M FY26 is 2645.70 million with a net profit of 3175.41 million.</li><li>Company remains committed to strengthening execution capabilities, improving working capital efficiency, and pursuing opportunities aligned with its risk framework.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1744d3c2-ae21-4135-8d9a-a4324a9a0840.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Globe Civil Projects Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SCI] Shipping Corporation of India&apos;s Director (Finance) Position Temporarily Filled by Director (Personnel &amp; Administration)</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHIPPING+CORPORATION+OF+INDIA+LTD.&title=Shipping+Corporation+of+India%27s+Director+%28Finance%29+Position+Temporarily+Filled+by+Director+%28Personnel+%26+Administration%29&newsId=2de0db18-00b9-483c-8523-f3ef20578b1a&token=MmRlMGRiMTgtMDBi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2de0db18-00b9-483c-8523-f3ef20578b1a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Shipping Corporation of India Ltd. has announced that the Ministry of Ports, Shipping and Waterways has informed them about the approval from the Appointments Committee of the Cabinet (ACC) for the entrustment of additional charge of the post of Director (Finance) to Shri Som Raj, Director (Personnel &amp; Administration), SCI. This appointment is for a period of three months starting from 1st January 2026, or until the assumption of charge of the post by the regular incumbent, or until further orders, whichever is the earliest.</p><ul><li>The Appointments Committee of the Cabinet (ACC) has approved the entrustment of additional charge of the post of Director (Finance) to Shri Som Raj, Director (Personnel &amp; Administration), SCI.</li><li>The appointment is for a period of three months starting from 1st January 2026.</li><li>The appointment is subject to the assumption of charge of the post by the regular incumbent or until further orders.</li><li>The decision was communicated by the Ministry of Ports, Shipping and Waterways.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ac38be1a-92b6-470a-8aca-ef0be1f7a67d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHIPPING CORPORATION OF INDIA LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>