<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:21:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[IWP] Promoter Mr. Krishna Kumar Mohta Acquires 0.043% Shares in The Indian Wood Products Company Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=The+Indian+Wood+Products+Company+Ltd&title=Promoter+Mr.+Krishna+Kumar+Mohta+Acquires+0.043%25+Shares+in+The+Indian+Wood+Products+Company+Ltd&newsId=8e441e44-3f56-4293-9f6a-59f6fe44ed6f&token=OGU0NDFlNDQtM2Y1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8e441e44-3f56-4293-9f6a-59f6fe44ed6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:15:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Buyback</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>On 27.02.2026, Mr. Krishna Kumar Mohta, a promoter of The Indian Wood Products Company Ltd, has acquired 27724 equity shares of the company from the open market. This acquisition increases his holding from 3.095% to 3.138%. The company&apos;s equity capital remains unchanged at Rs. 12,79,45,440 comprising of 63972720 equity shares of Rs. 2/- each.</p><ul><li>Mr. Krishna Kumar Mohta acquires 27724 equity shares</li><li>His shareholding increases from 3.095% to 3.138%</li><li>The acquisition is made from the open market</li><li>The company&apos;s equity capital remains unchanged</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ba2676a9-70c3-42ce-8d3b-60406c95e124.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: The Indian Wood Products Company Ltd | Category: Buyback</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZENITHEXPO] Zenith Exports Ltd Fined Rs. 3,95,300 for Violating SEBI LODR Regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ZENITH+EXPORTS+LTD.&title=Zenith+Exports+Ltd+Fined+Rs.+3%2C95%2C300+for+Violating+SEBI+LODR+Regulations&newsId=8673b51c-caf6-4e6e-bffa-be84f0af8013&token=ODY3M2I1MWMtY2Fm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8673b51c-caf6-4e6e-bffa-be84f0af8013</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:14:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Zenith Exports Ltd has received an email from the Stock Exchange regarding a penalty imposed on the company for violating Regulation 17(1) of the SEBI LODR Regulations, 2015. The company has been fined Rs. 3,95,300 (Rs. 3,35,000 plus 18% GST) by both BSE and NSE. The fine is for non-compliance during the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The company is in the process of submitting request letters for waiver of the fine to both stock exchanges.</p><ul><li>Zenith Exports Ltd fined Rs. 3,95,300 for violating SEBI LODR Regulations</li><li>The fine is for non-compliance during the quarter ended 31st December 2025</li><li>The company has received notices from BSE and NSE</li><li>The company is in the process of submitting request letters for waiver of the fine to both stock exchanges</li><li>There is no material impact on the company&apos;s financials, operations, or other activities</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6167a139-5d51-404c-91de-4ec025d92ed3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ZENITH EXPORTS LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GOACARBON] Goa Carbon Ltd Wins Environmental Pollution Case Against Company’s Goa Plant</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GOA+CARBON+LTD.-%24&title=Goa+Carbon+Ltd+Wins+Environmental+Pollution+Case+Against+Company%E2%80%99s+Goa+Plant&newsId=1b22c6b8-e8b9-4cec-b029-ee82dcda881f&token=MWIyMmM2YjgtZThi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b22c6b8-e8b9-4cec-b029-ee82dcda881f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:13:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Goa Carbon Limited has informed the Exchange regarding the final order dated 27/02/2026 of the National Green Tribunal (NGT) dismissing the original application filed by the applicants against the Company’s Goa plant over an alleged environmental pollution case. The Tribunal, after considering various factors, decided in favour of the Company, stating that no violation could be presumed at the stage of grant of consent and no ground was made out for directing shifting or closure of the Company’s Goa Plant.</p><ul><li>National Green Tribunal dismisses original application against Goa Carbon Ltd’s Goa plant.</li><li>Tribunal finds no violation at the stage of grant of consent and no ground for plant closure.</li><li>Joint Committee Inspection did not record any instance of non-compliance on the part of the Company.</li><li>Goa State Pollution Control Board granted Consent to Operate, demonstrating regulatory satisfaction.</li><li>No financial impact on Goa Carbon Ltd due to the dismissal of the case.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8e7967b6-d5e8-4856-a880-b5bd0d6c6e0a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GOA CARBON LTD.-$ | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VPRPL] Promoter Vijay Punglia Releases and Creates Pledges on Shares of Vishnu Prakash R Punglia Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vishnu+Prakash+R+Punglia+Ltd&title=Promoter+Vijay+Punglia+Releases+and+Creates+Pledges+on+Shares+of+Vishnu+Prakash+R+Punglia+Ltd&newsId=68c55359-b3fc-4ced-8586-2beb7af22587&token=NjhjNTUzNTktYjNm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68c55359-b3fc-4ced-8586-2beb7af22587</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:13:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>On February 20, 2026, Vijay Punglia, a promoter of Vishnu Prakash R Punglia Ltd, released a pledge of 800,000 shares. On February 23, 2026, he created a pledge for 250,000 shares to generate liquidity for trading. On February 24, 2026, he released a pledge of 2,700,000 shares. These transactions were reported under Regulation 31(1) and 31(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</p><ul><li>Vijay Punglia released a pledge of 800,000 shares on February 20, 2026.</li><li>Vijay Punglia created a pledge for 250,000 shares on February 23, 2026 to generate liquidity for trading.</li><li>Vijay Punglia released a pledge of 2,700,000 shares on February 24, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/FF64EC60_B670_402C_8C3D_F9264C056388_141318.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vishnu Prakash R Punglia Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BBOX] Black Box Ltd Allots 6,46,674 Equity Shares Following Warrant Conversion</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Black+Box+Ltd&title=Black+Box+Ltd+Allots+6%2C46%2C674+Equity+Shares+Following+Warrant+Conversion&newsId=8328d0f0-f6e0-440e-b108-8b157385ba12&token=ODMyOGQwZjAtZjZl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8328d0f0-f6e0-440e-b108-8b157385ba12</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:04:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Black Box Ltd has allotted 6,46,674 equity shares to three allottees following the conversion of warrants. The allottees include Excello Fin Lea Limited, Ushma Mehta, and Ajay Patadia. The warrants were allotted at a price of Rs. 417 each, including a premium of Rs. 415 each. The allottees have paid 75% of the issue price to convert the warrants into equity shares. The total consideration for the allotment is Rs. 26,96,63,058.</p><ul><li>Black Box Ltd has allotted 6,46,674 equity shares to three allottees.</li><li>The allotment follows the conversion of warrants held by the allottees.</li><li>The total consideration for the allotment is Rs. 26,96,63,058.</li><li>The allottees include Excello Fin Lea Limited, Ushma Mehta, and Ajay Patadia.</li><li>The warrants were allotted at a price of Rs. 417 each, including a premium of Rs. 415 each.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/80b17a02-0418-4a29-a716-f322397512a7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Black Box Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LOVABLE] Executive Director, Vindamuri Giri Raj, Resigns from Lovable Lingerie Ltd.</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LOVABLE+LINGERIE+LTD.&title=Executive+Director%2C+Vindamuri+Giri+Raj%2C+Resigns+from+Lovable+Lingerie+Ltd.&newsId=e258b28e-ca40-408c-851f-1bcfc3c4335a&token=ZTI1OGIyOGUtY2E0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e258b28e-ca40-408c-851f-1bcfc3c4335a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 09:04:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Lovable Lingerie Ltd. has announced the resignation of its Executive Director, Vindamuri Giri Raj, with effect from the close of business hours on February 28, 2026. The resignation is due to personal reasons. Mr. Raj has confirmed that there are no other material reasons for his resignation. The company has received his resignation letter and will comply with all necessary statutory and regulatory formalities.</p><ul><li>Vindamuri Giri Raj resigns from Lovable Lingerie Ltd.</li><li>Resignation takes effect from February 28, 2026</li><li>Resignation is due to personal reasons</li><li>No other material reasons for resignation</li><li>Company to comply with all necessary formalities</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/586c4baf-df55-466d-ac3a-bddcc201cb0b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LOVABLE LINGERIE LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHBAJRG] Shri Bajrang Alliance Ltd Reduces Partnership Interest in Shri Bajrang Chemical Distillery LLP</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shri+Bajrang+Alliance+Ltd&title=Shri+Bajrang+Alliance+Ltd+Reduces+Partnership+Interest+in+Shri+Bajrang+Chemical+Distillery+LLP&newsId=9d8e4961-de52-4093-9208-35d3758986cb&token=OWQ4ZTQ5NjEtZGU1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d8e4961-de52-4093-9208-35d3758986cb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 08:33:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Partnership</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shri Bajrang Alliance Ltd has reconstituted its partnership interest in its associate, Shri Bajrang Chemical Distillery LLP. The reconstitution has resulted in a reduction of the Company’s partnership interest from 30% to 16%. This has been done to optimize capital allocation, enhance liquidity and financial flexibility, reduce long-term capital commitment and contingent exposures, align investments with core business priorities, and enable redeployment of capital towards expansion of principal operating segments. The reconstitution does not involve any sale to a third party and has been effected internally among existing promoter-group partners. The transaction is not expected to affect control of the LLP.</p><ul><li>Shri Bajrang Alliance Ltd reduces its partnership interest in Shri Bajrang Chemical Distillery LLP from 30% to 16%.</li><li>The reconstitution is aimed at optimizing capital allocation, enhancing liquidity, and reducing long-term capital commitment.</li><li>The transaction is not a sale to a third party and has been effected internally among existing promoter-group partners.</li><li>The reconstitution is expected to improve capital efficiency, liquidity position, and funding flexibility.</li><li>The transaction does not affect control of the LLP.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3f4db815-5909-468e-8a82-cdcb344b9302.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shri Bajrang Alliance Ltd | Category: Partnership</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MAPMYINDIA] Decentralization and Premiumization Reshaping India’s Retail Sector: ClarityX and Mastercard Report</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=C.E.+Info+Systems+Ltd&title=Decentralization+and+Premiumization+Reshaping+India%E2%80%99s+Retail+Sector%3A+ClarityX+and+Mastercard+Report&newsId=48586838-ad6a-4b5e-973b-2707f7d8024a&token=NDg1ODY4MzgtYWQ2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48586838-ad6a-4b5e-973b-2707f7d8024a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 08:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>According to a report by ClarityX and Mastercard, decentralization of demand and rapid premiumization are accelerating India’s retail transformation. The report, co-powered by Mapmyindia data, examines demand and supply trends from 2023-2025 and highlights how multi-party data and hyperlocal decision-making are becoming essential in an increasingly diverse retail landscape. Non-metro India is powering the next phase of growth, with Tier 3-5 cities growing almost twice as fast as metros. The report also reveals that offline consumer spends grew 20% between 2023-2025, while retail outlets expanded 25% in the same period.</p><ul><li>Decentralization of demand and rapid premiumization accelerating India’s retail transformation</li><li>Multi-party data and hyperlocal decision-making becoming essential in diverse retail landscape</li><li>Tier 3-5 cities growing almost twice as fast as metros</li><li>Offline consumer spends grew 20% between 2023-2025</li><li>Retail outlets expanded 25% in the same period</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/79dc64a8-33be-47b4-9f8b-3ef28f796f22.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: C.E. Info Systems Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MEGASOFT] Sigma Advanced Systems Faces Fine for Non-Compliance with SEBI Regulations on Board Composition</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MEGASOFT+LTD.&title=Sigma+Advanced+Systems+Faces+Fine+for+Non-Compliance+with+SEBI+Regulations+on+Board+Composition&newsId=d47150d1-6a33-4861-97c8-3cbca028bac6&token=ZDQ3MTUwZDEtNmEz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d47150d1-6a33-4861-97c8-3cbca028bac6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 08:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sigma Advanced Systems Ltd. has received emails from BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange of India Limited, imposing a fine of Rs. 4,83,800 each for non-compliance with Regulation 17(1) of SEBI listing regulations. The non-compliance pertains to the composition of the board, having fallen short of one director. However, the company has already complied with the requirement by appointing Mr. Cheemarla Damodar Reddy as Additional Director. The fine will be paid in compliance with the applicable SEBI listing regulations and circulars.</p><ul><li>Sigma Advanced Systems received emails from BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange of India Limited imposing a fine for non-compliance with Regulation 17(1) of SEBI listing regulations.</li><li>The non-compliance is regarding the composition of the board, with the company falling short of one director.</li><li>The company has already complied with the requirement by appointing Mr. Cheemarla Damodar Reddy as Additional Director.</li><li>The fine imposed by each exchange is Rs. 4,83,800.</li><li>The company will pay the fines in compliance with the applicable SEBI listing regulations and circulars.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0bf0f901-7e0b-46a6-b8cd-fb52700979cf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MEGASOFT LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BHARTIARTL] Bharti Airtel Faces Penalties Totaling Rs. 2,53,000 for Subscriber Verification Norms Violation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BHARTI+AIRTEL+LTD.&title=Bharti+Airtel+Faces+Penalties+Totaling+Rs.+2%2C53%2C000+for+Subscriber+Verification+Norms+Violation&newsId=47a18973-076b-4b13-acd9-02d2a967ca1e&token=NDdhMTg5NzMtMDc2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47a18973-076b-4b13-acd9-02d2a967ca1e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 08:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bharti Airtel Ltd. has disclosed receiving notices from the Department of Telecommunications (DoT) in Madhya Pradesh and Uttar Pradesh (East) Licence Service Areas (LSA) imposing penalties for alleged violation of subscriber verification norms. The Madhya Pradesh LSA notice imposes a penalty of Rs. 1,44,000, while the Uttar Pradesh (East) LSA notice imposes a penalty of Rs. 1,09,000, totaling Rs. 2,53,000. The notices were received on February 27, 2026. The company has opted to pay the penalties instead of contesting them.</p><ul><li>Bharti Airtel received notices from the Department of Telecommunications in Madhya Pradesh and Uttar Pradesh (East) Licence Service Areas (LSA).</li><li>The notices were for alleged violation of subscriber verification norms.</li><li>The Madhya Pradesh LSA notice imposes a penalty of Rs. 1,44,000, while the Uttar Pradesh (East) LSA notice imposes a penalty of Rs. 1,09,000.</li><li>The company has opted to pay the penalties instead of contesting them.</li><li>The notices were received on February 27, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3e84f76a-4202-4e35-a33f-afbbc4ad22f3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BHARTI AIRTEL LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>