<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:22:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[MCX] MCX Reports 115% Y-o-Y Increase in Total Revenue for Q3 FY26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MULTI+COMMODITY+EXCHANGE+OF+INDIA+LTD.&title=MCX+Reports+115%25+Y-o-Y+Increase+in+Total+Revenue+for+Q3+FY26&newsId=e368ae58-0904-41a1-9f83-002b70625cef&token=ZTM2OGFlNTgtMDkw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e368ae58-0904-41a1-9f83-002b70625cef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:22:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>The Multi Commodity Exchange of India Ltd. (MCX) announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The total revenue stood at Rs. 697 crores, marking a 115% year-over-year increase. The EBITDA and Profit After Tax (PAT) also saw significant growth of 144% and 151% respectively. The average daily turnover for F&amp;O increased by 224% YoY.</p><ul><li>Total revenue of Rs. 697 crores, up by 115% Y-o-Y</li><li>EBITDA increased to Rs. 527 crore, 144% year-on-year growth</li><li>Profit After Tax (PAT) of Rs. 401 crore, 151% year-on-year growth</li><li>Average Daily Turnover (ADT) for F&amp;O increased by 224% YoY</li><li>Bullion segment share in ADT has grown to 69% QoQ</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6d79fc6a-6b52-49cb-a7f5-169f05be36df.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MULTI COMMODITY EXCHANGE OF INDIA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EXPLEOSOL] Expleo Solutions Ltd Faces Rs. 2.17 Crore Demand from Assistant Commissioner of Income Tax</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Expleo+Solutions+Ltd&title=Expleo+Solutions+Ltd+Faces+Rs.+2.17+Crore+Demand+from+Assistant+Commissioner+of+Income+Tax&newsId=7ee86fb9-e134-4d7b-be70-b66d35c57f16&token=N2VlODZmYjktZTEz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ee86fb9-e134-4d7b-be70-b66d35c57f16</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:21:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Expleo Solutions Ltd has disclosed an order issued by the Assistant Commissioner of Income Tax, Corporate Circle 1 (1), Chennai, raising a demand of Rs. 2,16,77,078 for the Assessment Year 2016-17. The demand is on account of the disallowance of MAT Credit utilized amounting to Rs. 80,00,000. The order was received on 23rd January 2026. The company has stated that there is no material impact on its financials, operations, or other activities.</p><ul><li>Expleo Solutions Ltd faces a demand of Rs. 2.17 Crore from the Assistant Commissioner of Income Tax</li><li>The demand is due to the disallowance of MAT Credit utilized amounting to Rs. 80,00,000 for the Assessment Year 2016-17</li><li>The order was received on 23rd January 2026</li><li>Expleo Solutions Ltd has stated that there is no material impact on its financials, operations, or other activities</li><li>The disclosure is made under Regulation 30 read with Clause 20 Para A of Part A of Schedule III of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3a313e14-92b5-40f2-a423-badfca705ad9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Expleo Solutions Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BANKBARODA] Bank of Baroda Branches May Be Affected by Proposed U.F.B.U. Strike on January 27, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BANK+OF+BARODA&title=Bank+of+Baroda+Branches+May+Be+Affected+by+Proposed+U.F.B.U.+Strike+on+January+27%2C+2026&newsId=378cf6cb-1883-4388-a336-00a26e4c859d&token=Mzc4Y2Y2Y2ItMTg4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">378cf6cb-1883-4388-a336-00a26e4c859d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:21:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Strike</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The United Forum of Bank Unions (U.F.B.U.) has announced a strike on Tuesday, January 27, 2026, over various issues and demands. This may impact the smooth functioning of Bank of Baroda&apos;s branches and offices. The bank is taking necessary steps to minimize disruption, but if the strike materializes, operations may be affected. This notice is pursuant to Regulation 30 of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015, and the information is required to be uploaded on the relevant website.</p><ul><li>United Forum of Bank Unions (U.F.B.U.) has announced a strike on January 27, 2026</li><li>The strike is due to various issues and demands</li><li>Bank of Baroda branches and offices may be affected if the strike materializes</li><li>Bank of Baroda is taking necessary steps to minimize disruption</li><li>This notice is pursuant to Regulation 30 of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c49f5fe5-8184-49d9-9519-b5d18f33415d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BANK OF BARODA | Category: Strike</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VOITHPAPR] Voith Paper Fabrics India Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine-Months Financial Results on February 4, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VOITH+PAPER+FABRICS+INDIA+LTD.-%24&title=Voith+Paper+Fabrics+India+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine-Months+Financial+Results+on+February+4%2C+2026&newsId=f43c6a91-8127-4705-ac42-e67bf380f1b7&token=ZjQzYzZhOTEtODEy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f43c6a91-8127-4705-ac42-e67bf380f1b7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:11:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Voith Paper Fabrics India Ltd has announced a Board Meeting scheduled on February 4, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for the third quarter and nine-months period ended December 31, 2025. This meeting is in accordance with Regulation 29(1)(a) of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Voith Paper Fabrics India Ltd has scheduled a Board Meeting on February 4, 2026</li><li>The meeting aims to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for the third quarter and nine-months period ended December 31, 2025</li><li>This meeting is in compliance with Regulation 29(1)(a) of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1e1adfab-591d-4bf1-a778-1274cbf82ac5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VOITH PAPER FABRICS INDIA LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MUTHTFN] Muthoot Capital Services Ltd: No Requests for Re-lodgment of Physical Shares in January 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MUTHOOT+CAPITAL+SERVICES+LTD.&title=Muthoot+Capital+Services+Ltd%3A+No+Requests+for+Re-lodgment+of+Physical+Shares+in+January+2026&newsId=250e3655-4148-43d5-9af6-803f482254b0&token=MjUwZTM2NTUtNDE0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">250e3655-4148-43d5-9af6-803f482254b0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:11:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>According to a report from Integrated Registry Management Services Private Limited, the Registrar and Share Transfer Agent (RTA) of Muthoot Capital Services Limited, there were no requests for re-lodgment of physical shares received during the period from January 01, 2026, to January 06, 2026. This information is provided in accordance with SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97 dated July 02, 2025.</p><ul><li>No requests for re-lodgment of physical shares received from January 01, 2026, to January 06, 2026.</li><li>Report provided by Integrated Registry Management Services Private Limited, the Registrar and Share Transfer Agent (RTA) of Muthoot Capital Services Limited.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6b0ae391-dc4e-45d3-8bf2-f58a5dd29163.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MUTHOOT CAPITAL SERVICES LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JSWINFRA] JSW Infrastructure Ltd Incorporates New Wholly Owned Subsidiary - Khurja Rail Terminal Private Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JSW+Infrastructure+Ltd&title=JSW+Infrastructure+Ltd+Incorporates+New+Wholly+Owned+Subsidiary+-+Khurja+Rail+Terminal+Private+Limited&newsId=4b93a708-99b9-4943-8ff7-ff167fb6c048&token=NGI5M2E3MDgtOTli</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4b93a708-99b9-4943-8ff7-ff167fb6c048</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Subsidiary Incorporation</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>JSW Infrastructure Ltd has incorporated a step-down wholly owned subsidiary named Khurja Rail Terminal Private Limited (KRTPL) on 234 January, 2026. KRTPL is a wholly owned subsidiary of JSW Port Logistics Private Limited (JSWPLPL), which in turn is a wholly owned subsidiary of JSW Infrastructure Ltd. The newly incorporated KRTPL has an authorized capital of 10,000 Equity shares of Rs. 10/- each and a paid-up share capital of 10,000 Equity shares of Rs. 10/- each. KRTPL is expected to play a role in the acquisition of NCR Rail Infrastructure Limited, as the Resolution Plan for NCR Rail submitted by the Company has been approved by National Company Law Tribunal, Mumbai, Bench Il. JSWPLPL shall subscribe to the shares capital of KRTPL for Rs. 1,00,000 (Rupees One Lakh Only) (10,000 Equity shares of Rs. 10/- each) for subscription to the memorandum of association of KRTPL.</p><ul><li>JSW Infrastructure Ltd incorporates a step-down wholly owned subsidiary - Khurja Rail Terminal Private Limited</li><li>Khurja Rail Terminal Private Limited is a wholly owned subsidiary of JSW Port Logistics Private Limited</li><li>JSWPLPL holds 100% shares of KRTPL</li><li>KRTPL is expected to play a role in the acquisition of NCR Rail Infrastructure Limited</li><li>JSWPLPL shall subscribe to the shares capital of KRTPL for Rs. 1,00,000</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a3c6e61c-f339-45b8-b1ff-8d9dc60a97d1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JSW Infrastructure Ltd | Category: Subsidiary Incorporation</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MEDPLUS] Medplus Health Services Ltd Subsidiary Receives Favorable Order in Tax Dispute</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Medplus+Health+Services+Ltd&title=Medplus+Health+Services+Ltd+Subsidiary+Receives+Favorable+Order+in+Tax+Dispute&newsId=a51b5fde-8d56-4fb5-afb7-feb0d7b2a9ce&token=YTUxYjVmZGUtOGQ1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a51b5fde-8d56-4fb5-afb7-feb0d7b2a9ce</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:51:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Medplus Health Services Ltd announced that its subsidiary, Optival Health Solutions Private Limited, received a favorable order dated November 21, 2025 from the Hon’ble High Court of Telangana with respect to the Assessment order for AY 2020-21. The Income Tax Department filed a review petition for the same on December 23, 2025. The disputed tax amount is Rs. 43.45 Crores. The Company filed a writ petition with the Telangana High Court on December 23, 2025, against the said order and received the intimation for filling the review petition on January 07, 2026. The Court allowed the writ petition.</p><ul><li>Medplus Health Services Ltd subsidiary received a favorable order from the Hon’ble High Court of Telangana</li><li>The order is with respect to the Assessment order for AY 2020-21</li><li>The disputed tax amount is Rs. 43.45 Crores</li><li>The Income Tax Department filed a review petition on December 23, 2025</li><li>The Company filed a writ petition and the Court allowed it</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/860fb589-db69-4c56-b6ac-6b6c12e40021.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Medplus Health Services Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ROSSARI] Rossari Biotech Ltd Completes Sale of Office Premises</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Rossari+Biotech+Ltd&title=Rossari+Biotech+Ltd+Completes+Sale+of+Office+Premises&newsId=010eeb32-414c-484c-8e72-fc797e506cf3&token=MDEwZWViMzItNDE0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">010eeb32-414c-484c-8e72-fc797e506cf3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rossari Biotech Ltd has completed the sale of its office premises at Kanjurmarg, Mumbai as of January 23, 2026. The transaction details were previously disclosed in the intimation letter dated January 17, 2026, and are in compliance with Regulation 30 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, SEBI Master Circular no. SEBI/HO/CFD/PoD2/CIR/P/0155 dated November 11, 2024, and Circular no. SEBI/HO/CFD/CFD-PoD-2/CIR/P/2024/185 dated December 31, 2024. The information is available on the company&apos;s website and should be disseminated to all concerned.</p><ul><li>Rossari Biotech Ltd completed the sale of its office premises on January 23, 2026.</li><li>The transaction details were disclosed in the intimation letter dated January 17, 2026.</li><li>The sale is in compliance with various SEBI regulations and circulars.</li><li>The information is available on the company&apos;s website.</li><li>The update should be disseminated to all concerned parties.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/76dff9b3-52a9-4da5-9086-da3c2b3c8f52.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Rossari Biotech Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GODREJCP] Godrej Consumer Products Ltd Declares Interim Dividend of Rs. 5/- per Equity Share for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GODREJ+CONSUMER+PRODUCTS+LTD.&title=Godrej+Consumer+Products+Ltd+Declares+Interim+Dividend+of+Rs.+5%2F-+per+Equity+Share+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=0a994e0b-7221-4f27-876b-1993c5e57fa6&token=MGE5OTRlMGItNzIy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a994e0b-7221-4f27-876b-1993c5e57fa6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:32:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Godrej Consumer Products Ltd has declared an interim dividend for FY 2025-26 at Rs. 5/- (Rupees Five Only) per Equity Share. The record date for the payment of dividend is Friday, January 30, 2026. All shareholders are requested to ensure that their mandatory information is updated with the company or the Registrar and Share Transfer Agent of the Company by the end of Friday, January 30, 2026. The company will rely on the updated details in the Register of Members as on the Record date for Tax Deducted at Source (TDS) purposes. The relevant provisions of the Income Tax Act, 1961, in relation to TDS for Resident and Non-Resident Shareholder categories, are also provided in the document.</p><ul><li>Godrej Consumer Products Ltd declares an interim dividend of Rs. 5/- per Equity Share for FY 2025-26.</li><li>The record date for the payment of dividend is Friday, January 30, 2026.</li><li>Shareholders are requested to update their mandatory information by the end of Friday, January 30, 2026.</li><li>The company will rely on the updated details in the Register of Members as on the Record date for TDS purposes.</li><li>The relevant provisions of the Income Tax Act, 1961, in relation to TDS for Resident and Non-Resident Shareholder categories, are provided in the document.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f446b842-3a71-48b3-bd15-ba45caa354d9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GODREJ CONSUMER PRODUCTS LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SCPL] Sheetal Cool Products Ltd. Issues Corrigendum to Extraordinary General Meeting Notice</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sheetal+Cool+Products+Ltd&title=Sheetal+Cool+Products+Ltd.+Issues+Corrigendum+to+Extraordinary+General+Meeting+Notice&newsId=ade3bbb8-ffe7-4234-a007-abf4d6e0d07a&token=YWRlM2JiYjgtZmZl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ade3bbb8-ffe7-4234-a007-abf4d6e0d07a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sheetal Cool Products Ltd. has issued a corrigendum to the notice of the Extraordinary General Meeting (EGM) scheduled for 05th February, 2026. The corrigendum includes changes to the explanatory statement, such as the intent of promoters, directors, and key managerial personnel to not subscribe to the offer, the identity of ultimate beneficial owners, a practicing company secretary&apos;s certificate, and a valuation report from an independent registered valuer. The EGM will be held through video conferencing and other audio-visual means.</p><ul><li>Corrigendum to the Notice of Extraordinary General Meeting issued by Sheetal Cool Products Ltd.</li><li>Changes to the Explanatory Statement, including the intent of promoters, directors, and key managerial personnel to not subscribe to the offer.</li><li>Identity of ultimate beneficial owners disclosed.</li><li>Practicing Company Secretary&apos;s Certificate and Valuation Report from an Independent Registered Valuer obtained.</li><li>EGM to be held on 05th February, 2026 through video conferencing and other audio-visual means.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2589cb77-f03b-4f0d-9971-f9c0574b327f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sheetal Cool Products Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>