<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 06:34:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[RELAXO] Relaxo Footwears Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results on Jan 30, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RELAXO+FOOTWEARS+LTD.-%24&title=Relaxo+Footwears+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+on+Jan+30%2C+2026&newsId=5b9ffbdf-6de1-4129-a3d2-7aec63cf54f0&token=NWI5ZmZiZGYtNmRl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b9ffbdf-6de1-4129-a3d2-7aec63cf54f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 06:33:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Relaxo Footwears Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 30, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing/trading in the securities of the company will remain closed for all designated persons and their immediate relatives till February 1, 2026.</p><ul><li>Relaxo Footwears Ltd to approve Q3 and nine months results on January 30, 2026</li><li>Unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025 to be considered and approved</li><li>Trading window for dealing/trading in the securities of the company to remain closed till February 1, 2026 for designated persons and their immediate relatives</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6e5056e6-6e8d-4ee6-8480-a176eeb2c393.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RELAXO FOOTWEARS LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RECLTD] REC Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on January 29, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=REC+Ltd&title=REC+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+January+29%2C+2026&newsId=b58e6f14-9288-45f1-9ec4-ef767e92c0de&token=YjU4ZTZmMTQtOTI4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b58e6f14-9288-45f1-9ec4-ef767e92c0de</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 06:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>REC Ltd, a renowned company with the scrip code 532955, has announced a meeting of its Board of Directors on January 29, 2026. The agenda includes the consideration and approval of the unaudited financial results (standalone &amp; consolidated) for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company has also informed that the trading window for designated persons and their immediate relatives will remain closed from January 1, 2026 to January 31, 2026, in accordance with its code of conduct and as informed in a letter dated December 26, 2025.</p><ul><li>REC Ltd to consider and approve unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Trading window for designated persons and their immediate relatives to remain closed from January 1, 2026 to January 31, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d5297933-fd01-418e-9145-fffb3f373cff.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: REC Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[REGAL] Regal Entertainment &amp; Consultants Ltd to Approve Unaudited Financials for Q3 and Nine Months of FY2025-2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Regal+Entertainment+%26+Consultants+Ltd&title=Regal+Entertainment+%26+Consultants+Ltd+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financials+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+of+FY2025-2026&newsId=cb647f07-e7ef-4fc0-93af-72496b076788&token=Y2I2NDdmMDctZTdl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb647f07-e7ef-4fc0-93af-72496b076788</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 06:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Regal Entertainment &amp; Consultants Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 27th January 2026 to consider and approve the unaudited Financials for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The meeting will be held at the company&apos;s registered office in Mumbai, Maharashtra. Additionally, the company has informed that the trading window for trading in the securities of the Company will remain closed till 29th January 2026.</p><ul><li>Regal Entertainment &amp; Consultants Ltd to consider and approve unaudited Financials for Q3 and nine months of FY2025-2026</li><li>Board Meeting scheduled on 27th January 2026</li><li>Meeting to be held at the company&apos;s registered office in Mumbai, Maharashtra</li><li>Trading window for the company&apos;s securities to remain closed till 29th January 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5ae3fc60-9456-4427-83af-0c7c54d5f022.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Regal Entertainment & Consultants Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LLFICL] Leading Leasing Finance and Investment Company Ltd Signs MoU with MFINS Services Private Limited for Solar Panel Loan Segment in India</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Leading+Leasing+Finance+And+Investment+Company+Ltd&title=Leading+Leasing+Finance+and+Investment+Company+Ltd+Signs+MoU+with+MFINS+Services+Private+Limited+for+Solar+Panel+Loan+Segment+in+India&newsId=1f8f92ff-c046-48f0-8c00-5395b16212d8&token=MWY4ZjkyZmYtYzA0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f8f92ff-c046-48f0-8c00-5395b16212d8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 06:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>MoU</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Leading Leasing Finance and Investment Company Limited has executed a Memorandum of Understanding with MFINS Services Private Limited to collaborate in the solar panel loan segment in India. The proposed MoU involves a strategic partnership to leverage their respective strengths to jointly develop and scale solar panel loan offerings. This collaboration aims to expand the Company’s loan book, strengthen market participation, and capitalize on the expanding solar panel loan segment with enhanced product reach and competitive positioning.</p><ul><li>Leading Leasing Finance and Investment Company Ltd has signed an MoU with MFINS Services Private Limited</li><li>The collaboration aims to jointly pursue opportunities in the solar panel loan segment in India</li><li>The strategic partnership will leverage the Company’s financial expertise and Mfins’s operational capabilities</li><li>The MoU is expected to expand the Company’s loan book, strengthen market participation, and improve competitive positioning</li><li>The MoU is valid for a period of One (1) year from 19° January 2026 and may be terminated by either party with Thirty (30) days’ written notice</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0793dd41-12fd-43eb-b153-28f6d530a9d0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Leading Leasing Finance And Investment Company Ltd | Category: MoU</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MOSCHIP] MosChip Delivers a Custom SoC to ISRO&apos;s Space Applications Centre for India&apos;s Satellite Navigation Program</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Moschip+Technologies+Ltd&title=MosChip+Delivers+a+Custom+SoC+to+ISRO%27s+Space+Applications+Centre+for+India%27s+Satellite+Navigation+Program&newsId=18520ef4-c119-4671-b47a-d06a9ff7a31a&token=MTg1MjBlZjQtYzEx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18520ef4-c119-4671-b47a-d06a9ff7a31a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 06:26:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>MosChip Technologies, a leading provider of silicon and product engineering services, has successfully completed an end-to-end turnkey ASIC program from Netlist to packaged silicon for ISRO’s Space Applications Centre (SAC) for India’s Satellite Navigation Program. The program exemplifies MosChip’s integrated Turnkey ASIC capability, managing every critical phase from DFT architecture to post-silicon bring-up and validation. Packaged silicon has been delivered and validated, enabling SAC to proceed to the next stage of productization.</p><ul><li>MosChip delivers a custom SoC to ISRO&apos;s Space Applications Centre for India&apos;s Satellite Navigation Program.</li><li>Successful silicon bring-up of SAC’s custom SoC in 28nm technology node.</li><li>End-to-end turnkey ASIC program from Netlist to packaged silicon completed.</li><li>Packaged silicon delivered and validated, enabling SAC to proceed to the next stage of productization.</li><li>MosChip&apos;s integrated Turnkey ASIC capability demonstrated.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bb33bf7f-ba27-4644-bbe7-3beec8339e27.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Moschip Technologies Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WEL] Wonder Electricals Ltd Clarifies Significant Increase in Share Trading Volume</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Wonder+Electricals+Ltd&title=Wonder+Electricals+Ltd+Clarifies+Significant+Increase+in+Share+Trading+Volume&newsId=85ad7713-203c-413b-9a33-d7e193f0f691&token=ODVhZDc3MTMtMjAz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85ad7713-203c-413b-9a33-d7e193f0f691</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 06:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Wonder Electricals Ltd has clarified that the significant increase in the trading volume of its shares is not due to any specific reason related to the company. The company has made all disclosures as per SEBI regulations and other applicable laws. The increase is deemed to be market-driven and beyond the control of the company and its management.</p><ul><li>Wonder Electricals Ltd has clarified the reason for the significant increase in its share trading volume.</li><li>The company has complied with all disclosure requirements as per SEBI regulations and other applicable laws.</li><li>The increase in trading volume is not due to any specific reason related to the company.</li><li>The increase is considered to be market-driven and beyond the control of the company and its management.</li><li>Wonder Electricals Ltd reiterates its commitment to comply with all requirements under the Listing Regulations and other applicable laws.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f5fdeb49-dc7a-4c58-8f9d-c34a2f8d90aa.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Wonder Electricals Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STERTOOLS] Sterling Tools Partners with China’s MINIEYE for ADAS and Driver Monitoring Solutions in Indian Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=STERLING+TOOLS+LTD.-%24&title=Sterling+Tools+Partners+with+China%E2%80%99s+MINIEYE+for+ADAS+and+Driver+Monitoring+Solutions+in+Indian+Market&newsId=2a9ebbb8-5b39-433a-9aed-a3cbc7c9af57&token=MmE5ZWJiYjgtNWIz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a9ebbb8-5b39-433a-9aed-a3cbc7c9af57</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 06:26:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Partnership</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Sterling Tools Limited, a leading automotive components and technology manufacturer, has partnered with MINIEYE, a China-based intelligent driving and in-cabin solutions company, to advance the deployment of Advanced Driver Assistance Systems (ADAS) and Driver Monitoring Systems (DMS) for the Indian automotive market. The collaboration is focused on engineering and perception adaptation for Indian driving environments, road conditions, and use cases, aligned with India’s mandatory ADAS and Driver Drowsiness and Attention Warning Systems (DDAWS) regulations effective January 1, 2027.</p><ul><li>Sterling Tools to support application engineering and on-ground adaptation of MINIEYE’s ADAS and Driver Monitoring Systems for the Indian market</li><li>Collaboration focused on engineering and perception adaptation for Indian driving environments, road conditions, and use cases</li><li>Partnership covering commercial and passenger vehicle segments</li><li>MINIEYE brings global experience in intelligent driving and in-cabin technologies</li><li>Sterling Tools continues to strengthen its position as a technology-led automotive partner through sustained investments in advanced engineering and manufacturing capabilities</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b9d042d3-4b0b-4335-853f-2fe8dfedbe9f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: STERLING TOOLS LTD.-$ | Category: Partnership</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PACEDIGITK] Pace Digitek&apos;s Material Subsidiary, Lineage Power Private Limited, Receives Rs. 94,35 Crores Contract from BSNL</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Pace+Digitek+Ltd&title=Pace+Digitek%27s+Material+Subsidiary%2C+Lineage+Power+Private+Limited%2C+Receives+Rs.+94%2C35+Crores+Contract+from+BSNL&newsId=93d0f3ee-e46e-4d2e-bd5b-eab6fd01d146&token=OTNkMGYzZWUtZTQ2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93d0f3ee-e46e-4d2e-bd5b-eab6fd01d146</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 06:26:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Pace Digitek Ltd&apos;s material subsidiary, Lineage Power Private Limited, has received an Advance Purchase Order worth Rs. 94,35,13,250/- (including GST) from Bharat Sanchar Nigam Limited (BSNL) to supply 25,000 quantities of Basic 100 AH/48V Li-ion Battery Modules with BMS, 2500 quantities of IP55 racks to house eight 48V/100AH modules with associated accessories, and 5-year AMC after warranty period of 5 years for 25000 Nos of 100AH/48V Li-ion Battery modules with BMS along with accessories.</p><ul><li>Contract worth Rs. 94,35 crores awarded to Lineage Power Private Limited, a Material Subsidiary of Pace Digitek Ltd.</li><li>Order includes supply of 25,000 quantities of Basic 100 AH/48V Li-ion Battery Modules with BMS and associated accessories.</li><li>Also includes supply of 2500 quantities of IP55 racks to house eight 48V/100AH modules with associated accessories.</li><li>5-year AMC after warranty period of 5 years for 25000 Nos of 100AH/48V Li-ion Battery modules with BMS along with accessories.</li><li>Contract awarded by Bharat Sanchar Nigam Limited (BSNL), a domestic entity.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e78b5c1c-20aa-4611-98d2-77f494c84c08.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Pace Digitek Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SWITCHTE] Switching Technologies Gunther Ltd. Amends Memorandum of Association, Approves Share Purchase Agreement</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SWITCHING+TECHNOLOGIES+GUNTHER+LTD.&title=Switching+Technologies+Gunther+Ltd.+Amends+Memorandum+of+Association%2C+Approves+Share+Purchase+Agreement&newsId=b7db19bb-f360-4641-84d8-c2dd6e6988a9&token=YjdkYjE5YmItZjM2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7db19bb-f360-4641-84d8-c2dd6e6988a9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 06:22:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Switching Technologies Gunther Ltd. held a Board Meeting on 19th January, 2026, where they approved and took on record several key decisions. The main highlights include the approval and authorization for the execution of a Share Purchase Agreement and an amendment in the Main Object Clause of the Memorandum of Association of the company. These decisions were made in compliance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The Board also authorized the convening of an Extraordinary General Meeting of the Company.</p><ul><li>Approval and Authorisation for Execution of Share Purchase Agreement</li><li>Amendment in the Main Object Clause of the Memorandum of Association of the Company</li><li>Authorisation for convening an Extraordinary General Meeting of the Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1bdbb1cb-85d6-47a4-ad7e-b21c1a05da08.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SWITCHING TECHNOLOGIES GUNTHER LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ROSSARI] Rossari Biotech Announces Q3 FY26 Results: Revenues Up 13%, EBITDA Up 6%, PAT Up 3%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Rossari+Biotech+Ltd&title=Rossari+Biotech+Announces+Q3+FY26+Results%3A+Revenues+Up+13%25%2C+EBITDA+Up+6%25%2C+PAT+Up+3%25&newsId=b1a9cde2-87f2-4f0c-943a-fb7bdf311a2d&token=YjFhOWNkZTItODdm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b1a9cde2-87f2-4f0c-943a-fb7bdf311a2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 06:20:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Rossari Biotech Limited, a Specialty-Chemicals manufacturer, has announced its financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a 13% YoY growth in revenues, a 6% YoY growth in EBITDA, and a 3% YoY growth in PAT. The Home, Personal Care and Performance Chemicals (HPPC) segment recorded an 11% YoY growth, while the Textile Specialty Chemicals (TSC) segment grew by 18% YoY, and the Animal Health and Nutrition (AHN) segment grew by 39% YoY. The company&apos;s international operations also contributed to the growth. However, profitability was impacted by ongoing investments in capacity expansion, product development, and market-seeding initiatives. The company also announced its plan to set up greenfield specialty chemicals manufacturing facilities in the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia (KSA).</p><ul><li>Q3 FY26 revenues at Rs. 581.7 Cr, up 13% YoY</li><li>EBITDA at Rs. 68.9 Cr, up 6% YoY</li><li>PAT at Rs. 32.8 Cr, up 3% YoY</li><li>HPPC recorded a YoY growth of 11%</li><li>TSC delivered a growth of 18% YoY</li><li>AHN grew by 39% YoY</li><li>Plan to set up greenfield specialty chemicals manufacturing facilities in KSA</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/aeca808c-2c14-47a0-bebd-33409cfb8f47.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Rossari Biotech Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>