<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 05:00:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SHARDFI] Executive Chairman of Eco Hotels and Resorts Ltd, Vinod Kumar Tripathi, Acquires 0.21% Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHARAD+FIBRES+%26+YARN+PROCESSORS+LTD.&title=Executive+Chairman+of+Eco+Hotels+and+Resorts+Ltd%2C+Vinod+Kumar+Tripathi%2C+Acquires+0.21%25+Shares&newsId=e8c18fd0-cbf1-4bc5-88d6-449d142f672a&token=ZThjMThmZDAtY2Jm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e8c18fd0-cbf1-4bc5-88d6-449d142f672a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>According to a disclosure under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011, Vinod Kumar Tripathi, Executive Chairman and Whole-Time Director of Eco Hotels and Resorts Limited, has purchased 1,34,799 Equity Shares of the company on February 09, 2026. This acquisition represents 0.21% of the total equity shares and voting rights of the company. The shares were acquired from the open market. Before the acquisition, Tripathi held 2362538 fully paid Equity Shares and 333098 partly paid Rights Issue Equity Shares. After the acquisition, his total holding increased to 2497337 fully paid Equity Shares and 333098 partly paid Rights Issue Equity Shares, representing 4.33% of the total equity shares and voting rights.</p><ul><li>Vinod Kumar Tripathi, Executive Chairman and Whole-Time Director of Eco Hotels and Resorts Limited, acquired 1,34,799 Equity Shares of the company.</li><li>The acquisition represents 0.21% of the total equity shares and voting rights of the company.</li><li>The shares were acquired from the open market.</li><li>Before the acquisition, Tripathi held 2362538 fully paid Equity Shares and 333098 partly paid Rights Issue Equity Shares.</li><li>After the acquisition, Tripathi&apos;s total holding increased to 2497337 fully paid Equity Shares and 333098 partly paid Rights Issue Equity Shares, representing 4.33% of the total equity shares and voting rights.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8CC13C15_D4C8_4C55_AF43_31FDE80FA826_102424.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHARAD FIBRES & YARN PROCESSORS LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TRU] TruCap Finance: Open Offer by Marwadi Chandarana Intermediaries Brokers Private Limited Terminated, SEBI Rejects Withdrawal Request</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TruCap+Finance+Ltd&title=TruCap+Finance%3A+Open+Offer+by+Marwadi+Chandarana+Intermediaries+Brokers+Private+Limited+Terminated%2C+SEBI+Rejects+Withdrawal+Request&newsId=21ae8c59-43c2-4c3b-bd91-bbaff8b3eac7&token=MjFhZThjNTktNDNj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21ae8c59-43c2-4c3b-bd91-bbaff8b3eac7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:52:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sundae Capital Advisors Pvt Ltd, the Manager to the Offer, has informed BSE about the termination of a Share Purchase Agreement (SPA) and a Securities Subscription Agreement (SSA) by Marwadi Chandarana Intermediaries Brokers Private Limited (Acquirer). The SPA was for the acquisition of 3,68,00,220 equity shares of the Target Company from the promoter and promoter group, and the SSA was for the subscription of 11,56,80,000 equity shares and 9,37,00,000 convertible warrants of the Target Company by the Acquirer. The Acquirer had requested SEBI to allow withdrawal of the Offer, but SEBI did not accede to the request. The Observations were issued by SEBI on the Draft Letter of Offer dated January 30, 2026. The Acquirer has filed an appeal with the Hon’ble Securities Appellate Tribunal (Hon’ble SAT), with a hearing fixed on February 11, 2026. No stay has been granted on the Offer proceedings as of the date of this intimation. If a stay is granted or there are any changes in the Offer process, schedule, or obligations, appropriate disclosures will be made in accordance with applicable law.</p><ul><li>Open Offer terminated by Marwadi Chandarana Intermediaries Brokers Private Limited</li><li>SEBI rejects Acquirer&apos;s request to withdraw the Offer</li><li>Acquirer files appeal with Hon’ble Securities Appellate Tribunal</li><li>No stay granted on the Offer proceedings as of the date of this intimation</li><li>Appropriate disclosures will be made in accordance with applicable law if a stay is granted or there are any changes in the Offer process, schedule, or obligations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6AE02761-C673-41F7-AE31-EAE808231969-102034.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TruCap Finance Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JUSTO] Promoter Puspamitra Das Acquires 16,000 Equity Shares of Justo Realfintech Ltd Through Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Justo+Realfintech+Ltd&title=Promoter+Puspamitra+Das+Acquires+16%2C000+Equity+Shares+of+Justo+Realfintech+Ltd+Through+Open+Market&newsId=450429d8-e7d8-4a20-9989-c52c9eb5c38e&token=NDUwNDI5ZDgtZTdk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">450429d8-e7d8-4a20-9989-c52c9eb5c38e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Puspamitra Das, a promoter of Justo Realfintech Ltd, has acquired 16,000 equity shares of the company through the open market. This acquisition represents 0.085% of the total diluted share and voting capital of the company. The acquisition was made on 9th February 2026. The total share and voting capital of the company remains unchanged at INR 18,79,81,420 consisting of 1,87,98,142 Equity Shares of Rs. 10 each.</p><ul><li>Puspamitra Das, a promoter of Justo Realfintech Ltd, has acquired 16,000 equity shares of the company.</li><li>The acquisition represents 0.085% of the total diluted share and voting capital of the company.</li><li>The acquisition was made on 9th February 2026.</li><li>The total share and voting capital of the company remains unchanged at INR 18,79,81,420 consisting of 1,87,98,142 Equity Shares of Rs. 10 each.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/B09C6EA0_F58A_4354_9584_D01A3E8814B6_102105.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Justo Realfintech Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AJANTPHARM] Ajanta Pharma Denies Rumors of Diversification into Restaurant Business</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AJANTA+PHARMA+LTD.&title=Ajanta+Pharma+Denies+Rumors+of+Diversification+into+Restaurant+Business&newsId=a0d0d3d9-a6bf-4ab0-9dd2-42d0a8c81884&token=YTBkMGQzZDktYTZi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0d0d3d9-a6bf-4ab0-9dd2-42d0a8c81884</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Clarification</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ajanta Pharma Ltd has clarified a news article published in The Economic Times dated February 10, 2026, and ET Online, stating that a section of the promoter group of Ajanta is independently acquiring Restaurant Brands Asia. Ajanta Pharma Limited and its Management are not parties to, and are in no manner involved in, any transaction referred to in the said news article. The Company has denied the rumors and speculation circulating in this regard.</p><ul><li>Ajanta Pharma denies rumors of diversification into the restaurant business</li><li>A section of Ajanta&apos;s promoter group is independently acquiring Restaurant Brands Asia</li><li>Ajanta Pharma and its Management are not involved in the acquisition</li><li>The news article&apos;s reference to Ajanta Pharma is factually incorrect</li><li>The Company has denied circulating rumors and speculation</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ab55a024-c2bd-429c-8a63-7626344aa3d5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AJANTA PHARMA LTD. | Category: Clarification</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SEPC] SEPC Limited to Execute ~Rs. 314 Crore Smart Prepaid Metering Project in Punjab under RDSS</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SEPC+Ltd&title=SEPC+Limited+to+Execute+~Rs.+314+Crore+Smart+Prepaid+Metering+Project+in+Punjab+under+RDSS&newsId=4c31b18f-41b8-46e4-937e-3fe3d24f4c31&token=NGMzMWIxOGYtNDFi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4c31b18f-41b8-46e4-937e-3fe3d24f4c31</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>SEPC Limited, one of India’s leading Engineering, Procurement and Construction (EPC) companies, has received a Letter of Intent (LOI) from Telecommunications Consultants India Limited (TCIL), a Government of India enterprise, for the implementation of a Smart Prepaid Metering project in Punjab (Central Zone) under the Revamped Distribution Sector Scheme (RDSS). The project, valued at approximately Rs. 314 crore, will be executed on a Design, Build, Finance, Own, Operate and Transfer (DBFOOT) basis in consortium with Adya Smart Metering Private Limited. The project scope includes the design, deployment, integration, commissioning, and long-term operation and maintenance of advanced metering infrastructure for Punjab State Power Corporation Limited (PSPCL). This order strengthens SEPC’s order momentum and expands its presence in power distribution and metering infrastructure, providing long-term revenue visibility and aligning with the company&apos;s strategy of building annuity-linked revenue streams.</p><ul><li>SEPC Limited received a Letter of Intent (LOI) from TCIL for a Smart Prepaid Metering project in Punjab under RDSS.</li><li>The project is valued at approximately Rs. 314 crore and will be executed on a DBFOOT basis with Adya Smart Metering Private Limited.</li><li>The project scope includes design, deployment, integration, commissioning, and long-term operation and maintenance of advanced metering infrastructure for PSPCL.</li><li>This order strengthens SEPC’s order momentum and expands its presence in power distribution and metering infrastructure.</li><li>The DBFOOT structure aligns with SEPC&apos;s strategy of building long-term, annuity-linked revenue streams.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3071583a-244e-4551-86c1-21c1414d2b3e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SEPC Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GPIL] Godawari Power and Ispat Ltd Receives Consent to Operate Expanded Ari Dongri Iron Ore Mines</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GODAWARI+POWER+%26+ISPAT+LTD.&title=Godawari+Power+and+Ispat+Ltd+Receives+Consent+to+Operate+Expanded+Ari+Dongri+Iron+Ore+Mines&newsId=0dc54b62-65c1-4d7a-8090-e96fe90834d4&token=MGRjNTRiNjItNjVj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0dc54b62-65c1-4d7a-8090-e96fe90834d4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:14:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Godawari Power and Ispat Ltd has announced the receipt of consent to operate the Ari Dongri Iron Ore Mines at an expanded capacity. The company received the consent from the Chhattisgarh Environment Conservation Board on 09.02.2026, following the receipt of Environmental Clearance from the Ministry of Environment, Forest and Climate Change on 31.01.2026. The expansion increases the capacity from 2.35 MTPA to 6 MTPA and the mining lease area from 138.96 Ha to 213.01 Ha. The mining operations at the enhanced capacity have commenced from 10.02.2026.</p><ul><li>Godawari Power and Ispat Ltd receives consent to operate expanded Ari Dongri Iron Ore Mines</li><li>Consent received from Chhattisgarh Environment Conservation Board on 09.02.2026</li><li>Environmental Clearance obtained on 31.01.2026 from Ministry of Environment, Forest and Climate Change</li><li>Capacity increased from 2.35 MTPA to 6 MTPA</li><li>Mining lease area increased from 138.96 Ha to 213.01 Ha</li><li>Mining operations at enhanced capacity commence from 10.02.2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d168f6bd-9a4c-4ed6-b5c7-60aa0bb495a3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GODAWARI POWER & ISPAT LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NUVAMA] Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd. to Present at Nuvama India Conference 2026: Financialization of Household Savings a Key Focus</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Nuvama+Wealth+Management+Ltd&title=Nuvama+Wealth+Management+Ltd.+to+Present+at+Nuvama+India+Conference+2026%3A+Financialization+of+Household+Savings+a+Key+Focus&newsId=67a73fa5-c72f-4ff6-b7fd-61a07bc7b8fe&token=NjdhNzNmYTUtYzcy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67a73fa5-c72f-4ff6-b7fd-61a07bc7b8fe</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 04:12:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd. will participate in the Nuvama India Conference 2026 on February 10, 2026, at the Grand Hyatt, Mumbai. The presentation will be delivered by Mr. Ashish Kehair, MD and CEO, Nuvama Group. The presentation will focus on the evolution of the wealth management ecosystem, with a particular emphasis on the financialization of household savings. This shift from physical to financial to investment assets has been driven by growing affluence and a rising share of financial assets in household balance sheets. Investment assets have grown by 2.5x in the last two years, with consistent quarter-over-quarter growth for the last 12 quarters. Monthly SIP flows have also increased significantly, now at ~30K, contributing 15% to the FY25 flows.</p><ul><li>Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd. to present at Nuvama India Conference 2026</li><li>Presentation to focus on the evolution of the wealth management ecosystem</li><li>Emphasis on the financialization of household savings</li><li>Investment assets have grown by 2.5x in the last two years</li><li>Significant increase in monthly SIP flows</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/185f4835-7819-4d78-81b1-8c8ec91923f5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Nuvama Wealth Management Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JSWSTEEL] JSW Steel Reports Consolidated Crude Steel Production of 24.75 Lakh Tonnes for January 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JSW+STEEL+LTD.&title=JSW+Steel+Reports+Consolidated+Crude+Steel+Production+of+24.75+Lakh+Tonnes+for+January+2026&newsId=d4eb3b74-8a33-4818-9b63-40587de036b4&token=ZDRlYjNiNzQtOGEz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4eb3b74-8a33-4818-9b63-40587de036b4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 03:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>JSW Steel, a leading integrated steel company, reported consolidated Crude Steel production for January 2026 at 24.75 Lakh tonnes. The Crude Steel production at Indian operations level was marginally higher YoY. However, the capacity utilisation at Indian operations was affected due to the shutdown of Blast Furnace 3 (BF3) at Vijayanagar for upgradation. Production at USA Ohio operations was also lower due to scheduled outage for caster upgrades. JSW Steel&apos;s next phase of growth will take consolidated capacity to 48.9 MTPA over the next four years.</p><ul><li>JSW Steel reported consolidated Crude Steel production of 24.75 Lakh tonnes for January 2026</li><li>Indian operations&apos; production was marginally higher YoY</li><li>BF3 at Vijayanagar is under shutdown for upgradation, affecting capacity utilisation</li><li>Production at USA Ohio operations was lower due to scheduled outage for caster upgrades</li><li>JSW Steel&apos;s next phase of growth will take consolidated capacity to 48.9 MTPA over the next four years</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/deb17990-69dd-4e17-a279-b3d9cfe9a905.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JSW STEEL LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MIC] MIC Electronics Secures Rs. 1.45 Crore Order from Firozpur Division of Indian Railways</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MIC+ELECTRONICS+LTD.&title=MIC+Electronics+Secures+Rs.+1.45+Crore+Order+from+Firozpur+Division+of+Indian+Railways&newsId=05a07019-e273-42f7-bc43-8b3d62b23c89&token=MDVhMDcwMTktZTI3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05a07019-e273-42f7-bc43-8b3d62b23c89</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 03:43:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>MIC Electronics Ltd has received a Letter of Acceptance from the Firozpur division of Indian Railways for Provision of Coach Guidance and PA system at SVDK and SINA stations over Jammu Division. The order amount is Rs. 1,45,75,627.69. The order will be executed within 3 months and the significant terms and conditions will be finalized at the time of execution of the agreement.</p><ul><li>MIC Electronics has secured an order from the Firozpur division of Indian Railways.</li><li>The order is for Provision of Coach Guidance and PA system at SVDK and SINA stations over Jammu Division.</li><li>The order amount is Rs. 1,45,75,627.69.</li><li>The order will be executed within 3 months.</li><li>The significant terms and conditions will be finalized at the time of execution of the agreement.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/17fb7f60-0183-42f1-a6ad-cd8ef642bcc1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MIC ELECTRONICS LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SATIN] Satin Finserv Limited Raises Rs. 50 Crores in NCDs, Signaling Strong Market Confidence</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Satin+Creditcare+Network+Ltd&title=Satin+Finserv+Limited+Raises+Rs.+50+Crores+in+NCDs%2C+Signaling+Strong+Market+Confidence&newsId=22c2fa24-c66e-4afa-b792-615d71204b63&token=MjJjMmZhMjQtYzY2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">22c2fa24-c66e-4afa-b792-615d71204b63</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 03:37:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Satin Finserv Limited (SFL), a wholly owned subsidiary of Satin Creditcare Network Limited, has successfully raised Rs. 50 crores in Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs) with a unique per-debenture face value of Rs. 10,000. This follows shareholder approval at the EGM for enhancing the NCD issuance limit to an aggregate outstanding of Rs. 600 crores. In the last 3 months, SFL has mobilized approximately Rs. 260 crores, marking its strongest fundraising performance. This momentum in fundraising reaffirms the market&apos;s confidence in SFL’s financial strength, strategy, and forward-looking growth plans. The funds will enhance SFL&apos;s visibility in the retail debt market, diversify its lender base and borrowing instruments, and build a resilient funding ecosystem. SFL maintains a solid foundation for sustained expansion and stability with sufficient liquidity and a strong Capital Adequacy Ratio of 36.1% as on December 2025. The company is advancing its growth strategy by expanding its product range to tap India&apos;s thriving MSME financing market, placing strategic emphasis on sustainability financing solutions that support the low-carbon economy transition.</p><ul><li>SFL raises Rs. 50 crores in NCDs with a unique per-debenture face value of Rs. 10,000</li><li>Shareholder approval for enhancing the NCD issuance limit to Rs. 600 crores</li><li>Mobilization of approximately Rs. 260 crores in the last 3 months</li><li>Strong market confidence in SFL’s financial strength, strategy, and growth plans</li><li>Expansion of product range to tap India&apos;s thriving MSME financing market</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1ae840bd-83d1-47a6-9485-17469458da84.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Satin Creditcare Network Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>