<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 06:28:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[HINDBIO] Hindustan Bio Sciences Ltd Opens Special Window for Re-lodgment of Transfer Requests of Physical Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HINDUSTAN+BIO+SCIENCES+LTD.&title=Hindustan+Bio+Sciences+Ltd+Opens+Special+Window+for+Re-lodgment+of+Transfer+Requests+of+Physical+Shares&newsId=75f7088b-f57a-407d-94d2-7a1e982d201a&token=NzVmNzA4OGItZjU3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75f7088b-f57a-407d-94d2-7a1e982d201a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 06:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hindustan Bio Sciences Ltd has announced a special window for the re-lodgment of transfer requests of physical shares. This move is in accordance with the SEBI Circular dated July 2, 2025. The company has provided a report from the RTA and the details of the requests received, processed, approved, and rejected during the month. This information will also be available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Hindustan Bio Sciences Ltd opens special window for re-lodgment of transfer requests of physical shares</li><li>Move in accordance with SEBI Circular dated July 2, 2025</li><li>Provided report from the RTA</li><li>Details of requests received, processed, approved, and rejected during the month</li><li>Information available on the company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fcf27eb4-6034-4fe8-a725-6ac4e7009a3b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HINDUSTAN BIO SCIENCES LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RETAGGIO] Retaggio Industries Ltd. Approves Allotment of Convertible Equity Warrants Worth Rs. 3,91,99,992/-</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Retaggio+Industries+Ltd&title=Retaggio+Industries+Ltd.+Approves+Allotment+of+Convertible+Equity+Warrants+Worth+Rs.+3%2C91%2C99%2C992%2F-&newsId=3baa5961-c864-4a93-8dbf-262e5c086933&token=M2JhYTU5NjEtYzg2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3baa5961-c864-4a93-8dbf-262e5c086933</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 06:25:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Retaggio Industries Ltd. has approved the allotment of 15,07,692 Convertible Equity Warrants at an issue price of Rs. 26/- per warrant. The warrants are convertible into Equity Shares, amounting to Rs. 3,91,99,992/-. The Company has received 25% of the issue price, i.e. Rs. 6.50/- per warrant, amounting to Rs. 97,99,998/-. The Equity Shares to be allotted on exercise of the Warrants shall rank pari passu with the existing Equity Shares of the Company in all respects.</p><ul><li>Retaggio Industries Ltd. approved the allotment of 15,07,692 Convertible Equity Warrants.</li><li>The warrants are convertible into Equity Shares, amounting to Rs. 3,91,99,992/-.</li><li>The Company has received 25% of the issue price, i.e. Rs. 6.50/- per warrant, amounting to Rs. 97,99,998/-.</li><li>The Equity Shares to be allotted on exercise of the Warrants shall rank pari passu with the existing Equity Shares of the Company in all respects.</li><li>The warrants can be converted into equity shares within a period of 18 months from the date of allotment.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ab4911c0-20c3-4dd8-a758-5f43414634ec.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Retaggio Industries Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZSANMCOM] Trading Holiday Extends Open Offer Closing Date for Sanmitra Commercial Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SANMITRA+COMMERCIAL+LTD.&title=Trading+Holiday+Extends+Open+Offer+Closing+Date+for+Sanmitra+Commercial+Ltd&newsId=c85d7ffc-3a74-4cdc-be70-5a273cd388cf&token=Yzg1ZDdmZmMtM2E3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c85d7ffc-3a74-4cdc-be70-5a273cd388cf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 06:19:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Open Offer Extension</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Navigant Corporate Advisors Ltd, on behalf of Ankit Jalan and Anuj Jalan, along with Manju Jalan, Radhika Jalan, Prachi Jalan, Ritu Jalan, Divyanshi Jalan and Daivik Jalan, have issued a corrigendum to the Letter of Offer for Sanmitra Commercial Ltd. The corrigendum was published on 13th January 2026 in the Financial Express - English Daily (all editions); Jansatta - Hindi Daily (all editions) and Pratahkaal - Marathi Daily (Mumbai edition). The corrigendum is in compliance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011, as amended. Due to a Trading Holiday declared on January 15, 2026, the tendering period for the Open Offer has been extended, and the Open Offer shall now close on January 20, 2026, instead of the earlier scheduled closing date of January 19, 2026.</p><ul><li>Navigant Corporate Advisors Ltd issues corrigendum to the Letter of Offer for Sanmitra Commercial Ltd</li><li>Corrigendum published on 13th January 2026 in English, Hindi, and Marathi dailies</li><li>Trading Holiday declared on January 15, 2026, leading to the extension of the Open Offer</li><li>Open Offer now closes on January 20, 2026, instead of January 19, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/61512E9B-2BC4-4607-90EE-BE396C030965-114141.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SANMITRA COMMERCIAL LTD. | Category: Open Offer Extension</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EASEMYTRIP] EaseMyTrip Announces &apos;Republic Day Travel Sale&apos; with Big Savings Deals on Flights, Hotels, Buses, Cabs, and Holiday Packages</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Easy+Trip+Planners+Ltd&title=EaseMyTrip+Announces+%27Republic+Day+Travel+Sale%27+with+Big+Savings+Deals+on+Flights%2C+Hotels%2C+Buses%2C+Cabs%2C+and+Holiday+Packages&newsId=6cab9dd2-2764-4a29-8750-7632ce385007&token=NmNhYjlkZDItMjc2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6cab9dd2-2764-4a29-8750-7632ce385007</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 06:13:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>EaseMyTrip, one of India’s leading online travel platforms, has announced the launch of its ‘Republic Day Travel Sale’, offering travellers attractive deals to plan their upcoming journeys during the Republic Day period and the early months of the year. The campaign, live from 13th to 17th January 2026, is designed to encourage travel across the country and beyond, combining value-driven pricing with seamless booking experiences. The sale brings together an extensive network of airline partners and hospitality partners, offering discounts on flights, hotels, buses, cabs, and holiday packages. EaseMyTrip has curated special holiday packages covering popular domestic and international destinations.</p><ul><li>EaseMyTrip announces &apos;Republic Day Travel Sale&apos; from 13th to 17th January 2026</li><li>Offering UP TO INR 10,000 OFF on flights, hotels, and holiday packages</li><li>UP TO INR 250 OFF on buses and UP TO INR 500 OFF on cabs</li><li>Special holiday packages for domestic and international destinations</li><li>Partnerships with various airlines and hospitality providers</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/be66323f-ad48-451c-b72b-2177ec8526f6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Easy Trip Planners Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IRFC] IRFC Faces Fine Over Board Composition and Committee Constitution Non-Compliance; Seeks Fine Waiver and Expedited Appointment of Independent Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Indian+Railway+Finance+Corporation+Ltd&title=IRFC+Faces+Fine+Over+Board+Composition+and+Committee+Constitution+Non-Compliance%3B+Seeks+Fine+Waiver+and+Expedited+Appointment+of+Independent+Directors&newsId=ba92c032-1593-4b45-9241-fd95ef9f8a3f&token=YmE5MmMwMzItMTU5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba92c032-1593-4b45-9241-fd95ef9f8a3f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 06:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In its meeting held on 18th December, 2025, the Indian Railway Finance Corporation Ltd (IRFC) Board discussed and noted the non-compliance with the requirements pertaining to the composition of the Board and constitution of committees namely Audit and Nomination and Remuneration for the quarter ended 30th September 2025. The Exchanges imposed a fine on the Company for the non-compliance, which the IRFC Board desires to be waived. The Company has requested the appointing authority, the Ministry of Railways (MoR), to expedite the appointment of requisite number of Independent Directors, including one Women Independent Director, on the IRFC Board. The IRFC, being a Government Company, has no control over the appointment of Directors on its Board. The Board has previously faced similar non-compliance issues, and the NSE &amp; BSE had waived fines imposed on the Company during the period of March, 2021 to December, 2021.</p><ul><li>IRFC Board discussed non-compliance with Board composition and committee constitution requirements</li><li>Exchanges imposed a fine on the Company for non-compliance</li><li>IRFC Board seeks waiver of the fine imposed by the Exchanges</li><li>Company requests Ministry of Railways to expedite Independent Director appointments</li><li>IRFC has no control over the appointment of Directors on its Board</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c6f03c2c-5f99-4641-a47f-7fd14ba8a0c7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Indian Railway Finance Corporation Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NAVNETEDUL] Navneet Education Ltd. Announces Composite Scheme of Arrangement for Demerging Publishing Business of Indiannica Learning Private Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Navneet+Education+Limited&title=Navneet+Education+Ltd.+Announces+Composite+Scheme+of+Arrangement+for+Demerging+Publishing+Business+of+Indiannica+Learning+Private+Limited&newsId=86a94a0f-3d1f-4c7a-a3cc-e2e61f5a7e89&token=ODZhOTRhMGYtM2Qx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86a94a0f-3d1f-4c7a-a3cc-e2e61f5a7e89</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 06:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Navneet Education Ltd. has submitted a Composite Scheme of Arrangement under Section 230 to 232 and Section 66 and other applicable provisions of the Companies, Act, 2013. The scheme proposes to demerge the &apos;Publishing Business&apos; of Indiannica Learning Private Limited into Navneet Education Limited and reduce the equity share capital, preference share capital and securities premium of Indiannica Learning Private Limited. The scheme has been approved by the Board of Directors of both companies. Navneet Education Limited is primarily engaged in publishing, marketing, and distribution of educational books and related printed material, including but not limited to textbooks, workbooks and reference books for CBSE and ICSE curriculum. Indiannica Learning Private Limited is primarily engaged in the same business along with digital products and trading. The rationale behind this scheme is to ensure a seamless blend of traditional print and progressive digital platforms and a simplified group business structure.</p><ul><li>Navneet Education Ltd. announces Composite Scheme of Arrangement</li><li>Proposal to demerge Publishing Business of Indiannica Learning Private Limited into Navneet Education Limited</li><li>Reduction of equity share capital, preference share capital and securities premium of Indiannica Learning Private Limited</li><li>Consolidation of publishing businesses of both companies</li><li>Seamless integration of content creation and technological development teams</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/946ff5a9-208e-4fac-83ee-d5cb4d35be09.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Navneet Education Limited | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RATEGAIN] RateGain&apos;s Sojern Named Best Digital Marketing Agency in 2026 HotelTechAwards</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RateGain+Travel+Technologies+Ltd&title=RateGain%27s+Sojern+Named+Best+Digital+Marketing+Agency+in+2026+HotelTechAwards&newsId=ab899401-37d9-4b38-ab9f-7f87b3d2b977&token=YWI4OTk0MDEtMzdk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab899401-37d9-4b38-ab9f-7f87b3d2b977</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 06:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Award</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>RateGain Travel Technologies Limited announced that Sojern, its recently acquired AI-powered marketing platform built for hospitality, has been named Best Digital Marketing Agency in the 2026 HotelTechAwards. The recognition is based on verified customer reviews and proprietary data signals, including market presence, integration capabilities, organizational health, and customer support quality. Sojern&apos;s Al-powered platform helps hospitality marketers cost-effectively drive direct demand, engage guests in real-time, and maximize revenue opportunities across the entire guest journey.</p><ul><li>Sojern named Best Digital Marketing Agency in 2026 HotelTechAwards</li><li>Recognition based on verified customer reviews and proprietary data signals</li><li>Sojern&apos;s Al-powered platform helps hospitality marketers drive direct demand and maximize revenue</li><li>RateGain and Sojern integrating AI-powered capabilities and global scale to accelerate innovation across the travel ecosystem</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6889379b-bb54-452c-a34e-0092e862c4b1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RateGain Travel Technologies Ltd | Category: Award</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ABINFRA] A B Infrabuild Ltd Secures Rs. 55 Crore Contract for Construction of Road Over Bridge</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=A+B+Infrabuild+Ltd&title=A+B+Infrabuild+Ltd+Secures+Rs.+55+Crore+Contract+for+Construction+of+Road+Over+Bridge&newsId=1d5c53c2-82a0-40f7-8c5c-50dc48455586&token=MWQ1YzUzYzItODJh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d5c53c2-82a0-40f7-8c5c-50dc48455586</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 05:56:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>A B Infrabuild Ltd has been awarded a new project for the construction of a Road Over Bridge (ROB) with a proposed span of 1x 36 mtr. Composite girder + 2x24 mtr. Composite girder + 4x18.75 mtr. RCCT-Beam Girder at Rly. Km. 641/19-21 in lieu of LC. No. 341 at KM 641/17-19 in between JHADUPUDI - SOMPETA Railway station main line under Khurda Road Division. The contract, worth Rs. 55,26,31,365.74, was awarded by East Coast Railways, Indian Railways, and has a time period of 24 months.</p><ul><li>A B Infrabuild Ltd has been awarded a new project for the construction of a Road Over Bridge (ROB)</li><li>The project is worth Rs. 55,26,31,365.74</li><li>The project has a time period of 24 months</li><li>The project was awarded by East Coast Railways, Indian Railways</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/30f87681-e1a6-471c-b622-c4ff6121bed4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: A B Infrabuild Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GRANULES] Granules India Ltd. Announces Corrigendum to EGM Notice with Changes to Preferential Issue of Convertible Warrants and Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GRANULES+INDIA+LTD.-%24&title=Granules+India+Ltd.+Announces+Corrigendum+to+EGM+Notice+with+Changes+to+Preferential+Issue+of+Convertible+Warrants+and+Equity+Shares&newsId=459abe70-c599-4289-95dc-b52948d5d528&token=NDU5YWJlNzAtYzU5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">459abe70-c599-4289-95dc-b52948d5d528</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 05:53:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Granules India Ltd. has issued a corrigendum to the notice of its Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) scheduled for January 22, 2026. The corrigendum includes changes to the notice regarding the proposed preferential issue of convertible warrants and equity shares. The changes are in response to observations from the National Stock Exchange of India Limited (NSE) and BSE Limited (BSE), and are in accordance with the SEBI (Issue of Capital and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2018, the Companies Act, 2013, and relevant MCA circulars. The corrigendum includes changes to the list of proposed allottees, the objects of the preferential issue, and the monitoring agency.</p><ul><li>Changes to the list of proposed allottees for the preferential issue of convertible warrants and equity shares</li><li>Modifications to the objects of the preferential issue</li><li>Appointment of M/s. India Ratings &amp; Research Private Limited as the monitoring agency to monitor the use of proceeds on preferential issue</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ed27f1c5-2f3f-4ef9-98ae-44ed1e827744.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GRANULES INDIA LTD.-$ | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BRGIL] B.R.Goyal Infrastructure Ltd Secures Rs. 86 Crore User Fee Collection Contract from NHAI</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=B.R.Goyal+Infrastructure+Ltd&title=B.R.Goyal+Infrastructure+Ltd+Secures+Rs.+86+Crore+User+Fee+Collection+Contract+from+NHAI&newsId=200d5b72-42ba-469c-b228-cbdb5c483d6b&token=MjAwZDViNzItNDJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">200d5b72-42ba-469c-b228-cbdb5c483d6b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 05:45:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>B.R.Goyal Infrastructure Limited (the Company) has received a work order for the engagement of user fee collection agency on the basis of competitive bidding through e-tender for Simliya Fee Plaza at km 409.680 and Fatehpur Fee Plaza at km 461 .290 for Kota — Baran Section from km 388.263 to km 492.322 of NH-76 in the State of Rajasthan. The accepted value of the said work order is Rs. 86,70,77,575/- (Rupees Eighty-Six Crore Seventy Lakh Seventy-Seven Thousand Five Hundred and Seventy-Five Only).</p><ul><li>B.R.Goyal Infrastructure Ltd has been awarded a user fee collection contract by NHAI.</li><li>The contract is for Simliya Fee Plaza at km 409.680 and Fatehpur Fee Plaza at km 461 .290.</li><li>The contract is for the Kota — Baran Section from km 388.263 to km 492.322 of NH-76 in the State of Rajasthan.</li><li>The accepted value of the contract is Rs. 86,70,77,575/- (Rupees Eighty-Six Crore Seventy Lakh Seventy-Seven Thousand Five Hundred and Seventy-Five Only).</li><li>The contract period is one year.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fc7a12d6-8118-4342-ad6c-3af0a1331a85.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: B.R.Goyal Infrastructure Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>