<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 01:30:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[GODREJPROP] Godrej Properties Acquires 8.5-Acre Land Parcel in Pune&apos;s Mahalunge Micro-Market with Estimated Revenue Potential of INR 2,000 Crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Godrej+Properties+Ltd&title=Godrej+Properties+Acquires+8.5-Acre+Land+Parcel+in+Pune%27s+Mahalunge+Micro-Market+with+Estimated+Revenue+Potential+of+INR+2%2C000+Crore&newsId=1b1aef85-3870-412a-8888-01ae92a15048&token=MWIxYWVmODUtMzg3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b1aef85-3870-412a-8888-01ae92a15048</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 00:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Godrej Properties Ltd. (GPL) has acquired an 8.5-acre land parcel in Mahalunge, Pune, through outright purchase. The proposed development will primarily comprise group housing and is expected to offer a developable potential of approximately 2.1 million square feet, with an estimated revenue potential of INR 2,000 crore. The land is strategically located in the Mahalunge-Maan-Nande belt, part of the Mahalunge - Hinjewadi micro-market, and benefits from proximity to the upcoming Pune Inner Ring Road and the city&apos;s fast-growing Hinjewadi—Balewadi corridor. The location offers convenient access to major IT and BFSI hubs in Pune and benefits from a well-developed social infrastructure.</p><ul><li>Godrej Properties acquires 8.5-acre land parcel in Mahalunge, Pune</li><li>Proposed development to offer approximately 2.1 million square feet of developable potential</li><li>Estimated revenue potential of INR 2,000 crore</li><li>Strategically located with proximity to the upcoming Pune Inner Ring Road and Hinjewadi—Balewadi corridor</li><li>Well-developed social infrastructure with convenient access to major IT and BFSI hubs in Pune</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/45fb0400-30a2-4193-a1e8-bdf3775cc948.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Godrej Properties Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MODIPON] Modipon Ltd Reports Zero Investor Complaints for Q4 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MODIPON+LTD.&title=Modipon+Ltd+Reports+Zero+Investor+Complaints+for+Q4+2025&newsId=56a35f72-c6ff-4435-bb16-b88358520cec&token=NTZhMzVmNzItYzZm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56a35f72-c6ff-4435-bb16-b88358520cec</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 00:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Modipon Ltd, as per the enclosed document, has reported zero investor complaints for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The report, in accordance with SEBI regulations, states that there were no pending complaints at the beginning of the quarter, no new complaints received during the quarter, and no complaints left unresolved at the end of the quarter. This report includes various categories of complaints such as non-receipt of refund allotment, non-receipt of dividend on shares, and non-receipt of interest on debentures, among others. All such complaints were reported as &apos;disposed of&apos; during the quarter.</p><ul><li>Modipon Ltd reported zero investor complaints for Q4 2025</li><li>No pending complaints at the beginning of the quarter</li><li>No new complaints received during the quarter</li><li>No complaints left unresolved at the end of the quarter</li><li>All categories of complaints reported as &apos;disposed of&apos; during the quarter</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0a7c5085-e6d0-4016-a4e8-1dcf2a8aba03.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MODIPON LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ACMESOLAR] ACME Solar Subsidiary Signs 250 MW Power Purchase Agreement with NHPC Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ACME+Solar+Holdings+Ltd&title=ACME+Solar+Subsidiary+Signs+250+MW+Power+Purchase+Agreement+with+NHPC+Limited&newsId=9ad30e2c-fdb3-4844-a120-4928af3e3128&token=OWFkMzBlMmMtZmRi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ad30e2c-fdb3-4844-a120-4928af3e3128</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:44:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>ACME Urja One Private Limited, a wholly owned subsidiary of ACME Solar Holdings Ltd, has executed a Power Purchase Agreement (PPA) with NHPC Limited to set up a 250 MW FDRE Project. The project has a scheduled commercial operation date of 30th June 2027 and a project tenure of 25 years from the date of signing of the PPA. The tariff for the project is set at Rs. 4.33 per unit.</p><ul><li>ACME Urja One Private Limited has signed a PPA with NHPC Limited for a 250 MW FDRE project</li><li>The project has a scheduled commercial operation date of 30th June 2027</li><li>The project tenure is 25 years from the date of signing of the PPA</li><li>The tariff for the project is set at Rs. 4.33 per unit</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/29201877-3ee9-4734-b989-a7ec86f46768.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ACME Solar Holdings Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KOTAKBANK] Kotak Mahindra Bank Allots 1,33,400 Equity Shares After Judicial Clearance</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KOTAK+MAHINDRA+BANK+LTD.&title=Kotak+Mahindra+Bank+Allots+1%2C33%2C400+Equity+Shares+After+Judicial+Clearance&newsId=35481a68-ecec-453f-8fff-c898feafb287&token=MzU0ODFhNjgtZWNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">35481a68-ecec-453f-8fff-c898feafb287</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kotak Mahindra Bank Ltd has allotted 1,33,400 equity shares of Re. 1/- each to eligible equity shareholders. This allotment is in respect of the rights shares and subsequent corporate benefits which had been kept in abeyance, pending judicial clearance. The allotment has been made in line with the order passed by the competent authority.</p><ul><li>Kotak Mahindra Bank allots 1,33,400 equity shares</li><li>Allotment made in respect of rights shares and subsequent corporate benefits</li><li>Allotment made after judicial clearance</li><li>Allotment in line with the order passed by the competent authority</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/98523991-b298-420e-b6b9-ae16e37992ce.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KOTAK MAHINDRA BANK LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WEBELSOLAR] Websol Energy System&apos;s 9M FY26 Revenue from Operations at Rs. 648 Cr, up by 61.0% Y-o-Y</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=WEBSOL+ENERGY+SYSTEM+LTD.&title=Websol+Energy+System%27s+9M+FY26+Revenue+from+Operations+at+Rs.+648+Cr%2C+up+by+61.0%25+Y-o-Y&newsId=f7fd39ef-89ac-4a4b-9080-e278561d7b3d&token=ZjdmZDM5ZWYtODlh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7fd39ef-89ac-4a4b-9080-e278561d7b3d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Websol Energy System Limited, a leading manufacturer of high-efficiency solar cells and solar modules in India, has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company reported a 61.0% Y-o-Y increase in Revenue from Operations, which stood at Rs. 648 Cr. The EBITDA for 9M FY26 was Rs. 282 Cr, with a margin of 43.6%, and the PAT was Rs. 179 Cr (EPS of Rs. 4.2), with a margin of 27.3%. The growth was driven by the commissioning of Cell Line-2 (600 MW Mono PERC facility) at Falta, West Bengal in September 2025. Websol also announced its approval for a proposed greenfield 4 GW solar cell and solar module manufacturing project in Andhra Pradesh.</p><ul><li>9M FY26 Revenue from Operations at Rs. 648 Cr, up by 61.0% Y-o-Y</li><li>9M FY26 EBITDA at Rs. 282 Cr, with a Margin of 43.6%</li><li>9M FY26 PAT at Rs. 179 Cr (EPS of Rs. 4.2), with a Margin of 27.3%</li><li>Approval for a proposed greenfield 4 GW solar cell and solar module manufacturing project in Andhra Pradesh</li><li>Commissioning of Cell Line-2 (600 MW Mono PERC facility) at Falta, West Bengal in September 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3f514dad-f6cb-4aa0-a2a5-917b8eb203a4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: WEBSOL ENERGY SYSTEM LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CGCL] Capri Global Capital Ltd Delivers Best-Ever Quarterly Performance with Consolidated AUM Crossing Rs 30,000 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Capri+Global+Capital+Limited&title=Capri+Global+Capital+Ltd+Delivers+Best-Ever+Quarterly+Performance+with+Consolidated+AUM+Crossing+Rs+30%2C000+Crores&newsId=24a92700-e89d-4be7-b38f-c5f856c71a72&token=MjRhOTI3MDAtZTg5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24a92700-e89d-4be7-b38f-c5f856c71a72</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:31:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Capri Global Capital Ltd (CGCL) announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, with a consolidated AUM of Rs 30,406 crores, representing a 47% YoY and 12% QoQ increase. The growth was broad-based across lending verticals, led by a 80% YoY increase in Gold Loans, 19% YoY increase in MSME Loans, and a 40% YoY rise in Housing Loans. Disbursements grew 87% YoY to Rs 10,879 crores. CGCL reported a highest ever quarterly PAT of Rs 255 crores, up 99% YoY, driven by expanding margins, operating leverage benefit, and consistent growth across all key business segments. The company delivered strong improvement in return metrics, with annualised RoAE at 15.0% and RoAA at 4.0%. Non-interest income grew 124% YoY to Rs 240 crores, contributing 32.0% of net total income during the quarter. The branch network expanded to 1,331 locations in 30QFY26, and operational efficiency strengthened with the cost-to-income ratio improving to 51.6%.</p><ul><li>CGCL delivered its strongest quarterly performance in 3QFY26 with consolidated AUM increasing 47% YoY and 12% QoQ to reach Rs 30,406 crores.</li><li>Profitability improved during the quarter, with a highest ever quarterly PAT of Rs 255 crores, up 99% YoY.</li><li>Non-interest income grew 124% YoY to Rs 240 crores, contributing 32.0% of net total income during the quarter.</li><li>The branch network expanded to 1,331 locations in 30QFY26, with a net addition of 107 branches.</li><li>Operational efficiency strengthened further with the cost-to-income ratio improving to 51.6% in 30FY26.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9023c9ea-98df-4660-a55d-ada7aff66a94.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Capri Global Capital Limited | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MAGADHSUGAR] Magadh Sugar &amp; Energy Ltd to Approve Q3 Results on Feb 6, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Magadh+Sugar+%26+Energy+Ltd&title=Magadh+Sugar+%26+Energy+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+Results+on+Feb+6%2C+2026&newsId=4cf37fb7-48fc-4bbc-9ecc-e4336a059066&token=NGNmMzdmYjctNDhm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4cf37fb7-48fc-4bbc-9ecc-e4336a059066</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Magadh Sugar &amp; Energy Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 6, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025. The meeting is in accordance with Regulation 29 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Magadh Sugar &amp; Energy Ltd to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for Q3 2025</li><li>The Board meeting is scheduled for February 6, 2026</li><li>The meeting is in accordance with Regulation 29 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6cdf0f59-f9c5-4fe3-b38d-a77c0ed17320.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Magadh Sugar & Energy Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[QUICKHEAL] Quick Heal Technologies Announces Appointments and Promotion in Senior Management</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Quick+Heal+Technologies+Ltd&title=Quick+Heal+Technologies+Announces+Appointments+and+Promotion+in+Senior+Management&newsId=334aa4a3-ee2c-4a03-8f58-0bf132317f4b&token=MzM0YWE0YTMtZWUy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">334aa4a3-ee2c-4a03-8f58-0bf132317f4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Quick Heal Technologies Ltd. has announced the appointment and promotion of several personnel in its senior management. Ms. Savita Nehra has been appointed as Vice President People and Culture, Mr. Amartya Mukherjee as Vice President and Head of Delivery, Ms. Netra Deshpande to Senior Management as Head of Engineering, and Mr. Nitin Bhogan as Director Cyber Awareness. The appointments are approved by the Nomination and Remuneration Committee and the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Ms. Savita Nehra appointed as Vice President People and Culture</li><li>Mr. Amartya Mukherjee appointed as Vice President and Head of Delivery</li><li>Ms. Netra Deshpande promoted to Senior Management as Head of Engineering</li><li>Mr. Nitin Bhogan appointed as Director Cyber Awareness</li><li>Appointments approved by the Nomination and Remuneration Committee and the Board of Directors</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c7a1767d-bbd2-458f-80f8-bd797a980e76.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Quick Heal Technologies Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ARCEEIN] Arcee Industries Ltd: Resignation of Statutory Auditor M/s. Jain Mittal Chaudhary &amp; Associates</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ARCEE+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Arcee+Industries+Ltd%3A+Resignation+of+Statutory+Auditor+M%2Fs.+Jain+Mittal+Chaudhary+%26+Associates&newsId=5d227d64-06eb-4bb3-9c4f-59c71ec63315&token=NWQyMjdkNjQtMDZl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d227d64-06eb-4bb3-9c4f-59c71ec63315</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Auditor</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Arcee Industries Ltd has announced the resignation of its statutory auditor, M/s. Jain Mittal Chaudhary &amp; Associates, due to preoccupation with other assignments. The resignation is effective from the close of business hours on January 29, 2026. The auditor has confirmed that there are no other material reasons for their resignation. The company will consider the appointment of new statutory auditors in due course.</p><ul><li>M/s. Jain Mittal Chaudhary &amp; Associates have resigned as statutory auditors of Arcee Industries Ltd.</li><li>The resignation is effective from the close of business hours on January 29, 2026.</li><li>The auditor has cited preoccupation with other assignments as the reason for their resignation.</li><li>There are no other material reasons for the resignation, according to the auditor.</li><li>The company will consider the appointment of new statutory auditors in due course.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8dbbda04-66ee-4d1b-bbc1-ee1578bce379.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ARCEE INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Auditor</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CUPIDALBV] Cupid Breweries And Distilleries Ltd Reports Q2 and H1 Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Cupid+Breweries+And+Distilleries+Ltd&title=Cupid+Breweries+And+Distilleries+Ltd+Reports+Q2+and+H1+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=f7ea0b53-50d2-4ce6-8396-6788dc6e624b&token=ZjdlYTBiNTMtNTBk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7ea0b53-50d2-4ce6-8396-6788dc6e624b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cupid Breweries And Distilleries Ltd, formerly known as Cupid Trades and Finance Limited, has reported its financial results for the quarter and half year ended September 30, 2025. The company&apos;s standalone and consolidated financial results were approved at a board meeting on January 29, 2026. The company&apos;s revenue from operations for the quarter is Rs. 9.34 crores, while the total revenue from operations for the half year is Rs. 19.67 crores. The company&apos;s profit before tax for the quarter is Rs. (11.98) crores and for the half year is Rs. (20.58) crores. The company&apos;s profit after tax for the quarter is Rs. 0.04 crores and for the half year is Rs. 0.04 crores.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter is Rs. 9.34 crores</li><li>Total revenue from operations for the half year is Rs. 19.67 crores</li><li>Profit before tax for the quarter is Rs. (11.98) crores</li><li>Profit before tax for the half year is Rs. (20.58) crores</li><li>Profit after tax for the quarter is Rs. 0.04 crores</li><li>Profit after tax for the half year is Rs. 0.04 crores</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/154a376e-4e44-42ca-a490-9d73e1d2e652.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Cupid Breweries And Distilleries Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>