<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 06:29:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[NYSSACORP] Nyssa Corporation Ltd: Appointment of New Directors &amp; KMP and Resignation of Existing Ones</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Nyssa+Corporation+Limited&title=Nyssa+Corporation+Ltd%3A+Appointment+of+New+Directors+%26+KMP+and+Resignation+of+Existing+Ones&newsId=1a84ca92-bfef-489e-b560-a5b83211f2ee&token=MWE4NGNhOTItYmZl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a84ca92-bfef-489e-b560-a5b83211f2ee</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 06:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Nyssa Corporation Ltd has announced changes in its management. The Board has approved the appointment of Brinda Kar as Non-Independent Non-Executive Director, Vandana Singh and Dhiraj Kumar Das as Independent Directors, and Arun Das as Chief Financial Officer (CFO). The Board has also approved the resignation of Prasanna Shirke as Executive Director and CFO, Shubhada Shirke as Non-Independent Non-Executive Director, Sonal Atal, Hemant N. Gokhale as Independent Directors. The appointments and resignations will be effective from 23rd January 2026.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Brinda Kar as Non-Independent Non-Executive Director</li><li>Appointment of Vandana Singh and Dhiraj Kumar Das as Independent Directors</li><li>Appointment of Arun Das as Chief Financial Officer (CFO)</li><li>Resignation of Prasanna Shirke as Executive Director and CFO</li><li>Resignation of Shubhada Shirke as Non-Independent Non-Executive Director</li><li>Resignation of Sonal Atal and Hemant N. Gokhale as Independent Directors</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0df43b4b-c06c-4acb-a1a1-39634af06b4f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Nyssa Corporation Limited | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ROUTE] Route Mobile Ltd Appoints Mr. Seckin Arikan as Chairman, Mr. Mark James Reid Resigns</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Route+Mobile+Ltd&title=Route+Mobile+Ltd+Appoints+Mr.+Seckin+Arikan+as+Chairman%2C+Mr.+Mark+James+Reid+Resigns&newsId=62f4a997-7872-4066-845c-9acf40eb59cd&token=NjJmNGE5OTctNzg3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62f4a997-7872-4066-845c-9acf40eb59cd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 06:27:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Route Mobile Limited has appointed Mr. Seckin Arikan as the Additional (Non-Executive, Non-Independent) Director and the Chairman of the Board of Directors. Mr. Arikan has been appointed with effect from January 22, 2026. The appointment is subject to the approval of the shareholders in the next General Meeting. Mr. Mark James Reid has resigned from his position as Chairman and Director due to preoccupation and other personal commitments.</p><ul><li>Mr. Seckin Arikan appointed as Additional (Non-Executive, Non-Independent) Director and Chairman of the Board</li><li>Mr. Arikan&apos;s appointment is subject to shareholder approval</li><li>Mr. Mark James Reid resigns as Chairman and Director</li><li>Re-composition of the Audit Committee, Stakeholders’ Relationship Committee, and Risk Management Committee</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/099a8f6a-f45c-4e0d-b6b2-fe0569b3e177.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Route Mobile Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[OCTAWARE] Octaware Technologies Ltd. Appoints Mr. Alok Ranjan and Mr. Pradeep Lavania as Additional Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Octaware+Technologies+Ltd&title=Octaware+Technologies+Ltd.+Appoints+Mr.+Alok+Ranjan+and+Mr.+Pradeep+Lavania+as+Additional+Directors&newsId=a76ad3ea-2eb7-4c09-9dba-915129ef4a9a&token=YTc2YWQzZWEtMmVi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a76ad3ea-2eb7-4c09-9dba-915129ef4a9a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 06:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Octaware Technologies Ltd. has appointed Mr. Alok Ranjan as an Additional Director (Whole time Director) and Mr. Pradeep Lavania as an Additional Director (Executive Director) on the Board of Directors of the Company. The appointments are subject to the approval of the Shareholders of the Company at the ensuing Annual General Meeting (AGM) for the FY 2025-26. Mr. Alok Ranjan and Mr. Pradeep Lavania will hold the office of Director till the date of ensuing Annual General Meeting of the Company.</p><ul><li>Mr. Alok Ranjan appointed as Additional Director (Whole time Director)</li><li>Mr. Pradeep Lavania appointed as Additional Director (Executive Director)</li><li>Appointments subject to approval of Shareholders at the ensuing AGM for the FY 2025-26</li><li>Mr. Alok Ranjan and Mr. Pradeep Lavania to hold office till the date of ensuing Annual General Meeting of the Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5626e220-2173-4291-b030-604198c3d152.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Octaware Technologies Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ORIRAIL] Oriental Rail Infrastructure Secures Order Worth Rs. 4.77 Crore from Central Railways</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Oriental+Rail+Infrastructure+Ltd&title=Oriental+Rail+Infrastructure+Secures+Order+Worth+Rs.+4.77+Crore+from+Central+Railways&newsId=37142f30-c69c-4a4c-a99b-ac7fad3f14ec&token=MzcxNDJmMzAtYzY5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37142f30-c69c-4a4c-a99b-ac7fad3f14ec</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 06:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Oriental Rail Infrastructure Ltd. has announced that it has secured an order worth Rs. 4,77,09,931.50 (Rupees Four Crore Seventy-Seven Lakh Nine Thousand Nine Hundred Thirty-One and Paise Fifty only) from Central Railways, CCOMT Mumbai, Indian Railways. The order is for the supply of RDSO-approved vinyl coated upholstery fabric (artificial leather) for Central Railway coaching stock. The delivery will be made to Central Railway upon inspection, delivery, acceptance of stores, and issue of CRN, with 95% payment on delivery against inspection certificate and duly acknowledged E-way-p= equally challan, and the balance 5% payable after acceptance of stores and issuance of CRN. The order is to be executed by January 22, 2027.</p><ul><li>Oriental Rail Infrastructure secures order worth Rs. 4.77 Crore from Central Railways</li><li>Order for the supply of RDSO-approved vinyl coated upholstery fabric (artificial leather) for Central Railway coaching stock</li><li>Delivery to be made upon inspection, delivery, acceptance of stores, and issue of CRN</li><li>Payment structure: 95% on delivery against inspection certificate and duly acknowledged E-way-p= equally challan, and the balance 5% payable after acceptance of stores and issuance of CRN</li><li>Order to be executed by January 22, 2027</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/089123ba-c2b7-49de-a2b4-d4d2f44a75d5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Oriental Rail Infrastructure Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDOBORAX] Indo Borax &amp; Chemicals Ltd. Announces Share Purchase Agreement Completion Date</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDO+BORAX+%26+CHEMICALS+LTD.-%24&title=Indo+Borax+%26+Chemicals+Ltd.+Announces+Share+Purchase+Agreement+Completion+Date&newsId=90e9b008-adb2-47ff-894c-8873f9c8c401&token=OTBlOWIwMDgtYWRi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90e9b008-adb2-47ff-894c-8873f9c8c401</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 06:17:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Indo Borax &amp; Chemicals Ltd. has announced that the parties to the Share Purchase Agreement (SPA) executed on December 15, 2025, have agreed to complete the transactions on January 23, 2026, as per a letter agreement executed on January 22, 2026. This agreement does not impose any additional restrictions on the company. The SPA involves the transfer of 1,63,00,230 equity shares, representing 50.80% of the total paid-up equity share capital of the company. Upon completion of the transfer on the Identified Closing Date, the sellers will cease to be in control of the company and will be declassified as members of the promoter/promoter group.</p><ul><li>Indo Borax &amp; Chemicals Ltd. announces the completion date of the Share Purchase Agreement.</li><li>The parties to the SPA have agreed to complete the transactions on January 23, 2026.</li><li>The SPA involves the transfer of 1,63,00,230 equity shares, representing 50.80% of the total paid-up equity share capital of the company.</li><li>Upon completion of the transfer, the sellers will cease to be in control of the company.</li><li>The SPA Letter Agreement does not impose any additional restrictions on the company.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4a2ba4c2-6563-43cf-b2cf-ba8d07f900b0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDO BORAX & CHEMICALS LTD.-$ | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ROUTE] Route Mobile Ltd Announces Changes in Board: Seckin Arikan Appointed as Chairman, Mark James Reid Resigns</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Route+Mobile+Ltd&title=Route+Mobile+Ltd+Announces+Changes+in+Board%3A+Seckin+Arikan+Appointed+as+Chairman%2C+Mark+James+Reid+Resigns&newsId=e3cee87e-8893-4910-83b8-14f792d11992&token=ZTNjZWU4N2UtODg5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3cee87e-8893-4910-83b8-14f792d11992</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 06:15:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Route Mobile Ltd has announced changes in its Board of Directors. Mr. Seckin Arikan has been appointed as the Additional (Non-Executive, Non-Independent) Director and the Chairman of the Board of Directors. He has been appointed with effect from January 22, 2026. On the other hand, Mr. Mark James Reid has tendered his resignation as Chairman and Director of the Company, citing preoccupation and other personal commitments. The Board has taken note of his resignation and has expressed its sincere appreciation for his contributions.</p><ul><li>Mr. Seckin Arikan appointed as Additional (Non-Executive, Non-Independent) Director and the Chairman of the Board of Directors</li><li>Mr. Mark James Reid resigns as Chairman and Director due to preoccupation and personal commitments</li><li>Mr. Seckin Arikan to hold office up to the date of the next General Meeting of the Company and is eligible for appointment as a Director, liable to retire by rotation, subject to approval of the shareholders</li><li>Mr. Mark James Reid ceases to be a member of the Audit Committee, Stakeholders’ Relationship Committee and Risk Management Committee of the Company</li><li>Board has approved the re-composition of the Audit Committee, Stakeholders’ Relationship Committee and Risk Management Committee</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d80ac4b7-28e4-4b5e-85d5-fa62c6221b82.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Route Mobile Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZAGGLE] Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd Secures Contract with Honda India Power Products Limited for Employee Expense Management &amp; Benefits</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Zaggle+Prepaid+Ocean+Services+Ltd&title=Zaggle+Prepaid+Ocean+Services+Ltd+Secures+Contract+with+Honda+India+Power+Products+Limited+for+Employee+Expense+Management+%26+Benefits&newsId=216f544a-a05c-4be3-816c-6805c853042d&token=MjE2ZjU0NGEtYTA1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">216f544a-a05c-4be3-816c-6805c853042d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 06:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Limited has entered into an agreement with Honda India Power Products Limited to provide Zaggle Save, an employee expense management &amp; benefits service. The contract is domestic and will be executed over a period of 2 years. The consideration or size of the order is not specified in the document. There is no indication of related party transactions or interests involving promoters or group companies.</p><ul><li>Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd has entered into an agreement with Honda India Power Products Limited</li><li>Zaggle to provide Honda India Power Products Limited with Zaggle Save, an employee expense management &amp; benefits service</li><li>The contract is domestic and will be executed over a period of 2 years</li><li>No related party transactions or interests involving promoters or group companies</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5dc29efc-2b10-442a-8768-31f09424f9c1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Zaggle Prepaid Ocean Services Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDOBORAX] Indo Borax &amp; Chemicals Ltd. Announces Share Transfer Completion Date with SPA Parties</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDO+BORAX+%26+CHEMICALS+LTD.-%24&title=Indo+Borax+%26+Chemicals+Ltd.+Announces+Share+Transfer+Completion+Date+with+SPA+Parties&newsId=88d80490-0cf3-499e-85b1-9eb393a5f847&token=ODhkODA0OTAtMGNm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88d80490-0cf3-499e-85b1-9eb393a5f847</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 06:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indo Borax &amp; Chemicals Ltd. has announced that the parties to the Share Purchase Agreement (SPA) executed on December 15, 2025, have signed a letter agreement on January 22, 2026, to set the completion date of the transactions under the SPA on January 23, 2026. The SPA Letter Agreement does not impose any additional restrictions on the company. The agreement marks the transfer of 1,63,00,230 equity shares, representing 50.80% of the total paid-up equity share capital, from the Sellers to the Purchasers. Upon completion of the transfer on the Identified Closing Date, the Sellers will cease to be in control of the company and will be declassified as members of the promoter/promoter group.</p><ul><li>Indo Borax &amp; Chemicals Ltd. has announced the completion date of transactions under the Share Purchase Agreement (SPA) dated December 15, 2025.</li><li>The SPA Letter Agreement sets the completion date on January 23, 2026.</li><li>The SPA Letter Agreement does not impose any additional restrictions on the company.</li><li>The transfer of shares represents 50.80% of the total paid-up equity share capital.</li><li>Upon completion of the transfer, the Sellers will cease to be in control of the company and will be declassified as members of the promoter/promoter group.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5de274a6-9a2e-471b-88a0-6f2443970e04.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDO BORAX & CHEMICALS LTD.-$ | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ANDHRAPAP] Andhra Paper Ltd to Approve Un-Audited Financial Results for Q3 &amp; 9M 2025 on Feb 4, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Andhra+Paper+Ltd&title=Andhra+Paper+Ltd+to+Approve+Un-Audited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+%26+9M+2025+on+Feb+4%2C+2026&newsId=85b3a902-89a9-4bcc-879c-4871004a6888&token=ODViM2E5MDItODlh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85b3a902-89a9-4bcc-879c-4871004a6888</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 06:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Andhra Paper Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 4, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. This meeting is in accordance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, and follows the closure of the trading window as of December 24, 2025.</p><ul><li>Andhra Paper Ltd to consider and approve un-audited financial results for Q3 and 9M 2025</li><li>Board meeting scheduled on February 4, 2026</li><li>Meeting in accordance with SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Trading window closed on December 24, 2025</li><li>Results pertain to the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6619414e-5418-46ad-8d3e-65470c884e7d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Andhra Paper Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TAVERNIER] Silverstone Consultancy Services Acquires 0.83% Stake in Tavernier Resources Ltd via Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Tavernier+Resources+Limi&title=Silverstone+Consultancy+Services+Acquires+0.83%25+Stake+in+Tavernier+Resources+Ltd+via+Open+Market&newsId=5e662c89-29f9-4d32-a5a5-1ce8795ad018&token=NWU2NjJjODktMjlm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5e662c89-29f9-4d32-a5a5-1ce8795ad018</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 06:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Silverstone Consultancy Services Pvt Ltd has acquired 50,000 shares carrying voting rights, equivalent to 0.83% stake in Tavernier Resources Ltd. The transaction took place on the open market. Before the transaction, Silverstone held 2.75% stake in Tavernier Resources, which has now increased to 3.58%.</p><ul><li>Silverstone Consultancy Services Pvt Ltd has acquired 50,000 shares of Tavernier Resources Ltd</li><li>The acquisition represents 0.83% stake in the company</li><li>The transaction took place on the open market</li><li>Before the transaction, Silverstone held 2.75% stake in Tavernier Resources</li><li>After the transaction, Silverstone&apos;s stake in Tavernier Resources has increased to 3.58%</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/B71D8801_398D_4BA5_AC9F_1CC29D93D256_113438.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Tavernier Resources Limi | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>