<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 01:25:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[GABRIEL] Gabriel India Ltd Subsidiary Company Jinhap Gabriel Auto India Private Limited Post Joint Venture</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GABRIEL+INDIA+LTD.-%24&title=Gabriel+India+Ltd+Subsidiary+Company+Jinhap+Gabriel+Auto+India+Private+Limited+Post+Joint+Venture&newsId=37b2e34a-c33c-44bf-b5a4-17e4dd6a3866&token=MzdiMmUzNGEtYzMz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37b2e34a-c33c-44bf-b5a4-17e4dd6a3866</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:34:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Gabriel India Ltd has fulfilled all conditions precedent in the matter of a Joint Venture with Jinos Co., Ltd. The joint venture company, Jinhap Gabriel Auto India Private Limited, has been formed to undertake the business of engineering, designing, developing, manufacturing, import, export, assembly, marketing, sales and distribution of fasteners for automotive and industrial applications. Gabriel and Jinos have been allotted equity shares in the ratio 51:49 respectively, making Jinhap Gabriel Auto India Private Limited a subsidiary company of Gabriel India Limited.</p><ul><li>Gabriel India Ltd and Jinos Co., Ltd form a Joint Venture company, Jinhap Gabriel Auto India Private Limited</li><li>The joint venture company will undertake the business of engineering, designing, developing, manufacturing, import, export, assembly, marketing, sales and distribution of fasteners for automotive and industrial applications</li><li>Gabriel India Ltd and Jinos Co., Ltd have been allotted equity shares in the ratio 51:49 respectively</li><li>Jinhap Gabriel Auto India Private Limited becomes a subsidiary company of Gabriel India Limited</li><li>The closing date for the joint venture is February 27, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4ea2fc08-02f2-4663-8353-03a2f3c31bb8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GABRIEL INDIA LTD.-$ | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RATHIST] Rathi Steel &amp; Power Ltd. Secures Stay on GST Recovery Proceedings Worth INR 11.46 Crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RATHI+STEEL+%26+POWER+LTD.-%24&title=Rathi+Steel+%26+Power+Ltd.+Secures+Stay+on+GST+Recovery+Proceedings+Worth+INR+11.46+Crore&newsId=50b96e9c-00ac-4aff-b519-59c79dd22bab&token=NTBiOTZlOWMtMDBh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50b96e9c-00ac-4aff-b519-59c79dd22bab</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rathi Steel &amp; Power Ltd. has secured a stay on recovery proceedings initiated by the Office of the Deputy Commissioner, Ghaziabad, Uttar Pradesh under section 74 of the GST Act, 2017. The Hon’ble Allahabad High Court passed the order on February 27, 2026, in respect of a writ petition filed by the company. The proceedings were initiated for a demand of INR 5,73,33,332 along with a penalty of a similar amount and applicable interest. This order will not have a material impact on the financial or operational activities of the listed entity.</p><ul><li>Rathi Steel &amp; Power Ltd. secures a stay on GST recovery proceedings</li><li>The proceedings were initiated for a demand of INR 5,73,33,332 along with a penalty of a similar amount and applicable interest</li><li>The stay was granted by the Hon’ble Allahabad High Court on February 27, 2026</li><li>The alleged issues are related to E-Way / contravention(s) committed or alleged to be committed, such as bills and availment of ineligible / excess Input Tax Credit</li><li>This order will not have a material impact on the financial or operational activities of the listed entity</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1c1fdf3d-1c05-44fc-9d93-fb0c965c6f0b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RATHI STEEL & POWER LTD.-$ | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GABRIEL] Gabriel India Ltd. Fulfills First Tranche Conditions Precedent in Joint Venture with SK On Co., Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GABRIEL+INDIA+LTD.-%24&title=Gabriel+India+Ltd.+Fulfills+First+Tranche+Conditions+Precedent+in+Joint+Venture+with+SK+On+Co.%2C+Ltd&newsId=7830055d-d700-4bba-8304-86ff89e606a6&token=NzgzMDA1NWQtZDcw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7830055d-d700-4bba-8304-86ff89e606a6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:21:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Gabriel India Ltd. has announced the fulfillment of First Tranche Conditions Precedent in the joint venture with SK On Co., Ltd. The joint venture company, SK Enmove Gabriel India Private Limited, has allotted equity shares to SK On Co., Ltd and Gabriel India Limited in a 51:49 ratio, respectively. The First Tranche Long Stop Date is set for February 27, 2026. Additionally, several agreements have been executed, including a Technology License Agreement, Corporate Service Agreement, ZIC Trademark Brand License Agreement, Business Transfer Agreement, and Joinder Agreement.</p><ul><li>Gabriel India Ltd. and SK On Co., Ltd. have fulfilled the First Tranche Conditions Precedent in their joint venture.</li><li>SK Enmove Gabriel India Private Limited has allotted equity shares to SK On Co., Ltd and Gabriel India Limited in a 51:49 ratio.</li><li>The First Tranche Long Stop Date is set for February 27, 2026.</li><li>Several agreements have been executed, including a Technology License Agreement, Corporate Service Agreement, ZIC Trademark Brand License Agreement, Business Transfer Agreement, and Joinder Agreement.</li><li>The joint venture company, SK Enmove Gabriel India Private Limited, has been incorporated.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1ddc0d58-5211-4b08-8b32-68e2d5d1a455.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GABRIEL INDIA LTD.-$ | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BHARTIARTL] Bharti Airtel Faces INR 17 Lakh Financial Disincentive from TRAI</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BHARTI+AIRTEL+LTD.&title=Bharti+Airtel+Faces+INR+17+Lakh+Financial+Disincentive+from+TRAI&newsId=86a8f483-dc65-4568-9d9a-15885a6b3e2b&token=ODZhOGY0ODMtZGM2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86a8f483-dc65-4568-9d9a-15885a6b3e2b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bharti Airtel Ltd has received an order from the Telecom Regulatory Authority of India (TRAI) imposing a financial disincentive of INR 17,01,000. The order was received on February 27, 2026, at 1123 Hrs IST. The violation pertains to the redressal of complaints not being in line with the provisions of the Telecom Commercial Communications Customer Preference Regulations, 2018, for the quarter ended March 2024. The company does not agree with the order and plans to take appropriate action for rectification or reversal.</p><ul><li>Bharti Airtel received an order from TRAI imposing a financial disincentive of INR 17,01,000</li><li>The violation pertains to the redressal of complaints not being in line with the Telecom Commercial Communications Customer Preference Regulations, 2018</li><li>The order was received on February 27, 2026</li><li>Bharti Airtel plans to take appropriate action for rectification or reversal of the order</li><li>The maximum financial impact is to the extent of the financial disincentive levied</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1b38870e-a366-4b07-aa16-f92eac462d13.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BHARTI AIRTEL LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDSOYA] Indsoya Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Draft Notice of EGM and Appointment of Scrutinizer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDSOYA+LTD.&title=Indsoya+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Draft+Notice+of+EGM+and+Appointment+of+Scrutinizer&newsId=7dd7db4d-1fab-43e5-bf68-160503c9c990&token=N2RkN2RiNGQtMWZh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7dd7db4d-1fab-43e5-bf68-160503c9c990</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:21:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indsoya Ltd, a company based in Maharashtra, India, has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 05th March 2026 to consider and approve the draft Notice of the Extraordinary General Meeting (EGM). The EGM is scheduled to be held on 30th March 2026 through Video Conferencing (VC) or Other Audio Visual Means (OAVM). The company will also appoint a Scrutinizer for conducting the e-voting. The meeting will take place at the company&apos;s registered office in Vasai, Maharashtra.</p><ul><li>Indsoya Ltd&apos;s Board Meeting scheduled on 05th March 2026</li><li>Draft Notice of the Extraordinary General Meeting (EGM) to be considered and approved</li><li>EGM scheduled for 30th March 2026 through VC/OAVM</li><li>Appointment of a Scrutinizer for conducting the e-voting</li><li>Meeting to be held at the company&apos;s registered office in Vasai, Maharashtra</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/920e11f6-a263-4d44-8bab-78f4e5664979.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDSOYA LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MUTHTFN] Muthoot Capital Services Ltd Raises 94.86 Crores Through Direct Assignment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MUTHOOT+CAPITAL+SERVICES+LTD.&title=Muthoot+Capital+Services+Ltd+Raises+94.86+Crores+Through+Direct+Assignment&newsId=5e9c6c7a-e696-4a92-a3cb-2dcf81e7179a&token=NWU5YzZjN2EtZTY5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5e9c6c7a-e696-4a92-a3cb-2dcf81e7179a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:57:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Muthoot Capital Services Limited has successfully completed a Direct Assignment transaction on February 27, 2026, raising an amount of 94,85,65,273/- (Rupees Ninety-Four Crores Eighty-Five Lakhs Sixty-Five Thousand Two Hundred and Seventy Three Only). This was achieved by assigning Two Wheeler Loans receivables totaling to 105,39,61,414/- (Rupees One Hundred and Five Crores Thirty-Nine Lakhs Sixty-One Thousand Four Hundred and Fourteen only). This is the fifth Securitization / Direct Assignment transaction carried out by the Company during the financial year 2025-26. The entire pool is from the non-priority sector, adhering to the guidelines prescribed by the Reserve Bank of India.</p><ul><li>Muthoot Capital Services Ltd raised 94.86 crores through Direct Assignment.</li><li>The transaction involved the assignment of Two Wheeler Loans receivables.</li><li>The total value of the assigned receivables was 105.40 crores.</li><li>This is the fifth Securitization / Direct Assignment transaction by the Company in FY 2025-26.</li><li>The entire pool is from the non-priority sector, complying with RBI guidelines.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bcafaf28-eafe-4e15-a7d3-74b75b5c236d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MUTHOOT CAPITAL SERVICES LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[J&amp;KBANK] Jammu &amp; Kashmir Bank Ltd Changes Registrar to an Issue and Share Transfer Agent</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JAMMU+%26+KASHMIR+BANK+LTD.&title=Jammu+%26+Kashmir+Bank+Ltd+Changes+Registrar+to+an+Issue+and+Share+Transfer+Agent&newsId=23149dd1-ecc4-42d6-8eb5-24a3d2bb91f8&token=MjMxNDlkZDEtZWNj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23149dd1-ecc4-42d6-8eb5-24a3d2bb91f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:51:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jammu &amp; Kashmir Bank Ltd has announced a change of Registrar to an Issue and Share Transfer Agent (RTA) of the Bank. The new RTA is M/s Bigshare Services Private Limited, replacing M/s KFin Technologies Limited. The effective date of this change is March 01, 2026. The tripartite agreement between the Bank, the new RTA, and the old RTA is in process and will be intimated in due course.</p><ul><li>Jammu &amp; Kashmir Bank Ltd changes its Registrar to an Issue and Share Transfer Agent</li><li>M/s Bigshare Services Private Limited is the new appointed RTA</li><li>M/s KFin Technologies Limited is the outgoing RTA</li><li>The effective date of the change is March 01, 2026</li><li>The tripartite agreement is in process</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/39de92fe-d3db-412e-b5ab-cb3af4ee5b44.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JAMMU & KASHMIR BANK LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TBOTEK] TBO TEK Ltd to Shift Registered Office from March 1, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TBO+TEK+Ltd&title=TBO+TEK+Ltd+to+Shift+Registered+Office+from+March+1%2C+2026&newsId=a79bb10c-61c0-4a39-84b0-fd41003d1eff&token=YTc5YmIxMGMtNjFj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a79bb10c-61c0-4a39-84b0-fd41003d1eff</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:47:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>TBO TEK Ltd, a company based in New Delhi, has announced the shifting of its Registered Office from E-78 South Extension Part- I, New Delhi-110049 to Unit No. 501, 5% Floor, Worldmark-4, Asset Area No. LP-IB-04 Gateway District, Aerocity, Near Indira Gandhi Airport, New Delhi- 110037 with effect from March 1, 2026. This information is being shared in accordance with the Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015 and has also been disseminated on the company&apos;s website. Neera Chandak, Company Secretary and Compliance Officer of TBO Tek Limited, has digitally signed this intimation.</p><ul><li>TBO TEK Ltd is shifting its Registered Office within New Delhi from E-78 South Extension Part- I to Unit No. 501, Worldmark-4, Aerocity.</li><li>The shift will be effective from March 1, 2026.</li><li>The disclosure is in accordance with the Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li><li>The information has been shared on the company&apos;s website.</li><li>Neera Chandak, Company Secretary and Compliance Officer of TBO Tek Limited, has digitally signed the intimation.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fe82aeee-3fdd-484b-ae5f-b72b6e33b698.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TBO TEK Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AHCL] Anlon Healthcare Extends Share Purchase Agreement Deadline with Bizotic Lifescience</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Anlon+Healthcare+Ltd&title=Anlon+Healthcare+Extends+Share+Purchase+Agreement+Deadline+with+Bizotic+Lifescience&newsId=e59912ea-710e-42be-ac48-bf78110be7af&token=ZTU5OTEyZWEtNzEw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e59912ea-710e-42be-ac48-bf78110be7af</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:41:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Anlon Healthcare Limited has announced an amendment in the Share Purchase Agreement (SPA) with Bizotic Lifescience Private Limited. The SPA, originally executed on November 28, 2025, was regarding the acquisition of 56.67% shareholding of the Target Company by Anlon Healthcare. Due to certain pending procedural requirements, the parties have agreed to extend the expected time period for completion of the acquisition until April 2, 2026, which is 125 days from the execution date of the SPA.</p><ul><li>Anlon Healthcare and Bizotic Lifescience Private Limited have amended their Share Purchase Agreement.</li><li>The agreement originally involved the acquisition of 56.67% shareholding of the Target Company by Anlon Healthcare.</li><li>The deadline for completion of the acquisition has been extended until April 2, 2026 due to pending procedural requirements.</li><li>The extension is for a period of 125 days from the execution date of the SPA.</li><li>Anlon Healthcare has requested that this information be taken on record.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8b9bb6ee-64a1-4da0-bb3b-f967c8bb6b8f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Anlon Healthcare Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LABELKRAFT] Labelkraft Technologies Ltd. to Consider Increasing Remuneration and Applying for KSFC Loan in Upcoming Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Labelkraft+Technologies+Ltd&title=Labelkraft+Technologies+Ltd.+to+Consider+Increasing+Remuneration+and+Applying+for+KSFC+Loan+in+Upcoming+Board+Meeting&newsId=0a0d9f03-4634-402e-adcd-b8c1c87ce06a&token=MGEwZDlmMDMtNDYz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a0d9f03-4634-402e-adcd-b8c1c87ce06a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 16:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Labelkraft Technologies Ltd. has announced a scheduled Board Meeting on 05 March 2026 at its registered office in Bangalore, Karnataka, India. The agenda includes the consideration of increasing the remuneration of Chairman &amp; Managing Director, Ranjeet Kumar Solanki, and Whole-time Director, Ms Raashi Jain. The company also plans to make an application to Karnataka State Financial Corporation (KSFC) to avail a loan up to Rs. 1 Crore. This information has been disclosed in accordance with Regulation 29 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Labelkraft Technologies Ltd. to consider increasing the remuneration of Chairman &amp; Managing Director, Ranjeet Kumar Solanki</li><li>Labelkraft Technologies Ltd. to consider increasing the remuneration of Whole-time Director, Ms Raashi Jain</li><li>Labelkraft Technologies Ltd. plans to make an application to Karnataka State Financial Corporation (KSFC) for a loan up to Rs. 1 Crore</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/199131d1-ac57-45b4-a41a-fea1c69bcb1b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Labelkraft Technologies Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>