<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:13:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[TTML] Tata Teleservices Faces Rs. 9 Lakhs Penalty for Failing to Control Unsolicited Commercial Communications</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TATA+TELESERVICES+%28MAHARASHTRA%29+LTD.&title=Tata+Teleservices+Faces+Rs.+9+Lakhs+Penalty+for+Failing+to+Control+Unsolicited+Commercial+Communications&newsId=25ea922c-275d-465f-b4fc-d50479791462&token=MjVlYTkyMmMtMjc1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">25ea922c-275d-465f-b4fc-d50479791462</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tata Teleservices (Maharashtra) Ltd. has received an order from the Telecom Regulatory Authority of India, imposing a financial disincentive of Rs. 9,12,000 for the quarter ending March 2024. The order was received on February 27, 2026, and is in relation to the company&apos;s failure to curb unsolicited commercial communications (UCC) sent through its network, as required under the Telecom Commercial Communications Customer Preference Regulations, 2018. The company is currently reviewing the order and evaluating the next steps in this matter.</p><ul><li>Tata Teleservices fined Rs. 9,12,000 by Telecom Regulatory Authority of India</li><li>Penalty imposed for failing to control unsolicited commercial communications</li><li>Order received on February 27, 2026</li><li>Company reviewing the order and evaluating next steps</li><li>Failure to comply with Telecom Commercial Communications Customer Preference Regulations, 2018</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3295fc43-8db9-475f-9aea-3c73e6b0db2f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TATA TELESERVICES (MAHARASHTRA) LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TANFACIND] TANFAC Industries Ltd. Revises Record Date for Equity Shares Sub-Division to March 09, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TANFAC+INDUSTRIES+LTD.-%24&title=TANFAC+Industries+Ltd.+Revises+Record+Date+for+Equity+Shares+Sub-Division+to+March+09%2C+2026&newsId=3403be9f-fa9c-4b1f-ae3e-0fba7130e3b4&token=MzQwM2JlOWYtZmE5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3403be9f-fa9c-4b1f-ae3e-0fba7130e3b4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Split</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>TANFAC Industries Ltd. has revised the record date for determining eligibility of equity shareholders for the sub-division of equity shares. The new record date is Monday, March 09, 2026. This change comes after the initial record date was set for Thursday, March 05, 2026. The sub-division will result in one equity share with a face value of ₹ 10/- being split into two equity shares with a face value of ₹ 5/- each, both ranking equally in all aspects.</p><ul><li>TANFAC Industries Ltd. revises record date for equity shares sub-division</li><li>New record date set to Monday, March 09, 2026</li><li>One equity share with ₹ 10/- face value to be split into two shares with ₹ 5/- face value each</li><li>No change in ranking or other aspects of the shares</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d711f1bd-3cdf-490b-a43b-d66ae76005bc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TANFAC INDUSTRIES LTD.-$ | Category: Split</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RSYSTEMINT] R Systems International Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Consider Interim Dividend for 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=R+Systems+International+Limited&title=R+Systems+International+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Consider+Interim+Dividend+for+2026&newsId=e420cbf0-9bb3-40a7-a194-e7f23ffc5a96&token=ZTQyMGNiZjAtOWJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e420cbf0-9bb3-40a7-a194-e7f23ffc5a96</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:02:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>R Systems International Ltd has informed the BSE that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on 06/03/2026. The agenda includes considering and approving the declaration of an interim dividend for the year 2026, if any. This announcement is in accordance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>R Systems International Ltd has scheduled a Board Meeting on 06/03/2026</li><li>The agenda includes considering and approving the declaration of an interim dividend for the year 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6aa37257-a6e0-4149-bf9f-bab1283105f3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: R Systems International Limited | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VERANDA] Promoters of Veranda Learning Solutions Ltd. Create Pledge Over Equity Shares Worth INR 112.50 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Veranda+Learning+Solutions+Ltd&title=Promoters+of+Veranda+Learning+Solutions+Ltd.+Create+Pledge+Over+Equity+Shares+Worth+INR+112.50+Crores&newsId=60ab0520-0a1c-4887-9247-d663b5c5d7c9&token=NjBhYjA1MjAtMGEx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60ab0520-0a1c-4887-9247-d663b5c5d7c9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:02:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The promoters of Veranda Learning Solutions Ltd. have executed two documents creating a pledge over equity shares held in the company. The first pledge, with City Union Bank Limited through SBICAP Trustee Company Limited, is for INR 50 crores, and the second pledge, with RBL Bank Limited, is for INR 62.50 crores. The purpose of these pledges is to secure credit facilities. The promoters have pledged 30,00,000 equity shares in the first pledge and an additional number of shares in the second pledge to maintain a minimum aggregate value of INR 62.50 crores. These pledges do not have any immediate impact on the management or control of the company. However, if the lenders invoke or enforce the pledge, it may have a consequential impact on the shareholding pattern of the company.</p><ul><li>Promoters of Veranda Learning Solutions Ltd. create pledge over equity shares worth INR 112.50 crores</li><li>First pledge with City Union Bank Limited through SBICAP Trustee Company Limited for INR 50 crores</li><li>Second pledge with RBL Bank Limited for INR 62.50 crores</li><li>Pledges secure credit facilities</li><li>No immediate impact on management or control of the company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0b9a9485-7d04-4cd0-bfdd-98687ae8e8fd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Veranda Learning Solutions Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[QUADFUTURE] Quadrant Future Tek Ltd. Faces Rs. 30 Lakhs Penalty for Private Placement Procedural Compliance Violations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Quadrant+Future+Tek+Ltd&title=Quadrant+Future+Tek+Ltd.+Faces+Rs.+30+Lakhs+Penalty+for+Private+Placement+Procedural+Compliance+Violations&newsId=ac273bb0-3861-437d-991f-b67f0364238e&token=YWMyNzNiYjAtMzg2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac273bb0-3861-437d-991f-b67f0364238e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:01:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Quadrant Future Tek Ltd. has received an order from the Regional Director, Northern Region, in response to an appeal filed by the company regarding ROC Adjudication Order dated 8th August, 2024. The order pertains to a penalty imposed on the company and its promoters for violating private placement procedural compliances under Section 42 of the Companies Act, 2013, during the financial year 2016-17. The company raised funds through preferential allotment by way of private placement of securities, but missed the procedural requirement to open a separate bank account for receipt of the share application money and utilization thereof prior to the allotment of equity shares. This led to a non-compliance under Section 42 of the Companies Act. The Regional Director has set aside the penalty imposed under Section 42(10) of the Companies Act, but upheld the penalty under Section 42(6), which amounts to Rs. 30 Lakhs on the company and Rs. 6 Lakhs on each promoter. The company has confirmed that there is no material effect on its operations.</p><ul><li>Quadrant Future Tek Ltd. faces a penalty of Rs. 30 Lakhs under Section 42(6) of the Companies Act, 2013.</li><li>Each promoter of the company is liable to pay a penalty of Rs. 6 Lakhs.</li><li>The penalty is in relation to private placement for issue of equity shares during the period from March, 2016 to April, 2017.</li><li>The Regional Director has set aside the penalty imposed under Section 42(10) of the Companies Act.</li><li>There is no material impact on the company&apos;s operations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/534eb8a8-f16c-4ebf-aa2b-8a858bf229b7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Quadrant Future Tek Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IRCTC] IRCTC Fined by BSE &amp; NSE for Non-Compliance with SEBI Regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Indian+Railway+Catering+and+Tourism+Corporation+Ltd&title=IRCTC+Fined+by+BSE+%26+NSE+for+Non-Compliance+with+SEBI+Regulations&newsId=55f1d1e9-5472-4e96-8c50-f3b17fc21253&token=NTVmMWQxZTktNTQ3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55f1d1e9-5472-4e96-8c50-f3b17fc21253</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:01:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indian Railway Catering and Tourism Corporation Ltd (IRCTC) has received notices from BSE and NSE regarding the imposition of fines for non-compliance with the provisions of Regulations 17(1) of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015. The non-compliance pertains to the composition of the Board of Directors, including the failure to appoint a woman director. The period of non-compliance is the quarter ended on December 31, 2025. The fine amount, including GST, is INR 5,42,800 each from BSE and NSE. IRCTC, being a Government Company, follows up with the Ministry of Railways, Government of India for the appointment of requisite number of Independent Directors, including Women Independent Director on its Board. The fine does not impact the financial, operation, or other activities of the Company. In the past, similar letters have been received and waiver requests were considered favorably by the Exchanges.</p><ul><li>IRCTC fined by BSE and NSE for non-compliance with SEBI regulations</li><li>Non-compliance pertains to the composition of the Board of Directors</li><li>Failure to appoint a woman director is the main issue</li><li>Fine amount is INR 5,42,800 each from BSE and NSE</li><li>IRCTC is a Government Company and follows up with Ministry of Railways for appointing Independent Directors</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/50bccac2-71bc-4a6a-9ec2-9a28288e8e04.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Indian Railway Catering and Tourism Corporation Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MOIL] Moil Ltd Fined Rs. 5,42,800 Each by NSE and BSE for Board Composition Violation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MOIL+LTD.&title=Moil+Ltd+Fined+Rs.+5%2C42%2C800+Each+by+NSE+and+BSE+for+Board+Composition+Violation&newsId=0c1f0407-9652-40de-88f1-2413a0a6bbe5&token=MGMxZjA0MDctOTY1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c1f0407-9652-40de-88f1-2413a0a6bbe5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Moil Ltd, named in the text, has been fined by the National Stock Exchange of India Limited (NSE) and BSE Limited (BSE) for non-compliance with the provisions related to the composition of the Board for the quarter ended on 31st Dec., 2025. The fine amounts to Rs. 5,42,800 (incl. GST) from each authority. This information is being submitted for records, with no impact stated on the financial, operational, or other activities of the company.</p><ul><li>Moil Ltd fined Rs. 5,42,800 each by NSE and BSE</li><li>Fines imposed for non-compliance with Board composition rules</li><li>No impact on Moil Ltd&apos;s financial, operational, or other activities</li><li>Fines communicated to Moil Ltd on 27.02.2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/46c35bab-f878-44f4-8cbe-0935830415fb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MOIL LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STYLEBAAZA] Baazar Style Retail Ltd Opens New Store at Midnapore, West Bengal</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Baazar+Style+Retail+Ltd&title=Baazar+Style+Retail+Ltd+Opens+New+Store+at+Midnapore%2C+West+Bengal&newsId=d1ffe905-a8fe-46da-bfb1-33cffe297979&token=ZDFmZmU5MDUtYThm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d1ffe905-a8fe-46da-bfb1-33cffe297979</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 04:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Baazar Style Retail Ltd, formerly known as Baazar Style Retail Pvt. Ltd., has announced the opening of a new Style Baazar store in Midnapore, West Bengal. This brings the total number of stores to 259 as of the date of this announcement. The company, headquartered at PSSrijan Tech Park, Sector-V, Salt Lake, North 24 Parganas, West Bengal 700091, is compliant with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Baazar Style Retail Ltd opens a new Style Baazar store in Midnapore, West Bengal.</li><li>The total number of stores as on date is now 259.</li><li>The company is headquartered at PSSrijan Tech Park, Sector-V, Salt Lake, North 24 Parganas, West Bengal 700091.</li><li>Baazar Style Retail Ltd is compliant with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8e7e3343-0034-40ab-ad98-19519253c214.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Baazar Style Retail Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GABRIEL] Gabriel India Ltd Subsidiary Company Jinhap Gabriel Auto India Private Limited Post Joint Venture</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GABRIEL+INDIA+LTD.-%24&title=Gabriel+India+Ltd+Subsidiary+Company+Jinhap+Gabriel+Auto+India+Private+Limited+Post+Joint+Venture&newsId=37b2e34a-c33c-44bf-b5a4-17e4dd6a3866&token=MzdiMmUzNGEtYzMz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37b2e34a-c33c-44bf-b5a4-17e4dd6a3866</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:34:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Gabriel India Ltd has fulfilled all conditions precedent in the matter of a Joint Venture with Jinos Co., Ltd. The joint venture company, Jinhap Gabriel Auto India Private Limited, has been formed to undertake the business of engineering, designing, developing, manufacturing, import, export, assembly, marketing, sales and distribution of fasteners for automotive and industrial applications. Gabriel and Jinos have been allotted equity shares in the ratio 51:49 respectively, making Jinhap Gabriel Auto India Private Limited a subsidiary company of Gabriel India Limited.</p><ul><li>Gabriel India Ltd and Jinos Co., Ltd form a Joint Venture company, Jinhap Gabriel Auto India Private Limited</li><li>The joint venture company will undertake the business of engineering, designing, developing, manufacturing, import, export, assembly, marketing, sales and distribution of fasteners for automotive and industrial applications</li><li>Gabriel India Ltd and Jinos Co., Ltd have been allotted equity shares in the ratio 51:49 respectively</li><li>Jinhap Gabriel Auto India Private Limited becomes a subsidiary company of Gabriel India Limited</li><li>The closing date for the joint venture is February 27, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4ea2fc08-02f2-4663-8353-03a2f3c31bb8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GABRIEL INDIA LTD.-$ | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RATHIST] Rathi Steel &amp; Power Ltd. Secures Stay on GST Recovery Proceedings Worth INR 11.46 Crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RATHI+STEEL+%26+POWER+LTD.-%24&title=Rathi+Steel+%26+Power+Ltd.+Secures+Stay+on+GST+Recovery+Proceedings+Worth+INR+11.46+Crore&newsId=50b96e9c-00ac-4aff-b519-59c79dd22bab&token=NTBiOTZlOWMtMDBh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50b96e9c-00ac-4aff-b519-59c79dd22bab</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 17:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rathi Steel &amp; Power Ltd. has secured a stay on recovery proceedings initiated by the Office of the Deputy Commissioner, Ghaziabad, Uttar Pradesh under section 74 of the GST Act, 2017. The Hon’ble Allahabad High Court passed the order on February 27, 2026, in respect of a writ petition filed by the company. The proceedings were initiated for a demand of INR 5,73,33,332 along with a penalty of a similar amount and applicable interest. This order will not have a material impact on the financial or operational activities of the listed entity.</p><ul><li>Rathi Steel &amp; Power Ltd. secures a stay on GST recovery proceedings</li><li>The proceedings were initiated for a demand of INR 5,73,33,332 along with a penalty of a similar amount and applicable interest</li><li>The stay was granted by the Hon’ble Allahabad High Court on February 27, 2026</li><li>The alleged issues are related to E-Way / contravention(s) committed or alleged to be committed, such as bills and availment of ineligible / excess Input Tax Credit</li><li>This order will not have a material impact on the financial or operational activities of the listed entity</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1c1fdf3d-1c05-44fc-9d93-fb0c965c6f0b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RATHI STEEL & POWER LTD.-$ | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>