<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:32:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[MAITHANALL] Maithan Alloys Ltd. Reclassifies Promoter Group Shareholders as Public Category</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MAITHAN+ALLOYS+LTD.&title=Maithan+Alloys+Ltd.+Reclassifies+Promoter+Group+Shareholders+as+Public+Category&newsId=57769290-f7d7-44a4-8602-8686d4e546c0&token=NTc3NjkyOTAtZjdk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57769290-f7d7-44a4-8602-8686d4e546c0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Maithan Alloys Ltd. has received approval for the re-classification request of certain Promoter Group Shareholders under Regulation 31A of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The Board of Directors, after considering the rational and justifications provided by the Outgoing Promoter Group Shareholders, formed an opinion that the request should be considered favorably. The re-classification is subject to necessary approvals of the Stock Exchanges and Members of the Company.</p><ul><li>Re-classification request received from Promoter Group Shareholders under Regulation 31A of the Listing Regulations.</li><li>Board of Directors considered and analyzed the request and formed an opinion to approve the re-classification.</li><li>Approval is subject to necessary approvals of the Stock Exchanges and Members of the Company.</li><li>Maithan Alloys Ltd. will comply with the requirement for minimum public shareholding as required under Regulation 38 of Listing Regulations.</li><li>Company has no outstanding dues to the Securities and Exchange Board of India, the stock exchanges or depositories.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/93cae2a2-c60b-4e3d-b32c-3aef0fbd6cbd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MAITHAN ALLOYS LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VINAYAKPOL] Vinayak Polycon International Ltd. Approves Un-audited Financial Results for Quarter and Nine Months Ended on 31st December, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VINAYAK+POLYCON+INTERNATIONAL+LTD.&title=Vinayak+Polycon+International+Ltd.+Approves+Un-audited+Financial+Results+for+Quarter+and+Nine+Months+Ended+on+31st+December%2C+2025&newsId=9534c6e2-67de-4f58-af8f-c95ea32245ba&token=OTUzNGM2ZTItNjdk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9534c6e2-67de-4f58-af8f-c95ea32245ba</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vinayak Polycon International Ltd. held a Board Meeting on Saturday, 31st January, 2026, where they approved the Un-audited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December, 2025. The meeting was conducted through Video Conferencing and the results were reviewed by the Audit Committee before approval. The Statutory Auditors have carried out a limited review of these results. The company&apos;s business activity falls within a single operating segment and the results are available on the company&apos;s website and on the website of BSE.</p><ul><li>Vinayak Polycon International Ltd. approved the Un-audited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December, 2025.</li><li>The results were reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved in the Board Meeting held on Saturday, 31st January, 2026.</li><li>The Statutory Auditors have carried out a limited review of these results.</li><li>The company&apos;s business activity falls within a single operating segment.</li><li>The Un-audited Financial Results are available on the company&apos;s website and on the website of BSE.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4325d5af-ac5a-4629-a31a-13a41cd5c878.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VINAYAK POLYCON INTERNATIONAL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHIVKAMAL] Shivkamal Impex Ltd to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 &amp; Nine Months Ended Dec 31, 2025 on Feb 7, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shivkamal+Impex+Ltd&title=Shivkamal+Impex+Ltd+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Ended+Dec+31%2C+2025+on+Feb+7%2C+2026&newsId=bc77e9fb-6bc3-4223-8507-aa9ad06c8d91&token=YmM3N2U5ZmItNmJj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc77e9fb-6bc3-4223-8507-aa9ad06c8d91</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shivkamal Impex Ltd has scheduled a Board of Directors meeting on February 7, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will be held at the registered office of the company in New Delhi. The trading window for all designated persons and their immediate relatives will remain closed from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results, i.e., till February 9, 2026.</p><ul><li>Shivkamal Impex Ltd to approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended Dec 31, 2025</li><li>Board of Directors meeting scheduled on Feb 7, 2026</li><li>Meeting to be held at the registered office in New Delhi</li><li>Trading window for designated persons and their immediate relatives to remain closed from Jan 1, 2026, to Feb 9, 2026</li><li>Financial Results to be declared on Feb 9, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5323390b-85ac-4f65-9b14-3d0396c86da0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shivkamal Impex Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BAIDFIN] Baid Finserv Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results on Feb 10, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Baid+Finserv+Ltd&title=Baid+Finserv+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+on+Feb+10%2C+2026&newsId=f3100a80-89c4-4395-8dc6-559349c14061&token=ZjMxMDBhODAtODlj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3100a80-89c4-4395-8dc6-559349c14061</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Baid Finserv Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 10, 2026, to consider and approve the Un-Audited Financial Results for the Quarter and Nine Months ended on December 31, 2025. The meeting will be held at the company&apos;s registered office in Jaipur, Rajasthan. The trading window for the directors, key managerial personnel, designated persons, connected persons, and their relatives will be closed from January 01, 2026, till the end of 48 hours after the declaration of the results.</p><ul><li>Baid Finserv Ltd to consider and approve Q3 and nine months results on Feb 10, 2026</li><li>The meeting will be held at the company&apos;s registered office in Jaipur, Rajasthan</li><li>Trading window for directors, key managerial personnel, designated persons, connected persons, and their relatives to be closed from Jan 1, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/951b569e-d99c-4486-b38b-d96c1b971958.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Baid Finserv Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VINAYAKPOL] Vinayak Polycon International Ltd. Announces Q3 and Nine-Months Results for 2025, Showing Increased Comprehensive Income</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VINAYAK+POLYCON+INTERNATIONAL+LTD.&title=Vinayak+Polycon+International+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+Nine-Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Showing+Increased+Comprehensive+Income&newsId=d552a4f7-ce9c-46f2-b5b7-69549c077b32&token=ZDU1MmE0ZjctY2U5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d552a4f7-ce9c-46f2-b5b7-69549c077b32</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vinayak Polycon International Ltd. has announced its un-audited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended on 31st December, 2025. The company&apos;s total comprehensive income for the period has increased significantly. The Board of Directors approved the results in a meeting held on 31st January, 2026 through video conferencing. The trading window for insiders, directors, promoters, connected persons, and designated employees will open from 3rd February, 2026. The results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and recommended for approval by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Total comprehensive income for the period has increased to Rs. 2,119.74 crore from Rs. 1,605.48 crore in the previous year.</li><li>Revenue from operations has also increased to Rs. 608.37 crore for the quarter.</li><li>The Board of Directors approved the results in a meeting held on 31st January, 2026 through video conferencing.</li><li>The trading window for insiders, directors, promoters, connected persons, and designated employees will open from 3rd February, 2026.</li><li>The results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and recommended for approval by the Board of Directors.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/964922ed-82a9-4843-9988-d1d3068d6e89.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VINAYAK POLYCON INTERNATIONAL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CSL] Continental Securities Ltd Approves Conversion of 7,00,000 Warrants into Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Continental+Securities+Ltd&title=Continental+Securities+Ltd+Approves+Conversion+of+7%2C00%2C000+Warrants+into+Equity+Shares&newsId=9e7f30c4-1563-45ab-98b1-75cf32d8e5de&token=OWU3ZjMwYzQtMTU2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e7f30c4-1563-45ab-98b1-75cf32d8e5de</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:24:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Continental Securities Ltd has considered and approved the conversion of 7,00,000 warrants into 7,00,000 Equity shares of face value of Rs. 2/- at a premium of Rs. 19/- Each. The warrants were allotted on January 31, 2025 on Preferential Basis to allottees of Promoter &amp; Non-Promoter Group. The special resolution was passed by the shareholders of the company in the general meeting dated January 07, 2025 and in-principal approval received from BSE Limited. Consequent to the aforesaid allotment, the paid-up equity capital of the Company has increased from Rs. 5,85,06,000/- consisting of 2,92,53,000 Equity Shares of Rs. 2/- each to Rs. 5,99,06,000/- consisting of 2,99,53,000 Equity Shares of Rs. 2/- each.</p><ul><li>Continental Securities Ltd approved the conversion of 7,00,000 warrants into 7,00,000 Equity shares</li><li>The warrants were allotted on January 31, 2025 on Preferential Basis to allottees of Promoter &amp; Non-Promoter Group</li><li>The special resolution was passed by the shareholders of the company in the general meeting dated January 07, 2025</li><li>In-principal approval received from BSE Limited</li><li>The paid-up equity capital of the Company has increased from Rs. 5,85,06,000/- to Rs. 5,99,06,000/</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cb7cbeb1-2e6d-4248-a071-49abfee32216.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Continental Securities Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ALNATRD] Alna Trading &amp; Exports Ltd Appoints Ms. Amita Sachin Karia as Additional Director, Ms. Mala Arun Todarwal Resigns</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ALNA+TRADING+%26+EXPORTS+LTD.&title=Alna+Trading+%26+Exports+Ltd+Appoints+Ms.+Amita+Sachin+Karia+as+Additional+Director%2C+Ms.+Mala+Arun+Todarwal+Resigns&newsId=f88392c0-66bc-40ff-a4a2-a612a0d45e28&token=Zjg4MzkyYzAtNjZi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f88392c0-66bc-40ff-a4a2-a612a0d45e28</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Alna Trading &amp; Exports Ltd has appointed Ms. Amita Sachin Karia as an Additional Director (Non-Executive &amp; Independent) for a term of five years, subject to the approval of the shareholders. The appointment is in compliance with the applicable provisions of the Companies Act, 2013, and the SEBI LODR Regulations, 2015. The company also announced the resignation of Ms. Mala Arun Todarwal from the position of Independent Director due to pre-occupation and other professional commitments.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Ms. Amita Sachin Karia as an Additional Director (Non-Executive &amp; Independent) of Alna Trading &amp; Exports Ltd.</li><li>Ms. Amita Sachin Karia appointed for a term of five (5) consecutive years.</li><li>Resignation of Ms. Mala Arun Todarwal from the position of Independent Director due to pre-occupation and other professional commitments.</li><li>Ms. Mala Arun Todarwal ceased to be a member/chairperson of all the Board Committees.</li><li>The Board placed on record its sincere appreciation for the valuable contributions made by Ms. Mala Arun Todarwal during her tenure as an Independent Director.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/13326062-a921-4868-81d8-609b5680bbd5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ALNA TRADING & EXPORTS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ALNATRD] Alna Trading &amp; Exports Ltd Appoints New Independent Director, Ms. Amita Sachin Karia</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ALNA+TRADING+%26+EXPORTS+LTD.&title=Alna+Trading+%26+Exports+Ltd+Appoints+New+Independent+Director%2C+Ms.+Amita+Sachin+Karia&newsId=b8562a3e-db71-450c-9575-2c4aef03014d&token=Yjg1NjJhM2UtZGI3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8562a3e-db71-450c-9575-2c4aef03014d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:22:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Appointments &amp; Resignations</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Alna Trading &amp; Exports Ltd, a company based in Mumbai, Maharashtra, has announced the appointment of Ms. Amita Sachin Karia as an Additional Director (Non-Executive &amp; Independent) and the resignation of Ms. Mala Arun Todarwal from the position of Independent Director. Ms. Karia&apos;s appointment is subject to the approval of the shareholders of the Company at the ensuing General Meeting. Ms. Todarwal has resigned due to pre-occupation and other professional commitments.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Ms. Amita Sachin Karia as an Additional Director (Non-Executive &amp; Independent)</li><li>Ms. Karia&apos;s appointment is subject to the approval of shareholders at the ensuing General Meeting</li><li>Resignation of Ms. Mala Arun Todarwal from the position of Independent Director</li><li>Ms. Todarwal&apos;s resignation is due to pre-occupation and other professional commitments</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b0b8778c-5ef5-4ce5-9729-37863942fb4d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ALNA TRADING & EXPORTS LTD. | Category: Appointments & Resignations</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ALNATRD] Alna Trading &amp; Exports Ltd: Appointment of Ms. Amita Sachin Karia as Additional Director and Resignation of Ms. Mala Arun Todarwal as Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ALNA+TRADING+%26+EXPORTS+LTD.&title=Alna+Trading+%26+Exports+Ltd%3A+Appointment+of+Ms.+Amita+Sachin+Karia+as+Additional+Director+and+Resignation+of+Ms.+Mala+Arun+Todarwal+as+Independent+Director&newsId=2cb8a8fa-ba13-4e3e-b4b0-04b9a0f57109&token=MmNiOGE4ZmEtYmEx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2cb8a8fa-ba13-4e3e-b4b0-04b9a0f57109</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:22:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Alna Trading &amp; Exports Ltd announced the appointment of Ms. Amita Sachin Karia as an Additional Director (Non-Executive &amp; Independent) and the resignation of Ms. Mala Arun Todarwal from the position of Independent Director due to pre-occupation and other professional commitments. Ms. Karia&apos;s appointment is subject to the approval of the shareholders at the ensuing General Meeting, while Ms. Todarwal ceased to be a member/chairperson of all the Board Committees in which she was a member/chairperson.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Ms. Amita Sachin Karia as Additional Director (Non-Executive &amp; Independent)</li><li>Resignation of Ms. Mala Arun Todarwal from the position of Independent Director</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/20e582a5-61fa-4ebd-b868-654510a2d708.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ALNA TRADING & EXPORTS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SIMANDHAR] Simandhar Impex Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine-Month Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Simandhar+Impex+Ltd&title=Simandhar+Impex+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine-Month+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=34951e6c-870c-4231-a5ac-ce478ee38094&token=MzQ5NTFlNmMtODcw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">34951e6c-870c-4231-a5ac-ce478ee38094</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:22:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Simandhar Impex Ltd has announced its un-audited standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The meeting of the Board of Directors was held on 31st January 2026, where the results were approved. The company&apos;s financial statements and the independent auditor’s review report were submitted to the board.</p><ul><li>Simandhar Impex Ltd reported its un-audited standalone financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s results were approved in a Board of Directors meeting on 31st January 2026.</li><li>Bohara Shah &amp; Co., Chartered Accountants, submitted the independent auditor’s review report on the company&apos;s financial results.</li><li>The review was conducted in accordance with the Standard on Review Engagement (SRE) 2410 issued by the Institute of Chartered Accountants of India.</li><li>The financial results were prepared in accordance with the recognition and measurement principles laid down in Indian Accounting Standard 34 (Ind AS - 34).</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/846f45d1-c429-4e3f-a76c-bd62cc0354ec.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Simandhar Impex Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>