<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 21:15:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[OROSMITHS] Orosil Smiths India Ltd. to Approve Un-audited Financial Results for Q3 2025 on Feb 06, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=OROSIL+SMITHS+INDIA+LTD.-%24&title=Orosil+Smiths+India+Ltd.+to+Approve+Un-audited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+2025+on+Feb+06%2C+2026&newsId=1bef2c9b-2857-47ae-9f90-c5667329c84e&token=MWJlZjJjOWItMjg1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1bef2c9b-2857-47ae-9f90-c5667329c84e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 17:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Orosil Smiths India Ltd. has informed the BSE that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on February 06, 2026. The agenda includes the consideration and approval of the Un-audited Financial Results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, as per the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The Statutory Auditors&apos; Limited Review Report(s) will also be noted during the meeting.</p><ul><li>Orosil Smiths India Ltd. to consider and approve Un-audited Financial Results for Q3 2025</li><li>Meeting of the Board of Directors scheduled on February 06, 2026</li><li>Consideration of the Un-audited Financial Results in accordance with SEBI Regulations</li><li>Statutory Auditors&apos; Limited Review Report(s) to be noted</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/39920e21-ca6f-4ebc-9620-671eba44ecdc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: OROSIL SMITHS INDIA LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INSECTICID] Insecticides (India) Ltd: Promoters Acquire 67.65% Shares via Off-market Transfer by Way of Gift</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INSECTICIDES+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Insecticides+%28India%29+Ltd%3A+Promoters+Acquire+67.65%25+Shares+via+Off-market+Transfer+by+Way+of+Gift&newsId=bbf13bbc-38b8-4988-b7ec-b191421d31f3&token=YmJmMTNiYmMtMzhi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bbf13bbc-38b8-4988-b7ec-b191421d31f3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 17:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Insecticides (India) Ltd has received intimations from promoters and promoter group about the acquisition of 1,96,83,052 (67.65%) equity shares via Off-market transfer by way of Gift having NIL Value from promoter and promoter group. The acquisition is a private family arrangement and a non-commercial transaction for smooth succession planning of the promoter’s family and to streamline the promoter’s family assets and businesses. The acquirers include Hari Chand Aggarwal, Rajesh Kumar Aggarwal, Nikunj Aggarwal, Sanskar Aggarwal, Pushpa Aggarwal, and Kritika Gupta.</p><ul><li>Insecticides (India) Ltd promoters acquire 67.65% shares</li><li>Acquisition is a private family arrangement and non-commercial transaction</li><li>Transaction is for smooth succession planning and to streamline promoter’s family assets and businesses</li><li>Acquirers include Hari Chand Aggarwal, Rajesh Kumar Aggarwal, Nikunj Aggarwal, Sanskar Aggarwal, Pushpa Aggarwal, and Kritika Gupta</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/89DA7CD2_7455_43C7_9897_3CDB7B7D004E_153421.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INSECTICIDES (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BURNPUR] Burnpur Cement Ltd Seeks No-Objection for Promoter to Public Category Reclassification</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BURNPUR+CEMENT+LTD.&title=Burnpur+Cement+Ltd+Seeks+No-Objection+for+Promoter+to+Public+Category+Reclassification&newsId=80abe8bc-2428-40fe-ab1c-cf132f25d389&token=ODBhYmU4YmMtMjQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80abe8bc-2428-40fe-ab1c-cf132f25d389</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 17:48:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Burnpur Cement Ltd has submitted an application with BSE Limited for seeking no-objection from the stock exchange for reclassification of two promoters from the &apos;promoter/promoter group&apos; category to the &apos;public&apos; category. The two promoters in question are Shehul Sandip Parikh and Rakhi Parikh, both currently holding 0% of the company&apos;s equity shares. This action is in compliance with Regulation 31A (8) of the SEBI (LODR) Regulation, 2015.</p><ul><li>Burnpur Cement Ltd seeks no-objection for promoter reclassification</li><li>Shehul Sandip Parikh and Rakhi Parikh to be reclassified from &apos;promoter/promoter group&apos; to &apos;public&apos; category</li><li>Both promoters currently hold 0% of the company&apos;s equity shares</li><li>Application submitted to BSE Limited</li><li>In compliance with Regulation 31A (8) of the SEBI (LODR) Regulation, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c8298516-d16b-4418-8fda-fce45758f1a3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BURNPUR CEMENT LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JSFB] Jana Small Finance Bank to Approve Q4 2025 Results on Feb 6, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jana+Small+Finance+Bank+Ltd&title=Jana+Small+Finance+Bank+to+Approve+Q4+2025+Results+on+Feb+6%2C+2026&newsId=13ea7179-4b44-4b74-9263-d915fa76c4f8&token=MTNlYTcxNzktNGI0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13ea7179-4b44-4b74-9263-d915fa76c4f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 17:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jana Small Finance Bank Ltd has announced a meeting of its Board of Directors on February 6, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the Bank has been closed from January 1, 2026, to February 8, 2026, for all Directors and designated employees.</p><ul><li>Jana Small Finance Bank to approve Q4 2025 results on Feb 6, 2026</li><li>Trading window closed for Directors and designated employees from Jan 1, 2026, to Feb 8, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/61f7afe8-4373-4520-a8a4-99106154a84a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jana Small Finance Bank Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADVIKCA] Advik Capital Ltd. Announces Q3 2025 Financial Results and Board Meeting Updates</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Advik+Capital+Ltd&title=Advik+Capital+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+2025+Financial+Results+and+Board+Meeting+Updates&newsId=bc7133e9-0f8d-454c-9ad4-96bfc5682931&token=YmM3MTMzZTktMGY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc7133e9-0f8d-454c-9ad4-96bfc5682931</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 17:47:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Advik Capital Ltd. announced the outcomes of their board meeting held on January 24, 2026. The board approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, along with the reconstitution of various committees. The company&apos;s revenue from operations for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, was INR 282.97 Lakhs, down from INR 1,280.39 Lakhs in the same period last year. The net profit for the quarter was INR (2,087.33) Lakhs, compared to INR 734.74 Lakhs in the same period last year. The board also approved the presentation of transactions relating to the sale and purchase of shares and securities on a net basis, in line with the requirements of Ind AS 109.</p><ul><li>Advik Capital Ltd. announced the outcomes of their board meeting held on January 24, 2026.</li><li>The board approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue from operations for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, was INR 282.97 Lakhs.</li><li>The net profit for the quarter was INR (2,087.33) Lakhs.</li><li>The board approved the presentation of transactions relating to the sale and purchase of shares and securities on a net basis.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3633650e-93ad-4d9e-bac2-ec1506c7b029.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Advik Capital Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KIRLPNU] Kirloskar Pneumatic Provisional Winner in 4th Round of PLI Scheme for White Goods</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KIRLOSKAR+PNEUMATIC+CO.LTD.&title=Kirloskar+Pneumatic+Provisional+Winner+in+4th+Round+of+PLI+Scheme+for+White+Goods&newsId=b224650e-0f9d-48c7-b26c-0a5a70da163e&token=YjIyNDY1MGUtMGY5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b224650e-0f9d-48c7-b26c-0a5a70da163e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 17:47:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Kirloskar Pneumatic Company Limited has been provisionally selected in the 4th Round of the Production-Linked Incentive (PLI) Scheme for White Goods by the Ministry of Commerce and Industry. The company is expected to achieve a total production of ₹8,337.24 crore and generate 1,799 additional direct jobs by FY 2027-28. The PLI Scheme for White Goods aims to create a robust domestic component ecosystem for the Air Conditioners and LED Lights industry and position India as an integral part of the global supply chains. The scheme offers incentives ranging from 6% to 4% on a reducing basis on incremental sales for a period of five years.</p><ul><li>Kirloskar Pneumatic provisionally selected in 4th Round of PLI Scheme for White Goods</li><li>Committed investment of ₹320 crore</li><li>Expected production of ₹8,337.24 crore by FY 2027-28</li><li>Generation of 1,799 additional direct jobs</li><li>PLI Scheme aims to create a robust domestic component ecosystem for the Air Conditioners and LED Lights industry</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f6624c35-c2b7-4430-96c4-e0f896735649.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KIRLOSKAR PNEUMATIC CO.LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RMDRIP] R M Drip and Sprinklers Systems Ltd to Approve Q4 2025 Financial Results on Jan 29, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=R+M+Drip+and+Sprinklers+Systems+Ltd&title=R+M+Drip+and+Sprinklers+Systems+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+2025+Financial+Results+on+Jan+29%2C+2026&newsId=93d31c4f-7f13-49b0-b863-220385affddd&token=OTNkMzFjNGYtN2Yx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93d31c4f-7f13-49b0-b863-220385affddd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 17:47:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>R M Drip and Sprinklers Systems Ltd has scheduled a Board of Directors meeting on 29th January 2026 to consider and approve the unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The meeting will also cover any other business as specified in the agenda. The trading window for dealing in the equity shares of the company is closed for all designated persons, their immediate relatives, and other connected persons until 48 hours after the declaration of the aforesaid financial results.</p><ul><li>R M Drip and Sprinklers Systems Ltd to consider and approve the unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q4 2025</li><li>Board of Directors meeting scheduled on 29th January 2026</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the equity shares of the company is closed for all designated persons, their immediate relatives, and other connected persons</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/24bd9568-dbc9-43c0-84e2-36d4e98b7185.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: R M Drip and Sprinklers Systems Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VAKRANGEE] Vakrangee Ltd. Announces Q3 and 9M Financial Results for 2025, Appoints New CFO</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vakrangee+Limited-%24&title=Vakrangee+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+9M+Financial+Results+for+2025%2C+Appoints+New+CFO&newsId=b54a3f05-1fa2-4871-8545-798ce001bec9&token=YjU0YTNmMDUtMWZh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b54a3f05-1fa2-4871-8545-798ce001bec9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 17:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vakrangee Ltd. announced the outcome of its Board Meeting held on January 24, 2026. The company reported its un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at INR 4,855.76 lakhs for the quarter and INR 13,911.31 lakhs for the nine months. The Board also approved the appointment of Mr. Aditya Jani as the Chief Financial Officer (CFO) and Key Managerial Personnel (KMP) of the company with effect from January 24, 2026.</p><ul><li>Vakrangee Ltd. reported its un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 and 9M ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at INR 4,855.76 lakhs for the quarter and INR 13,911.31 lakhs for the nine months.</li><li>The Board approved the appointment of Mr. Aditya Jani as the Chief Financial Officer (CFO) and Key Managerial Personnel (KMP) of the company.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6e0e6672-4619-4ca2-9bbd-c56fdd553136.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vakrangee Limited-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MANGLMCEM] Mangalam Cement Ltd. to Approve Un-audited Standalone Financial Results for Q3 &amp; 9M on Feb 6, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MANGALAM+CEMENT+LTD.&title=Mangalam+Cement+Ltd.+to+Approve+Un-audited+Standalone+Financial+Results+for+Q3+%26+9M+on+Feb+6%2C+2026&newsId=bd2ae541-38c6-4536-bb5b-1a716022cac1&token=YmQyYWU1NDEtMzhj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd2ae541-38c6-4536-bb5b-1a716022cac1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 17:45:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mangalam Cement Ltd. has informed the BSE that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on 6th February 2026. The meeting will consider and approve the Un-audited Standalone Financial Results of the Company for the 3rd Quarter and 9th Months ended on 31st December 2025. The trading window for dealing securities of the Company will be closed for 48 hours after the results are made public.</p><ul><li>Mangalam Cement Ltd. to consider and approve Un-audited Standalone Financial Results for Q3 &amp; 9M 2025-2026.</li><li>Trading window for dealing securities of the Company to be closed for 48 hours after the results are made public.</li><li>Meeting of the Board of Directors scheduled on 6th February 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/38f66da2-7e13-4780-bcc2-dce415792722.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MANGALAM CEMENT LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ALFATRAN] Alfa Transformers Ltd to Consider and Approve Q4 2025 Results on 31st January 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ALFA+TRANSFORMERS+LTD.&title=Alfa+Transformers+Ltd+to+Consider+and+Approve+Q4+2025+Results+on+31st+January+2026&newsId=21eef1e2-edf8-461c-8683-5f4154a529d5&token=MjFlZWYxZTItZWRm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21eef1e2-edf8-461c-8683-5f4154a529d5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 17:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Alfa Transformers Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 31st January 2026 to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The meeting will also discuss potential fund raising through right issue and/or preferential allotment.</p><ul><li>Alfa Transformers Ltd to consider and approve Q4 2025 results on 31st January 2026</li><li>The meeting will also discuss potential fund raising through right issue and/or preferential allotment</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6da5c51f-db10-42e1-88d9-1a40ef2a6ee3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ALFA TRANSFORMERS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>