<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:51:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[APOLLOFI] Apollo Finvest India Ltd Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=APOLLO+FINVEST+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Apollo+Finvest+India+Ltd+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=51aa2e8f-076b-4fb8-8f16-d8df1c8e6b67&token=NTFhYTJlOGYtMDc2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">51aa2e8f-076b-4fb8-8f16-d8df1c8e6b67</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Apollo Finvest India Ltd announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s profit before tax stands at INR 15.77 crores, and the profit after tax is INR 16.54 crores. The earnings per equity share (of 210 each) are INR 4.91 (basic) and INR 4.67 (diluted). The results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Profit before tax for the quarter is INR 15.77 crores.</li><li>Profit after tax for the quarter is INR 16.54 crores.</li><li>Earnings per equity share (of 210 each) are INR 4.91 (basic) and INR 4.67 (diluted).</li><li>The results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</li><li>The financial results have been prepared in accordance with the Companies (Indian Accounting Standards) Rules, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cbf34040-dc78-4ecd-9639-a6f75a6a38a2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: APOLLO FINVEST (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ORISSAMINE] Manish Raj Gupta Appointed as Non-Executive Chairman of Orissa Minerals Development Company Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ORISSA+MINERALS+DEVELOPMENT+COMPANY+LTD.&title=Manish+Raj+Gupta+Appointed+as+Non-Executive+Chairman+of+Orissa+Minerals+Development+Company+Ltd&newsId=c75a59ee-8efb-482e-8e53-93625aedc7fe&token=Yzc1YTU5ZWUtOGVm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c75a59ee-8efb-482e-8e53-93625aedc7fe</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:47:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Orissa Minerals Development Company Ltd has appointed Manish Raj Gupta as its Non-Executive Chairman. Gupta, who is currently the CMD (additional charge) at Rashtriya Ispat Nigam Limited (RINL), will replace AK Saxena. Gupta is a seasoned professional with over three decades of experience in the steel industry. He has served in various roles at Steel Authority of India Limited (SAIL) and RINL, demonstrating strong leadership and technical expertise. Gupta&apos;s appointment is in compliance with the Companies Act, 2013 and SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Manish Raj Gupta appointed as Non-Executive Chairman of Orissa Minerals Development Company Ltd</li><li>Gupta replaces AK Saxena as Chairman</li><li>Gupta is a seasoned professional with over three decades of experience in the steel industry</li><li>Appointment is in compliance with the Companies Act, 2013 and SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Gupta is currently the CMD (additional charge) at Rashtriya Ispat Nigam Limited (RINL)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/42599880-6e98-4a1b-9ada-6c6469fbf2d9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ORISSA MINERALS DEVELOPMENT COMPANY LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SKFINDUS] SKF India Appoints Ms. Deeksha Hapawat as Interim Head — Legal, Secretarial &amp; Corporate Affairs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SKF+India+%28Industrial%29+Ltd&title=SKF+India+Appoints+Ms.+Deeksha+Hapawat+as+Interim+Head+%E2%80%94+Legal%2C+Secretarial+%26+Corporate+Affairs&newsId=0022a454-14be-47ee-afd2-fb31eb23c7fe&token=MDAyMmE0NTQtMTRi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0022a454-14be-47ee-afd2-fb31eb23c7fe</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:41:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SKF India has announced the appointment of Ms. Deeksha Hapawat as the Interim Head — Legal, Secretarial &amp; Corporate Affairs, replacing Mr. Ranjan Kumar who resigned to pursue an external opportunity. Ms. Hapawat, an experienced legal professional with over 16 years of combined experience, will take up her new role from February 03, 2026. She holds LLB and LLM degrees from National Law University, Jodhpur and University of Rajasthan respectively, and has a strong focus on Contracts, Commercial Litigation, Compliance, Corporate Governance, Employment laws, Policy Advocacy, and general business advisory.</p><ul><li>SKF India announces the appointment of Ms. Deeksha Hapawat as Interim Head — Legal, Secretarial &amp; Corporate Affairs</li><li>Ms. Hapawat will replace Mr. Ranjan Kumar who resigned to pursue an external opportunity</li><li>Ms. Hapawat holds LLB and LLM degrees from National Law University, Jodhpur and University of Rajasthan</li><li>She has over 16 years of combined experience in legal sector</li><li>Her areas of specialization include Contracts, Commercial Litigation, Compliance, Corporate Governance, Employment laws, Policy Advocacy, and general business advisory</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e6b0bf52-ebff-480e-971c-411f5a248e15.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SKF India (Industrial) Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RCL] Radhagobind Commercial Ltd Holds 3rd COC Meeting on 05-02-2026: Discusses CIRP Progress, Forensic Auditors Appointment, and More</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Radhagobind+Commercial+Ltd&title=Radhagobind+Commercial+Ltd+Holds+3rd+COC+Meeting+on+05-02-2026%3A+Discusses+CIRP+Progress%2C+Forensic+Auditors+Appointment%2C+and+More&newsId=acda9795-e4a9-4950-a08c-1a25a857265c&token=YWNkYTk3OTUtZTRh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">acda9795-e4a9-4950-a08c-1a25a857265c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Radhagobind Commercial Ltd (formerly Tejmangal Commercial Company Limited) held its 3rd Committee of Creditors (COC) meeting on 05-02-2026. The meeting, chaired by the Interim Resolution Professional (IRP) Mr. Najeeb TP, discussed the progress on the Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP), appointment of Forensic Auditors, reconstitution of the CoC, status issuance of Form G, Income Tax appeal, and more. The meeting also ratified CIRP Cost incurred by the IRP and contributed by the Applicants. The company&apos;s registered and corporate offices are in Kolkata and Ernakulam, respectively.</p><ul><li>Radhagobind Commercial Ltd held its 3rd COC meeting on 05-02-2026.</li><li>The meeting was chaired by the Interim Resolution Professional (IRP) Mr. Najeeb TP.</li><li>The progress on the Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP) and various related matters were discussed.</li><li>The appointment of Forensic Auditors and reconstitution of the CoC were updated.</li><li>The meeting ratified CIRP Cost incurred by the IRP and contributed by the Applicants.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4d8cf0d8-a174-40c1-86ca-f68f55058d7c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Radhagobind Commercial Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LLOYDSME] Lloyds Metals and Energy Ltd: No Deviation from Objects in Q4 2025 Monitoring Agency Report</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LLOYDS+METALS+AND+ENERGY+LTD.&title=Lloyds+Metals+and+Energy+Ltd%3A+No+Deviation+from+Objects+in+Q4+2025+Monitoring+Agency+Report&newsId=23c94555-6724-4e5a-b355-02670d28e886&token=MjNjOTQ1NTUtNjcy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23c94555-6724-4e5a-b355-02670d28e886</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:27:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Lloyds Metals and Energy Ltd, a manufacturing and mining company, has received a clean chit from India Ratings &amp; Research Private Limited for the quarter ended 31st December, 2025. The Monitoring Agency Report, issued pursuant to Regulation 162A(2) of the SEBI ICDR Regulations, states that there has been no deviation from the objects as per the Management undertaking and the Statutory Auditor Certificate. The report also mentions that all Government/Statutory approvals related to the object(s) have been obtained and all arrangements pertaining to technical assistance/collaboration are in operation.</p><ul><li>No deviation from the objects as per the Management undertaking and the Statutory Auditor Certificate</li><li>All Government/Statutory approvals related to the object(s) have been obtained</li><li>All arrangements pertaining to technical assistance/collaboration are in operation</li><li>No major deviations observed over the earlier monitoring agency reports</li><li>No unfavorable events affecting the viability of the object(s)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f8fdb8b6-9f36-48cd-834f-1fa96c2dd28d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LLOYDS METALS AND ENERGY LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SKFINDUS] SKF India (Industrial) Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Month Results for 2025, Announces New Factory and Personnel Changes</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SKF+India+%28Industrial%29+Ltd&title=SKF+India+%28Industrial%29+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Month+Results+for+2025%2C+Announces+New+Factory+and+Personnel+Changes&newsId=19321ff2-227c-4314-88f6-b7d1ec8f240d&token=MTkzMjFmZjItMjI3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19321ff2-227c-4314-88f6-b7d1ec8f240d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:12:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SKF India (Industrial) Ltd has reported its unaudited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The Board approved the results, which were prepared in accordance with Ind AS 34 and other accounting principles generally accepted in India. The company announced the resignation of Mr. Ranjan Kumar as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer, and the appointment of Ms. Poorva Bang and Ms. Deeksha Hapawat as Company Secretary, Compliance Officer, and Interim Head of Legal, Secretarial, and Corporate Affairs, respectively. Additionally, the Board approved the setting up of a new factory in Pune, Maharashtra.</p><ul><li>SKF India (Industrial) Ltd reported Q3 and nine-month results for 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s financial results were prepared in accordance with Ind AS 34 and other accounting principles generally accepted in India.</li><li>Mr. Ranjan Kumar resigned as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer, while Ms. Poorva Bang and Ms. Deeksha Hapawat were appointed as Company Secretary, Compliance Officer, and Interim Head of Legal, Secretarial, and Corporate Affairs.</li><li>The Board approved the setting up of a new factory in Pune, Maharashtra.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e3515f2f-9d6b-4bae-a34b-276aa489d30e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SKF India (Industrial) Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[POONAWALLA] Poonawalla Fincorp Ltd Receives RBI Approval for Factoring Business</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Poonawalla+Fincorp+Ltd&title=Poonawalla+Fincorp+Ltd+Receives+RBI+Approval+for+Factoring+Business&newsId=39115f9d-0120-4fa6-b445-98e7c5e6c86f&token=MzkxMTVmOWQtMDEy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">39115f9d-0120-4fa6-b445-98e7c5e6c86f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Poonawalla Fincorp Ltd has announced that it has received approval from the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) to commence and carry on the factoring business. The approval was received on February 03, 2026, and permits the company to operate under the terms and conditions of the Bank&apos;s notification DOR.FIN.080/CGM(JPS) - 2022 dated January 14, 2022, on &apos;Registration of Factors (Reserve Bank) Regulations, 2022.&apos;</p><ul><li>Poonawalla Fincorp Ltd receives approval from RBI for factoring business</li><li>The approval allows the company to commence and carry on factoring business</li><li>The company is required to comply with the terms and conditions of the RBI&apos;s notification</li><li>The approval is in accordance with the Bank&apos;s notification DOR.FIN.080/CGM(JPS) - 2022 dated January 14, 2022</li><li>The factoring business is subject to the Registration of Factors (Reserve Bank) Regulations, 2022</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/386a4d24-ecb4-4539-8f11-b0f6d470b087.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Poonawalla Fincorp Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IREDA] Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency Ltd to Raise Funds Up to 32,994 Crore Through QIP</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Indian+Renewable+Energy+Development+Agency+Ltd&title=Indian+Renewable+Energy+Development+Agency+Ltd+to+Raise+Funds+Up+to+32%2C994+Crore+Through+QIP&newsId=dcdacc5b-1b60-48aa-a968-4350b5d11455&token=ZGNkYWNjNWItMWI2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dcdacc5b-1b60-48aa-a968-4350b5d11455</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency Ltd has announced that a Board of Directors meeting is scheduled for February 06, 2026, to consider and approve raising of funds up to 32,994 Crore through a qualified institutions placement (QIP). The decision is subject to approval from shareholders and necessary regulatory authorities. The company will also convene a postal ballot to seek shareholder approval for the aforementioned matter.</p><ul><li>Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency Ltd plans to raise funds up to 32,994 Crore through QIP</li><li>The fundraising is subject to approval from shareholders and regulatory authorities</li><li>The company will host the information on their website: www.ireda.in</li><li>Trading Window for dealings in the Company’s securities is closed with immediate effect till 48 hours after the conclusion of the board meeting</li><li>A postal ballot will be conducted to seek shareholder approval for the proposed fundraising</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0ed2c167-bda7-4b7f-8118-d17e5cdfd57d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NAZARA] Nazara Technologies Ltd: No Deviation in Utilization of Preferential Issue Proceeds as per Monitoring Agency Report</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Nazara+Technologies+Ltd&title=Nazara+Technologies+Ltd%3A+No+Deviation+in+Utilization+of+Preferential+Issue+Proceeds+as+per+Monitoring+Agency+Report&newsId=b637f625-3ba4-43cb-aa73-ee11b6af0749&token=YjYzN2Y2MjUtM2Jh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b637f625-3ba4-43cb-aa73-ee11b6af0749</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Nazara Technologies Ltd, a software company, has not deviated from the objects of its preferential issue as per the Monitoring Agency Report by ICRA Limited for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The utilization of the issuance proceeds is in line with the objects of the issue. The Monitoring Agency report does not constitute a commentary on the quality of the objects of the issue, appropriateness or reasonableness of costs or spending by Nazara Technologies Limited against any objects / heads or assurance on outcome of such spending.</p><ul><li>Nazara Technologies Ltd has not deviated from the objects of its preferential issue as per the Monitoring Agency Report by ICRA Limited</li><li>The utilization of the issuance proceeds is in line with the objects of the issue</li><li>The Monitoring Agency report does not constitute a commentary on the quality of the objects of the issue</li><li>No deviation observed in the utilization of the issuance proceeds</li><li>The Monitoring Agency report is prepared as per SEBI (Issue of Capital and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1375a518-3d56-4be6-a1d7-ca538ec45e3d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Nazara Technologies Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IREDA] Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency Ltd to Raise 32,994 Crore Through QIP</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Indian+Renewable+Energy+Development+Agency+Ltd&title=Indian+Renewable+Energy+Development+Agency+Ltd+to+Raise+32%2C994+Crore+Through+QIP&newsId=cd1d8f7a-d8e2-428d-89d1-4ebe9f620422&token=Y2QxZDhmN2EtZDhl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd1d8f7a-d8e2-428d-89d1-4ebe9f620422</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency Ltd has announced the closure of its trading window in accordance with the SEBI LODR Regulations. The Board of Directors will meet on February 06, 2026, to consider and approve the raising of funds through the issuance of equity shares by way of a qualified institutions placement (QIP) for an amount aggregating up to 32,994 Crore. The decision is subject to approval from the shareholders of the Company and any necessary governmental/regulatory/statutory authorities. A postal ballot will be convened to seek approval from the shareholders. The trading window will remain closed 48 hours after the conclusion of the board meeting.</p><ul><li>Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency Ltd to raise 32,994 Crore through QIP</li><li>Trading window closed till 48 hours after the board meeting</li><li>Funds to be raised through equity shares by way of a QIP</li><li>Approval sought from shareholders and necessary authorities</li><li>Postal ballot to be convened for shareholder approval</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/44f995fe-3966-4993-9e6d-c363de68cf5c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>