<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:55:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ERIS] Eris Lifesciences Partners with Natco Pharma for Semaglutide Launch in India</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Eris+Lifesciences+Ltd&title=Eris+Lifesciences+Partners+with+Natco+Pharma+for+Semaglutide+Launch+in+India&newsId=841216d5-818b-4d05-a661-00ddd3519c1b&token=ODQxMjE2ZDUtODE4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">841216d5-818b-4d05-a661-00ddd3519c1b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:52:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Eris Lifesciences, a leading Indian branded formulations company, has announced a strategic partnership with Natco Pharma Limited for the commercialisation of Semaglutide in India. Semaglutide, a GLP-1 receptor agonist, has emerged globally as a transformative therapy in the management of Type 2 diabetes and chronic weight management. Eris has built a strong presence in diabetology and the addition of semaglutide is expected to further strengthen its portfolio in advanced diabetes therapies. The product will target Type 2 diabetes management aligning with unmet needs in India’s expanding metabolic care landscape. The launch is expected in March 2026, subject to regulatory approvals and other factors.</p><ul><li>Eris Lifesciences and Natco Pharma announce strategic partnership for Semaglutide launch in India</li><li>Semaglutide is a transformative therapy in Type 2 diabetes and chronic weight management</li><li>Eris has a strong presence in diabetology and the addition of semaglutide is expected to strengthen its portfolio</li><li>Product will target Type 2 diabetes management in India&apos;s expanding metabolic care landscape</li><li>Launch expected in March 2026, subject to regulatory approvals and other factors</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ada5a8cc-9e4f-4b91-8109-529e4d9f2f06.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Eris Lifesciences Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CAPPL] Caplin Steriles Limited Receives USFDA Approval for Sodium Phosphates Injection USP</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CAPLIN+POINT+LABORATORIES+LTD.&title=Caplin+Steriles+Limited+Receives+USFDA+Approval+for+Sodium+Phosphates+Injection+USP&newsId=ae3514f6-c074-44c3-89a0-925f0d9f09eb&token=YWUzNTE0ZjYtYzA3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae3514f6-c074-44c3-89a0-925f0d9f09eb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:49:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>USFDA</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Caplin Steriles Limited, a subsidiary of Caplin Point Laboratories Limited, has received final approval from the USFDA for its Abbreviated New Drug Application (ANDA) Sodium Phosphates Injection USP, 15mM P/5mL, 45mM P/15mL and 150mM P/50mL (3mM P/mL) Single-Dose Vials. This generic therapeutic equivalent version of the Reference Listed Drug (RLD) from Hospira, Inc., USA (NDA 018892) is indicated as a source of phosphorus and for addition to large volume intravenous fluids. The product had total US sales of approximately $67 million for the 12-month period ending December 2025.</p><ul><li>Caplin Steriles Limited receives final approval from the USFDA for Sodium Phosphates Injection USP</li><li>Product is a generic therapeutic equivalent version of the Reference Listed Drug (RLD) from Hospira, Inc., USA (NDA 018892)</li><li>Indicated as a source of phosphorus and for addition to large volume intravenous fluids</li><li>Total US sales of approximately $67 million for the 12-month period ending December 2025</li><li>Caplin Steriles Limited is a subsidiary of Caplin Point Laboratories Limited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0bf66511-5a8f-4f33-a8b5-bb994bb2cc0f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CAPLIN POINT LABORATORIES LTD. | Category: USFDA</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KOCL] Kome-On Communication Ltd Reports Q2 and H1 Financial Results for FY 2023-2024</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kome-On+Communication+Ltd&title=Kome-On+Communication+Ltd+Reports+Q2+and+H1+Financial+Results+for+FY+2023-2024&newsId=4c40aa13-ee5e-45b1-a386-295395a5244b&token=NGM0MGFhMTMtZWU1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4c40aa13-ee5e-45b1-a386-295395a5244b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:48:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Kome-On Communication Ltd has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and half year ended on 30th September, 2023, and the financial statements for the quarterly and year-end for the financial year 2023-2024. The company&apos;s board of directors approved the results in a meeting on 23rd February, 2026. The financial results for the quarter ended on 30th June, 2022, were also reviewed.</p><ul><li>Unaudited financial results for Q2 and H1 FY 2023-2024 announced</li><li>Financial statements for FY 2023-2024 and FY 2024-2025 approved</li><li>Review of financial results for the quarter ended on 30th June, 2022</li><li>Board meeting held on 23rd February, 2026, to approve the results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/88ef35fd-4b2e-4d10-9985-ac1ecbfcf13d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kome-On Communication Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BINNYMILLS] Binny Mills Ltd. Approves Allotment of ISIN and Admission in NSDL</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BINNY+MILLS+LTD.&title=Binny+Mills+Ltd.+Approves+Allotment+of+ISIN+and+Admission+in+NSDL&newsId=3c4331c6-96da-43c1-a602-d6eb86c3821e&token=M2M0MzMxYzYtOTZk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3c4331c6-96da-43c1-a602-d6eb86c3821e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Binny Mills Ltd. held a Board meeting on 24th February 2026, where they considered and approved the allotment of ISIN and admission of the company&apos;s securities in the National Securities Depository Limited (NSDL). The meeting was held from 11.30 A.M to 11.52 A.M, and the Board also appointed an RTA for Dematerialization. This information is for your records.</p><ul><li>Binny Mills Ltd. approved the allotment of ISIN for their securities.</li><li>The company&apos;s securities will be admitted in the National Securities Depository Limited (NSDL).</li><li>An RTA for Dematerialization has been appointed by the Board.</li><li>The meeting was held from 11.30 A.M to 11.52 A.M on 24th February 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8d40f6c3-8a58-4fc1-8302-5f6355004e2d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BINNY MILLS LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PROFINC] Ramesh Sawalram Saraogi Sells Shares of Pro Fin Capital Services Ltd, Reducing Holding to 11.32%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PRO+FIN+CAPITAL+SERVICES+LTD.&title=Ramesh+Sawalram+Saraogi+Sells+Shares+of+Pro+Fin+Capital+Services+Ltd%2C+Reducing+Holding+to+11.32%25&newsId=148cb7d9-ee90-4c32-a09b-121d794ccede&token=MTQ4Y2I3ZDktZWU5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">148cb7d9-ee90-4c32-a09b-121d794ccede</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Sale</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ramesh Sawalram Saraogi, a significant shareholder in Pro Fin Capital Services Ltd, has sold 1.40% of the company&apos;s shares, reducing his total holding to 11.32%. The sale, which took place on 23rd February 2026, involved 69,00,000 shares. The shares were sold via open market transaction. Post-sale, the company&apos;s equity share capital remains at Rs. 59,25,94,326.</p><ul><li>Ramesh Sawalram Saraogi sells 1.40% of Pro Fin Capital Services Ltd shares</li><li>Total shares sold: 69,00,000</li><li>Sale value: Open market transaction</li><li>Pre-sale holding: 12.49%</li><li>Post-sale holding: 11.32%</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/25BF0263_E3B2_491D_B97D_3361B0E0E09D_121246.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PRO FIN CAPITAL SERVICES LTD. | Category: Sale</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KOCL] Kome-On Communication Ltd Reports Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months of FY 2023-2024</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kome-On+Communication+Ltd&title=Kome-On+Communication+Ltd+Reports+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+of+FY+2023-2024&newsId=a89bd260-dc6b-4607-a511-ae5857bb8dcc&token=YTg5YmQyNjAtZGM2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a89bd260-dc6b-4607-a511-ae5857bb8dcc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Kome-On Communication Ltd has released its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December, 2023. The results were reviewed by Jitendra Chandulal Mehta &amp; Co., Chartered Accountants. The company&apos;s revenue from operations, expenses, and taxes were reported in accordance with the Indian Accounting Standards 34 and other generally accepted accounting principles in India.</p><ul><li>Unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months of FY 2023-2024 reported</li><li>Reviewed by Jitendra Chandulal Mehta &amp; Co., Chartered Accountants</li><li>Revenue from operations, expenses, and taxes reported in accordance with Indian Accounting Standards 34</li><li>Financial statements for FY 2023-2024 and FY 2024-2025 also approved</li><li>Results include Cost of materials consumed, Purchases of stock-in-trade, Changes In Inventories, Finance Cost, Employee Benefits Expenses, Depreciation and amortisation expense, and Other expenses</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0989a16b-eeb9-4516-b28b-6cb0cccc6861.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kome-On Communication Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ORIENTELEC] Orient Electric Ltd&apos;s CHRO, Aditya Kohli, Resigns After 4 Years</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Orient+Electric+Ltd&title=Orient+Electric+Ltd%27s+CHRO%2C+Aditya+Kohli%2C+Resigns+After+4+Years&newsId=3e3d646e-2fc9-4aa9-881b-88714e4d5b7e&token=M2UzZDY0NmUtMmZj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e3d646e-2fc9-4aa9-881b-88714e4d5b7e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:36:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Orient Electric Ltd&apos;s Chief Human Resources Officer, Aditya Kohli, has resigned from his position to pursue another professional opportunity outside of the company. His last working day will be March 24, 2026. During his tenure, Orient Electric has transformed into a high-performing, people-centric organisation and has been recognised as a Great Place to Work for the seventh consecutive year. Kohli expressed his gratitude to the Board, the leadership team, and his colleagues across Orient Electric and the CKA Birla Group for their trust, support, and partnership throughout his tenure.</p><ul><li>Aditya Kohli, Chief Human Resources Officer of Orient Electric Ltd, has resigned.</li><li>Kohli has decided to pursue another professional opportunity outside of the company.</li><li>His last working day will be March 24, 2026.</li><li>During his tenure, Orient Electric has been recognised as a Great Place to Work for seven consecutive years.</li><li>Kohli expressed his gratitude to the Board, the leadership team, and his colleagues for their support.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5f22f9af-7393-41f3-a78d-8c1b6b0b29d2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Orient Electric Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MEIL] Mangal Electrical Industries Ltd: Chief Operating Officer (EPC) Mr Ramkishan Bairwa Resigns</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Mangal+Electrical+Industries+Ltd&title=Mangal+Electrical+Industries+Ltd%3A+Chief+Operating+Officer+%28EPC%29+Mr+Ramkishan+Bairwa+Resigns&newsId=0df80c98-f003-4073-aa33-aeb6869a0b9f&token=MGRmODBjOTgtZjAw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0df80c98-f003-4073-aa33-aeb6869a0b9f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:36:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mangal Electrical Industries Ltd announced the resignation of its Chief Operating Officer (EPC), Mr Ramkishan Bairwa, due to personal reasons. The resignation was tendered on 23rd February, 2026 at 7:22 PM. The company has disclosed the details as required by the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. Mr Bairwa had been with the company for over 10 years.</p><ul><li>Mangal Electrical Industries Ltd announces the resignation of Mr Ramkishan Bairwa, Chief Operating Officer (EPC)</li><li>Mr Bairwa tendered his resignation on 23rd February, 2026 at 7:22 PM due to personal reasons</li><li>Mr Bairwa had been with the company for over 10 years</li><li>The company has disclosed the details as required by the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/aaedc098-3087-4b8d-b687-1ee8bbadb5b1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Mangal Electrical Industries Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PATINTLOG] Patel Integrated Logistics Ltd. Receives Income Tax Refund of Rs. 3.93 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PATEL+INTEGRATED+LOGISTICS+LTD.-%24&title=Patel+Integrated+Logistics+Ltd.+Receives+Income+Tax+Refund+of+Rs.+3.93+Crores&newsId=5b41afbf-e32d-4ca3-afb8-2ae59742727c&token=NWI0MWFmYmYtZTMy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b41afbf-e32d-4ca3-afb8-2ae59742727c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:25:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Patel Integrated Logistics Ltd. has announced the receipt of an Income Tax refund of Rs. 3.93 Crores. This refund, as per the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, has been deposited in the company&apos;s bank account. This influx of funds is expected to positively impact the company&apos;s financials.</p><ul><li>Patel Integrated Logistics Ltd. has received an Income Tax refund of Rs. 3.93 Crores.</li><li>The refund has been deposited in the company&apos;s bank account.</li><li>This refund is expected to positively impact the company&apos;s financials.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d0f27bc4-5294-44aa-8337-cb153f137139.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PATEL INTEGRATED LOGISTICS LTD.-$ | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KESARENT] Kesar Enterprises Ltd. Closes Crushing Operations for Sugar Season 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KESAR+ENTERPRISES+LTD.-%24&title=Kesar+Enterprises+Ltd.+Closes+Crushing+Operations+for+Sugar+Season+2025-26&newsId=18ccca3b-0b01-46d4-93da-6033d22a5171&token=MThjY2NhM2ItMGIw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18ccca3b-0b01-46d4-93da-6033d22a5171</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:22:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kesar Enterprises Ltd. has announced the closure of its crushing operations for the Sugar Season 2025-26 at its sugar factory in Baheri, Uttar Pradesh. This information is shared in accordance with the LODR Regulations, 2015. Kindly note this update.</p><ul><li>Kesar Enterprises Ltd. has closed its crushing operations for the Sugar Season 2025-26</li><li>The closure is announced for the sugar factory located at Baheri, Uttar Pradesh</li><li>This update is shared in accordance with the LODR Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c1f4cd7a-e6e9-440a-992c-e64cfe14f028.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KESAR ENTERPRISES LTD.-$ | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>