<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 12:32:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[IOC] Indian Oil Corporation Ltd Announces Changes in Senior Management Personnel</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDIAN+OIL+CORPORATION+LTD.&title=Indian+Oil+Corporation+Ltd+Announces+Changes+in+Senior+Management+Personnel&newsId=89967917-17e1-4850-90a3-fa1ed9424558&token=ODk5Njc5MTctMTdl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">89967917-17e1-4850-90a3-fa1ed9424558</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 11:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indian Oil Corporation Ltd has announced changes in its senior management personnel. The new appointees include Manas Ranjan Dwibedy, Prakash Abraham, Sanjib Biswas, G R K Murthy, R R Raje, Samarendra Nath Jha, R. Ravichandran, Sarvesh Kumar, and Nitin Bhatnagar. The new executives bring a combined experience of over 300 years in various fields such as Fire &amp; Safety, HR, Industrial Engineering, Mechanical Engineering, Electrical Engineering, Chemical Engineering, and Finance. This move is seen as a strategic move by the company to strengthen its leadership and management.</p><ul><li>Indian Oil Corporation Ltd announces changes in senior management personnel</li><li>Manas Ranjan Dwibedy appointed as Executive Director (H,S&amp;E), Corporate Office</li><li>Prakash Abraham appointed as Executive Director (Employee Relations), Corporate Office</li><li>Sanjib Biswas appointed as Director (MO-LPG), Grade ‘I’ OISD, Noida</li><li>G R K Murthy appointed as Executive Director (Projects), Refineries HQ</li><li>R R Raje appointed as Executive Director (HR), Refineries HQ</li><li>Samarendra Nath Jha appointed as Executive Director (CC &amp; Branding), Corporate Office</li><li>R. Ravichandran appointed as Executive Director (Operations), Marketing Head Office</li><li>Nitin Bhatnagar appointed as Executive Director &amp; State Head, IndianOil AOD State Office</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a0746e31-c766-4cf9-a5ff-e9df7954d7d2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDIAN OIL CORPORATION LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CHCL] Cian Healthcare Ltd to Approve Un-audited Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 and H1 of FY 2025-26 on Jan 14, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Cian+Healthcare+Ltd&title=Cian+Healthcare+Ltd+to+Approve+Un-audited+Consolidated+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+H1+of+FY+2025-26+on+Jan+14%2C+2026&newsId=ec9ff4d0-b411-4e0b-96d3-763cba7d1b8a&token=ZWM5ZmY0ZDAtYjQx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ec9ff4d0-b411-4e0b-96d3-763cba7d1b8a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 10:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cian Healthcare Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 14, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and half year ended on September 30, 2025. The meeting will also approve the Limited Review Reports issued by the Statutory Auditors of the Company, M/s. SS R C A &amp; Co., Chartered Accountants. The company is an ISO 9001:2015 and WHO GMP certified entity, with its registered office in Pune and manufacturing unit in Haridwar, Uttarakhand.</p><ul><li>Cian Healthcare Ltd to approve un-audited Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 and H1 of FY 2025-26 on Jan 14, 2026</li><li>The meeting will also approve the Limited Review Reports issued by the Statutory Auditors of the Company, M/s. SS R C A &amp; Co., Chartered Accountants</li><li>Cian Healthcare Ltd is an ISO 9001:2015 and WHO GMP certified entity</li><li>The company&apos;s registered office is in Pune and manufacturing unit is in Haridwar, Uttarakhand</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5391e11b-fbe6-4379-88ba-4740b6d28b3d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Cian Healthcare Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TRIMURTHI] Novelix Pharmaceuticals Appoints Ms. Sridevi Belide as Non-Executive Non-Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Trimurthi+Ltd&title=Novelix+Pharmaceuticals+Appoints+Ms.+Sridevi+Belide+as+Non-Executive+Non-Independent+Director&newsId=cd077a57-2584-466b-b9df-98e429d83499&token=Y2QwNzdhNTctMjU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd077a57-2584-466b-b9df-98e429d83499</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 10:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Novelix Pharmaceuticals Ltd. has announced the appointment of Ms. Sridevi Belide as a Non-Executive Non-Independent Director. The appointment was approved in an Extra Ordinary General Meeting held on 09th January, 2026. Ms. Belide, a medical professional with an MBBS degree, brings her expertise in healthcare and scientific understanding to corporate leadership. She is not related to any of the directors and is not debarred from holding the office of Director by any SEBI order or any other such authority.</p><ul><li>Ms. Sridevi Belide appointed as Non-Executive Non-Independent Director</li><li>Appointment approved in Extra Ordinary General Meeting on 09th January, 2026</li><li>Ms. Belide is a medical professional with an MBBS degree</li><li>Ms. Belide is not related to any of the directors</li><li>Ms. Belide is not debarred from holding the office of Director by any SEBI order or any other such authority</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/35c562d1-6be6-4f63-ae47-663c09f992ea.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Trimurthi Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BCG] Brightcom Group&apos;s Weekly Update: Insightful Presentation on Digital Advertising Market Structure</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Brightcom+Group+Ltd&title=Brightcom+Group%27s+Weekly+Update%3A+Insightful+Presentation+on+Digital+Advertising+Market+Structure&newsId=b3d61776-c508-4dfe-a015-60d7b99ba1df&token=YjNkNjE3NzYtYzUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3d61776-c508-4dfe-a015-60d7b99ba1df</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 09:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Brightcom Group Ltd. has released the next explanatory presentation in a series, providing background information on the digital advertising market structure, operating mechanisms, and industry context. This presentation is intended solely as reference material and does not contain any forward-looking statements, financial guidance, or projections. The presentation highlights the digital advertising market&apos;s size, its growing significance, and the differences between digital and traditional advertising. The digital advertising market is structured around software platforms and consists of advertisers, brands, publishers, platforms, technology, agencies, and networks that allocate budgets, connect demand and supply, and measure outcomes.</p><ul><li>Digital advertising now represents the majority of global advertising spend.</li><li>Global advertising expenditure has exceeded $1.5 trillion.</li><li>Digital advertising is measurable, addressable, and automated, making it different from traditional media.</li><li>The digital advertising market operates through software platforms and consists of various players such as advertisers, publishers, platforms, technology, agencies, and networks.</li><li>Nearly all incremental growth in advertising is digital.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/df17aae3-33fc-46f0-8e91-6acb07b79675.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Brightcom Group Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SPARC] Sun Pharma Advanced Research Company to Raise Funds and Approve Employee Stock Option Scheme</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SUN+PHARMA+ADVANCED+RESEARCH+COMPANY+LTD.&title=Sun+Pharma+Advanced+Research+Company+to+Raise+Funds+and+Approve+Employee+Stock+Option+Scheme&newsId=a63df017-c49b-4a76-a12a-cad4ad4f9e66&token=YTYzZGYwMTctYzQ5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a63df017-c49b-4a76-a12a-cad4ad4f9e66</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 08:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sun Pharma Advanced Research Company Ltd has informed BSE that the meeting of the Board of Directors of the Company is scheduled on 14/01/2026. The agenda includes considering and approving the proposal for raising funds by the Company through a preferential issue of securities to an identified member of the promoter group. The Company also plans to approve the Employee Stock Option Scheme in terms of Securities and Exchange Board of India (Share Based Employee Benefits and Sweat Equity) Regulations, 2021. The Trading Window for dealing in shares of the Company has been closed effective from January 01, 2026.</p><ul><li>Sun Pharma Advanced Research Company to raise funds through preferential issue of securities</li><li>The funds will be raised from an identified member of the promoter group</li><li>The Company also plans to approve the Employee Stock Option Scheme</li><li>The decision is subject to approval from members of the Company, NSE, and BSE</li><li>Trading Window for dealing in shares of the Company has been closed since January 01, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ec968440-0f0b-4e0b-9ee4-5932039e9fa2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SUN PHARMA ADVANCED RESEARCH COMPANY LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RANEHOLDIN] Rane Steering Systems Receives Order from Income Tax Authority, Chennai with Proposed Downward Adjustment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RANE+HOLDINGS+LTD.&title=Rane+Steering+Systems+Receives+Order+from+Income+Tax+Authority%2C+Chennai+with+Proposed+Downward+Adjustment&newsId=cd534772-d480-4ccb-81e9-8df9d2c00c9c&token=Y2Q1MzQ3NzItZDQ4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd534772-d480-4ccb-81e9-8df9d2c00c9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 07:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rane Steering Systems Private Limited, a wholly owned subsidiary of Rane Holdings Ltd, has received an order from the Office of Deputy Commissioner of Income Tax, Transfer Pricing, Chennai. The order, received on January 10, 2026, pertains to an adjustment on purchase of raw material transaction for Rs. 2.33 Crores for the Assessment Year 2023-24. The proposed adjustment excludes miscellaneous expenses and rates and taxes from the computation of operating margin, which may result in a financial implication of Rs. 0.59 Cr (excluding applicable interest and penalty, if any). Rane Steering Systems is currently in consultation with its consultants and tax advisors, and plans to contest the order before the appropriate authority.</p><ul><li>Rane Steering Systems Private Limited received an order from the Office of Deputy Commissioner of Income Tax, Transfer Pricing, Chennai</li><li>The order pertains to an adjustment on purchase of raw material transaction for Rs. 2.33 Crores</li><li>The proposed adjustment excludes miscellaneous expenses and rates and taxes from the computation of operating margin</li><li>The financial implication is estimated to be Rs. 0.59 Cr (excluding applicable interest and penalty, if any)</li><li>Rane Steering Systems is planning to contest the order before the appropriate authority</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/45246fd7-5976-42f4-99a4-fd9ba9df9a7c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RANE HOLDINGS LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SIGNATURE] Signatureglobal (India) Ltd Reports Q3 FY26 Operational Updates with 27% YoY Drop in Pre-sales</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Signatureglobal+%28India%29+Ltd&title=Signatureglobal+%28India%29+Ltd+Reports+Q3+FY26+Operational+Updates+with+27%25+YoY+Drop+in+Pre-sales&newsId=2a0af545-97c6-4358-8756-82fb794b6c19&token=MmEwYWY1NDUtOTdj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a0af545-97c6-4358-8756-82fb794b6c19</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 04:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Signatureglobal (India) Ltd has released its operational updates for Q3 FY26, revealing a 27% YoY decrease in pre-sales, reaching INR 20.2 billion compared to INR 27.7 billion in Q3 FY25. The number of units sold also decreased by 73% YoY and 27% QoQ, amounting to 408 units. However, average sales realization increased by 21% YoY to INR 15,182 per sq. ft. Collections stood at INR 12.3 billion in Q3 FY26, a 14% YoY increase. Net debt rose by 16% YoY to INR 10.2 billion at the end of 9MFY26. These figures are provisional and subject to audit.</p><ul><li>Q3 FY26 pre-sales of INR 20.2 billion, down 27% YoY</li><li>27.7 billion in Q3 FY25, with a 73% YoY decrease in units sold</li><li>Average sales realization increased by 21% YoY to INR 15,182 per sq. ft.</li><li>Q3 FY26 collections at INR 12.3 billion, a 14% YoY increase</li><li>Net debt rose by 16% YoY to INR 10.2 billion at the end of 9MFY26</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f54efb79-aacc-4e49-b40f-691dd158b4fe.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Signatureglobal (India) Ltd | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SIGNATURE] Signature Global Reports INR 66.8 Billion in Pre-Sales for 9M FY26; Collections Rise 14% in Q3 FY26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Signatureglobal+%28India%29+Ltd&title=Signature+Global+Reports+INR+66.8+Billion+in+Pre-Sales+for+9M+FY26%3B+Collections+Rise+14%25+in+Q3+FY26&newsId=ea8d58eb-2419-4fa9-832d-0c5a0c0638d3&token=ZWE4ZDU4ZWItMjQx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ea8d58eb-2419-4fa9-832d-0c5a0c0638d3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 04:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Signature Global (India) Ltd, a leading real estate development company in India, reported a healthy set of pre-sales numbers and strong collections for the first nine months of FY26. The pre-sales during 9M FY26 stood at INR 66.8 billion, while collections during the same period were INR 30.9 billion. During Q3FY26, the company’s pre-sales amounted to INR 20.2 billion, while collections rose to INR 12.3 billion. The average sales realization increased to INR 15,182 per sq. ft. from INR 12,457 per sq. ft. in FY25. The company’s net debt stood at INR 10.2 billion at the end of 9MFY26. The company has a market share of 13% in the National Capital Region (NCR) and 20% share in Gurugram within the price range of INR 20 million to INR 50 million.</p><ul><li>Pre-sales of INR 66.8 billion in 9M FY26</li><li>Collections of INR 30.9 billion in 9M FY26</li><li>Pre-sales of INR 20.2 billion in Q3 FY26</li><li>Collections of INR 12.3 billion in Q3 FY26</li><li>Average sales realization increased to INR 15,182 per sq. ft. in 9MFY26</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/da3ab595-06d5-473a-b794-ff50c50f2f64.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Signatureglobal (India) Ltd | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SATCH] Satchmo Holdings Ltd Completes De-subsidization of Marathalli Ventures Private Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Satchmo+Holdings+Ltd&title=Satchmo+Holdings+Ltd+Completes+De-subsidization+of+Marathalli+Ventures+Private+Limited&newsId=78fff2a3-b976-4fea-ab86-a4ddcefbfe9d&token=NzhmZmYyYTMtYjk3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78fff2a3-b976-4fea-ab86-a4ddcefbfe9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 22:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Satchmo Holdings Ltd has completed the de-subsidization of its wholly owned subsidiary, Marathalli Ventures Private Limited (MVPL), following the approval from shareholders on February 23, 2022. The de-subsidization was subject to the completion of a final one-time settlement with the existing lender or receipt of a no-objection certificate (NOC). Satchmo Holdings Ltd has successfully settled its debt with the existing lender and executed a Share Purchase Agreement for the sale of its holdings in MVPL. As a result, MVPL has ceased to be a subsidiary of the Company with immediate effect. Satchmo Holdings Ltd will provide handholding support during the transition period and bear sole responsibility for the satisfaction and performance of certain conditions precedent and conditions subsequent.</p><ul><li>Shareholders of Satchmo Holdings Ltd approved the de-subsidization of Marathalli Ventures Private Limited on February 23, 2022</li><li>Satchmo Holdings Ltd has settled its debt with the existing lender and executed a Share Purchase Agreement for the sale of its holdings in MVPL</li><li>Marathalli Ventures Private Limited has ceased to be a subsidiary of Satchmo Holdings Ltd with immediate effect</li><li>Satchmo Holdings Ltd will provide handholding support during the transition period</li><li>Satchmo Holdings Ltd is responsible for the satisfaction and performance of certain conditions precedent and conditions subsequent</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/661187c1-1469-4a91-bafe-dc3cd732cad8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Satchmo Holdings Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BLBLIMITED] BLB Limited Incorporates Wholly Owned Subsidiary, BLB Growth Ventures Private Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BLB+LTD.&title=BLB+Limited+Incorporates+Wholly+Owned+Subsidiary%2C+BLB+Growth+Ventures+Private+Limited&newsId=69edcf21-5202-4627-9daa-b988ac7cd571&token=NjllZGNmMjEtNTIw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69edcf21-5202-4627-9daa-b988ac7cd571</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 22:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>BLB Limited has incorporated a Wholly Owned Subsidiary, BLB Growth Ventures Private Limited, with the Ministry of Corporate Affairs, Government of India issuing the Certificate of Incorporation on January 10, 2026. The new subsidiary will engage in property, real estate business including purchase, sale, and construction and other allied activities. The objective of incorporating the WOS is to diversify and expand the current business operations, making the Company more agile and diversified. BLB Limited will hold 100% share capital of BLB Growth Ventures Private Limited.</p><ul><li>BLB Limited incorporates a Wholly Owned Subsidiary, BLB Growth Ventures Private Limited</li><li>BLB Growth Ventures Private Limited registered with Registrar of Companies, Delhi &amp; NCT</li><li>New subsidiary to engage in property, real estate business</li><li>Objective is to diversify and expand current business operations</li><li>BLB Limited to hold 100% share capital of BLB Growth Ventures Private Limited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/59dcfdb7-7703-4280-b93d-75802c85f369.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BLB LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>