<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:29:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[REGAL] Regal Entertainment &amp; Consultants Ltd. Approves Financial Results for Q3 2025, Extends Internal Auditor&apos;s Term, and Appoints Scrutinizer for FY 2026-27</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Regal+Entertainment+%26+Consultants+Ltd&title=Regal+Entertainment+%26+Consultants+Ltd.+Approves+Financial+Results+for+Q3+2025%2C+Extends+Internal+Auditor%27s+Term%2C+and+Appoints+Scrutinizer+for+FY+2026-27&newsId=3bd95788-3d88-49db-b328-b948aa87aaec&token=M2JkOTU3ODgtM2Q4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3bd95788-3d88-49db-b328-b948aa87aaec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:29:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Regal Entertainment &amp; Consultants Ltd. announced its un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 31.84 lakhs for the quarter and 86.03 lakhs for the nine months ended period. The board approved the extension of the term of appointment of Nitin Bhatia &amp; Associates, Chartered Accountants as an Internal Auditor for the Financial Year 2026-27. The board also approved the appointment of Palak Desai, Company Secretary in Practice, as a Scrutinizer of the Company for the Financial Year 2026-27. The review report by Rajesh Raj Gupta &amp; Associates LLP, the independent auditor, states that the company&apos;s investments amounting to 818.73 lakhs could not be verified due to the unavailability of demat statements and supporting documents.</p><ul><li>Regal Entertainment &amp; Consultants Ltd. announced its un-audited financial results for Q3 2025</li><li>Revenue from operations stands at 31.84 lakhs for the quarter and 86.03 lakhs for the nine months ended period</li><li>Nitin Bhatia &amp; Associates&apos; term as Internal Auditor extended for FY 2026-27</li><li>Palak Desai appointed as Scrutinizer of the Company for FY 2026-27</li><li>Review report highlights unverified investments amounting to 818.73 lakhs</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/95e89bcd-9ccd-4296-8bd6-d36db1ac8f5d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Regal Entertainment & Consultants Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CENLUB] Cenlub Industries Ltd. Changes Registered Office and Approves Land &amp; Property Purchase for Future Investment Plan</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CENLUB+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Cenlub+Industries+Ltd.+Changes+Registered+Office+and+Approves+Land+%26+Property+Purchase+for+Future+Investment+Plan&newsId=2084b02a-01d6-4c50-af88-67e8d1c85304&token=MjA4NGIwMmEtMDFk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2084b02a-01d6-4c50-af88-67e8d1c85304</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:29:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Cenlub Industries Ltd. has changed its registered office within Faridabad, Haryana, and approved the purchase of land and a property for its future investment plan. The land, purchased for Rs 2,30,00,000, is located at Plot No 514-A, Sector-64, Faridabad, Haryana. The property, purchased for Rs 7,43,99,415, is located at Tower-4 of ‘SNN CLERMOUNT’, Nagavara Village, Kasaba Hubli, Bengaluru North, Taluk Bengaluru. The decisions were made during a Board Meeting held on January 27, 2026.</p><ul><li>Change in the registered office of Cenlub Industries Ltd.</li><li>Purchase of land in Faridabad for Rs 2,30,00,000.</li><li>Purchase of a property in Bengaluru for Rs 7,43,99,415.</li><li>Both purchases are for the company&apos;s future investment plan.</li><li>Decisions made during the Board Meeting held on January 27, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6b9fb2ab-ca81-4bca-9cc6-1ed73ed8600c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CENLUB INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CGPOWER] CG Power and Industrial Solutions Reports Record High Revenue and PBT in Q3FY26, with 66% YoY Order Backlog Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CG+Power+and+Industrial+Solutions+Ltd&title=CG+Power+and+Industrial+Solutions+Reports+Record+High+Revenue+and+PBT+in+Q3FY26%2C+with+66%25+YoY+Order+Backlog+Growth&newsId=f691225c-49e3-4b32-a1b9-90330f90fdb3&token=ZjY5MTIyNWMtNDll</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f691225c-49e3-4b32-a1b9-90330f90fdb3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>CG Power and Industrial Solutions Limited announced a robust performance for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. Q3FY26 sales grew 22% YoY to INR 2,909 Cr, while PBT grew 35% YoY to INR 454 Cr, with a 148 bps margin expansion. Orders remained strong, with a 66% YoY increase in backlog to INR 14,859 Cr. The company&apos;s Industrial Systems segment showed steady sales growth but faced margin impact from commodity cost headwinds. The Power Systems segment continued its growth trajectory with further margin expansion. The consolidated results include the performance of operating subsidiaries in Sweden, Germany, Netherlands, India, and other non-operating subsidiaries.</p><ul><li>CG Power reports record high quarterly revenue and PBT in Q3FY26.</li><li>148 bps margin expansion in Q3FY26 compared to Q3FY25.</li><li>66% YoY increase in order backlog to INR 14,859 Cr.</li><li>Steady sales growth in Industrial Systems segment, despite margin impact from commodity cost headwinds.</li><li>Continued growth trajectory and margin expansion in Power Systems segment.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a9c8bafc-f506-4e49-b3b3-79da8fa75907.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CG Power and Industrial Solutions Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GRAVISSHO] Graviss Hospitality Ltd: Ravi Ghai&apos;s Shareholding Drops to 6.6%, Reclassified from &apos;Promoter&apos; to &apos;Promoter Group&apos;</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GRAVISS+HOSPITALITY+LTD.&title=Graviss+Hospitality+Ltd%3A+Ravi+Ghai%27s+Shareholding+Drops+to+6.6%25%2C+Reclassified+from+%27Promoter%27+to+%27Promoter+Group%27&newsId=e5859715-f660-4350-b7fa-7d15c22fdc85&token=ZTU4NTk3MTUtZjY2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5859715-f660-4350-b7fa-7d15c22fdc85</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:27:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Graviss Hospitality Ltd announced the outcome of a Board Meeting held on January 27, 2026. The total interest in the shareholding of Graviss Hospitality Limited’s shares of Mr. Ravi Ghai has reduced to around 6.6% of the capital of the Company. Consequently, the Board decided to reclassify Mr. Ravi Ghai from ‘Promoter’ to ‘Promoter group’ and inform SEBI accordingly. Mr. Ravi Ghai will no longer serve as the Non-Executive Chairman of the Company. The meeting started at 11.45 A.M. and concluded at 12.06 P.M.</p><ul><li>Ravi Ghai&apos;s shareholding in Graviss Hospitality Ltd has reduced to 6.6%</li><li>Mr. Ravi Ghai has been reclassified from ‘Promoter’ to ‘Promoter group’</li><li>Mr. Ravi Ghai will no longer serve as the Non-Executive Chairman of the Company</li><li>The decision was made at a Board Meeting held on January 27, 2026</li><li>The meeting was concluded at 12.06 P.M.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8a555f02-0e2c-4a3e-ad83-57ab843764fd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GRAVISS HOSPITALITY LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[REGAL] Regal Entertainment &amp; Consultants Ltd Appoints Internal Auditor for FY 2026-27 and Reports Q3 Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Regal+Entertainment+%26+Consultants+Ltd&title=Regal+Entertainment+%26+Consultants+Ltd+Appoints+Internal+Auditor+for+FY+2026-27+and+Reports+Q3+Financial+Results&newsId=4778ed3d-245e-44e1-be98-eedcd9da7745&token=NDc3OGVkM2QtMjQ1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4778ed3d-245e-44e1-be98-eedcd9da7745</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:25:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Regal Entertainment &amp; Consultants Ltd, a company with CIN L65923MH1992PLC064689, has appointed Nitin Bhatia &amp; Associates, Chartered Accountants as the Internal Auditor for the financial year 2026-27. The company has also announced the un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The revenue from operations stands at 31.84 lakhs for the quarter and 86.03 lakhs for the nine months period. The profit before tax for the same periods is -8.96 lakhs and 69.37 lakhs respectively. The company has also reported an extraordinary item of 69.37 lakhs and a tax expense of 30.05 lakhs. The total comprehensive income for the period is 51.88 lakhs.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Nitin Bhatia &amp; Associates, Chartered Accountants as the Internal Auditor for FY 2026-27</li><li>Un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025 announced</li><li>Revenue from operations stands at 31.84 lakhs for the quarter and 86.03 lakhs for the nine months period</li><li>Profit before tax for the same periods is -8.96 lakhs and 69.37 lakhs respectively</li><li>Extraordinary item of 69.37 lakhs and a tax expense of 30.05 lakhs reported</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4549e41b-7e00-470c-a200-e315ae050da0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Regal Entertainment & Consultants Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ONWARDTEC] Onward Technologies Transfers Shares to IEPF Under Special Window</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ONWARD+TECHNOLOGIES+LTD.&title=Onward+Technologies+Transfers+Shares+to+IEPF+Under+Special+Window&newsId=fee5f5a0-f2b4-43ac-900c-7aca647a08e3&token=ZmVlNWY1YTAtZjJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fee5f5a0-f2b4-43ac-900c-7aca647a08e3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:23:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Onward Technologies Ltd. has transferred shares of the company under the Special Window for re-lodgement of transfer of physical shares, as per SEBI Circular no. SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97 dated 2nd July, 2025. The shares and corresponding dividend amounts have been transferred to Investor Education and Protection Fund Authority (IEPF) pursuant to IEPF Rules, 2016. The shares will be under lock-in for 6 months from the date of transfer and can be claimed from IEPF post completion of the lock-in period. The information is available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Onward Technologies transfers shares under Special Window</li><li>Shares transferred to Investor Education and Protection Fund Authority (IEPF)</li><li>Shares under lock-in for 6 months from the date of transfer</li><li>Can be claimed from IEPF post completion of the lock-in period</li><li>Information available on the company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/50b465e8-882b-4d6d-9a7a-0ff9951fa7f4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ONWARD TECHNOLOGIES LTD. | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASHOKLEY] Ashok Leyland Announces New President &amp; Head — Human Resources: Jasmeet Bhatia</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ASHOK+LEYLAND+LTD.&title=Ashok+Leyland+Announces+New+President+%26+Head+%E2%80%94+Human+Resources%3A+Jasmeet+Bhatia&newsId=e21cfd69-b6e9-46f4-8052-ad03081c81d5&token=ZTIxY2ZkNjktYjZl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e21cfd69-b6e9-46f4-8052-ad03081c81d5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:23:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ashok Leyland Ltd. has announced a change in its Senior Management Personnel (SMP) in the Human Resources function. Mr. Jasmeet Bhatia has joined the company as President &amp; Head — Human Resources with effect from January 27, 2026, replacing Mr. Raja Radhakrishnan. Mr. Radhakrishnan will now manage Special Projects within Ashok Leyland / Hinduja Group. Mr. Bhatia, an MBA in Human Resources and a Bachelor of Science in Computers, brings over 25 years of experience in Human Resources, having designed and implemented various initiatives such as leadership development, succession planning, diversity, equity &amp; inclusion, performance &amp; rewards excellence, organization change management and maintaining harmonious industrial relations.</p><ul><li>Mr. Jasmeet Bhatia appointed as President &amp; Head — Human Resources at Ashok Leyland</li><li>Mr. Raja Radhakrishnan to manage Special Projects within Ashok Leyland / Hinduja Group</li><li>Mr. Bhatia brings over 25 years of experience in Human Resources</li><li>Mr. Bhatia has designed and implemented various HR initiatives</li><li>New SMP in Human Resources function pursuant to SEBI Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/05531534-0122-4229-826d-078146f5d749.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ASHOK LEYLAND LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[REGAL] Regal Entertainment &amp; Consultants Ltd. Approves Q3 &amp; 9M FY2025-26 Financial Results and Extends Internal Auditor&apos;s Term</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Regal+Entertainment+%26+Consultants+Ltd&title=Regal+Entertainment+%26+Consultants+Ltd.+Approves+Q3+%26+9M+FY2025-26+Financial+Results+and+Extends+Internal+Auditor%27s+Term&newsId=943dddea-d062-4183-a7d6-6d8efebc5d83&token=OTQzZGRkZWEtZDA2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">943dddea-d062-4183-a7d6-6d8efebc5d83</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:23:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Regal Entertainment &amp; Consultants Ltd. announced the approval of its un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025, along with a Limited Review Report issued by the statutory auditor. The company has also extended the term of appointment of its internal auditor, Nitin Bhatia &amp; Associates, Chartered Accountants, for a further period of one year, i.e., for the Financial Year 2026-27. The decision was made in the Board of Directors meeting held on 27th January 2026.</p><ul><li>Approval of un-audited financial results for Q3 and 9M FY2025-26</li><li>Limited Review Report issued by the statutory auditor</li><li>Extension of term of appointment for the internal auditor, Nitin Bhatia &amp; Associates, Chartered Accountants, for FY2026-27</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d7ed3c7a-37ea-4156-b9cf-5c677bbe1872.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Regal Entertainment & Consultants Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PSPPROJECT] PSP Projects Ltd Receives ESG Rating of &apos;66.9&apos; (Grade B) for 2025 from SES ESG</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PSP+Projects+Ltd&title=PSP+Projects+Ltd+Receives+ESG+Rating+of+%2766.9%27+%28Grade+B%29+for+2025+from+SES+ESG&newsId=0a6ccb0f-4911-4312-a8bd-a638b4577da9&token=MGE2Y2NiMGYtNDkx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a6ccb0f-4911-4312-a8bd-a638b4577da9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:20:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Rating</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>PSP Projects Ltd, a company based in Ahmedabad, Gujarat, has been assigned an Environmental, Social and Governance (ESG) rating of ‘66.9’ (Grade B) - Medium risk by M/s. SES ESG Research Pvt. Ltd. for the year 2025. The company has not engaged SES ESG for this rating and it has been independently prepared based on data available in the public domain. This disclosure is in accordance with the Intimation of ESG Rating Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015 (&apos;SEBI Listing Regulations&apos;) and the SEBI Master Circular SEBI/HO/CFD/PoD2/CIR/P/0155 dated November 11, 2024. The ESG rating report is available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>PSP Projects Ltd receives ESG rating of &apos;66.9&apos; (Grade B) - Medium risk from SES ESG for 2025</li><li>The rating is based on data available in the public domain</li><li>The company has not engaged SES ESG for this rating</li><li>Disclosure is in accordance with SEBI Listing Regulations and SEBI Master Circular</li><li>ESG rating report is available on the company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/708ca062-f078-466a-97b1-7622e848b846.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PSP Projects Ltd | Category: Rating</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LUDLOWJUT] Ludlow Jute &amp; Specialities Ltd Board Meeting for 28/01/2026 Cancelled</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LUDLOW+JUTE+%26+SPECIALITIES+LTD.&title=Ludlow+Jute+%26+Specialities+Ltd+Board+Meeting+for+28%2F01%2F2026+Cancelled&newsId=84123708-e993-4686-9c1a-eb5079010f4a&token=ODQxMjM3MDgtZTk5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">84123708-e993-4686-9c1a-eb5079010f4a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 09:18:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board Meeting of Ludlow Jute &amp; Specialities Ltd, originally scheduled for 28th January 2026, has been cancelled due to unavoidable reasons. The company will announce the new date in due course. The cancellation notice is also available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>The Board Meeting of Ludlow Jute &amp; Specialities Ltd, originally scheduled for 28th January 2026, has been cancelled</li><li>The company will announce the new date in due course</li><li>The cancellation notice is available on the company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/705b75aa-b7e5-4ea3-8e3b-dff9d2c27b81.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LUDLOW JUTE & SPECIALITIES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>