<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:20:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[LGEINDIA] LG Electronics India Ltd. Signs Advance Pricing Agreement with CBDT, Reducing Contingent Liabilities by INR 4,877.38 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LG+Electronics+India+Ltd&title=LG+Electronics+India+Ltd.+Signs+Advance+Pricing+Agreement+with+CBDT%2C+Reducing+Contingent+Liabilities+by+INR+4%2C877.38+Million&newsId=122b1510-48fe-4e55-bb91-093170d46d19&token=MTIyYjE1MTAtNDhm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">122b1510-48fe-4e55-bb91-093170d46d19</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:07:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>LG Electronics India Ltd. has signed an Advance Pricing Agreement (APA) with the Central Board of Direct Taxes (CBDT) in India, effective from April 1, 2014, to March 31, 2023. The APA signing led to the reduction of contingent liabilities related to direct taxes by INR 1,724.38 Million and eliminated a contingency amount of INR 3,153.00 Million for royalty payments to LG Electronics Inc., Korea (Promoter). The company will incur a net tax expense of INR 177.12 Million (excluding applicable interest) and pay a net amount of INR 38.59 Million to LG Electronics Inc. for secondary adjustment provisions compliance with Indian transfer pricing laws.</p><ul><li>LG Electronics India Ltd. signed an Advance Pricing Agreement (APA) with the Central Board of Direct Taxes (CBDT) in India</li><li>APA effective from April 1, 2014, to March 31, 2023</li><li>Contingent liabilities related to direct taxes reduced by INR 1,724.38 Million</li><li>Elimination of contingency amount of INR 3,153.00 Million for royalty payments to LG Electronics Inc., Korea (Promoter)</li><li>Net tax expense of INR 177.12 Million (excluding applicable interest) and a net amount of INR 38.59 Million to LG Electronics Inc. for secondary adjustment provisions compliance</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3d92329f-a0c2-49c5-84bc-411c874973c7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LG Electronics India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CRISIL] CRISIL Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q4 and FY2025 Financial Results and Dividend Payment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CRISIL+LTD.&title=CRISIL+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q4+and+FY2025+Financial+Results+and+Dividend+Payment&newsId=2e20d200-de54-4510-a99c-af74b214b0a6&token=MmUyMGQyMDAtZGU1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e20d200-de54-4510-a99c-af74b214b0a6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>CRISIL Ltd, a company of S&amp;P Global, has informed the BSE that its Board of Directors will meet on February 12 and 13, 2026, to consider and approve the audited consolidated and standalone financial results for the fourth quarter and year ended December 31, 2025. The Board will also consider the payment of a final dividend for the financial year ending December 31, 2025. The &apos;No Trading Window&apos; for the employees of Crisil Limited and its subsidiary companies has commenced from December 16, 2025, to February 17, 2026.</p><ul><li>CRISIL Ltd to consider and approve Q4 and FY2025 financial results on February 12 and 13, 2026</li><li>The company will also consider the payment of a final dividend for FY2025</li><li>The &apos;No Trading Window&apos; for employees of Crisil Limited and its subsidiaries is in effect from December 16, 2025, to February 17, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c209eb0f-ca39-4d7f-a5cf-5a9007f582a2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CRISIL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CRISIL] CRISIL Ltd Announces Meeting of Board of Directors on February 12-13, 2026 to Approve Q4 and Year-End Financial Results for 2025 and Consider Final Dividend Payment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CRISIL+LTD.&title=CRISIL+Ltd+Announces+Meeting+of+Board+of+Directors+on+February+12-13%2C+2026+to+Approve+Q4+and+Year-End+Financial+Results+for+2025+and+Consider+Final+Dividend+Payment&newsId=6f0f7c82-0c40-4312-a7dd-c0a48a3e3c90&token=NmYwZjdjODItMGM0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f0f7c82-0c40-4312-a7dd-c0a48a3e3c90</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>CRISIL Ltd, a company of S&amp;P Global, has announced that a meeting of the Board of Directors will be held on February 12-13, 2026. The Board will consider and approve the audited consolidated and standalone financial results for the fourth quarter and year ended December 31, 2025. The audited financial results and the proposal for dividend will be presented to the Board on February 13, 2026, for their approval. The &apos;No Trading Window&apos; for the employees of Crisil Limited and its subsidiary companies has commenced from December 16, 2025, to February 17, 2026 (both days inclusive).</p><ul><li>CRISIL Ltd Board of Directors to meet on February 12-13, 2026</li><li>Board to consider and approve Q4 and year-end financial results for 2025</li><li>Audited financial results and dividend proposal to be presented on February 13, 2026</li><li>No Trading Window for employees from December 16, 2025, to February 17, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4f9e76f7-df83-4c71-8080-0875da02eef2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CRISIL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HMT] HMT Ltd Files Application to Strike Off Subsidiary HMT Watches Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HMT+LTD.&title=HMT+Ltd+Files+Application+to+Strike+Off+Subsidiary+HMT+Watches+Limited&newsId=365ff117-bb37-49d9-9d17-2f250f440a22&token=MzY1ZmYxMTctYmIz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">365ff117-bb37-49d9-9d17-2f250f440a22</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>HMT Ltd has filed an application with the Ministry of Corporate Affairs, Government of India, to strike off the name of its wholly owned subsidiary, HMT Watches Limited, from the records of the Registrar of Companies under section 248 of the Companies Act, 2013. This move comes after the approval of the Cabinet Committee on Economic Affairs in its meeting dated January 6, 2016, for the closure of three subsidiary companies of HMT Limited, namely: HMT Watches Limited, HMT Bearings Limited and HMT Chinar Watches Limited. The stock exchanges were previously informed about the status of this process at various stages.</p><ul><li>HMT Ltd files application to strike off HMT Watches Limited</li><li>Application filed with Ministry of Corporate Affairs, Government of India</li><li>Move follows approval of Cabinet Committee on Economic Affairs in 2016</li><li>Three subsidiary companies including HMT Watches Limited were approved for closure</li><li>Stock exchanges previously informed about the process</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/234b8305-40e4-4191-970d-b9feaf0c7892.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HMT LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CUMMINSIND] Cummins India Ltd to Invest Rs. 2.70 Crores in Clean Max Yellowstone Private Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CUMMINS+INDIA+LTD.&title=Cummins+India+Ltd+to+Invest+Rs.+2.70+Crores+in+Clean+Max+Yellowstone+Private+Limited&newsId=e39711dc-b218-4377-bda6-07f5bcfc141c&token=ZTM5NzExZGMtYjIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e39711dc-b218-4377-bda6-07f5bcfc141c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:47:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Cummins India Ltd has entered into a Shareholders’ Agreement (SHA) with Clean Max Yellowstone Private Limited, agreeing to invest an amount up to Rs. 2.70 Crores by subscribing to at least 8.78% of Clean Max’s equity share capital in one or more tranches. The company has also entered into Energy Supply Agreements with Clean Max for procuring renewable power for its factories and premises. This announcement follows the company&apos;s earlier intimation dated December 18, 2025, and December 29, 2025, with no changes in relevant details.</p><ul><li>Cummins India Ltd to invest up to Rs. 2.70 Crores in Clean Max Yellowstone Private Limited</li><li>Investment will be made by subscribing to at least 8.78% of Clean Max’s equity share capital</li><li>Energy Supply Agreements signed for procuring renewable power for Cummins India Ltd’s factories and premises</li><li>No changes in relevant details since the last intimation dated December 18, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/442168b7-bfc9-47e2-97ef-79b9147341ea.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CUMMINS INDIA LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ANGELONE] Ajit Sinha Joins Angel One as General Counsel</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Angel+One+Ltd&title=Ajit+Sinha+Joins+Angel+One+as+General+Counsel&newsId=2eac3102-b315-410d-9993-0acba44affa8&token=MmVhYzMxMDItYjMx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2eac3102-b315-410d-9993-0acba44affa8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Angel One Limited, a leading FinTech player, announces that Ajit Sinha has joined as General Counsel. With over 24 years of experience in corporate law, financial services, capital markets, and banking, Ajit will lead the legal function and provide strategic counsel to the Board and leadership team. He joins from the National Stock Exchange of India Limited (NSE), where he served as Vice President and Heading the Corporate Legal team since December 2018. Ajit&apos;s experience across exchanges, banking, and capital markets will be invaluable as Angel One scales its businesses and innovates responsibly within a strong regulatory framework.</p><ul><li>Ajit Sinha joins Angel One as General Counsel</li><li>Over 24 years of experience in corporate law, financial services, capital markets, and banking</li><li>Will lead the legal function and provide strategic counsel to the Board and leadership team</li><li>Joins from the National Stock Exchange of India Limited (NSE)</li><li>Experience across exchanges, banking, and capital markets will be invaluable as Angel One scales its businesses and innovates responsibly within a strong regulatory framework</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/30752788-e772-4c20-a09f-f8866a09a0ae.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Angel One Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHINEFASH] Shine Fashions (India) Ltd. Schedules Board Meeting to Evaluate Strategic Acquisition and Loan Proposal</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shine+Fashions+%28India%29+Ltd&title=Shine+Fashions+%28India%29+Ltd.+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Evaluate+Strategic+Acquisition+and+Loan+Proposal&newsId=217e030c-9ae0-49d4-833d-021e748cb684&token=MjE3ZTAzMGMtOWFl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">217e030c-9ae0-49d4-833d-021e748cb684</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:41:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shine Fashions (India) Ltd. has announced a board meeting scheduled for January 8th, 2026. The agenda includes evaluating a strategic acquisition of a company, which could potentially bring long-term value. The board will also consider obtaining an unsecured loan from directors or promoters to meet urgent fund requirements. This decision could significantly impact the company&apos;s financial strategy and future growth.</p><ul><li>Shine Fashions (India) Ltd. is considering a strategic acquisition of a company for long-term value creation.</li><li>The company is planning to obtain an unsecured loan from directors or promoters to meet urgent fund requirements.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/77fdb08b-988f-40ed-9d81-e0047ed1d850.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shine Fashions (India) Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CDG] Jujhar Logistic &amp; Travels Limited, a CDG Petchem Subsidiary, Reports Strong Operating &amp; Financial Performance in 9M FY26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CDG+Petchem+Ltd&title=Jujhar+Logistic+%26+Travels+Limited%2C+a+CDG+Petchem+Subsidiary%2C+Reports+Strong+Operating+%26+Financial+Performance+in+9M+FY26&newsId=25897f8b-bd4b-4549-88fe-f3e0afee653d&token=MjU4OTdmOGItYmQ0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">25897f8b-bd4b-4549-88fe-f3e0afee653d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:41:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Jujhar Logistic &amp; Travels Limited, a 51% subsidiary of CDG Petchem Ltd, has announced strong operating and financial performance for the first nine months of FY26. The company, a leading automotive logistics solutions provider, achieved significant growth across key operating and financial metrics compared to FY25. Despite a challenging macro &amp; operating environment, Jujhar Logistic &amp; Travels Ltd reported a revenue from operations of 159.88 Cr, an EBITDA of 33.14 Cr, and a Profit After Tax of 20.39 Cr for 9M FY26.</p><ul><li>Revenue from Operations for 9M FY26 is 159.88 Cr, compared to 124.87 Cr in FY25</li><li>EBITDA for 9M FY26 is 33.14 Cr, compared to 32.90 Cr in FY25</li><li>Profit After Tax for 9M FY26 is 20.39 Cr, compared to 22.64 Cr in FY25</li><li>Jujhar Logistic &amp; Travels Ltd became a subsidiary of CDG Petchem Ltd on 18 November 2025</li><li>The company serves leading Original Equipment Manufacturers (OEMs) including Maruti, Mahindra, Tata, Kia, Hyundai, Skoda, Toyata, and Land Rover</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/18915d3f-d3bc-44ef-9bec-b036d274ab10.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CDG Petchem Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GRANDFONRY] Madhu Garg Sells 70.16% Shares of Grand Foundry Ltd Through Open Offer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GRAND+FOUNDRY+LTD.&title=Madhu+Garg+Sells+70.16%25+Shares+of+Grand+Foundry+Ltd+Through+Open+Offer&newsId=1d23916c-fef1-4b2e-ad8a-7b3243b0f131&token=MWQyMzkxNmMtZmVm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d23916c-fef1-4b2e-ad8a-7b3243b0f131</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:37:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>According to a disclosure made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011, Madhu Garg has sold 2,13,50,360 Equity Shares of Grand Foundry Limited, representing 70.16% of its paid-up equity share capital. The sale was made through a share purchase agreement in terms of an open offer. The transaction took place on 24th January 2026. After the sale, Madhu Garg does not hold any shares or voting rights in Grand Foundry Ltd.</p><ul><li>Madhu Garg sells 70.16% shares of Grand Foundry Ltd</li><li>Sale through share purchase agreement in open offer</li><li>Transaction amount: 2,13,50,360 Equity Shares</li><li>Sale date: 24th January 2026</li><li>No shares or voting rights held by Madhu Garg after the sale</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/08BF2FFF_7EBD_4BAB_834F_BB95C503F743_195255.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GRAND FOUNDRY LTD. | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STLNETWORK] Bandhan Mutual Fund Reduces Holding in STL Networks Limited by Over 2%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=STL+Networks+Ltd&title=Bandhan+Mutual+Fund+Reduces+Holding+in+STL+Networks+Limited+by+Over+2%25&newsId=0612db99-ddaf-4e12-98e6-756dc4b31ca2&token=MDYxMmRiOTktZGRh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0612db99-ddaf-4e12-98e6-756dc4b31ca2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bandhan Mutual Fund has sold 2,78,655 equity shares of STL Networks Limited on January 02, 2026, resulting in a decrease of its holding from 5.3635% to 3.3509%. This disposal represents a 0.0571% change in the total voting rights of STL Networks Limited.</p><ul><li>Bandhan Mutual Fund sold 2,78,655 equity shares of STL Networks Limited.</li><li>This sale resulted in a decrease of Bandhan Mutual Fund&apos;s holding from 5.3635% to 3.3509%.</li><li>The sale represents a 0.0571% change in the total voting rights of STL Networks Limited.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/F0A7AC37_BA3B_439A_AA57_429367FCCE68_195129.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: STL Networks Ltd | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>