<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:30:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[JBCHEPHARM] JB Chemicals &amp; Pharmaceuticals Ltd Appoints New Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=J.B.CHEMICALS+%26+PHARMACEUTICALS+LTD.&title=JB+Chemicals+%26+Pharmaceuticals+Ltd+Appoints+New+Directors&newsId=24503fd9-65e3-48e4-859a-b6306f6e6839&token=MjQ1MDNmZDktNjVl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24503fd9-65e3-48e4-859a-b6306f6e6839</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:29:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>JB Chemicals &amp; Pharmaceuticals Ltd has appointed several new directors in its recent meeting. Mr. Aman Mehta has been appointed as an Additional Director and Managing Director for a term of 3 years. Mr. Amal Kelshikar, Mr. Hasmukh Patel, and Mr. Sudhir Menon have been appointed as Additional Directors (Non-Executive and Non-Independent). The appointments are subject to the approval of the shareholders of the company. The company also affirmed that the directors are not debarred from holding the office of director by virtue of any Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) order or any other such authority.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Aman Mehta as Additional Director and Managing Director</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Amal Kelshikar, Mr. Hasmukh Patel, and Mr. Sudhir Menon as Additional Directors (Non-Executive and Non-Independent)</li><li>Appointments subject to shareholders&apos; approval</li><li>Directors not debarred by SEBI or any other authority</li><li>Company in compliance with Companies Act, 2013 and SEBI Listing Regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0428e00d-a42c-45c6-bda4-c2a93c3385bb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: J.B.CHEMICALS & PHARMACEUTICALS LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDOUS] Indo US Bio-Tech Ltd. Approves Q3 Results for FY2025-26, Announces Bonus Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Indo+Us+Bio-Tech+Ltd&title=Indo+US+Bio-Tech+Ltd.+Approves+Q3+Results+for+FY2025-26%2C+Announces+Bonus+Shares&newsId=349b930e-3149-4502-8b55-1386e3dd1668&token=MzQ5YjkzMGUtMzE0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">349b930e-3149-4502-8b55-1386e3dd1668</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indo US Bio-Tech Ltd. has approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 2,279.83 lakhs. The company has also announced the issuance of bonus shares in the ratio of 1:1 as on 01st September 2023. The company is assessing the impact of the new Labour Codes notified by the Government of India.</p><ul><li>Indo US Bio-Tech Ltd. approves Q3 results for FY2025-26</li><li>Revenue from operations stands at 2,279.83 lakhs</li><li>Company announces bonus shares in the ratio of 1:1 as on 01st September 2023</li><li>Company is assessing the impact of new Labour Codes notified by the Government of India</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ce14e1a0-04a3-4e78-a0b8-7f8ba403a3ba.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Indo Us Bio-Tech Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STANCAP] Standard Capital Markets Ltd Announces Q3 and Nine Months Unaudited Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=STANDARD+CAPITAL+MARKETS+LTD.&title=Standard+Capital+Markets+Ltd+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=8d6367c2-fb9d-462c-a8c6-d5dcd62c3a24&token=OGQ2MzY3YzItZmI5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d6367c2-fb9d-462c-a8c6-d5dcd62c3a24</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:26:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Standard Capital Markets Ltd has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s standalone and consolidated financial results were approved in a board meeting. The results will be published in newspapers shortly. The company&apos;s financial results are also available on the stock exchange website.</p><ul><li>Standard Capital Markets Ltd has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s standalone and consolidated financial results were approved in a board meeting.</li><li>The results will be published in newspapers shortly.</li><li>The company has incorporated a wholly-owned subsidiary, Standard ARC Limited, on 08 September 2025.</li><li>The financial results are also available on the stock exchange website.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d9720157-7949-4f25-ac89-b48d8f9d280c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: STANDARD CAPITAL MARKETS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SIMPLEXINF] Simplex Infrastructures Ltd Secures Rs.154 Crores EPC Contract in Power Sector</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SIMPLEX+INFRASTRUCTURES+LTD.&title=Simplex+Infrastructures+Ltd+Secures+Rs.154+Crores+EPC+Contract+in+Power+Sector&newsId=58e66eaa-682b-4023-a336-a93c50d182c1&token=NThlNjZlYWEtNjgy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58e66eaa-682b-4023-a336-a93c50d182c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:26:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Simplex Infrastructures Ltd has been awarded a new EPC contract in the power sector, amounting to approximately Rs.154 Crores. This development is in line with the company&apos;s regular business operations and is expected to bolster the company&apos;s order book. The new contract is a positive sign for the company&apos;s growth and stability in the power sector.</p><ul><li>Simplex Infrastructures Ltd has been awarded a new EPC contract in the power sector.</li><li>The contract is worth approximately Rs.154 Crores.</li><li>This development is in the normal course of business.</li><li>The new contract is expected to strengthen the Company’s order book.</li><li>The power sector continues to be a focus area for Simplex Infrastructures Ltd.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ac737f29-4aa2-44e2-b237-4e7c0706f114.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SIMPLEX INFRASTRUCTURES LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JAMSHRI] Jamshri Realty Ltd. to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on 3rd February 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jamshri+Realty+Ltd-%24&title=Jamshri+Realty+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+3rd+February+2026&newsId=605785e0-9919-4310-90f1-72e17ef74692&token=NjA1Nzg1ZTAtOTkx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">605785e0-9919-4310-90f1-72e17ef74692</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:26:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jamshri Realty Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 3rd February 2026 to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the 3rd quarter and nine months ended on 31st December 2025. The trading window for dealing/trading in securities of the company by insiders will be closed from 1st January 2026 to 6th February 2026 (both days inclusive).</p><ul><li>Jamshri Realty Ltd. to consider and approve Q3 and nine months financial results for 2025</li><li>Board meeting scheduled on 3rd February 2026</li><li>Trading window for insiders to be closed from 1st January 2026 to 6th February 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1f4a0431-d7fd-4fd6-8d26-20bd3d0b53ab.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jamshri Realty Ltd-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ELIN] Elin Electronics Ltd to Approve Q3 FY2025-26 Financial Results on Feb 6, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Elin+Electronics+Ltd&title=Elin+Electronics+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+FY2025-26+Financial+Results+on+Feb+6%2C+2026&newsId=f1c71b4f-7680-4e30-b171-c04584c35460&token=ZjFjNzFiNGYtNzY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f1c71b4f-7680-4e30-b171-c04584c35460</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:23:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Elin Electronics Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 6, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The meeting is scheduled in accordance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The company will inform the stock exchanges about the financial results upon the conclusion of the board meeting. The trading window for insiders will remain closed until February 10, 2026.</p><ul><li>Elin Electronics Ltd to consider and approve Q3 FY2025-26 financial results on Feb 6, 2026</li><li>Meeting scheduled in accordance with SEBI regulations</li><li>Company to inform stock exchanges about the financial results post-meeting</li><li>Trading window for insiders to remain closed until Feb 10, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d3e74b50-403f-4087-a521-94c06d428afc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Elin Electronics Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RATHIBAR] Rathi Bars Ltd Reports Q3 2025 Un-Audited Financial Results with 49,628.82 Lacs Revenue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RATHI+BARS+LTD.&title=Rathi+Bars+Ltd+Reports+Q3+2025+Un-Audited+Financial+Results+with+49%2C628.82+Lacs+Revenue&newsId=5ab3efb8-089d-4157-9dbe-7ee28ce1ab6e&token=NWFiM2VmYjgtMDg5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ab3efb8-089d-4157-9dbe-7ee28ce1ab6e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:22:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rathi Bars Ltd has reported its un-audited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 9,062.40 Lacs, with a total revenue of 9,096.76 Lacs. The net profit for the period (before tax) is 70.32 Lacs, and the net profit (after tax) is 256.56 Lacs. The total comprehensive income is 256.56 Lacs.</p><ul><li>Rathi Bars Ltd reports Q3 2025 un-audited financial results</li><li>Revenue from operations stands at 9,062.40 Lacs</li><li>Total revenue is 9,096.76 Lacs</li><li>Net profit (before tax) is 70.32 Lacs</li><li>Net profit (after tax) is 256.56 Lacs</li><li>Total comprehensive income is 256.56 Lacs</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0e8e3463-c1ec-46e2-95d1-1347a8a277f3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RATHI BARS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FIBERWEB] Fiberweb India Ltd. to Announce Q3 and Nine Months Results on January 30, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=FIBERWEB+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Fiberweb+India+Ltd.+to+Announce+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+on+January+30%2C+2026&newsId=ffa1a810-7245-4836-b050-403d52688205&token=ZmZhMWE4MTAtNzI0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ffa1a810-7245-4836-b050-403d52688205</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:20:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Fiberweb India Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 30, 2026, to consider and approve the Standalone Unaudited Financial Results for the Third quarter and Nine Months ended 31st December, 2025. The meeting will be held at Kiran Building, 128, Bhaudaji Road, Matunga (East), Mumbai - 400019. The trading window for the company&apos;s equity shares will be closed from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of the results.</p><ul><li>Fiberweb India Ltd. to announce Q3 and Nine Months results on January 30, 2026</li><li>Board of Directors to meet on January 30, 2026, to consider and approve the results</li><li>Results are for the period ended 31st December, 2025</li><li>Meeting will be held at Kiran Building, Matunga (East), Mumbai</li><li>Trading window for the company&apos;s equity shares will be closed from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of the results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7a325821-d3cb-4e3e-84cc-ad42970f5787.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: FIBERWEB (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WENDT] Wendt (India) Ltd Declares Interim Dividend of 200% for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=WENDT+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Wendt+%28India%29+Ltd+Declares+Interim+Dividend+of+200%25+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=1ed30665-cb52-4730-89bc-12d58e19cdee&token=MWVkMzA2NjUtY2I1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1ed30665-cb52-4730-89bc-12d58e19cdee</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:19:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Wendt (India) Ltd has declared an interim dividend of 200% i.e. Rs. 20/- per equity share for the year ending 31st March 2026. The record date for determining the members eligible to receive this interim dividend is Wednesday, 28th January 2026. The company has also reported its unaudited financial results for the quarter/period ended 31st December 2025.</p><ul><li>Interim dividend of 200% declared for FY 2025-26</li><li>Record date for dividend eligibility is 28th January 2026</li><li>Unaudited financial results for Q3 2025-26 reported</li><li>Revenue from operations stands at Rs. 15,148 lakhs for the quarter</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ea3507d6-f5c7-4c5a-9626-65f7da75b72a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: WENDT (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WENDT] Wendt (India) Ltd Declares 200% Interim Dividend and Reports Q3 Results for FY2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=WENDT+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Wendt+%28India%29+Ltd+Declares+200%25+Interim+Dividend+and+Reports+Q3+Results+for+FY2026&newsId=107bc2f1-de9e-4b94-bc88-cb0484517cee&token=MTA3YmMyZjEtZGU5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">107bc2f1-de9e-4b94-bc88-cb0484517cee</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 09:19:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Wendt (India) Ltd has declared an interim dividend of 200% for the year ending 31st March 2026. The company&apos;s Q3 results for FY2026 showed a revenue from operations of Rs. 15,005 lakhs and a profit before tax of Rs. 2,043 lakhs. The record date for the dividend is 28th January 2026.</p><ul><li>Wendt (India) Ltd declares 200% interim dividend for FY2026</li><li>Q3 revenue from operations stood at Rs. 15,005 lakhs</li><li>Profit before tax for Q3 FY2026 was Rs. 2,043 lakhs</li><li>Record date for dividend is 28th January 2026</li><li>The company&apos;s Q3 results showed a profit for the period of Rs. 1,529 lakhs</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d84f73fb-2e6e-4c94-886d-5084286a0679.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: WENDT (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>