<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 15:21:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SAKUMA] Sakuma Exports Ltd to Approve Q4 Results on Feb 14, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SAKUMA+EXPORTS+LTD.&title=Sakuma+Exports+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+Results+on+Feb+14%2C+2026&newsId=06b94ae9-bacf-49b9-b9fb-22856d6603c5&token=MDZiOTRhZTktYmFj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06b94ae9-bacf-49b9-b9fb-22856d6603c5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 14:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sakuma Exports Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 14, 2026, to consider and approve the Un-Audited Financial Results (Standalone and Consolidated) for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The meeting will also consider and approve the Limited Review Report (Standalone and Consolidated) by the statutory Auditor of the Company. The trading window for dealing in securities of the Company will remain closed from 1st January, 2026, and will open 48 hours after the declaration of the said Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Sakuma Exports Ltd to consider and approve Q4 results for the year 2025 on Feb 14, 2026</li><li>The meeting will also approve the Limited Review Report by the statutory Auditor</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities of the Company will remain closed from 1st January, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0fad0449-833f-4235-9b54-2770898db985.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SAKUMA EXPORTS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASHAPURMIN] Independent Director, Mr. Pundarik Sanyal, Completes His Second Term at Ashapura Minechem Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ASHAPURA+MINECHEM+LTD.&title=Independent+Director%2C+Mr.+Pundarik+Sanyal%2C+Completes+His+Second+Term+at+Ashapura+Minechem+Ltd&newsId=fc4d6a1a-0ce6-4a26-96ee-7c672c1f108f&token=ZmM0ZDZhMWEtMGNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc4d6a1a-0ce6-4a26-96ee-7c672c1f108f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ashapura Minechem Ltd announces the completion of the second term of Mr. Pundarik Sanyal as an Independent Director. He ceased to be the Independent Director from the close of business hours on 08th February, 2026. The Board of Directors acknowledges his valuable contributions and guidance during his tenure.</p><ul><li>Mr. Pundarik Sanyal completes his second term as an Independent Director at Ashapura Minechem Ltd.</li><li>He ceased to be the Independent Director from the close of business hours on 08th February, 2026.</li><li>The Board of Directors acknowledges his valuable contributions and guidance during his tenure.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/16208b60-963a-4226-8a24-0d6338b1a874.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ASHAPURA MINECHEM LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[URAVI] Uravi Defence and Technology Ltd. Announces EGM for Shareholder Approval on Key Decisions</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Uravi+T+And+Wedge+Lamps+Ltd&title=Uravi+Defence+and+Technology+Ltd.+Announces+EGM+for+Shareholder+Approval+on+Key+Decisions&newsId=91fb808e-7256-43f2-b4da-6d7146606a05&token=OTFmYjgwOGUtNzI1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">91fb808e-7256-43f2-b4da-6d7146606a05</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Uravi Defence and Technology Ltd., formerly known as Uravi T &amp; Wedge Lamps Limited, has announced an Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) to be held on March 02, 2026, at 4.00 P.M. The meeting will be conducted through video conferencing in accordance with MCA and SEBI guidelines. The agenda includes the appointment of M/S Viren Gandhi &amp; Co as the new Statutory Auditors, consideration of a proposal for disinvestment in SKL India Private Limited, and approval of a material related party transaction for disinvestment of 50.01% shareholding in SKL. The remote e-voting will commence on February 27, 2026, and end on March 01, 2026.</p><ul><li>Appointment of M/S Viren Gandhi &amp; Co as Statutory Auditors.</li><li>Consideration of a proposal for disinvestment in SKL India Private Limited.</li><li>Approval of a material related party transaction for disinvestment of 50.01% shareholding in SKL.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7e7284a8-f566-4779-a529-eb9b6361a476.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Uravi T And Wedge Lamps Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HCG] HealthCare Global Enterprises Ltd. to Consider Fund Raise by Rights Issue on Feb 17, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HealthCare+Global+Enterprises+Ltd&title=HealthCare+Global+Enterprises+Ltd.+to+Consider+Fund+Raise+by+Rights+Issue+on+Feb+17%2C+2026&newsId=a8a17a43-54f9-47c5-9651-7ca96b44665b&token=YThhMTdhNDMtNTRm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8a17a43-54f9-47c5-9651-7ca96b44665b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 12:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>HealthCare Global Enterprises Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 17, 2026, to consider and approve a proposal for a fund raise through a rights issue. The company&apos;s trading window for dealing in securities will be closed for all designated persons from February 9, 2026, to February 26, 2026, in accordance with the Company&apos;s Code of Conduct for Prevention of Insider Trading.</p><ul><li>HealthCare Global Enterprises Ltd. to consider a fund raise by rights issue on Feb 17, 2026</li><li>The company&apos;s trading window for dealing in securities will be closed for all designated persons from Feb 9, 2026, to Feb 26, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f6471e06-c9e9-4a00-833a-8b17c3f51bf7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HealthCare Global Enterprises Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DATIWARE] Datiware Maritime Infra Ltd to Approve Q4 2025 Unaudited Financial Results on Feb 14, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Datiware+Maritime+Infra+Ltd&title=Datiware+Maritime+Infra+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+2025+Unaudited+Financial+Results+on+Feb+14%2C+2026&newsId=039efbc8-1f34-4047-8ee9-1361fe27f411&token=MDM5ZWZiYzgtMWYz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">039efbc8-1f34-4047-8ee9-1361fe27f411</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 08:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Datiware Maritime Infra Ltd has announced a Board of Directors meeting on February 14, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025. This is in accordance with Regulation 29(1)(a) of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Datiware Maritime Infra Ltd has scheduled a Board of Directors meeting on February 14, 2026.</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025.</li><li>This announcement is in compliance with Regulation 29(1)(a) of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ea2b9e8a-235d-406f-9f43-cc1919c3fd63.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Datiware Maritime Infra Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASINPET] Asian Petroproducts &amp; Exports Ltd to Approve Un-Audited Financial Statements for Q3 2025 on Feb 14, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ASIAN+PETROPRODUCTS+%26+EXPORTS+LTD.&title=Asian+Petroproducts+%26+Exports+Ltd+to+Approve+Un-Audited+Financial+Statements+for+Q3+2025+on+Feb+14%2C+2026&newsId=d7982c53-c57f-4404-8811-7321980f0bae&token=ZDc5ODJjNTMtYzU3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7982c53-c57f-4404-8811-7321980f0bae</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Asian Petroproducts &amp; Exports Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 14, 2026, to consider and approve the Un-Audited Financial Statements for the third quarter ended on December 31, 2025. In compliance with the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, the trading window for all designated persons as defined under the Company&apos;s Code of Conduct will be closed from January 1, 2026, to February 16, 2026. The trading window will reopen from February 17, 2026.</p><ul><li>Asian Petroproducts &amp; Exports Ltd to consider and approve Un-Audited Financial Statements for Q3 2025</li><li>Board Meeting scheduled on February 14, 2026</li><li>Trading window to remain closed from January 1, 2026, to February 16, 2026</li><li>Trading window to reopen from February 17, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7a20ab00-506c-4e44-95b7-e4d1a1d595fc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ASIAN PETROPRODUCTS & EXPORTS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASIL] Amit Spinning Industries Ltd to Approve Q4 Results on Feb 14, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Amit+Spinning+Industries+Ltd&title=Amit+Spinning+Industries+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+Results+on+Feb+14%2C+2026&newsId=f3a19a2b-a7cf-4dcf-a037-d5186516de21&token=ZjNhMTlhMmItYTdj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3a19a2b-a7cf-4dcf-a037-d5186516de21</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 07:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Amit Spinning Industries Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 14, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited Financial Results for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025. This meeting is in accordance with Regulation 29(1)(a) of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Amit Spinning Industries Ltd to consider and approve unaudited Financial Results for Q4 2025</li><li>Board Meeting scheduled for February 14, 2026</li><li>Meeting in accordance with SEBI Regulations 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e52bc0a5-51ba-42f4-83a6-783a585a2670.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Amit Spinning Industries Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHAQUAK] Shantanu Sheorey Aquakult Ltd to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q4 2025 in Board Meeting on 11th February 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHANTANU+SHEOREY+AQUAKULT+LTD.&title=Shantanu+Sheorey+Aquakult+Ltd+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q4+2025+in+Board+Meeting+on+11th+February+2026&newsId=5b44cdcc-001d-446a-8987-8d485569a643&token=NWI0NGNkY2MtMDAx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b44cdcc-001d-446a-8987-8d485569a643</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shantanu Sheorey Aquakult Ltd has announced a Board Meeting scheduled for 11th February 2026. The meeting will consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The trading window for dealing in shares of the company will be closed for Directors/ KMP‘s/ Designated Employees/ Connected Persons until 48 hours after the information is made public, in accordance with SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015 and the Company’s Code of Internal Procedures and Conduct for Regulating, Monitoring and Reporting of Trading by Insiders.</p><ul><li>Shantanu Sheorey Aquakult Ltd scheduled a Board Meeting on 11th February 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025</li><li>Trading window for dealing in shares of the company will be closed for Directors/ KMP‘s/ Designated Employees/ Connected Persons until 48 hours after the information is made public</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/13be18cc-5f67-4619-af93-6e7e2302156f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHANTANU SHEOREY AQUAKULT LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHK] S H Kelkar and Company Ltd Announces Q3 &amp; 9M FY2026 Results: Revenue from Operations at Rs. 1,718 crore, EBITDA at Rs. 182 crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=S+H+Kelkar+and+Company+Ltd&title=S+H+Kelkar+and+Company+Ltd+Announces+Q3+%26+9M+FY2026+Results%3A+Revenue+from+Operations+at+Rs.+1%2C718+crore%2C+EBITDA+at+Rs.+182+crore&newsId=7cc6ea3d-7fcd-49c3-8c29-a364dce31fbd&token=N2NjNmVhM2QtN2Zj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7cc6ea3d-7fcd-49c3-8c29-a364dce31fbd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>S H Kelkar and Company Limited (SHK), the largest Indian origin Fragrance and Flavour Company in India, has announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a revenue from operations of Rs. 1,718 crore and an EBITDA of Rs. 182 crore for the nine months ended FY2026. The company is investing in strategic initiatives for long-term growth, including strengthening global Creative Development Centres and expanding capacity. The US Creative Development Centre secured its first customer order during the quarter.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations at Rs. 1,718 crore for 9M FY2026</li><li>EBITDA stood at Rs. 182 crore for 9M FY2026</li><li>Adjusted EBITDA at Rs. 240 crore for 9M FY2026</li><li>US Creative Development Centre secured its first customer order</li><li>Investing in strategic initiatives for long-term growth</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f67c1c48-dded-4dfe-96f2-44d781cb4d87.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: S H Kelkar and Company Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BRIJLEAS] Brijlaxmi Leasing &amp; Finance Ltd to Approve Q3 Financial Statements on Feb 14, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BRIJLAXMI+LEASING+%26+FINANCE+LTD.&title=Brijlaxmi+Leasing+%26+Finance+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+Financial+Statements+on+Feb+14%2C+2026&newsId=421782e5-d455-44c0-9336-99c332e067c4&token=NDIxNzgyZTUtZDQ1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">421782e5-d455-44c0-9336-99c332e067c4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Brijlaxmi Leasing &amp; Finance Ltd has scheduled a Board Meeting on February 14, 2026, to consider and approve the Un-Audited Financial Statements for the Third Quarter ended on December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in securities of the Company will be closed from January 1, 2026, for all designated persons and will open 48 hours after the announcement of the results.</p><ul><li>Brijlaxmi Leasing &amp; Finance Ltd to hold a Board Meeting on February 14, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve Un-Audited Financial Statements for Q3 2025</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities to close on January 1, 2026</li><li>Trading window to open 48 hours after the announcement of results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8767e587-043c-4132-877b-b50096ef72bb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BRIJLAXMI LEASING & FINANCE LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>