<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:39:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ANUBHAV] Kaizen Agro Infrabuild Ltd: Changes in Management and Financial Results for Q3 &amp; Nine Months Ended December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Anubhav+Infrastructure+Ltd&title=Kaizen+Agro+Infrabuild+Ltd%3A+Changes+in+Management+and+Financial+Results+for+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Ended+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=d5641ea6-79c3-42aa-9339-20d71f942284&token=ZDU2NDFlYTYtNzlj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5641ea6-79c3-42aa-9339-20d71f942284</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:39:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kaizen Agro Infrabuild Ltd announced the outcomes of its Board Meeting on February 13, 2026. The meeting led to the approval of un-audited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company also announced the resignation of Mrs. Pooja Agarwal as Chief Financial Officer and the appointment of Mr. Pawan Kumar Jhunjhunwala as her successor. Additionally, the registered office address of the company will be changed. </p><ul><li>Approval of un-audited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Resignation of Mrs. Pooja Agarwal as Chief Financial Officer</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Pawan Kumar Jhunjhunwala as the new Chief Financial Officer</li><li>Change of registered office address of the company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b7ceea21-2f87-4299-94d0-4d103a63dbfb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Anubhav Infrastructure Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KAMDHENU] Kamdhenu Ltd Board Approves Purchase of Immovable Property Worth ~Rs. 16 Crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kamdhenu+Ltd&title=Kamdhenu+Ltd+Board+Approves+Purchase+of+Immovable+Property+Worth+~Rs.+16+Crore&newsId=e14a1e38-c69a-411d-9e5b-7abd81070fb8&token=ZTE0YTFlMzgtYzY5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e14a1e38-c69a-411d-9e5b-7abd81070fb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:39:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Kamdhenu Ltd announced that their Board of Directors has approved the proposal for purchasing an immovable property situated at Vill. Hajipur, Tehsil Kotkasim, District Alwar, Rajasthan. The purchase is subject to completion of due diligence, title verification, compliance checks, property inspections, and necessary approvals from Bhiwadi Integrated Development Authority (BIDA) or other authorities. The property has a plot size of approximately 23,600 Sq. Mtr. with special rights like the right to appoint directors and first right to share subscription in case of issuance of shares.</p><ul><li>Kamdhenu Ltd Board approved the proposal for purchasing an immovable property worth approximately Rs. 16 Crore.</li><li>The property is located at Vill. Hajipur, Tehsil Kotkasim, District Alwar, Rajasthan with a plot size of approximately 23,600 Sq. Mtr.</li><li>The purchase is subject to due diligence, title verification, and necessary approvals from BIDA or other authorities.</li><li>The property comes with special rights like the right to appoint directors and first right to share subscription in case of issuance of shares.</li><li>The transaction does not fall under related party transactions.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ce5d2e9c-c52a-4031-9171-68b6a285a13e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kamdhenu Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NCLIND] NCL Industries Ltd Announces Q3 Results for FY 2025-26: Declares Interim Dividend of 15% and Postal Ballot Notice</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NCL+INDUSTRIES+LTD.-%24&title=NCL+Industries+Ltd+Announces+Q3+Results+for+FY+2025-26%3A+Declares+Interim+Dividend+of+15%25+and+Postal+Ballot+Notice&newsId=2d79c425-88ba-424f-a7bf-157d6ac56116&token=MmQ3OWM0MjUtODhi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2d79c425-88ba-424f-a7bf-157d6ac56116</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>NCL Industries Ltd has announced the outcome of its Board meeting held on 13 February 2026. The company has reported the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at ₹ 1,29,388.21 lakhs for the quarter and ₹ 1,41,083.67 lakhs for the nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company has declared an interim dividend of 15% for the financial year 2025-26. A postal ballot notice has been issued for the appointment of Dr. Durga Prasad Subramanyam Anapindi as an Independent Director of the company.</p><ul><li>NCL Industries Ltd announces Q3 results for FY 2025-26</li><li>Revenue from operations stands at ₹ 1,29,388.21 lakhs for the quarter</li><li>Company declares an interim dividend of 15% for the financial year 2025-26</li><li>Postal ballot notice issued for the appointment of an Independent Director</li><li>Unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results reported for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f6ef852a-cad9-4c5e-973b-89e712835295.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NCL INDUSTRIES LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INSILCO] Insilco Ltd. Announces Q3 Results, Appoints New Managing Director, and Provides Update on Voluntary Liquidation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Insilco+Ltd&title=Insilco+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+Results%2C+Appoints+New+Managing+Director%2C+and+Provides+Update+on+Voluntary+Liquidation&newsId=14705dca-612f-477b-a390-523d477593eb&token=MTQ3MDVkY2EtNjEy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">14705dca-612f-477b-a390-523d477593eb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:38:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Insilco Ltd. has announced its un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company has reported a loss before exceptional items and tax for the period. The Board has accepted the resignation of Ms. Chaitali Talele as Managing Director and appointed Ms. Shivangi Negi as the new Managing Director. Ms. Deepa Jha has been appointed as an Additional Director. The company has also provided an update on its voluntary liquidation process. The liquidation process commenced on June 25, 2021, and the company has settled claims amounting to INR 97.18 lakhs.</p><ul><li>Insilco Ltd. reports loss for Q3 2025</li><li>Ms. Chaitali Talele resigns as Managing Director</li><li>Ms. Shivangi Negi appointed as new Managing Director</li><li>Ms. Deepa Jha appointed as Additional Director</li><li>Update on voluntary liquidation process</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bca4f464-1f52-4d42-9e02-76afc8752e86.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Insilco Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[YUKEN] Yuken India Ltd Announces Q3 2025 Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=YUKEN+INDIA+LTD.-%24&title=Yuken+India+Ltd+Announces+Q3+2025+Financial+Results&newsId=7f9a85f6-52ad-4a0a-9c44-af8b266df819&token=N2Y5YTg1ZjYtNTJh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7f9a85f6-52ad-4a0a-9c44-af8b266df819</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Yuken India Limited has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The Board of Directors approved the results in a meeting that started at 12:50 PM IST and ended at 14:50 PM IST on February 13, 2026. The financial results were reviewed by Walker Chandiok &amp; Co LLP, the independent auditor, in accordance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Yuken India Ltd announced its unaudited financial results for Q3 2025.</li><li>The results were approved by the Board of Directors in a meeting held on February 13, 2026.</li><li>The financial results were reviewed by Walker Chandiok &amp; Co LLP.</li><li>The review was conducted in accordance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/543bc6f3-41ec-4c63-80c5-0bfdfeab6d63.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: YUKEN INDIA LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDITALIA] Inditalia Refcon Ltd Approves Un-Audited Financial Results for Quarter and Nine Months Ended - December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Inditalia+Refcon+Ltd&title=Inditalia+Refcon+Ltd+Approves+Un-Audited+Financial+Results+for+Quarter+and+Nine+Months+Ended+-+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=388ae834-b97d-46d6-985f-289f45a93cfd&token=Mzg4YWU4MzQtYjk3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">388ae834-b97d-46d6-985f-289f45a93cfd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:37:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Inditalia Refcon Limited, a company with CIN No. L28129MH1986PLC039591, held a Board of Directors meeting on February 13, 2026, and approved the un-audited financial results for the quarter and half year ended December 31, 2025. The approval includes unaudited financial results, limited review report, and integrated filing with required disclosures. There were no deviations, defaults, or related party transactions during the period. The company&apos;s financial position remains stable with no material misstatements in the financial statements.</p><ul><li>Approval of un-audited financial results for the quarter and half year ended December 31, 2025</li><li>No deviations, defaults, or related party transactions during the period</li><li>Stable financial position with no material misstatements in the financial statements</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/09c8450d-e276-4e20-a5a8-cbc517890c51.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Inditalia Refcon Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BOMOXY-B1] Bombay Oxygen Investments Ltd. Approves Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended 31st December, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Bombay+Oxygen+Investments+Ltd&title=Bombay+Oxygen+Investments+Ltd.+Approves+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+31st+December%2C+2025&newsId=c9c1a3e6-78af-4d72-bf49-febf074a7d38&token=YzljMWEzZTYtNzhh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9c1a3e6-78af-4d72-bf49-febf074a7d38</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:37:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bombay Oxygen Investments Ltd. held a Board Meeting on 13th February, 2026, where they approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The company&apos;s total income stands at Rs. 451 lakhs for the quarter and Rs. 3,379 lakhs for the nine months ended. The net profit for the quarter is Rs. 1,140 lakhs and Rs. 1,413 lakhs for the nine months ended.</p><ul><li>Unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December, 2025 approved.</li><li>Total income for the quarter is Rs. 451 lakhs and Rs. 3,379 lakhs for the nine months ended.</li><li>Net profit for the quarter is Rs. 1,140 lakhs and Rs. 1,413 lakhs for the nine months ended.</li><li>The company is a Non Banking Financial Company with no activities other than Investments.</li><li>No subsidiary/associate/joint venture entities for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2222ec3f-fb5c-43a2-b3bb-a5a39d642aca.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Bombay Oxygen Investments Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ICIL] Indo Count Industries Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Results for FY 2025-2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDO+COUNT+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Indo+Count+Industries+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+FY+2025-2026&newsId=a2eca10b-9430-4db1-a4dc-77d60ff7fdf1&token=YTJlY2ExMGItOTQz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2eca10b-9430-4db1-a4dc-77d60ff7fdf1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indo Count Industries Ltd has announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company reported a net profit of Rs. XX Lakhs for Q3 and Rs. XX Lakhs for the nine-month period. The Board of Directors approved these results in a meeting held on 13th February 2026. The results are prepared in compliance with Indian Accounting Standards (IndAS) as notified under section 133 of the Companies Act, 2013.</p><ul><li>Indo Count Industries Ltd reported a net profit of Rs. XX Lakhs for Q3 FY 2025-2026.</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at Rs. XX Lakhs for Q3 FY 2025-2026.</li><li>The Board of Directors approved the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results in a meeting held on 13th February 2026.</li><li>The results are prepared in compliance with Indian Accounting Standards (IndAS) as notified under section 133 of the Companies Act, 2013.</li><li>The company is primarily engaged in the activity of manufacture of textile products.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/469efe90-7f69-4fd1-aa30-594d3c4e5c12.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDO COUNT INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VIJAYA] Vijaya Diagnostic Centre Ltd Reports 21.4% YoY Revenue Growth in Q3 FY26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vijaya+Diagnostic+Centre+Ltd&title=Vijaya+Diagnostic+Centre+Ltd+Reports+21.4%25+YoY+Revenue+Growth+in+Q3+FY26&newsId=94894b00-feac-4536-8895-cfc482aa1b1e&token=OTQ4OTRiMDAtZmVh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">94894b00-feac-4536-8895-cfc482aa1b1e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Vijaya Diagnostic Centre Ltd, one of India’s leading integrated diagnostic chains, has announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31 December 2025. The company reported a consolidated revenue from operations of 860.5 million rupees in Q3 FY26, representing a 28.2% year-over-year growth. The EBITDA margin stood at 41.9% and 40.6% for Q3 FY26 and 9M FY26 respectively. The profit after tax (PAT) was 21.0% for both Q3 FY26 and 9M FY26.</p><ul><li>21.4% YoY revenue growth in Q3 FY26</li><li>17.1% YoY revenue growth in 9M FY26</li><li>EBITDA margin at 41.9% in Q3 FY26</li><li>EBITDA margin at 40.6% in 9M FY26</li><li>PAT margin at 21.0% in both Q3 FY26 and 9M FY26</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f952dbbb-259d-4048-bd32-360c402464b9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vijaya Diagnostic Centre Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JUSTO] Promoter Puspamitra Das Acquires 14,000 Equity Shares of Justo Realfintech Ltd Through Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Justo+Realfintech+Ltd&title=Promoter+Puspamitra+Das+Acquires+14%2C000+Equity+Shares+of+Justo+Realfintech+Ltd+Through+Open+Market&newsId=862ebb8e-cc85-485e-b620-a9cc821c84a4&token=ODYyZWJiOGUtY2M4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">862ebb8e-cc85-485e-b620-a9cc821c84a4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 09:35:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Puspamitra Das, a promoter of Justo Realfintech Ltd, has acquired 14,000 equity shares of the company through the open market. This acquisition represents 0.074% of the total diluted share and voting capital of the company. The acquisition was made on 13th February 2026. The total share and voting capital of the company remains unchanged at INR 18,79,81,420 consisting of 1,87,98,142 Equity Shares of Rs. 10 each.</p><ul><li>Puspamitra Das, a promoter of Justo Realfintech Ltd, has acquired 14,000 equity shares of the company.</li><li>The acquisition represents 0.074% of the total diluted share and voting capital of the company.</li><li>The acquisition was made on 13th February 2026.</li><li>The total share and voting capital of the company remains unchanged.</li><li>The shares were acquired through the open market.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/B6BBF8BF_FCEA_460A_B5B4_960FF8960685_150304.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Justo Realfintech Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>