<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 12:39:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[COMFINCAP] Comfort Fincap Ltd to Approve Unaudited Financial Results on Jan 15, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=COMFORT+FINCAP+LTD.&title=Comfort+Fincap+Ltd+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+on+Jan+15%2C+2026&newsId=1a6d905e-c716-4cc2-9e0b-1b9761cf3888&token=MWE2ZDkwNWUtYzcx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a6d905e-c716-4cc2-9e0b-1b9761cf3888</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 12:37:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Comfort Fincap Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 15, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will be held at the corporate office of the company in accordance with the Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The trading window for dealing in securities of the company will remain closed from January 01, 2026, to January 17, 2026.</p><ul><li>Comfort Fincap Ltd to consider and approve unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Meeting scheduled on January 15, 2026, in accordance with SEBI Listing Regulations</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities of the company to remain closed from January 01, 2026, to January 17, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/359cf8d8-73c7-417a-bf33-be116b602a2f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: COMFORT FINCAP LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SKFINDIA] SKF India Ltd Announces Resignation of Director Mr. Karl Robin Joakim Landholm</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SKF+India+Ltd&title=SKF+India+Ltd+Announces+Resignation+of+Director+Mr.+Karl+Robin+Joakim+Landholm&newsId=3fbac9da-38cb-4a88-822e-ec538570a3f0&token=M2ZiYWM5ZGEtMzhj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3fbac9da-38cb-4a88-822e-ec538570a3f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 12:35:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SKF India Ltd has announced the resignation of Mr. Karl Robin Joakim Landholm as a Director (Non-Executive, Non-Independent) of the company with effect from the closure of business hours of 12th January 2026. The resignation is due to his other pre-occupancies and commitments. The company has complied with the necessary disclosure requirements as per Regulation 30 of SEBI LODR and the SEBI Master Circular No. SEBI/HO/CFD/PoD2/CIR/P/0155 dated 11 November 2024.</p><ul><li>Mr. Karl Robin Joakim Landholm has resigned as Director (Non-Executive, Non-Independent) of SKF India Ltd.</li><li>The resignation is effective from the closure of business hours of 12th January 2026.</li><li>The resignation is due to Mr. Landholm&apos;s other pre-occupancies and commitments.</li><li>The company has complied with the necessary disclosure requirements as per Regulation 30 of SEBI LODR and the SEBI Master Circular No. SEBI/HO/CFD/PoD2/CIR/P/0155 dated 11 November 2024.</li><li>Mr. Landholm has thanked the Board Members for their support and guidance during his tenure.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8e4ffd1f-5487-4973-b1c5-95ec01f182c0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SKF India Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[URJAGLOBA] Urja Global Ltd Appoints Mr. Manoj Aggarwal as Deputy Company Secretary</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=URJA+GLOBAL+LTD.&title=Urja+Global+Ltd+Appoints+Mr.+Manoj+Aggarwal+as+Deputy+Company+Secretary&newsId=98d4cfa5-5d21-42ed-976e-6eb083e7157e&token=OThkNGNmYTUtNWQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98d4cfa5-5d21-42ed-976e-6eb083e7157e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 12:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Urja Global Ltd has appointed Mr. Manoj Aggarwal as Deputy Company Secretary with effect from 12 January 2026. The company also proposes to regularize his appointment as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer at the forthcoming meeting of the Board of Directors, subject to necessary approvals. Mr. Aggarwal is a Fellow Company Secretary with the qualification number FCS-6652. He is not related to any Director or Key Managerial Personnel of the Company and is not debarred from holding office by any regulatory authority.</p><ul><li>Urja Global Ltd appoints Mr. Manoj Aggarwal as Deputy Company Secretary</li><li>Mr. Aggarwal&apos;s appointment to be regularized as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer at the next Board Meeting</li><li>Mr. Aggarwal is a Fellow Company Secretary with qualification FCS-6652</li><li>Mr. Aggarwal is not related to any Director or Key Managerial Personnel of the Company</li><li>Mr. Aggarwal is not debarred from holding office by any regulatory authority</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5891c245-2b62-49d7-8121-17d8e692dd8a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: URJA GLOBAL LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RFLL] Statutory Auditor J. Singh &amp; Associates Resigns from Rita Finance and Leasing Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Rita+Finance+and+Leasing+Ltd&title=Statutory+Auditor+J.+Singh+%26+Associates+Resigns+from+Rita+Finance+and+Leasing+Ltd&newsId=981271bc-a752-4a6f-b29d-af1eb074589b&token=OTgxMjcxYmMtYTc1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">981271bc-a752-4a6f-b29d-af1eb074589b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 12:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Auditor</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>J. Singh &amp; Associates, the Statutory Auditor of Rita Finance and Leasing Ltd, has resigned with immediate effect. The resignation is due to the completion of the maximum permissible tenure of 3 years as per the RBI Guidelines. The firm has expressed gratitude to the Board and Management for their cooperation during their tenure.</p><ul><li>J. Singh &amp; Associates resigns as Statutory Auditor of Rita Finance and Leasing Ltd.</li><li>The resignation is due to the completion of the maximum permissible tenure of 3 years as per the RBI Guidelines.</li><li>The firm has expressed gratitude to the Board and Management for their cooperation during their tenure.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/851a160d-2fea-4a97-a018-8118b043b791.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Rita Finance and Leasing Ltd | Category: Auditor</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BLUECHIP] Blue Chip India Ltd Board Meeting Approves EGM Notice, Appoints Scrutinizer, and Grants E-Voting Rights</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BLUE+CHIP+INDIA+LTD.&title=Blue+Chip+India+Ltd+Board+Meeting+Approves+EGM+Notice%2C+Appoints+Scrutinizer%2C+and+Grants+E-Voting+Rights&newsId=29bf4e0f-faf5-44d7-be57-75d044a77af2&token=MjliZjRlMGYtZmFm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29bf4e0f-faf5-44d7-be57-75d044a77af2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 12:31:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Blue Chip India Ltd held a Board Meeting on 12th January, 2026, and approved several key matters. The company has rescheduled the Extraordinary General Meeting (EGM) of the Financial Year 2025-2026 to be held on Friday, 6th February, 2026, at 03:00 p.m. through Video-conference (VC)/ Other Audio-Visual Means (OAVM). The Board appointed CS Suprabhat Chakraborty as a Scrutinizer to Scrutinize the e-voting and submit their report as prescribed under Companies Act, 2013. Blue Chip India Ltd will provide e-voting facilities to shareholders for the ensuing EGM, with Central Depository Services (India) Limited (CDSL) appointed to provide remote e-voting and Voting at the Extraordinary General Meeting (EGM) facility. The share transfer books of the company will be closed for the EGM.</p><ul><li>Blue Chip India Ltd rescheduled the Extraordinary General Meeting (EGM) of the Financial Year 2025-2026 for Friday, 6th February, 2026</li><li>CS Suprabhat Chakraborty appointed as Scrutinizer for the e-voting process</li><li>E-voting facilities to be provided to shareholders for the ensuing EGM</li><li>Central Depository Services (India) Limited (CDSL) appointed for remote e-voting and Voting at the Extraordinary General Meeting (EGM) facility</li><li>Share transfer books of the company will be closed for the EGM</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b76c7205-53f1-4cc0-b510-b71ef4198eed.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BLUE CHIP INDIA LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SKFINDIA] SKF India Ltd Announces Resignation of Director Mukund Vasudevan</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SKF+India+Ltd&title=SKF+India+Ltd+Announces+Resignation+of+Director+Mukund+Vasudevan&newsId=b4298b41-a9d0-4f68-862e-5b6b96a761e2&token=YjQyOThiNDEtYTlk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4298b41-a9d0-4f68-862e-5b6b96a761e2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 12:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SKF India Ltd has announced the resignation of Mr. Mukund Vasudevan as Director (Non-executive Non-independent) with effect from the closure of business hours on 12th January 2026. The resignation is due to his other occupancies and commitments. The company has complied with the necessary disclosure requirements as per Regulation 30 of SEBI LODR Regulations and the SEBI Master Circular No. SEBI/HO/CFD/PoD2/CIR/P/0155 dated 11th November 2024.</p><ul><li>SKF India Ltd announces resignation of Director Mukund Vasudevan</li><li>Resignation is due to Mr. Vasudevan&apos;s other occupancies and commitments</li><li>Resignation effective from the closure of business hours on 12th January 2026</li><li>Company has complied with necessary disclosure requirements</li><li>SKF India Ltd thanks Mr. Vasudevan for his contributions</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f8228760-c72a-4fb3-a899-05261f521088.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SKF India Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LERTHAI] Lerthai Finance Ltd: No Deviations in Public, Rights or Preferential Issues for Q4 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Lerthai+Finance+Ltd&title=Lerthai+Finance+Ltd%3A+No+Deviations+in+Public%2C+Rights+or+Preferential+Issues+for+Q4+2025&newsId=12a53bc3-cf6c-446a-8923-d4da7ffb267d&token=MTJhNTNiYzMtY2Y2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12a53bc3-cf6c-446a-8923-d4da7ffb267d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 12:31:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Lerthai Finance Ltd has released a statement of deviation or variation under Reg 32(1) of SEBI (Listing Obligation Disclosure Requirements), Regulation, 2015 for the quarter ended on December 2025. The company has reported no public issue, rights issue, preferential issue, etc. during the quarter ended on December 31, 2025. Therefore, the statement of deviation or variation in public issue, rights issue, preferential issue, etc. under Regulation 32(1) of SEBI (Listing Obligations Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015 for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025 is not applicable to the company.</p><ul><li>Lerthai Finance Ltd reported no deviations in public, rights, or preferential issues for Q4 2025.</li><li>The company has not issued any public, rights, or preferential shares during the quarter ended on December 31, 2025.</li><li>The statement of deviation or variation under Reg 32(1) of SEBI (Listing Obligation Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015 is not applicable for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/70ef3506-ec20-4824-bdbc-8b93162fe3d5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Lerthai Finance Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ATLANTAELE] Atlanta Electricals Ltd. to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on Jan 19, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Atlanta+Electricals+Ltd&title=Atlanta+Electricals+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+Jan+19%2C+2026&newsId=868a67b8-a5df-4e40-8d4f-046362cc22d6&token=ODY4YTY3YjgtYTVk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">868a67b8-a5df-4e40-8d4f-046362cc22d6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 12:31:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Atlanta Electricals Ltd. has announced a Board of Directors meeting on January 19, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The trading window for dealing in securities of the company will remain closed till 48 hours after the declaration of the unaudited financial results. This is in accordance with the company&apos;s Code of Conduct for Prohibition of Insider Trading, framed pursuant to SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Atlanta Electricals Ltd. to consider and approve Q3 and nine months financial results for 2025</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities of the company to be closed till 48 hours after the declaration of financial results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4f5065b8-7ae9-4b8b-9842-d9950840cc50.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Atlanta Electricals Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PREMIERENE] Premier Energies Clarifies Capacity Addition Information, No New Unpublished Price Sensitive Info</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Premier+Energies+Ltd&title=Premier+Energies+Clarifies+Capacity+Addition+Information%2C+No+New+Unpublished+Price+Sensitive+Info&newsId=4314913c-8450-497f-956e-d534b0aab48d&token=NDMxNDkxM2MtODQ1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4314913c-8450-497f-956e-d534b0aab48d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 12:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Premier Energies Ltd. has clarified a news item appearing on ndtvprofit.com on 12th January 2026 regarding their capacity additions. The company stated that they had already disclosed their capacity additions through various press releases, disclosures, and board meeting outcomes. The capacity expansion plan was detailed in the LODR 30 Disclosure dated 17th May 2025 and the outcome of the board meeting. The company aims to achieve 10.6 GW of solar cell capacity and 11.1 GW of solar module capacity by September 2026. The company confirmed that there is no unpublished price sensitive information pending to be disclosed to the stock exchanges and no regulatory or legal proceedings are being initiated in relation to the aforementioned announcement.</p><ul><li>Premier Energies clarified capacity addition information</li><li>Company had already disclosed capacity additions through press releases, disclosures, and board meetings</li><li>Aims to achieve 10.6 GW of solar cell capacity and 11.1 GW of solar module capacity by September 2026</li><li>No unpublished price sensitive information pending</li><li>No regulatory or legal proceedings being initiated</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bece68f4-efc0-4bdd-b0c2-5eac6ef1def8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Premier Energies Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PIDILITIND] Pidilite Industries Ltd to Consider and Approve Q3 Financial Results on 3 February, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PIDILITE+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Pidilite+Industries+Ltd+to+Consider+and+Approve+Q3+Financial+Results+on+3+February%2C+2026&newsId=a58f5370-fa6e-42d3-be55-74a1ecd46cf0&token=YTU4ZjUzNzAtZmE2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a58f5370-fa6e-42d3-be55-74a1ecd46cf0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 12:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pidilite Industries Ltd, a renowned company, has announced that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on 3 February, 2026. The agenda includes the consideration and approval of the unaudited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended on 31st December, 2025. The meeting is in accordance with Regulation 29 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Pidilite Industries Ltd to consider and approve Q3 financial results on 3 February, 2026.</li><li>The meeting is in accordance with Regulation 29 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/49a91408-64b9-4d7d-8ea4-23452dd096a6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PIDILITE INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>