<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 18:24:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[POWERGRID] Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd Announces Changes in Senior Management</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=POWER+GRID+CORPORATION+OF+INDIA+LTD.&title=Power+Grid+Corporation+of+India+Ltd+Announces+Changes+in+Senior+Management&newsId=b6eebd42-5486-47cd-93e4-a5cb30aa22a6&token=YjZlZWJkNDItNTQ4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6eebd42-5486-47cd-93e4-a5cb30aa22a6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 16:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd has announced changes in its senior management. The Board of Directors has approved the promotion/appointment of Sanjay Sharma, Abhay Kumar, Abhinav Verma, Vineeta Agarwal, M S Hejib, Akhilesh Kumar Dixit, Kumud Wadhwa, and Harinarayanan Puthan Kalam as Executive Directors. These changes are effective from 25th January 2026. The new appointees bring a combined experience of over 200 years in various fields including telecom marketing, commercial, corporate planning, asset monetization, electrical engineering, project management, and human resource management.</p><ul><li>Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd has announced changes in its senior management.</li><li>Sanjay Sharma, Abhay Kumar, Abhinav Verma, Vineeta Agarwal, M S Hejib, Akhilesh Kumar Dixit, Kumud Wadhwa, and Harinarayanan Puthan Kalam have been appointed as Executive Directors.</li><li>The new appointees bring a combined experience of over 200 years in various fields.</li><li>The appointments are effective from 25th January 2026.</li><li>The new appointees have diverse experience in telecom marketing, commercial, corporate planning, asset monetization, electrical engineering, project management, and human resource management.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b5bb03d8-7bd7-452c-b4e7-1f66ae477904.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: POWER GRID CORPORATION OF INDIA LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MEDPLUS] Medplus Health Services Subsidiary Faces Three-Day Drug License Suspension in Telangana</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Medplus+Health+Services+Ltd&title=Medplus+Health+Services+Subsidiary+Faces+Three-Day+Drug+License+Suspension+in+Telangana&newsId=1ec71efd-7016-4a68-8e60-0fdbcc0d439d&token=MWVjNzFlZmQtNzAx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1ec71efd-7016-4a68-8e60-0fdbcc0d439d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 16:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Medplus Health Services Ltd. has announced that its subsidiary, Optival Health Solutions Private Limited, has received a suspension order for a Drug License of a store situated in the state of Telangana. The suspension is issued under Rule 65 of the Drugs and Cosmetics Act, 1945 and Drugs and Cosmetics Rules, 1945. The order, issued by the Assistant Director, Drugs Control License, Telangana, will result in a potential revenue loss of Rs 2.94 lacs for the three-day suspension period. The company will post the order on its website and on the websites of BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange of India Ltd.</p><ul><li>Medplus Health Services&apos; subsidiary, Optival Health Solutions Private Limited, receives a three-day suspension order for a Drug License in Telangana.</li><li>The suspension is issued under Rule 65 of the Drugs and Cosmetics Act, 1945 and Drugs and Cosmetics Rules, 1945.</li><li>The suspension will potentially cause a revenue loss of Rs 2.94 lacs for the three-day period.</li><li>The order is available on the company&apos;s website and the websites of BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange of India Ltd.</li><li>Medplus Health Services is taking necessary actions to comply with the order and manage the impact on their financials.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e53ca5ad-e9bb-4a91-b088-4e53f18af778.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Medplus Health Services Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[POWERGRID] Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd Announces Changes in Senior Management</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=POWER+GRID+CORPORATION+OF+INDIA+LTD.&title=Power+Grid+Corporation+of+India+Ltd+Announces+Changes+in+Senior+Management&newsId=c01ecd61-792e-40f3-a8f2-d569b3cd6f29&token=YzAxZWNkNjEtNzky</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c01ecd61-792e-40f3-a8f2-d569b3cd6f29</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 16:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd has announced changes in its senior management. The Board of Directors has approved the promotion/appointment of five senior level officials as Executive Directors (ED) effective from 25th January, 2026. The new appointees include Sanjay Sharma, Abhay Kumar, Abhinav Verma, Vineeta Agarwal, and M S Hejib. The company has also announced the promotion of Akhilesh Kumar Dixit and Harinarayanan Puthan Kalam to Executive Directors. Kumud Wadhwa has been appointed as Executive Director (ERP &amp; IT).</p><ul><li>Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd has announced changes in its senior management.</li><li>Five senior level officials have been promoted/appointed as Executive Directors (ED) effective from 25th January, 2026.</li><li>Akhilesh Kumar Dixit and Harinarayanan Puthan Kalam have been promoted to Executive Directors.</li><li>Kumud Wadhwa has been appointed as Executive Director (ERP &amp; IT).</li><li>The new appointees bring a combined experience of over 180 years in various fields including telecom marketing, commercial, corporate planning, asset monetization, substation engineering, asset management, international consultancy, engineering functions, HVDC technology, corporate planning, distribution management system, HR management, and IT.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8fa4d9cc-494f-4f07-866e-f22a095102ec.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: POWER GRID CORPORATION OF INDIA LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JPASSOCIAT] Jaiprakash Associates Executive Director Released on Interim Bail</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JAIPRAKASH+ASSOCIATES+LTD.&title=Jaiprakash+Associates+Executive+Director+Released+on+Interim+Bail&newsId=43d5b509-f93d-4f54-86e5-a39eea760ffa&token=NDNkNWI1MDktZjkz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43d5b509-f93d-4f54-86e5-a39eea760ffa</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 16:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jaiprakash Associates Ltd. has informed that Shri Manoj Gaur, the Executive Director of the company, who was arrested by the Enforcement Directorate in connection with an ongoing investigation under the Prevention of Money Laundering Act (PMLA) initiated against Jaypee Infratech Ltd. and Jaiprakash Associates Ltd., has been released on Interim Bail for 14 days by the Hon’ble Court of Additional Sessions Judge-7, Patiala House, New Delhi on 24th January 2026. This information is in continuation to the disclosure made on 13th November 2025.</p><ul><li>Shri Manoj Gaur, Executive Director of Jaiprakash Associates Ltd., has been released on Interim Bail for 14 days.</li><li>The bail was granted by the Hon’ble Court of Additional Sessions Judge-7, Patiala House, New Delhi on 24th January 2026.</li><li>Gaur was arrested in connection with an ongoing investigation under the Prevention of Money Laundering Act (PMLA) against Jaypee Infratech Ltd. and Jaiprakash Associates Ltd.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4e9fdfed-449e-4ddb-a022-54f838454295.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JAIPRAKASH ASSOCIATES LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SPICEISL] Spice Islands Industries Ltd. Receives First Export Order from UAE Worth INR 13.8 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SPICE+ISLANDS+APPARELS+LTD.-%24&title=Spice+Islands+Industries+Ltd.+Receives+First+Export+Order+from+UAE+Worth+INR+13.8+Million&newsId=4b948b87-9115-4847-8a54-0bf930bc87fd&token=NGI5NDhiODctOTEx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4b948b87-9115-4847-8a54-0bf930bc87fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Spice Islands Industries Ltd. has announced its first international purchase order from Emazing Deals, UAE, for the supply of perfumes, amounting to USD 166,136 (INR 13.8 million). The company will execute this order by placing a corresponding purchase order with Sterling Perfumes Industries LLC, UAE, the owner of the globally recognized fragrance brand ARMAF. This strategic milestone marks the beginning of the company&apos;s Global Trade vertical, focusing on fragrances, personal care, and lifestyle products. The management believes this order reflects international confidence in their execution capabilities and signals their intent to expand into global markets, particularly across the Middle East and other high-growth regions.</p><ul><li>Spice Islands Industries Ltd. receives first international purchase order from Emazing Deals, UAE, worth INR 13.8 million.</li><li>The order will be executed by placing a corresponding purchase order with Sterling Perfumes Industries LLC, UAE, the owner of the ARMAF brand.</li><li>This strategic milestone marks the beginning of the company&apos;s Global Trade vertical.</li><li>The focus is on fragrances, personal care, and lifestyle products.</li><li>The management sees this order as a reflection of international confidence in their execution capabilities and an intent to expand into global markets.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2ea73fcf-3d9c-4c57-ae7f-a2fbeb17f2f4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SPICE ISLANDS APPARELS LTD.-$ | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CUPIDALBV] Cupid Breweries And Distilleries Ltd to Approve Q2 and Q3 Financial Results on January 29, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Cupid+Breweries+And+Distilleries+Ltd&title=Cupid+Breweries+And+Distilleries+Ltd+to+Approve+Q2+and+Q3+Financial+Results+on+January+29%2C+2026&newsId=d30c63fe-47d8-4f7a-adaf-264152330114&token=ZDMwYzYzZmUtNDdk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d30c63fe-47d8-4f7a-adaf-264152330114</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:01:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cupid Breweries And Distilleries Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 29, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and half year ended September 30, 2025, along with the Limited Review Report of the Auditor. The Board will also consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, along with the Limited Review Report of the Auditor. The information will be made available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Cupid Breweries And Distilleries Ltd to consider and approve Q2 and Q3 financial results for the year 2025</li><li>The meeting is scheduled for January 29, 2026</li><li>The results will be accompanied by the Limited Review Report of the Auditor</li><li>The information will be made available on the company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5d8a0d4b-3ecc-4242-837c-a403b97f3d52.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Cupid Breweries And Distilleries Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VINYOFL] Vinyoflex Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q4 Results of 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VINYOFLEX+LTD.&title=Vinyoflex+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q4+Results+of+2025&newsId=21d57361-cd6d-46b1-ba7e-66fdd7417851&token=MjFkNTczNjEtY2Q2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21d57361-cd6d-46b1-ba7e-66fdd7417851</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vinyoflex Ltd has announced a Board of Directors meeting on February 09, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The meeting is in accordance with Regulation 29 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The trading window for dealing in securities of the Company will be closed for the Designated Persons from January 01, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of the Unaudited Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Vinyoflex Ltd scheduled a Board of Directors meeting on February 09, 2026, to approve Q4 results of 2025.</li><li>The meeting is in accordance with Regulation 29 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li><li>The trading window for dealing in securities of the Company will be closed for the Designated Persons from January 01, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of the Unaudited Financial Results.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bb8812d0-a24a-44aa-b62a-95b8c6fb6e99.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VINYOFLEX LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GARGI] PNGS Gargi Fashion Jewellery Ltd Opens New Exclusive Brand Store</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PNGS+Gargi+Fashion+Jewellery+Ltd&title=PNGS+Gargi+Fashion+Jewellery+Ltd+Opens+New+Exclusive+Brand+Store&newsId=f0299696-70e1-4b12-97d6-a9aa2073e719&token=ZjAyOTk2OTYtNzBl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0299696-70e1-4b12-97d6-a9aa2073e719</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>PNGS Gargi Fashion Jewellery Ltd has announced the opening of its new exclusive brand store at Unit No 4, B Wing, Ground Floor of Nyati Plaza of Project Nyati Enthral, S. No 12, Hissa No 1A, Kharadi, Pune, Maharashtra -411014. This announcement was made on January 25, 2026, in accordance with Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirement) Rules, 2015.</p><ul><li>PNGS Gargi Fashion Jewellery Ltd has opened a new exclusive brand store</li><li>The store is located at Unit No 4, B Wing, Ground Floor of Nyati Plaza of Project Nyati Enthral, S. No 12, Hissa No 1A, Kharadi, Pune, Maharashtra -411014</li><li>The opening was announced on January 25, 2026</li><li>The announcement was made in accordance with Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirement) Rules, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2124e3f4-e437-4aa3-96e9-fbd1eae366d2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PNGS Gargi Fashion Jewellery Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EVERESTIND] Everest Industries Extends Land Sale Timeline to March 31, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=EVEREST+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Everest+Industries+Extends+Land+Sale+Timeline+to+March+31%2C+2026&newsId=299e7150-622c-4e0e-953d-130beb3f2647&token=Mjk5ZTcxNTAtNjIy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">299e7150-622c-4e0e-953d-130beb3f2647</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Everest Industries Ltd. has announced an extension of the timeline for the sale of its land at Podanur. The sale, which was earlier estimated to be concluded on the day of the announcement, has been extended till March 31, 2026. This extension is due to the progress of needed government approvals and has been mutually agreed upon by the Company and G Square Realtors Private Limited. This intimation is given pursuant to Regulation 30 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Everest Industries extends the timeline for land sale at Podanur till March 31, 2026</li><li>The extension is due to the progress of needed government approvals</li><li>The decision has been mutually agreed upon by the Company and G Square Realtors Private Limited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/656f5fed-79a3-4432-a2e3-4c1d1c5f88e6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: EVEREST INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AADHARHFC] Blackstone-led Consortium to Acquire 25.82% Stake in Aadhar Housing Finance for $5.3 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Aadhar+Housing+Finance+Ltd&title=Blackstone-led+Consortium+to+Acquire+25.82%25+Stake+in+Aadhar+Housing+Finance+for+%245.3+Billion&newsId=15df204e-2fbf-4605-ac99-e28ffb672335&token=MTVkZjIwNGUtMmZi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">15df204e-2fbf-4605-ac99-e28ffb672335</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>A consortium led by BCP Asia IT Holdco VII PTE. LTD., a private limited company incorporated under the laws of Singapore, and including Blackstone Capital Partners (CYM) IX AIV-F L.P. and Blackstone Capital Partners Asia ITL.P., both exempted limited partnerships registered under the laws of Cayman Islands, has made a cash offer to acquire up to 11,35,25,761 fully paid-up equity shares of face value of INR 10 each of Aadhar Housing Finance Limited, representing 25.82% of the expanded voting share capital of the company. The offer price is INR 469.97 per equity share along with the applicable interest of INR 2.71 per equity share. The offer is not a conditional offer and is not subject to any minimum level of acceptance. It is also not a competing offer. The offer is being made in compliance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011 and subsequent amendments thereto. The offer is not subject to any statutory or regulatory approvals other than as set out in Part C (Statutory and Other Approvals) of Section VIII (Terms and Conditions of the Open Offer) which have now been received.</p><ul><li>Blackstone-led consortium to acquire 25.82% stake in Aadhar Housing Finance</li><li>Offer price is INR 469.97 per equity share along with INR 2.71 interest</li><li>Not a conditional or competing offer</li><li>Compliant with Securities and Exchange Board of India regulations</li><li>Subject to certain statutory and regulatory approvals</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ca488181-d7b3-4bdd-93ac-92cc15bf4162.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>