<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:46:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[VRUDDHI] Vruddhi Engineering Works Ltd: Board Approves Reappointment of Managing Director and Whole-time Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vruddhi+Engineering+Works+Ltd&title=Vruddhi+Engineering+Works+Ltd%3A+Board+Approves+Reappointment+of+Managing+Director+and+Whole-time+Directors&newsId=de89ff73-9c24-4944-a7ca-81329b034491&token=ZGU4OWZmNzMtOWMy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de89ff73-9c24-4944-a7ca-81329b034491</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:41:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vruddhi Engineering Works Ltd announced that its Board of Directors has approved the reappointment of Mrs. Bindi Kunal Mehta as Managing Director, Mr. Vedant Mukesh Mehta and Mrs. Varsha Mukesh Mehta as Whole-time Directors for a further period of three years. The reappointments will be effective from March 15, 2026, and July 3, 2026, respectively. The Board also approved the notice of Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) to be held on March 12, 2026.</p><ul><li>Reappointment of Mrs. Bindi Kunal Mehta as Managing Director for three years</li><li>Reappointment of Mr. Vedant Mukesh Mehta as Whole-time Director for three years</li><li>Reappointment of Mrs. Varsha Mukesh Mehta as Whole-time Director for three years</li><li>Approval of Notice of Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) on March 12, 2026</li><li>Closure of Trading Window for Designated Persons and their relatives till February 24, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/993d7138-2a2e-4eae-b55c-136331d695c3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vruddhi Engineering Works Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PTIL] Prabhat Technologies Board Meeting Rescheduled for Approval of Un-audited Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Prabhat+Technologies+%28India%29+Ltd&title=Prabhat+Technologies+Board+Meeting+Rescheduled+for+Approval+of+Un-audited+Financial+Results&newsId=d0a8f067-fb12-404d-b398-b7561bc770f1&token=ZDBhOGYwNjctZmIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d0a8f067-fb12-404d-b398-b7561bc770f1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:41:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Prabhat Technologies (India) Ltd has informed the BSE that the meeting of the Board of Directors, originally scheduled for February 18, 2026, has been adjourned and rescheduled to February 19, 2026. The meeting will consider and approve the Un-audited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in shares of the company will remain closed till 48 hours after the announcement of these results, in accordance with the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015 and the company&apos;s Code of Conduct for Prevention of Insider Trading.</p><ul><li>Prabhat Technologies Board Meeting rescheduled to February 19, 2026</li><li>Meeting to consider and approve Un-audited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Trading window for dealing in shares of the company to remain closed till 48 hours after the announcement of results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e0c9908f-8962-4382-80e5-7825b5c09eff.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Prabhat Technologies (India) Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EXPLEOSOL] Expleo Solutions Ltd Officially Closes Competence Centre in Coimbatore, Tamil Nadu, India</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Expleo+Solutions+Ltd&title=Expleo+Solutions+Ltd+Officially+Closes+Competence+Centre+in+Coimbatore%2C+Tamil+Nadu%2C+India&newsId=2500b4fe-09d0-4577-89dd-4e9a6f70c25e&token=MjUwMGI0ZmUtMDlk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2500b4fe-09d0-4577-89dd-4e9a6f70c25e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:24:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Expleo Solutions Ltd has officially closed its Competence Centre in Coimbatore, Tamil Nadu, India, as of February 18, 2026. The decision to close the centre is aimed at consolidating operations with the company&apos;s MEPZ branch office in Chennai for improved delivery efficiency and administrative oversight. The centre&apos;s contribution to the company&apos;s revenue for the financial year 2024-25 was INR 5.43 Mn, which is 0.05% of the total revenue, and the net worth was INR 29.11 Mn.</p><ul><li>Expleo Solutions Ltd has officially closed its Competence Centre in Coimbatore, Tamil Nadu, India.</li><li>The closure is aimed at consolidating operations with the company&apos;s MEPZ branch office in Chennai.</li><li>The Competence Centre contributed INR 5.43 Mn to the company&apos;s revenue in FY 2024-25.</li><li>The net worth of the Competence Centre was INR 29.11 Mn.</li><li>The closure is expected to improve delivery efficiency and administrative oversight.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e2688557-e172-4224-9f70-7fa32912f704.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Expleo Solutions Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SPAR] Sparc Electrex Ltd. Announces Q3 Results with Profit of Rs. 6.47 Lakhs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sparc+Electrex+Ltd&title=Sparc+Electrex+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+Results+with+Profit+of+Rs.+6.47+Lakhs&newsId=0ec1f398-4d12-4c3f-8f2b-8f298455e670&token=MGVjMWYzOTgtNGQx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ec1f398-4d12-4c3f-8f2b-8f298455e670</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:21:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sparc Electrex Ltd. announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The company reported a profit of Rs. 6.47 lakhs for the quarter and Rs. 8.00 lakhs for the nine months period. The revenue from operations for the quarter was Rs. 322.51 lakhs and for the nine months period was Rs. 501.91 lakhs. The company operates in two segments: Manufacturing of Electrical Tools &amp; Service and Trading. The manufacturing segment reported a loss of Rs. 19.37 lakhs for the quarter and Rs. 57.99 lakhs for the nine months period. The trading segment reported a profit of Rs. 13.00 lakhs for the quarter and Rs. 18.50 lakhs for the nine months period. The bank accounts of the company were provisionally attached/frozen by the Income Tax Department under the provisions of section 226(3) of Income tax Act, 1961, which has impacted the company’s banking operations and may affect its short-term liquidity position.</p><ul><li>Profit of Rs. 6.47 Lakhs for the quarter</li><li>Revenue from operations of Rs. 322.51 Lakhs for the quarter</li><li>Loss of Rs. 19.37 Lakhs for the manufacturing segment for the quarter</li><li>Profit of Rs. 13.00 Lakhs for the trading segment for the quarter</li><li>Provisionally attachment of bank accounts by Income Tax Department</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3d3260e5-835d-400d-a3cd-28bb4c3c8f70.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sparc Electrex Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SPAR] Sparc Electrex Ltd. Approves Q3 Financial Results, Reports on Bank Account Attachment by Tax Department</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sparc+Electrex+Ltd&title=Sparc+Electrex+Ltd.+Approves+Q3+Financial+Results%2C+Reports+on+Bank+Account+Attachment+by+Tax+Department&newsId=8ed5b72b-c21c-49f8-9199-20651ba52a64&token=OGVkNWI3MmItYzIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ed5b72b-c21c-49f8-9199-20651ba52a64</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sparc Electrex Ltd. held a board meeting on February 18, 2026, where they approved the un-audited standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s bank accounts were provisionally attached/frozen by the Income Tax Department under the provisions of section 226(3) of the Income tax Act, 1961, which has impacted their banking operations and may affect their short-term liquidity position. However, no adjustment has been made in the financial results in this regard. The company has represented its case before the appropriate authorities and is in the process of seeking appropriate relief in the matter.</p><ul><li>Sparc Electrex Ltd. approved the un-audited standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s bank accounts were provisionally attached/frozen by the Income Tax Department, affecting their banking operations and short-term liquidity position.</li><li>The company has represented their case before the appropriate authorities and is seeking appropriate relief in the matter.</li><li>The financial results do not include any adjustments related to the bank account attachment.</li><li>The board also took note of compliances made under SEBI (LODR) Regulation, 2015 for the quarter ended 31st December, 2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a7885ca3-dd59-4681-91d6-4ad511ac0c70.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sparc Electrex Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[YATRA] Promoter Entity THCL Travel Holding Cyprus Limited Sells around 1.8% Shares in Yatra Online Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Yatra+Online+Ltd&title=Promoter+Entity+THCL+Travel+Holding+Cyprus+Limited+Sells+around+1.8%25+Shares+in+Yatra+Online+Ltd&newsId=dde65262-4b7c-475c-b450-eec129a91ed0&token=ZGRlNjUyNjItNGI3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dde65262-4b7c-475c-b450-eec129a91ed0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:12:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Sale</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Yatra Online Ltd has received a disclosure from its Promoter entity, THCL Travel Holding Cyprus Limited, about sale of around 1.8% equity shares (28,33,000 equity shares) of Yatra Online Limited in the open market. This sale was intended to fund certain legal and compliance expenses of the Promoter Entity, Promoter group entity including Yatra Online, Inc. which is listed on Nasdaq in US. The Promoter do not foresee any further sale in near future.</p><ul><li>Yatra Online Ltd received disclosure from Promoter entity THCL Travel Holding Cyprus Limited about sale of around 1.8% shares</li><li>Sale of 28,33,000 equity shares in the open market</li><li>Sale intended to fund legal and compliance expenses of Promoter Entity and group</li><li>No further sale expected in near future</li><li>Transaction value not explicitly mentioned in the document</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5badd11d-1730-4064-8e34-37681e496b27.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Yatra Online Ltd | Category: Sale</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[COCHINSHIP] Cochin Shipyard Secures Mega Order for LNG-Fuelled Feeder Vessels from European Client</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Cochin+Shipyard+Ltd&title=Cochin+Shipyard+Secures+Mega+Order+for+LNG-Fuelled+Feeder+Vessels+from+European+Client&newsId=84aea393-19c0-403b-ba31-a3e93a5c00ea&token=ODRhZWEzOTMtMTlj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">84aea393-19c0-403b-ba31-a3e93a5c00ea</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Cochin Shipyard Ltd. has signed a contract with a prominent European Client for the design and construction of six LNG-fuelled feeder vessels, each with a capacity of approximately 1,700 TEU. The contract, valued between 500 to 1000 crores, is categorized as a Mega order as per CSL’s order classification criteria. The first vessel is to be delivered in 36 months and the last vessel in 64 months. This order does not involve any related party transactions and is a significant development for the company.</p><ul><li>Cochin Shipyard has signed a contract with a European Client for the construction of six LNG-fuelled feeder vessels.</li><li>The order is valued between 500 to 1000 crores and is categorized as a Mega order.</li><li>The first vessel is to be delivered in 36 months and the last in 64 months.</li><li>This order does not involve any related party transactions.</li><li>This development is significant for Cochin Shipyard Ltd.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2ee0f469-4189-4dc2-8e20-c1b09682f2cc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Cochin Shipyard Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[63MOONS] 63 Moons Technologies Ltd Completes Sale of Residual Stake in NTT Data Payment Services India Private Limited to NTT Data Group Corporation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=63+Moons+Technologies+Ltd&title=63+Moons+Technologies+Ltd+Completes+Sale+of+Residual+Stake+in+NTT+Data+Payment+Services+India+Private+Limited+to+NTT+Data+Group+Corporation&newsId=733373a4-1755-4862-add8-a65293e2273a&token=NzMzMzczYTQtMTc1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">733373a4-1755-4862-add8-a65293e2273a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>63 Moons Technologies Ltd has completed the sale of its residual stake in NTT Data Payment Services India Private Limited to NTT Data Group Corporation. The transaction resulted in the Company receiving INR equivalent of USD 18,432,925 and 21,00,86,610 equity shares held by the Company in NTT Data Payment Services India Private Limited. The consideration amount, after deducting applicable taxes, has been deposited by the Company in the designated bank account of the Competent Authority NSEL MPID as security in lieu of attachment. With this sale, NTT Data Payment Services India Private Limited has ceased to be an Associate of 63 moons technologies limited.</p><ul><li>63 Moons Technologies Ltd completes the sale of its residual stake in NTT Data Payment Services India Private Limited to NTT Data Group Corporation.</li><li>The transaction resulted in the Company receiving INR equivalent of USD 18,432,925 and 21,00,86,610 equity shares held by the Company.</li><li>The consideration amount has been deposited by the Company in the designated bank account of the Competent Authority NSEL MPID as security in lieu of attachment.</li><li>NTT Data Payment Services India Private Limited has ceased to be an Associate of 63 moons technologies limited.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6cdbbed7-40f1-4b99-971f-73c31d987b7c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: 63 Moons Technologies Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SIGNATURE] Sad Demise of Signatureglobal (India) Ltd&apos;s Independent Director - Mr. Kundan Mal Agarwal</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Signatureglobal+%28India%29+Ltd&title=Sad+Demise+of+Signatureglobal+%28India%29+Ltd%27s+Independent+Director+-+Mr.+Kundan+Mal+Agarwal&newsId=8f47c428-4e83-43c5-ab2d-18b52b23a046&token=OGY0N2M0MjgtNGU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f47c428-4e83-43c5-ab2d-18b52b23a046</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:11:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Signatureglobal (India) Ltd has informed about the demise of its Independent Director, Mr. Kundan Mal Agarwal (DIN: 00043115) on Tuesday night, the 17th of February, 2026. The company expresses its deep sympathy and condolences to his family and acknowledges his remarkable contribution and guidance during his tenure as an Independent Director. The details required by Regulation 30 of the Listing Regulations are provided in Annexure - I.</p><ul><li>Demise of Independent Director - Mr. Kundan Mal Agarwal</li><li>Company expresses deep sympathy and condolences to the family</li><li>Remarkable contribution and guidance during his tenure as an Independent Director</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/18d4da38-94f7-4132-9fe3-826875d18256.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Signatureglobal (India) Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ALTIUSINVIT] Altius Telecom Infrastructure Trust to Declare Distribution to Unitholders</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Altius+Telecom+Infrastructure+Trust&title=Altius+Telecom+Infrastructure+Trust+to+Declare+Distribution+to+Unitholders&newsId=43c4fc25-a9d0-40b2-9e9a-e885ff136c8d&token=NDNjNGZjMjUtYTlk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43c4fc25-a9d0-40b2-9e9a-e885ff136c8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 15:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Altius Telecom Infrastructure Trust has informed the Exchange about a material issue. A meeting of the Board of Directors of Data Link Investment Manager Private Limited, the Investment Manager of the Trust, is scheduled for February 25, 2026, to consider and declare distribution to the unitholders. The record date for the purpose of this distribution, if declared, will be March 2, 2026. The trading window for dealing in the listed securities of the Trust will be closed from February 19, 2026, and will open 48 hours after the announcement of the outcome of the Board Meeting. The information is also available on the Trust&apos;s website: www.altiusinfra.com.</p><ul><li>Altius Telecom Infrastructure Trust to declare distribution to unitholders</li><li>Board Meeting scheduled for February 25, 2026</li><li>Record date set for March 2, 2026</li><li>Trading window for securities to close on February 19, 2026</li><li>Information available on the Trust&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6461e615-adaf-44d5-8490-e80a181b49c6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Altius Telecom Infrastructure Trust | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>