<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:25:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[VINEETLAB] Vineet Laboratories Ltd. Approves Appointment of Ms. Jasmin Kunal Tailor as Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vineet+Laboratories+Ltd&title=Vineet+Laboratories+Ltd.+Approves+Appointment+of+Ms.+Jasmin+Kunal+Tailor+as+Independent+Director&newsId=29d2a5b7-730a-4e44-9814-e5fb4135274c&token=MjlkMmE1YjctNzMw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29d2a5b7-730a-4e44-9814-e5fb4135274c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Vineet Laboratories Ltd. announced an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting to obtain shareholder approval for the appointment of Ms. Jasmin Kunal Tailor as an Independent Director. The cut-off date for ascertaining members and determining eligibility to vote is January 09, 2026 and January 30, 2026 respectively. Remote e-voting begins on February 4, 2026 and concludes on February 6, 2026. The Board Meeting took place from 2.00 PM to 2.40 PM on Wednesday, January 07, 2026.</p><ul><li>Vineet Laboratories Ltd. to appoint Ms. Jasmin Kunal Tailor as an Independent Director</li><li>Extra-Ordinary General Meeting to obtain shareholder approval for the appointment</li><li>Cut-off date for ascertaining members: January 09, 2026</li><li>Determining eligibility to vote: January 30, 2026</li><li>Remote e-voting from February 4, 2026 to February 6, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7c7f80c4-9099-499d-8a07-5410e8150ea5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vineet Laboratories Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AIIL] Authum Investment &amp; Infrastructure Ltd Fixes Record Date for 4:1 Bonus Equity Shares Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Authum+Investment+%26+Infrastructure+Ltd&title=Authum+Investment+%26+Infrastructure+Ltd+Fixes+Record+Date+for+4%3A1+Bonus+Equity+Shares+Issue&newsId=e3ab77ce-f7e5-43a4-86a3-986dfc5a63a6&token=ZTNhYjc3Y2UtZjdl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3ab77ce-f7e5-43a4-86a3-986dfc5a63a6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:21:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Bonus</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Authum Investment &amp; Infrastructure Ltd has fixed the Record Date as Tuesday, January 13, 2026, for the purpose of ascertaining the eligibility of shareholders entitled for allotment of Bonus Equity Shares. The company has received in-principal approvals from BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange of India Limited for the proposed issue and allotment of 67,93,80,400 fully paid-up Bonus Equity Shares of Rs. 1/- each in the proportion of 4:1. The deemed date of allotment is Wednesday, January 14, 2026. The company will ensure that the fully paid-up Bonus Equity Shares will be made available for trading on the next working date from the deemed date of allotment.</p><ul><li>Authum Investment &amp; Infrastructure Ltd has fixed the Record Date for the purpose of ascertaining the eligibility of shareholders for Bonus Equity Shares.</li><li>The company has received in-principal approvals from BSE and NSE for the proposed issue and allotment of Bonus Equity Shares.</li><li>67,93,80,400 fully paid-up Bonus Equity Shares of Rs. 1/- each will be issued in the proportion of 4:1.</li><li>The deemed date of allotment is Wednesday, January 14, 2026.</li><li>The company will ensure that the Bonus Equity Shares will be made available for trading on the next working date from the deemed date of allotment.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e381541e-2cd1-4e1f-a13c-5da2abaec438.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Authum Investment & Infrastructure Ltd | Category: Bonus</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PATINTLOG] Patel Integrated Logistics Ltd Incorporates Wholly Owned Subsidiary &apos;House of Patels Limited&apos;</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PATEL+INTEGRATED+LOGISTICS+LTD.-%24&title=Patel+Integrated+Logistics+Ltd+Incorporates+Wholly+Owned+Subsidiary+%27House+of+Patels+Limited%27&newsId=6f158d13-d104-495a-ab59-5c89c7af522a&token=NmYxNThkMTMtZDEw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f158d13-d104-495a-ab59-5c89c7af522a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:21:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Patel Integrated Logistics Ltd has incorporated a wholly owned subsidiary named &apos;House of Patels Limited&apos; with a registered office in Mumbai, Maharashtra. The Certificate of Incorporation has been issued by the Ministry of Corporate Affairs, Government of India, on January 06, 2026.</p><ul><li>Patel Integrated Logistics Ltd has incorporated a new wholly owned subsidiary.</li><li>The new subsidiary is named &apos;House of Patels Limited&apos;.</li><li>The subsidiary is registered in Mumbai, Maharashtra.</li><li>The Certificate of Incorporation has been issued on January 06, 2026.</li><li>The subsidiary is expected to carry on the business related to Logistics, Real Estate and Facility Management.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e5a8cca7-6db8-4671-835d-451b6ce61e03.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PATEL INTEGRATED LOGISTICS LTD.-$ | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JBCHEPHARM] JB Chemicals &amp; Pharmaceuticals to Invest Additional Rs. 18 Crores in Wholly-Owned Dubai Subsidiary</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=J.B.CHEMICALS+%26+PHARMACEUTICALS+LTD.&title=JB+Chemicals+%26+Pharmaceuticals+to+Invest+Additional+Rs.+18+Crores+in+Wholly-Owned+Dubai+Subsidiary&newsId=00d70ebe-cd60-4bd3-bf77-4fd45243f02b&token=MDBkNzBlYmUtY2Q2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00d70ebe-cd60-4bd3-bf77-4fd45243f02b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:20:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>JB Chemicals &amp; Pharmaceuticals Ltd. has approved an additional investment of up to Rs. 18 crores in its wholly-owned subsidiary, Unique Pharmaceutical Laboratories, FZE (UPL FZE) at Dubai. The investment is aimed at meeting the operational requirements of UPL FZE. UPL FZE, incorporated in December 2013, is engaged in medicines trading and reported a revenue of AED 627,639 in FY 2024-25. The transaction is at arm&apos;s length and does not involve any related party transactions beyond the Company&apos;s shareholding in UPL FZE. The investment is likely to be completed within three months and will be in cash.</p><ul><li>JB Chemicals to invest additional Rs. 18 crores in its Dubai subsidiary, Unique Pharmaceutical Laboratories, FZE</li><li>Investment aimed at meeting operational requirements of the subsidiary</li><li>Subsidiary engaged in medicines trading and reported a revenue of AED 627,639 in FY 2024-25</li><li>Transaction is at arm&apos;s length</li><li>Investment likely to be completed within three months</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9390c824-316f-4e62-bfc3-1bc4d69c9c94.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: J.B.CHEMICALS & PHARMACEUTICALS LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GGAUTO] GG Automotive Gears Ltd to Approve Q4 Results on Jan 12, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=G.G.AUTOMOTIVE+GEARS+LTD.&title=GG+Automotive+Gears+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+Results+on+Jan+12%2C+2026&newsId=1699f667-4663-48f7-bafa-e15a34093e2b&token=MTY5OWY2NjctNDY2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1699f667-4663-48f7-bafa-e15a34093e2b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>GG Automotive Gears Ltd has announced a Board of Directors meeting on January 12, 2026, at its registered office in Dewas, Madhya Pradesh. The agenda includes the consideration and approval of the un-audited financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025, along with the Limited Review Report. Any other business with the permission of the Chair will also be discussed.</p><ul><li>GG Automotive Gears Ltd has scheduled a Board of Directors meeting on January 12, 2026</li><li>The meeting will be held at the company&apos;s registered office in Dewas, Madhya Pradesh</li><li>The board will consider and approve the un-audited financial results for Q4 2025</li><li>A Limited Review Report will also be reviewed</li><li>Other business may be discussed with the permission of the Chair</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5c803a89-1714-4607-a42d-1eb5a34faa54.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: G.G.AUTOMOTIVE GEARS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SATTRIX] Sattrix Information Security Ltd Announces Strategic Partnership with CrowdStrike as Official Indirect Reseller Partner for India</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sattrix+Information+Security+Ltd&title=Sattrix+Information+Security+Ltd+Announces+Strategic+Partnership+with+CrowdStrike+as+Official+Indirect+Reseller+Partner+for+India&newsId=dcc25149-0f17-416e-83eb-26f58994b157&token=ZGNjMjUxNDktMGYx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dcc25149-0f17-416e-83eb-26f58994b157</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Partnership</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Sattrix Information Security Ltd, a leading provider of innovative cybersecurity solutions and managed services, has successfully onboarded as an Indirect Reseller Partner for CrowdStrike in India. This partnership enables Sattrix to expand its robust security portfolio with the industry-leading AI-native CrowdStrike Falcon platform, providing more integrated solutions and managed services around it. The partnership aims to strengthen cybersecurity for the Indian market, leveraging CrowdStrike&apos;s Partner echo system and Sattrix&apos;s SOC/Managed Service environment to manage, provision, and scale cybersecurity deployments for its customers.</p><ul><li>Platform-Driven Security: Access to the full suite of CrowdStrike Falcon modules</li><li>Enhanced Threat Intelligence: Integration of CrowdStrike’s world-class threat intelligence</li><li>Operational Efficiency: Utilizing the CrowdStrike portal for license management and service delivery through SOC and managed services operations</li><li>Local Expertise, Global Technology: Combining Sattrix’s deep understanding of the Indian regulatory and security landscape with CrowdStrike’s global leadership in cloud-native security</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/45d423d5-ef30-43a1-91e7-890441264036.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sattrix Information Security Ltd | Category: Partnership</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IIFLSEC] IIFL Capital Services Ltd Clarifies No Disclosure Obligations as of Now</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IIFL+Securities+Ltd&title=IIFL+Capital+Services+Ltd+Clarifies+No+Disclosure+Obligations+as+of+Now&newsId=1b8e7959-4d93-4d30-9ab5-a72155afd8fb&token=MWI4ZTc5NTktNGQ5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b8e7959-4d93-4d30-9ab5-a72155afd8fb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Clarification</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>IIFL Capital Services Ltd, formerly known as IIFL Securities Limited, clarified to BSE Limited regarding a recent news item on the company. The company stated that they are not aware of any information that has not been announced to the exchanges, but they explore various strategic opportunities from time to time. They also mentioned that if any disclosure becomes necessary, they will comply with applicable laws. They confirmed that there are no regulatory or legal proceedings related to the news item.</p><ul><li>IIFL Capital Services Ltd clarified recent news item appearing in &apos;Media/Publication&apos;.</li><li>Company is not aware of any undisclosed information requiring announcement under SEBI regulations.</li><li>IIFL Capital Services Ltd explores strategic opportunities from time to time.</li><li>Company will make appropriate announcements if disclosure becomes necessary.</li><li>No regulatory or legal proceedings related to the news item.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4a392216-79cf-4642-b14c-0b03e5937e14.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IIFL Securities Ltd | Category: Clarification</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GHCL] GHCL Ltd Schedules Board Meeting on January 29, 2026 to Approve Q3 Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GHCL+LTD.&title=GHCL+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+on+January+29%2C+2026+to+Approve+Q3+Results&newsId=b4a0bad1-366a-4f12-9c9b-99b707b211cf&token=YjRhMGJhZDEtMzY2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4a0bad1-366a-4f12-9c9b-99b707b211cf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>GHCL Ltd, a leading company, has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 29, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will be held through audio &amp; video conferencing. The company&apos;s trading window will remain closed from January 1, 2026, to January 31, 2026, in connection with the board meeting. The financial results, along with the limited review report of the Statutory Auditors, will be sent to the stakeholders after the board&apos;s approval.</p><ul><li>GHCL Ltd board meeting scheduled on January 29, 2026</li><li>Meeting to consider and approve Q3 results for the period ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Trading window to remain closed from January 1, 2026, to January 31, 2026</li><li>Results and limited review report to be sent to stakeholders after approval</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/333229ba-8dbb-41b4-adaa-5d98ce313e1f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GHCL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PPAP] PPAP Automotive Sells 50% Stake in Joint Venture Company PPAP Tokai India Rubber to Tokai Kogyo Co. Ltd for Rs. 100 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PPAP+Automotive+Limited&title=PPAP+Automotive+Sells+50%25+Stake+in+Joint+Venture+Company+PPAP+Tokai+India+Rubber+to+Tokai+Kogyo+Co.+Ltd+for+Rs.+100+Crores&newsId=1d17bb1e-b6b3-43ee-8952-a1c686ff6144&token=MWQxN2JiMWUtYjZi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d17bb1e-b6b3-43ee-8952-a1c686ff6144</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:10:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>PPAP Automotive Ltd has entered into a settlement agreement with Tokai Kogyo Co. Ltd and PPAP Tokai India Rubber Private Limited for the sale of its entire 50% stake in PPAP Tokai India Rubber to Tokai Kogyo Co. Ltd. The joint venture company between PPAP and Tokai will cease to exist upon execution of the settlement agreement. The sale is expected to be completed by February 28, 2026, with PPAP receiving Rs. 100 Crores as consideration. Tokai Kogyo Co. Ltd, the buyer, does not belong to the promoter group.</p><ul><li>PPAP Automotive sells 50% stake in PPAP Tokai India Rubber to Tokai Kogyo Co. Ltd for Rs. 100 Crores</li><li>PPAP Tokai India Rubber will cease to be a joint venture company between PPAP and Tokai</li><li>The sale is expected to be completed by February 28, 2026</li><li>Tokai Kogyo Co. Ltd, the buyer, does not belong to the promoter group</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/307161d1-bcef-459d-88d9-845eb1fd4986.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PPAP Automotive Limited | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GICHSGFIN] GIC Housing Finance Ltd Submits &apos;Nil&apos; Report for Re-lodgement of Physical Shares Transfer Requests</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GIC+HOUSING+FINANCE+LTD.&title=GIC+Housing+Finance+Ltd+Submits+%27Nil%27+Report+for+Re-lodgement+of+Physical+Shares+Transfer+Requests&newsId=97c019ca-7ec4-43bb-bfdb-d56209f59fc3&token=OTdjMDE5Y2EtN2Vj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97c019ca-7ec4-43bb-bfdb-d56209f59fc3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 09:09:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>GIC Housing Finance Ltd has submitted a &apos;Nil&apos; report regarding the re-lodgement of transfer requests for physical shares as on January 06, 2026. This is in accordance with the SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97 dated July 02, 2025. The report was received from M/s. KFin Technologies Limited, the Registrar and Share Transfer Agent (RTA) of the Company. The status of the re-lodgement of transfer requests of physical shares as on January 06, 2026, indicates no requests were received, processed, approved, or rejected during the month.</p><ul><li>GIC Housing Finance Ltd submits &apos;Nil&apos; report for physical shares transfer requests re-lodgement.</li><li>Report submitted in accordance with SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97 dated July 02, 2025.</li><li>No requests received, processed, approved, or rejected during the month for physical shares transfer.</li><li>Status confirmed by GIC Housing Finance Ltd regarding shareholders&apos; lodgment of transfer requests for physical shares.</li><li>Special window provided by the SEBI Circular dated 2nd July 2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d3d5dc85-134b-47e4-9272-c7a4cc6d51d3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GIC HOUSING FINANCE LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>