<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 18:27:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[KHYATI] Khyati Multimedia Entertainment Ltd Announces Application for Re-classification of Promoters under SEBI Regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KHYATI+MULTIMEDIA-ENTERTAINMENT+LTD.&title=Khyati+Multimedia+Entertainment+Ltd+Announces+Application+for+Re-classification+of+Promoters+under+SEBI+Regulations&newsId=2fcee99a-daf2-405f-b321-60df7fdbc066&token=MmZjZWU5OWEtZGFm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2fcee99a-daf2-405f-b321-60df7fdbc066</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Khyati Multimedia Entertainment Ltd has informed about the filing of an application for re-classification of certain promoters from the category of ‘promoter group’ to ‘public’ in terms of Regulation 31A of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The application was filed with BSE Limited on 23rd January, 2026. The company will keep BSE informed of the developments in relation to the reclassification application in accordance with SEBI LODR.</p><ul><li>Khyati Multimedia Entertainment Ltd files application for re-classification of promoters</li><li>Promoters to be re-classified from ‘promoter group’ to ‘public’ category</li><li>Application filed with BSE Limited on 23rd January, 2026</li><li>Company to keep BSE informed of the developments as per SEBI LODR regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e7bf834e-8a2f-4c04-b333-1559cb3110ea.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KHYATI MULTIMEDIA-ENTERTAINMENT LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CEWATER] Concord Enviro Systems Acquires Convertible Preference Shares of Nala Membranes Inc. for US$ 1,999,310.04</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Concord+Enviro+Systems+Ltd&title=Concord+Enviro+Systems+Acquires+Convertible+Preference+Shares+of+Nala+Membranes+Inc.+for+US%24+1%2C999%2C310.04&newsId=a0e801d9-c2b6-452a-a63b-c684f07da22a&token=YTBlODAxZDktYzJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0e801d9-c2b6-452a-a63b-c684f07da22a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:51:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Concord Enviro Systems Ltd has acquired Preferred Stock of NALA Membranes Inc., a corporation incorporated in the state of North Carolina, USA. The company operates in the advanced membrane and filtration technology space and is engaged in the development and manufacture of flat sheet membranes and membrane elements. The acquisition is in line with the Company’s strategic objectives and is expected to strengthen its business and technological capabilities. Nala Membranes Inc. has developed a one of its kind chlorine resistant membrane, which is expected to transform the wastewater recycle and ZLD process. The investment is proposed to support capital expenditure and commercialization of the technology of NALA Membranes Inc. that will help to scale up the business of the company. Further, the investment aligns with the listed entity’s focus on environmental and waste water treatment technologies. The proposed investment by the Company is US$ 1,999,310.04 for 8% and control of 528,918 shares.</p><ul><li>Concord Enviro Systems Ltd acquires Preferred Stock of NALA Membranes Inc.</li><li>NALA Membranes Inc. operates in the advanced membrane and filtration technology space.</li><li>The acquisition is in line with Concord Enviro Systems&apos; strategic objectives.</li><li>NALA Membranes Inc. has developed a one of its kind chlorine resistant membrane.</li><li>The investment aligns with Concord Enviro Systems&apos; focus on environmental and waste water treatment technologies.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1f33a715-c744-494d-9bcb-f329c8a6a03c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Concord Enviro Systems Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDOBORAX] Promoter Sajal Sushilkumar Jain Sells 26.35% Stake in Indo Borax &amp; Chemicals Ltd for INR 2,16,71,16,450</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDO+BORAX+%26+CHEMICALS+LTD.-%24&title=Promoter+Sajal+Sushilkumar+Jain+Sells+26.35%25+Stake+in+Indo+Borax+%26+Chemicals+Ltd+for+INR+2%2C16%2C71%2C16%2C450&newsId=d69b9804-67ed-4a20-bd74-8a68e62dc862&token=ZDY5Yjk4MDQtNjdl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d69b9804-67ed-4a20-bd74-8a68e62dc862</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Sale of Property</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sajal Sushilkumar Jain, a promoter of Indo Borax &amp; Chemicals Ltd, has sold 84,55,390 equity shares of the company, representing approximately 26.35% of the total paid-up equity share capital. The sale took place on January 23, 2026, off the market, for a total consideration of INR 2,16,71,16,450. This sale was disclosed to the company and the stock exchanges as required under applicable laws.</p><ul><li>Sajal Sushilkumar Jain sells 26.35% stake in Indo Borax &amp; Chemicals Ltd</li><li>Transaction value INR 2,16,71,16,450</li><li>Sale took place on January 23, 2026</li><li>Off-market transaction</li><li>Disclosure made to the company and stock exchanges</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/22bebbce-e8ae-4e74-b0cc-e7c4e6f87fcc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDO BORAX & CHEMICALS LTD.-$ | Category: Sale of Property</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BHARTIARTL] Bharti Airtel Faces Rs. 1,11,000 Penalty for Subscriber Verification Norms Violation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BHARTI+AIRTEL+LTD.&title=Bharti+Airtel+Faces+Rs.+1%2C11%2C000+Penalty+for+Subscriber+Verification+Norms+Violation&newsId=d4646191-0f38-4683-9d49-b5fa00ad67e9&token=ZDQ2NDYxOTEtMGYz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4646191-0f38-4683-9d49-b5fa00ad67e9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bharti Airtel Ltd. has received a notice from the Department of Telecommunications, Uttar Pradesh (East) LSA, imposing a penalty of Rs. 1,11,000 for alleged violation of subscriber verification norms. The penalty is in accordance with the License agreement, which requires the company to ensure adequate verification of customers before enrolling them as subscribers. The penalty is a result of a sample Customer Application Form Audit (CAF Audit) conducted in October 2025, which revealed non-compliance with the subscriber verification norms under the License Agreement. The company has opted not to contest and pay the penalty.</p><ul><li>Bharti Airtel Ltd. has been imposed a penalty of Rs. 1,11,000 by the Department of Telecommunications</li><li>The penalty is for alleged violation of subscriber verification norms</li><li>The violation was discovered during a sample Customer Application Form Audit (CAF Audit) conducted in October 2025</li><li>Bharti Airtel has decided not to contest the penalty and will pay the amount</li><li>The maximum financial impact of the penalty is quantifiable to the extent of Rs. 1,11,000</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5c01e86f-6d5d-49a9-a553-f3662c306790.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BHARTI AIRTEL LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[COFORGE] Coforge Ltd Releases Q3 FY26 Earnings Call Transcript</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Coforge+Ltd&title=Coforge+Ltd+Releases+Q3+FY26+Earnings+Call+Transcript&newsId=12d3920c-0275-4235-8661-a3eb3851879f&token=MTJkMzkyMGMtMDI3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12d3920c-0275-4235-8661-a3eb3851879f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Coforge Ltd has released the audio transcript of its Earnings Conference Call for the third quarter of the financial year 2026. The conference call was held after the Board meeting on January 23, 2026. The transcript is available for access on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Coforge Ltd has released the audio transcript of its Q3 FY26 Earnings Conference Call.</li><li>The conference call was held after the Board meeting on January 23, 2026.</li><li>The transcript is available for access on the company&apos;s website.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ece30336-6771-415c-8a36-2f4bb81c846c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Coforge Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INFY*] Infosys Ltd Announces Investor Al Day in Bengaluru on February 17, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INFOSYS+LTD.&title=Infosys+Ltd+Announces+Investor+Al+Day+in+Bengaluru+on+February+17%2C+2026&newsId=f8dfdd6c-4f3d-416c-91d4-3144fcc8e3eb&token=ZjhkZmRkNmMtNGYz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f8dfdd6c-4f3d-416c-91d4-3144fcc8e3eb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:21:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Infosys Ltd has announced that it will hold an Investor Al day in Bengaluru on February 17, 2026. The agenda of the event will be finalized in due course and will be webcast live on the Company&apos;s website. The presentations made at the event and transcripts of discussions will also be hosted on the Company’s website subsequently. This information is for your records and can also be found on the Company’s website at www.infosys.com.</p><ul><li>Infosys Ltd to hold Investor Al day in Bengaluru on February 17, 2026</li><li>The event will be webcast live on the Company&apos;s website</li><li>Presentations and transcripts of discussions will be hosted on the Company’s website</li><li>This information is for your records</li><li>Additional details can be found on the Company’s website, www.infosys.com</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/72d15234-66c4-418e-adc2-636647537124.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INFOSYS LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZENTEC] ZEN Technologies Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results of FY2025-2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ZEN+TECHNOLOGIES+LTD.&title=ZEN+Technologies+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+of+FY2025-2026&newsId=75aed271-5c5a-490c-9890-e6b93fab5218&token=NzVhZWQyNzEtNWM1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75aed271-5c5a-490c-9890-e6b93fab5218</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>ZEN Technologies Ltd, a company based in Hyderabad, India, has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 31, 2026, to consider and approve the Standalone and Consolidated Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company has also announced the closure of its trading window from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of the results, which will reopen on February 2, 2026.</p><ul><li>ZEN Technologies Ltd to hold a Board Meeting on January 31, 2026, to approve Q3 and nine months results of FY2025-2026</li><li>The company has closed its trading window from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of results</li><li>The trading window will reopen on February 2, 2026</li><li>The results are for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f09e5b4c-48ec-4b1d-9d3b-2d12a23a4a66.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ZEN TECHNOLOGIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDOBORAX] Indo Borax &amp; Chemicals: Zenrock Chemicals Acquires Control, Open Offer for 26.00% Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDO+BORAX+%26+CHEMICALS+LTD.-%24&title=Indo+Borax+%26+Chemicals%3A+Zenrock+Chemicals+Acquires+Control%2C+Open+Offer+for+26.00%25+Shares&newsId=6d88059f-8083-419c-9054-7f5a5f068901&token=NmQ4ODA1OWYtODA4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d88059f-8083-419c-9054-7f5a5f068901</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indo Borax &amp; Chemicals Ltd. has announced the completion of the transfer of 50.80% equity shares to Zenrock Chemicals Private Limited, India Special Assets Fund III, ISAF III Onshore Fund, and Special Situation India Fund. Following the transfer, Zenrock Chemicals has acquired control of the company and has become the promoter. The erstwhile promoters, the Sellers, have ceased to be members of the promoter group. Zenrock Chemicals, along with the other purchasers, is undertaking an open offer to acquire up to 26.00% of the voting share capital from public shareholders. The Sellers have been declassified as members of the promoter group, effective from January 23, 2026.</p><ul><li>Zenrock Chemicals Private Limited has acquired control of Indo Borax &amp; Chemicals Ltd.</li><li>The acquisition follows the transfer of 50.80% equity shares from the Sellers to Zenrock Chemicals and other purchasers.</li><li>The Sellers, who were the promoters of Indo Borax &amp; Chemicals Ltd., have ceased to be members of the promoter group.</li><li>Zenrock Chemicals, along with other purchasers, is undertaking an open offer to acquire up to 26.00% of the voting share capital from public shareholders.</li><li>The Sellers have been declassified as members of the promoter group, effective from January 23, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0b0c2980-f480-486d-b4a9-c7c2ee450302.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDO BORAX & CHEMICALS LTD.-$ | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DELHIVERY] Delhivery Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on January 31, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Delhivery+Ltd&title=Delhivery+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+January+31%2C+2026&newsId=893791fd-8a82-458b-bed2-d1f1a1e068fc&token=ODkzNzkxZmQtOGE4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">893791fd-8a82-458b-bed2-d1f1a1e068fc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Delhivery Ltd, a well-known entity in the stock exchange, has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 31, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting is in accordance with Regulation 29 and other applicable provisions of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. Furthermore, in line with the Insider Trading Code and the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, the trading window for dealing in securities of the Company by Designated Persons and their immediate relatives will remain closed till 48 hours after the declaration of the Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Delhivery Ltd to consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Meeting scheduled on January 31, 2026, in accordance with Regulation 29 and other applicable provisions of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities of the Company by Designated Persons and their immediate relatives to remain closed till 48 hours after the declaration of the Financial Results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6c5a5e7f-7568-4589-8804-5e156ff290bc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Delhivery Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SRMENERGY] SRM Energy Ltd Receives SEBI Final Observations for Open Offer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SRM+ENERGY+LTD.&title=SRM+Energy+Ltd+Receives+SEBI+Final+Observations+for+Open+Offer&newsId=a909a7ca-9ae7-4d5a-96e1-0e014b75036a&token=YTkwOWE3Y2EtOWFl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a909a7ca-9ae7-4d5a-96e1-0e014b75036a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:41:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SRM Energy Ltd has announced that they have received final observations dated 23rd January, 2026 from the Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) for an Open Offer. The observations were received by M/s. Sobhagya Capital Options Private Limited, the Manager to the Open Offer, in accordance with the provisions of SEBI SAST Regulations, 2011. The Manager will take suitable actions for opening the Offer on behalf of the Acquirers as per the directions contained in the final observation from the Regulator.</p><ul><li>SRM Energy Ltd has received final observations from SEBI for an Open Offer.</li><li>The observations were received by M/s. Sobhagya Capital Options Private Limited, the Manager to the Open Offer.</li><li>The Manager will take suitable actions for opening the Offer on behalf of the Acquirers as per the directions from the Regulator.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/341d17d7-3791-411d-aed4-e3221dcb278e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SRM ENERGY LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>