<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:19:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SHANTIGEAR] Shanthi Gears Ltd: Interim Dividend Declared, CFO to Step Down, Q3 Financial Results Released</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHANTHI+GEARS+LTD.&title=Shanthi+Gears+Ltd%3A+Interim+Dividend+Declared%2C+CFO+to+Step+Down%2C+Q3+Financial+Results+Released&newsId=854b4ce2-eb07-4228-b18d-570ef297e196&token=ODU0YjRjZTItZWIw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">854b4ce2-eb07-4228-b18d-570ef297e196</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:47:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shanthi Gears Ltd has declared an interim dividend of Rs. 3/- per Equity Share for the financial year 2025-26. The company&apos;s Chief Financial Officer, Mr. Ranjan Kumar Pati, will be stepping down effective from 19th March 2026. The company has also released its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025, showing a revenue of X116.82 Crores and a profit before tax of X21.59 Crores.</p><ul><li>Interim dividend of Rs. 3/- per Equity Share declared for the financial year 2025-26</li><li>Mr. Ranjan Kumar Pati, CFO, to step down from his position effective from 19th March 2026</li><li>Revenue of X116.82 Crores recorded in Q3 FY26</li><li>Profit before tax of X21.59 Crores in Q3 FY26</li><li>Achieved Return on average Invested Capital (ROIC) of 31% in Q3 FY26</li><li>Negative Free Cash Flow of X1.72 Crores during Q3 FY26</li><li>Highest-ever order booking of 169 Crores in Q3 FY26 with 28% growth over Q3FY25</li><li>Unexecuted order book as on 31st December 2025 stood at X 305 Crores</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9f657956-f5fc-4444-a120-4a3edf4d9503.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHANTHI GEARS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHANTIGEAR] Shanthi Gears Ltd. Declares Interim Dividend, Reports Q3 FY26 Financial Results, and Announces Stepping Down of CFO</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHANTHI+GEARS+LTD.&title=Shanthi+Gears+Ltd.+Declares+Interim+Dividend%2C+Reports+Q3+FY26+Financial+Results%2C+and+Announces+Stepping+Down+of+CFO&newsId=659cfa9e-92d1-4bfd-9a1f-423ebe52e1dd&token=NjU5Y2ZhOWUtOTJk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">659cfa9e-92d1-4bfd-9a1f-423ebe52e1dd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:47:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shanthi Gears Ltd. has declared an interim dividend of Rs. 3/- per equity share for the financial year 2025-26. The company reported financial results for Q3 FY26 with a revenue of X116.82 Crores and a profit before tax of X 21.59 Crores. The company achieved its highest-ever order booking of 169 Crores in Q3 FY26 with 28% growth over Q3FY25 and has an unexecuted order book of X 305 Crores. The Board has also announced the stepping down of Mr. Ranjan Kumar Pati as the Chief Financial Officer, effective closing hours of 19th March, 2026.</p><ul><li>Declared interim dividend of Rs. 3/- per equity share for FY2025-26</li><li>Revenue of X116.82 Crores in Q3 FY26</li><li>Profit before tax of X 21.59 Crores in Q3 FY26</li><li>Highest-ever order booking of 169 Crores in Q3 FY26 with 28% growth</li><li>Unexecuted order book of X 305 Crores as on 31st December 2025</li><li>Stepping down of Mr. Ranjan Kumar Pati as CFO, effective 19th March, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b330d53e-cc38-483e-b54e-ed187fda1157.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHANTHI GEARS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BGPL] String Metaverse Ltd. Announces Board Meeting Outcomes: Capital Increase, ESOPs, and OFS Proposal</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Bio+Green+Papers+Ltd&title=String+Metaverse+Ltd.+Announces+Board+Meeting+Outcomes%3A+Capital+Increase%2C+ESOPs%2C+and+OFS+Proposal&newsId=67a7a414-efb6-456c-bf87-3db456732cee&token=NjdhN2E0MTQtZWZi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67a7a414-efb6-456c-bf87-3db456732cee</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:47:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>String Metaverse Ltd. (Formerly known as Bio Green Papers Limited) announced the outcomes of its Board Meeting held on 22nd January, 2026. The Board approved the Standalone and Consolidated Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. They also proposed to increase the Authorized Share Capital from INR 130,00,00,000 to INR 3200,00,00,000. The Board evaluated options for Employee Stock Option Schemes (ESOPs) and proposed an Offer for Sale (OFS) by the Promoter Group to meet Minimum Public Shareholding (MPS) norms. The meeting commenced at 11:45 AM (IST) and concluded at 01:15 PM (IST).</p><ul><li>Approval of Standalone and Consolidated Unaudited Financial Results for Q4 2025</li><li>Proposal to increase Authorized Share Capital from INR 130,00,00,000 to INR 3200,00,00,000</li><li>Consideration of Employee Stock Option Schemes (ESOPs) implementation</li><li>Proposal for an Offer for Sale (OFS) by the Promoter Group to meet MPS norms</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a5ebf675-aeda-449d-8a2f-ed0023737196.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Bio Green Papers Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GODIGIT] Go Digit General Insurance Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Unaudited Financial Results for the Period Ended 31st December 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Go+Digit+General+Insurance+Ltd&title=Go+Digit+General+Insurance+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+the+Period+Ended+31st+December+2025&newsId=505b021c-9fb5-452c-9878-8ebd9afc6984&token=NTA1YjAyMWMtOWZi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">505b021c-9fb5-452c-9878-8ebd9afc6984</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:46:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Go Digit General Insurance Ltd announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s board approved the unaudited financial results, along with the limited review report submitted by the Joint Statutory Auditors, PKF Sridhar and Santhanam LLP, Chartered Accountants and Kirtane &amp; Pandit LLP, Chartered Accountants. The report includes details on the company&apos;s financial performance, compliance with accounting standards, and regulatory requirements.</p><ul><li>Go Digit General Insurance Ltd announced its unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended on 31st December 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s board approved the unaudited financial results, along with the limited review report submitted by the Joint Statutory Auditors.</li><li>The report includes details on the company&apos;s financial performance, compliance with accounting standards, and regulatory requirements.</li><li>The financial results are prepared in accordance with the recognition and measurement principles laid down in the Accounting Standard 25, Insurance Act, 1938, IRDA Act, 1999, and IRDAI (Actuarial, finance and investment functions of insurers) Regulations, 2024.</li><li>The review is conducted in accordance with the Standard on Review Engagements (SRE) 2410, issued by the Institute of Chartered Accountants of India.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e8a6aac6-16ba-415b-aa88-b1c588ae6c15.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Go Digit General Insurance Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SRF] SRF Ltd Faces Rs. 38.49 Crores Customs Duty Penalty for Wrong HSN Classification</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SRF+LTD.&title=SRF+Ltd+Faces+Rs.+38.49+Crores+Customs+Duty+Penalty+for+Wrong+HSN+Classification&newsId=fc5b65f3-8725-43b5-b3da-a7679e7c60ba&token=ZmM1YjY1ZjMtODcy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc5b65f3-8725-43b5-b3da-a7679e7c60ba</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:46:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SRF Ltd has disclosed receiving a penalty notice from the Commissioner of Customs, Chennai-II (Imports) for an approximate amount of Rs. 38.49 Crores. The penalty is due to wrong HSN classification for import of raw materials and process chemicals, denying the benefits of the Free Trade Agreement (FTA) and exemption notification. The department has also alleged wrongful availing of export incentives. Based on legal advice, the management is confident that the demand is not legally tenable and will contest it before appropriate legal forums.</p><ul><li>SRF Ltd faces a penalty of approximately Rs. 38.49 Crores due to wrong HSN classification of imported raw materials and process chemicals.</li><li>The penalty is a result of denying the benefits of the Free Trade Agreement (FTA) and exemption notification.</li><li>The department has alleged wrongful availing of export incentives by SRF Ltd.</li><li>The management is confident that the demand is not legally tenable and will contest it before appropriate legal forums.</li><li>The disclosure is made pursuant to the SEBI (Listing Obligations &amp; Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b66755f0-87eb-4b1c-9422-76e57160542a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SRF LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SWARNSAR] Swarnsarita Jewels India Ltd: Open Offer for 22.97% Stake by Chordia Family at ₹32.15 per Share</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Swarnsarita+Jewels+India+Ltd&title=Swarnsarita+Jewels+India+Ltd%3A+Open+Offer+for+22.97%25+Stake+by+Chordia+Family+at+%E2%82%B932.15+per+Share&newsId=40e6ad19-c0ef-4655-ac02-6582a266c40a&token=NDBlNmFkMTktYzBl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40e6ad19-c0ef-4655-ac02-6582a266c40a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:46:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Open Offer</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mark Corporate Advisors Pvt Ltd, on behalf of Acquirers Mr. Mahendra Madanlal Chordia, Mrs. Asha M Chordia, and Mr. Sunny Mahendra Chordia, has submitted a Public Announcement for an Open Offer under Regulation 6 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeover) Regulations, 2011. The Offer is for acquiring up to 47,94,987 equity shares (22.97% of the Voting Share Capital) of Swarnsarita Jewels India Ltd at a price of ₹32.15 per share, amounting to a total consideration of ₹15,41,58,832.05.</p><ul><li>Open Offer for 22.97% stake in Swarnsarita Jewels India Ltd by Chordia family</li><li>Offer price set at ₹32.15 per equity share</li><li>Total consideration of ₹15,41,58,832.05</li><li>Voluntary Offer made under Regulation 6 of SEBI (SAST) Regulations, 2011</li><li>Offer triggered by Acquirers&apos; shareholding in the Target Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/D0764C40-7995-4D8A-9C99-AF8DE468202C-173630.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Swarnsarita Jewels India Ltd | Category: Open Offer</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZENSARTECH] Zensar Technologies Ltd Declares Interim Dividend of INR 2.40 in Q4 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ZENSAR+TECHNOLOGIES+LTD.&title=Zensar+Technologies+Ltd+Declares+Interim+Dividend+of+INR+2.40+in+Q4+2025&newsId=5da25d0e-773a-4967-a335-c17001661161&token=NWRhMjVkMGUtNzcz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5da25d0e-773a-4967-a335-c17001661161</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:46:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Zensar Technologies Ltd approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company declared an interim dividend of INR 2.40 per equity share of INR 2.00 each. The dividend will be paid to the shareholders on or before February 17, 2026, whose names appear on the Register of Members or in the records of the Depositories as beneficial owners as on January 29, 2026. The review report by SR B C &amp; CO LLP, the independent auditor, concluded that the financial results were prepared in accordance with the recognition and measurement principles laid down in Indian Accounting Standard 34 and other accounting principles generally accepted in India.</p><ul><li>Q4 2025 unaudited financial results approved</li><li>Interim dividend of INR 2.40 per equity share declared</li><li>Dividend payment date set for on or before February 17, 2026</li><li>Record date for dividend set as January 29, 2026</li><li>Review report confirms financial results prepared in accordance with Indian Accounting Standards</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bafa1cd6-c76c-486e-a404-d09e8c0512db.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ZENSAR TECHNOLOGIES LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PVP] PVP Ventures Ltd Appoints Mr. Dileep Badey as Additional Director and Reconstitutes Board Committees</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PVP+VENTURES+LTD.&title=PVP+Ventures+Ltd+Appoints+Mr.+Dileep+Badey+as+Additional+Director+and+Reconstitutes+Board+Committees&newsId=9d1b2339-3081-4e98-8009-9fca5526ca51&token=OWQxYjIzMzktMzA4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d1b2339-3081-4e98-8009-9fca5526ca51</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:46:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>PVP Ventures Ltd has appointed Mr. Dileep Badey as an Additional Director (Executive) and reconstituted its Board Committees. The Audit Committee, Investment Committee, and Non-Convertible Debenture Committee have been reconstituted with Mr. Dileep Badey as a member. Mr. Badey has over 15 years of experience in engineering, project management, and real estate development. He holds a Bachelor&apos;s degree in Civil Engineering and a Postgraduate qualification in Advanced Construction Management from NICMAR.</p><ul><li>PVP Ventures Ltd appoints Mr. Dileep Badey as Additional Director (Executive)</li><li>Mr. Dileep Badey is not debarred from holding the office of Director by any order of SEBI or any other regulatory authority</li><li>Reconstitution of Audit Committee, Investment Committee, and Non-Convertible Debenture Committee</li><li>Mr. Dileep Badey is a member of all reconstituted Committees</li><li>Mr. Dileep Badey has over 15 years of experience in engineering, project management, and real estate development</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/09339a7d-d147-43ce-ad4e-b049d7d22d53.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PVP VENTURES LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TRAVELS] Travels &amp; Rentals Ltd Announces Rights Issue of 1,12,02,685 Shares at ₹15 Each</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Travels+%26+Rentals+Ltd&title=Travels+%26+Rentals+Ltd+Announces+Rights+Issue+of+1%2C12%2C02%2C685+Shares+at+%E2%82%B915+Each&newsId=617148d2-0178-49c6-b7d1-6469506e0d11&token=NjE3MTQ4ZDItMDE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">617148d2-0178-49c6-b7d1-6469506e0d11</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Rights Issue</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Travels &amp; Rentals Ltd, a company based in Kolkata, India, has announced a rights issue of 1,12,02,685 fully paid-up equity shares of face value ₹10 each at a price of ₹15 per share, including a premium of ₹5. The rights issue is expected to raise ₹16,80,40,275, assuming full subscription. The record date for determining the eligible shareholders is January 28, 2026. The issue will open on February 5, 2026, and close on March 6, 2026. No withdrawal of application will be permitted after the issue closing date. The company will have the right to extend the issue period. The rights entitlements will be credited in the demat accounts of the eligible equity shareholders prior to the issue opening date.</p><ul><li>Rights issue of 1,12,02,685 shares at ₹15 each</li><li>Assuming full subscription, the issue will raise ₹16,80,40,275</li><li>Record date for determining eligible shareholders is January 28, 2026</li><li>Issue opens on February 5, 2026, and closes on March 6, 2026</li><li>Company has the right to extend the issue period</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6b1da3cd-ea42-46e1-a2b2-95da8b1decdf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Travels & Rentals Ltd | Category: Rights Issue</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GENUSPRIME] Genus Power Infrastructures Fixes Record Date for Scheme of Arrangement with Genus Prime Infra</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Genus+Prime+Infra+Ltd&title=Genus+Power+Infrastructures+Fixes+Record+Date+for+Scheme+of+Arrangement+with+Genus+Prime+Infra&newsId=4712b848-8b47-4e56-8170-ccb8891134ef&token=NDcxMmI4NDgtOGI0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4712b848-8b47-4e56-8170-ccb8891134ef</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Genus Power Infrastructures Limited has fixed the Record Date as Friday, February 06, 2026, for the purpose of determining the shareholders of Genus Power Infrastructures Limited to whom fully paid up equity shares of Genus Prime Infra Limited shall be issued and allotted in terms of the Scheme. The Equity Shareholders of Demerged Company whose names are recorded in the Register of Members and records of the Depositories as a Member of Demerged Company on Friday, February 06, 2026, being the Record Date fixed, will be entitled for allotment of 1 Equity share of Genus Prime Infra Limited of Rs. 2/- (Rupees Two only) each fully paid-up for every 6 Equity Shares held in Genus Power Infrastructures Limited of Re. 1/- (Rupee One only) each fully paid-up. The equity shares of the Resulting Company so held in Suspense Escrow account shall be transferred to the respective member once such member provides details of his/ her/ its demat account to the Resulting Company.</p><ul><li>Genus Power Infrastructures Limited has fixed the Record Date for the Scheme of Arrangement with Genus Prime Infra Limited.</li><li>The Record Date is fixed as Friday, February 06, 2026.</li><li>Shareholders of Genus Power Infrastructures Limited will be entitled for allotment of Genus Prime Infra Limited shares.</li><li>The equity shares of the Resulting Company will be held in Suspense Escrow account and will be transferred to the respective member once details of demat account are provided.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2386522f-fc3c-49de-864b-f259080e9415.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Genus Prime Infra Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>