<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 06:29:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[CYBERMEDIA] Cyber Media India Ltd Approves First and Final Call on Partly Paid-up Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CYBER+MEDIA+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Cyber+Media+India+Ltd+Approves+First+and+Final+Call+on+Partly+Paid-up+Equity+Shares&newsId=2482faa0-e17f-455d-98fa-76586f60be29&token=MjQ4MmZhYTAtZTE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2482faa0-e17f-455d-98fa-76586f60be29</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 06:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cyber Media India Ltd announced that its Committee has approved the making of the First and Final Call on the partly paid-up equity shares. The call amounts to 50% of the issue price of 715.80 (including a premium of 5.80) per share, i.e., 77.90 (including a premium of 22.90) per partly paid-up equity share. The Record Date for the purpose of ascertaining the holders of partly paid-up equity shares to whom the First and Final Call Notice would be sent is fixed on Friday, January 09, 2026.</p><ul><li>Cyber Media India Ltd Committee approves First and Final Call on partly paid-up equity shares.</li><li>The call amounts to 50% of the issue price of 715.80 (including a premium of 5.80) per share.</li><li>The Record Date for the purpose of ascertaining the holders of partly paid-up equity shares is fixed on Friday, January 09, 2026.</li><li>The Committee&apos;s meeting commenced at 11:00 a.m. (IST) and concluded at 11:40 a.m. (IST).</li><li>The information is also available on the Company’s website at www.cybermedia.co.in.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2b090494-6217-4f43-8c1f-c8b9340f0663.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CYBER MEDIA (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BHEL] BHEL Commences Supply of Semi-High-Speed Underslung Traction Converters for Vande Bharat Sleeper Train Project</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BHARAT+HEAVY+ELECTRICALS+LTD.&title=BHEL+Commences+Supply+of+Semi-High-Speed+Underslung+Traction+Converters+for+Vande+Bharat+Sleeper+Train+Project&newsId=df1658d9-5261-4a4f-815c-6dd979eb8808&token=ZGYxNjU4ZDktNTI2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df1658d9-5261-4a4f-815c-6dd979eb8808</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 06:19:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Bharat Heavy Electricals Limited (BHEL) has achieved a major milestone in its ‘Make in India’ initiatives for the rail transportation sector by commencing supply of underslung traction converters for the prestigious Vande Bharat Sleeper Train project being executed by BHEL- led consortium with TRSL. This marks BHEL&apos;s strategic entry into the semi-high-speed propulsion segment. The traction converters are specifically designed for the Vande Bharat Sleeper Trains and are equipped with state-of-the-art IGBT-based traction converters, the underslung design places the propulsion equipment beneath the train car, freeing up significant onboard space for passenger amenities and increasing the overall payload capacity of the train. The key highlights of the propulsion system include operational speed of up to 160 kmph with design speed of 176 kmph, and high-efficiency power conversion utilizing advanced thermal management to ensure reliability during long-distance overnight journeys.</p><ul><li>BHEL commences supply of underslung traction converters for Vande Bharat Sleeper Train project</li><li>Strategic entry into the semi-high-speed propulsion segment</li><li>Equipped with state-of-the-art IGBT-based traction converters</li><li>Underslung design frees up significant onboard space for passenger amenities</li><li>Propulsion system includes operational speed of up to 160 kmph and high-efficiency power conversion</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/59ea801b-2f5b-4332-8d75-8d7d1f3bea2f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BHARAT HEAVY ELECTRICALS LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[OSWALPUMPS] Oswal Pumps Addresses Observations in a Report; Maintains Confidence in Financial Reporting and Governance</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Oswal+Pumps+Ltd&title=Oswal+Pumps+Addresses+Observations+in+a+Report%3B+Maintains+Confidence+in+Financial+Reporting+and+Governance&newsId=e9920253-e747-458e-b2bb-a7dd842f3338&token=ZTk5MjAyNTMtZTc0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9920253-e747-458e-b2bb-a7dd842f3338</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 06:12:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Oswal Pumps Limited, one of India&apos;s fastest-growing solar pump manufacturers, has addressed certain observations contained in a report circulating in the public domain. The company believes that some interpretations in the report do not fully reflect its operating realities and has provided a detailed response to key observations. Oswal Pumps remains confident in the integrity of its financial reporting and governance framework and encourages investors and stakeholders to engage directly with management for any further clarifications or queries. The company is operating in a high-growth phase, driven by government-led programs, and has reported a Profit After Tax of 22,806 million in FY25, although operating cash flows were negative due to elevated working capital requirements.</p><ul><li>Oswal Pumps addresses observations in a report currently circulating in the public domain</li><li>Company maintains confidence in the integrity of its financial reporting and governance framework</li><li>Operating in a high-growth phase driven by government-led programs</li><li>Profit After Tax of 22,806 million in FY25, negative operating cash flows due to working capital requirements</li><li>Initiated migration from older ERP system to Microsoft Business Central for enhanced audit trail</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/abede73f-19dd-4fe0-91d9-d1b93205eb17.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Oswal Pumps Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[URJAGLOBA] Urja Global Ltd: No Transfer Requests for Physical Shares Processed from July 2025 to January 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=URJA+GLOBAL+LTD.&title=Urja+Global+Ltd%3A+No+Transfer+Requests+for+Physical+Shares+Processed+from+July+2025+to+January+2026&newsId=9e71c34b-d853-483b-a607-ec3a97b012df&token=OWU3MWMzNGItZDg1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e71c34b-d853-483b-a607-ec3a97b012df</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 06:07:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>According to a report from the Registrar and Share Transfer Agent of Urja Global Ltd, M/s. Alankit Assignments Limited, no transfer requests for physical shares were received, processed, approved, or rejected during the period from 07.07.2025 to 06.01.2026.</p><ul><li>No transfer requests for physical shares were received from 07.07.2025 to 06.01.2026.</li><li>No transfer requests for physical shares were processed during the same period.</li><li>No transfer requests for physical shares were approved during the same period.</li><li>No transfer requests for physical shares were rejected during the same period.</li><li>This information is provided for record purposes.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/626bca99-c09d-4e87-83cc-a816f8ae2762.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: URJA GLOBAL LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IFCI] IFCI Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q4 FY2025 Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IFCI+LTD.&title=IFCI+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q4+FY2025+Financial+Results&newsId=e7dfa650-f521-43f8-a8a0-a88a174f9dc9&token=ZTdkZmE2NTAtZjUy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e7dfa650-f521-43f8-a8a0-a88a174f9dc9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 06:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>IFCI Ltd, a leading financial institution, has informed the BSE that its Board of Directors will meet on January 29, 2026, to consider and approve the standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. In accordance with SEBI regulations, the trading window will be closed from December 31, 2025, to January 31, 2026.</p><ul><li>IFCI Ltd&apos;s Board of Directors to meet on January 29, 2026, to approve Q4 FY2025 financial results.</li><li>Meeting scheduled to consider and approve standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>Trading window to remain closed from December 31, 2025, to January 31, 2026, in line with SEBI regulations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/37713c81-0dc1-47b3-b5ec-f943d72ec8b4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IFCI LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[REFEX] Refex Industries Secures INR 34.61 Crore Order for Pond Ash Transportation to NHAI Road Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Refex+Industries+Limited&title=Refex+Industries+Secures+INR+34.61+Crore+Order+for+Pond+Ash+Transportation+to+NHAI+Road+Projects&newsId=c175007a-5ef2-48c1-836b-d82b06a4f240&token=YzE3NTAwN2EtNWVm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c175007a-5ef2-48c1-836b-d82b06a4f240</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 06:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Refex Industries Limited (RIL), a Refex Group Company, has procured an order for Excavation, Loading and Transportation of pond ash to NHAI road projects. The value of the order is approximately INR 34.61 Crore and it is to be executed within 4 months. The order has been awarded by a domestic entity based in Maharashtra. There are no related party transactions involved in this contract.</p><ul><li>Refex Industries secures INR 34.61 Crore order for pond ash transportation</li><li>Order to be executed within 4 months</li><li>Awarded by a domestic entity based in Maharashtra</li><li>No related party transactions involved</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e397691d-196d-4b1e-82ff-ab3b349c95fc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Refex Industries Limited | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ABDL] Scotch Whisky Veteran Martin Leonard Joins Allied Blenders and Distillers to Advise on Single Malt Foray</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Allied+Blenders+and+Distillers+Ltd&title=Scotch+Whisky+Veteran+Martin+Leonard+Joins+Allied+Blenders+and+Distillers+to+Advise+on+Single+Malt+Foray&newsId=045e069b-b671-4b99-a9f6-da7847ed5db0&token=MDQ1ZTA2OWItYjY3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">045e069b-b671-4b99-a9f6-da7847ed5db0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 06:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Allied Blenders and Distillers Limited (ABD), India’s largest domestic spirits company by volume, has appointed globally renowned Scotch whisky specialist Dr. Martin Leonard as Consultant. He will advise the company on commissioning of the Malt Distillery and on its single malt whisky initiative. Martin brings over three decades of experience in the global Scotch whisky industry, covering distillation, maturation, blending, bottling, and supply chain operations. The Rangapur-based single malt distillery is being developed with an investment of ~%75 Cr and a ~4.0 MLPA capacity to meet the current requirement of ~2.0 MLPA for blending and future single malt whiskies. The appointment of Martin marks an important step as ABD progresses its single malt plans and prepares to advance this business through its next phase of development.</p><ul><li>Allied Blenders and Distillers Limited (ABD) appoints Scotch whisky veteran Dr. Martin Leonard as Consultant</li><li>Martin to advise ABD on commissioning of the Malt Distillery and on its single malt whisky initiative</li><li>Martin brings over three decades of experience in the global Scotch whisky industry</li><li>Rangapur-based single malt distillery being developed with an investment of ~%75 Cr and a ~4.0 MLPA capacity</li><li>Appointment marks an important step as ABD progresses its single malt plans</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3f79b4be-0088-4220-a7db-c8f967e9d262.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Allied Blenders and Distillers Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MMTC] MMTC Ltd. Reports on SEBI Circular Compliance for Physical Share Transfers</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MMTC+LTD.&title=MMTC+Ltd.+Reports+on+SEBI+Circular+Compliance+for+Physical+Share+Transfers&newsId=bf278199-0e00-47ea-833a-c61f63829941&token=YmYyNzgxOTktMGUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf278199-0e00-47ea-833a-c61f63829941</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 05:53:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>MMTC Ltd. has informed the exchange about the receipt of a request for re-logement of Transfer of Requests of Physical Shares as per SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97. The company received no requests for physical shares re-lodged for transfer cum demat during the period from December 7, 2025 to January 06, 2026. This information is in accordance with the SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97 dated July 2, 2025. The report was received from the Company’s Registrar and Transfer Agent, MCS Share Transfer Agent Limited.</p><ul><li>MMTC Ltd. complies with SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97</li><li>No requests for physical shares re-lodged for transfer cum demat from December 7, 2025 to January 06, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/be6d3ece-c1ab-4f88-95aa-0deb5ea9e68a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MMTC LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AKZOINDIA] Akzo Nobel India Ltd Receives Order from Maharashtra GST Department for Duplicate E-way Bill</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Akzo+Nobel+India+Limited&title=Akzo+Nobel+India+Ltd+Receives+Order+from+Maharashtra+GST+Department+for+Duplicate+E-way+Bill&newsId=202b7548-8de4-452a-bf8d-01486771e0dc&token=MjAyYjc1NDgtOGRl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">202b7548-8de4-452a-bf8d-01486771e0dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 05:50:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Akzo Nobel India Ltd has received an Order from the Maharashtra GST Department regarding a duplicate E-way bill issued under u/s 74 of CGST/SGST Act, 2017. The Order, received on 7th January 2026, demands a total amount of Rs. 4,51,208/- (comprising Tax, Interest, and Penalty). The Company is currently reviewing the Order and preparing to respond within the given timeframe.</p><ul><li>Akzo Nobel India Ltd received an Order from the Maharashtra GST Department on 7th January 2026</li><li>The Order is regarding a duplicate E-way bill issued under u/s 74 of CGST/SGST Act, 2017</li><li>The demanded amount is Rs. 4,51,208/- (comprising Tax, Interest, and Penalty)</li><li>The Company is reviewing the Order and preparing to respond within the given timeframe</li><li>The Order is in relation to a Show Cause Notice issued on 1st July 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8d73c1b0-bf26-464b-b761-b7577940e0dd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Akzo Nobel India Limited | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AKZOINDIA] Akzo Nobel India Ltd Receives Order from Maharashtra GST Department: Tax Demand Dropped Completely</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Akzo+Nobel+India+Limited&title=Akzo+Nobel+India+Ltd+Receives+Order+from+Maharashtra+GST+Department%3A+Tax+Demand+Dropped+Completely&newsId=7816ece5-5d6b-4daa-ab04-ff595a05ff7f&token=NzgxNmVjZTUtNWQ2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7816ece5-5d6b-4daa-ab04-ff595a05ff7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 05:48:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Akzo Nobel India Ltd has received an Order from the Maharashtra GST Department on 7th January 2026, following a Show Cause Notice issued on 9th October 2025. The Notice concerned the disallowance of ISD input tax credit under u/s 730f CGST/SGST Act, 2017 and demanded a total of Rs. 3,94,59,459/-. However, upon the Company&apos;s response and submission of supporting documents, the Deputy Commissioner of State Tax, Belapur, Maharashtra GST (ISD) Department has dropped the entire tax demand, including interest and penalty. This annuls the original Demand Order.</p><ul><li>Akzo Nobel India Ltd receives Order from Maharashtra GST Department</li><li>Company had received Show Cause Notice for disallowance of ISD input tax credit</li><li>Tax demand of Rs. 3,94,59,459/- initially issued</li><li>Company responded with supporting documents</li><li>Tax demand including interest and penalty completely dropped</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/45c7298c-c808-4b48-8770-7bbbd4bab725.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Akzo Nobel India Limited | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>