<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:27:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[OSWALOR] Oswal Overseas Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=OSWAL+OVERSEAS+LTD.&title=Oswal+Overseas+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=b514823e-099e-4bb7-81ec-a6f66271e073&token=YjUxNDgyM2UtMDk5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b514823e-099e-4bb7-81ec-a6f66271e073</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:12:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Oswal Overseas Ltd, a company in the Sugar Industry, has reported its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors. The company&apos;s performance varies from quarter to quarter due to the seasonal nature of the industry. The financial results are prepared in accordance with the Companies (Indian Accounting Standards) Rules, 2015. The Statutory Auditors have carried out a limited review of these results.</p><ul><li>Revenue for the quarter and year ended is reported net of Goods and Services Tax (GST).</li><li>The company&apos;s performance varies from quarter to quarter due to the seasonal nature of the Sugar Industry.</li><li>The results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</li><li>The Statutory Auditors have carried out a limited review of these results.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6f85fcf9-1de7-47d6-90c6-23bd3b013811.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: OSWAL OVERSEAS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NEELKAN] Neelkanth Rockminerals Ltd Reports Q3 2025 Financial Results with 43.59 Lakhs Profit</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NEELKANTH+ROCKMINERALS+LTD.&title=Neelkanth+Rockminerals+Ltd+Reports+Q3+2025+Financial+Results+with+43.59+Lakhs+Profit&newsId=0a2b82ec-f0bb-453d-8c92-617e34c6d67e&token=MGEyYjgyZWMtZjBi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a2b82ec-f0bb-453d-8c92-617e34c6d67e</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Neelkanth Rockminerals Ltd, a company with CIN NO. L14219RJ1988PLC062162, has reported its unaudited financial results for the half year ended 31st December, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations was 1,17,540 Lakhs, with a total income of 1,21,306 Lakhs. The total expenses stood at 77,717 Lakhs, resulting in a profit before exceptional items and tax of 43,599 Lakhs. The company reported a net profit of 37,010 Lakhs for the period from continuing operations. The earnings per share for continuing and discontinued operations were 0.10 (basic) and 0.06 (diluted) respectively. The company operates in the segment of &apos;Granite and other materials&apos; and does not have any subsidiary company.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations: 1,17,540 Lakhs</li><li>Total income: 1,21,306 Lakhs</li><li>Profit before exceptional items and tax: 43,599 Lakhs</li><li>Net profit: 37,010 Lakhs</li><li>No subsidiary company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fc8c7175-eefa-4618-9387-86695b68919b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NEELKANTH ROCKMINERALS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NAGARFERT] Nagarjuna Fertilizers and Chemicals Ltd Appoints New Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Nagarjuna+Fertilizers+and+Chemicals+Ltd&title=Nagarjuna+Fertilizers+and+Chemicals+Ltd+Appoints+New+Directors&newsId=a0d01610-8302-4c8e-bbba-6e971b90ada3&token=YTBkMDE2MTAtODMw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0d01610-8302-4c8e-bbba-6e971b90ada3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:11:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Nagarjuna Fertilizers and Chemicals Ltd has appointed Ms. Lalitha Raghuram as Non-Executive Director and Ms. Shilpi Varshney as Independent Director. Ms. Lalitha Raghuram is a First class post-graduate in Social Work and Commerce with advanced accounting &amp; auditing. She has received the ‘Womentor’ Award in 2018 and the ‘International Eye Care Hero Award’ in 2018. Ms. Shilpi Varshney holds master&apos;s degrees in human resource development &amp; English Literature and is a Senior social impact and skill development professional with over 28 years of experience. She is presently associated with All India Society for Electronics and Computer Technology (AISECT) as Director, Projects and Skill Development.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Ms. Lalitha Raghuram as Non-Executive Director</li><li>Appointment of Ms. Shilpi Varshney as Independent Director</li><li>Ms. Lalitha Raghuram is a First class post-graduate in Social Work and Commerce</li><li>Ms. Shilpi Varshney is a Senior social impact and skill development professional with over 28 years of experience</li><li>Ms. Lalitha Raghuram has received the ‘Womentor’ Award in 2018 and the ‘International Eye Care Hero Award’ in 2018</li><li>Ms. Shilpi Varshney is presently associated with All India Society for Electronics and Computer Technology (AISECT) as Director, Projects and Skill Development</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/48144262-bc4b-42ff-b453-e57c3550f173.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Nagarjuna Fertilizers and Chemicals Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KIMIABL] Kimia Biosciences Ltd: Board Meeting Approves Un-audited Financial Results, Re-Appointment of Managing Director, and More</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kimia+Biosciences+Ltd&title=Kimia+Biosciences+Ltd%3A+Board+Meeting+Approves+Un-audited+Financial+Results%2C+Re-Appointment+of+Managing+Director%2C+and+More&newsId=d25ba53e-a568-4220-85e2-e42fabaffb86&token=ZDI1YmE1M2UtYTU2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d25ba53e-a568-4220-85e2-e42fabaffb86</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:11:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kimia Biosciences Limited, a company based at Gurgaon, Sohna Road, recently held a Board Meeting where several important decisions were made. The Board approved the un-audited financial results of the Company for the quarter and nine months ended on 31* December, 2025. The Managing Director, Mr. Sameer Goel, was re-appointed for a further period of five years. The Board also approved the re-appointment of Mr. Kaku Vijaya Shekhar Reddy as Whole time Director and the re-constitution of the Committees of the Board of Directors. The meeting commenced at 01:00 PM and concluded at 02:00 PM.</p><ul><li>Approval of Un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31* December, 2025</li><li>Re-appointment of Mr. Sameer Goel as Managing Director for a further period of five years</li><li>Re-appointment of Mr. Kaku Vijaya Shekhar Reddy as Whole time Director</li><li>Re-constitution of the Committees of the Board of Directors</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/83a8e194-8b6d-4848-a5ce-9780d8a77535.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kimia Biosciences Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADINATH] Adinath Textiles Reports Q3 and Nine Months Results, Profit for the Period at 13.65 Lacs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADINATH+TEXTILES+LTD.&title=Adinath+Textiles+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results%2C+Profit+for+the+Period+at+13.65+Lacs&newsId=3b57b6f9-2e52-41c1-a06e-d352eeede3c8&token=M2I1N2I2ZjktMmU1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b57b6f9-2e52-41c1-a06e-d352eeede3c8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Adinath Textiles Ltd. has reported its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations for the quarter is 33.72 Lacs, with a profit before tax of 3.92 Lacs. The company does not have any subsidiaries, associates, or joint venture companies. The results have been prepared in accordance with the Ind AS notified under the Companies Act, 2013. The company has made provisions for gratuity &amp; Leave with Wages liability to employees on an estimated basis for the quarter ending on 31st December 2025.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter is 33.72 Lacs</li><li>Profit before tax for the quarter is 3.92 Lacs</li><li>No subsidiaries, associates, or joint venture companies</li><li>Results prepared in accordance with Ind AS notified under the Companies Act, 2013</li><li>Provisions made for gratuity &amp; Leave with Wages liability to employees on an estimated basis</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3fe804c6-e05f-47b9-9003-c193f79c56b4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADINATH TEXTILES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KALLAM] Kallam Textiles Ltd. Approves Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025, Plans Sale of Investments</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kallam+Textiles+Ltd-%24&title=Kallam+Textiles+Ltd.+Approves+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025%2C+Plans+Sale+of+Investments&newsId=ca450a71-69db-4be4-bb93-53d56a774507&token=Y2E0NTBhNzEtNjlk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ca450a71-69db-4be4-bb93-53d56a774507</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 08:53:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kallam Textiles Ltd. has approved the un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company reported a profit before tax and exceptional items of INR 1,966.24 lakhs for the quarter and INR 1,915.87 lakhs for the nine months period. However, the profit after tax showed a loss of INR 1,978.58 lakhs for the quarter and INR 1,928.21 lakhs for the nine months period. The company also announced its plans to sell 7,15,000 equity shares in M/s Espar Pack Pvt Ltd and 3,18,305 equity shares in Shivani Power Spinners Pvt Ltd, subject to necessary approvals and compliance. The company&apos;s independent auditors, Brahmayya &amp; Co, have expressed a material uncertainty that may cast significant doubt on the company&apos;s ability to continue as a going concern due to continuous losses, default in repayment of financial debts, and legal actions for recovery of dues.</p><ul><li>Kallam Textiles Ltd. approved the un-audited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December 2025.</li><li>The company reported a profit before tax and exceptional items of INR 1,966.24 lakhs for the quarter and INR 1,915.87 lakhs for the nine months period.</li><li>The profit after tax showed a loss of INR 1,978.58 lakhs for the quarter and INR 1,928.21 lakhs for the nine months period.</li><li>The company plans to sell 7,15,000 equity shares in M/s Espar Pack Pvt Ltd and 3,18,305 equity shares in Shivani Power Spinners Pvt Ltd, subject to necessary approvals and compliance.</li><li>The company&apos;s independent auditors have expressed a material uncertainty regarding the company&apos;s ability to continue as a going concern.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1c5087d1-3289-4222-9146-5f36ac6ff213.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kallam Textiles Ltd-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PROCAL] Procal Electronics India Ltd. Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PROCAL+ELECTRONICS+INDIA+LTD.&title=Procal+Electronics+India+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025&newsId=41ea10bd-7413-47db-89bf-2272a6918cf5&token=NDFlYTEwYmQtNzQx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41ea10bd-7413-47db-89bf-2272a6918cf5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 08:52:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Procal Electronics India Ltd. has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at Rs. X lakhs for the quarter and Rs. Y lakhs for the nine months ended. The total income for the quarter is Rs. Z lakhs and for the nine months ended is Rs. A lakhs. The company&apos;s profit before exceptional items for the quarter is Rs. B and for the nine months ended is Rs. C. The net profit for the quarter is Rs. D and for the nine months ended is Rs. E. The company&apos;s earnings per share for the quarter is Rs. F and for the nine months ended is Rs. G.</p><ul><li>Procal Electronics India Ltd. has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at Rs. X lakhs for the quarter and Rs. Y lakhs for the nine months ended.</li><li>The total income for the quarter is Rs. Z lakhs and for the nine months ended is Rs. A lakhs.</li><li>The company&apos;s profit before exceptional items for the quarter is Rs. B and for the nine months ended is Rs. C.</li><li>The net profit for the quarter is Rs. D and for the nine months ended is Rs. E.</li><li>The company&apos;s earnings per share for the quarter is Rs. F and for the nine months ended is Rs. G.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dba6dd41-e601-40df-920f-fab45394264e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PROCAL ELECTRONICS INDIA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DCMSRMIND] DCM Shriram Industries Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Unaudited Financial Results for the Period Ended 31.12.2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DCM+SHRIRAM+INDUSTRIES+LTD.-%24&title=DCM+Shriram+Industries+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+the+Period+Ended+31.12.2025&newsId=8db49a13-fed9-4772-b2d6-cf9f34342fe0&token=OGRiNDlhMTMtZmVk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8db49a13-fed9-4772-b2d6-cf9f34342fe0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 08:52:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>DCM Shriram Industries Ltd has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue, expenses, and net profit have been reported. The results reflect the impact of a Composite Scheme of Arrangement, including the amalgamation of Lily Commercial Private Limited and the demerger of the Chemical and Rayon undertakings into DCM Shriram Fine Chemical Limited and DCM Shriram International Limited, respectively.</p><ul><li>Unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025</li><li>Impact of a Composite Scheme of Arrangement, including amalgamation and demerger</li><li>Revenue, expenses, and net profit reported</li><li>Adjustments made for cancellation of shares and investments</li><li>Creation of Amalgmation deficit adjustment account</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/04d7bd15-303b-4003-a763-618b9a73ad82.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DCM SHRIRAM INDUSTRIES LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUNDARAM] Sundaram Multi Pap Ltd Approves Unaudited Financial Statement for Q3 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SUNDARAM+MULTI+PAP+LTD.&title=Sundaram+Multi+Pap+Ltd+Approves+Unaudited+Financial+Statement+for+Q3+2025&newsId=27e7571f-c666-4eda-95b5-85017cb580ac&token=MjdlNzU3MWYtYzY2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27e7571f-c666-4eda-95b5-85017cb580ac</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 08:52:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sundaram Multi Pap Ltd held a board meeting on February 14, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited standalone financial statement for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025. The meeting commenced at 11.00 A.M. and concluded at 02.00 P.M. The board approved the unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 2,606.83 Lacs for the quarter ended and 9,276.26 Lacs for the nine months ended. The net profit for the period is 161.99 Lacs.</p><ul><li>Sundaram Multi Pap Ltd held a board meeting to approve the unaudited financial statement for Q3 2025.</li><li>The meeting resulted in the approval of the unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 2,606.83 Lacs for the quarter ended and 9,276.26 Lacs for the nine months ended.</li><li>The net profit for the period is 161.99 Lacs.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2f98d154-9f7a-4794-8b89-ebffe2073bee.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SUNDARAM MULTI PAP LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SOURCENTRL] Source Natural Foods Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025, Reports ¥5,398.75 Million in Net Sales</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SOURCE+NATURAL+FOODS+%26+HERBAL+SUPPL+LTD.&title=Source+Natural+Foods+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Reports+%C2%A55%2C398.75+Million+in+Net+Sales&newsId=9027746e-6a69-4f48-8a6b-53557146a375&token=OTAyNzc0NmUtNmE2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9027746e-6a69-4f48-8a6b-53557146a375</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 08:52:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Source Natural Foods and Herbal Supplements Ltd. has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company reported net sales of ¥5,398.75 million, an increase from the previous year. The Board also approved a loan and investment in the company’s subsidiary companies for execution and development of green energy projects.</p><ul><li>Source Natural Foods reported net sales of ¥5,398.75 million for the nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s Board approved a loan of up to ¥10 Crore to the company’s subsidiary(ies) companies for green energy projects.</li><li>The Board also approved an investment of up to ¥10 Crore in the equity capital of company’s subsidiary companies for green energy projects.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/06d60122-e075-4e83-98f6-a76263b81aae.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SOURCE NATURAL FOODS & HERBAL SUPPL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>