<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 12:32:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[INDIGO] InterGlobe Aviation Faces INR 22.20 Crore Penalty and Systemic Reforms by DGCA</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=InterGlobe+Aviation+Ltd&title=InterGlobe+Aviation+Faces+INR+22.20+Crore+Penalty+and+Systemic+Reforms+by+DGCA&newsId=7002db29-c42b-4ba6-9c67-0e056f7231a9&token=NzAwMmRiMjktYzQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7002db29-c42b-4ba6-9c67-0e056f7231a9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 12:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Regulatory Action</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>InterGlobe Aviation Ltd, the parent company of IndiGo, has been issued 8 orders by the Director General of Civil Aviation (DGCA) based on the findings of an Inquiry Committee. The orders include a one-time systemic penalty of INR 1.80 crore for non-compliances under applicable Civil Aviation Requirements (CARs) and a penalty of INR 20.40 crore for continued non-compliance with revised FDTL CAR for 68 days. The company is also required to furnish a Bank Guarantee of INR 50 crore under the ISRAS. The DGCA has issued cautions, warnings, and operational directives to several key personnel. The financial impact from the orders is INR 22.20 crore. The company has restored normal operations following the December 2025 disruptions and is reviewing the DGCA orders.</p><ul><li>InterGlobe Aviation faces INR 22.20 crore penalty from DGCA</li><li>DGCA issues 8 orders based on Inquiry Committee findings</li><li>Company required to furnish INR 50 crore Bank Guarantee under ISRAS</li><li>Cautions, warnings, and operational directives issued to key personnel</li><li>Company restored normal operations following December 2025 disruptions</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/75766a82-dc42-4009-a71a-7ef17989cc69.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: InterGlobe Aviation Ltd | Category: Regulatory Action</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INSPIRISYS] Inspirisys Solutions Limited Announces Change in Statutory Auditor&apos;s Name</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Inspirisys+Solutions+Ltd&title=Inspirisys+Solutions+Limited+Announces+Change+in+Statutory+Auditor%27s+Name&newsId=33316500-4f44-484c-9cc1-9db3429d71f8&token=MzMzMTY1MDAtNGY0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33316500-4f44-484c-9cc1-9db3429d71f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 12:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Inspirisys Solutions Limited has informed the Exchange about a change in the constitution of the Statutory Auditors as per the LODR Regulations, 2015. The Statutory Auditor of the Company, M/s. MSKA &amp; Associates, Chartered Accountants, has converted from a partnership firm into a Limited Liability Partnership (LLP) under the provisions of the Limited Liability Partnership Act, 2008. The firm is now known as MSKA &amp; Associates LLP, Chartered Accountants bearing ICAI Firm Registration Number 105047W (Old) / W101187 (New). This change pertains only to the constitution of the audit firm and does not result in the engagement of new Statutory Auditors. MSKA &amp; Associates LLP shall continue to act and discharge its responsibilities as the Statutory Auditors of the Company for the remaining period of the approved tenure.</p><ul><li>Inspirisys Solutions Limited announces change in Statutory Auditor&apos;s name</li><li>MSKA &amp; Associates, Chartered Accountants, converts into a Limited Liability Partnership (LLP)</li><li>The new name of the Statutory Auditor is MSKA &amp; Associates LLP, Chartered Accountants</li><li>The change is in compliance with the Limited Liability Partnership Act, 2008</li><li>MSKA &amp; Associates LLP will continue as Statutory Auditors for the remaining tenure</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9aa3e943-87b6-4e2a-b5ec-860af9a7276d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Inspirisys Solutions Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SOFTBPO] Softbpo Global Services Ltd. Approves Corrigendum to Extra Ordinary General Meeting Notice</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SOFTBPO+GLOBAL+SERVICES+LTD.&title=Softbpo+Global+Services+Ltd.+Approves+Corrigendum+to+Extra+Ordinary+General+Meeting+Notice&newsId=c4519bd8-2ce1-4c26-905e-6906291dec95&token=YzQ1MTliZDgtMmNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4519bd8-2ce1-4c26-905e-6906291dec95</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 12:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Softbpo Global Services Ltd. board of directors approved a corrigendum to the notice of the Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) scheduled for Monday, 19th January, 2026 at 11:30 a.m. The meeting was held on Sunday, 18th January, 2026, and it commenced at 4.00 p.m., concluding at 4.30 p.m. The corrigendum will be available on the company&apos;s website and on the BSE Limited website in due course.</p><ul><li>Softbpo Global Services Ltd. board approved a corrigendum to the notice of the EGM</li><li>The EGM is scheduled for Monday, 19th January, 2026 at 11:30 a.m.</li><li>The board meeting was held on Sunday, 18th January, 2026</li><li>The corrigendum will be available on the company&apos;s website and on the BSE Limited website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0fc11713-595b-4c54-839f-f45755d2c6cc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SOFTBPO GLOBAL SERVICES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VEDL] Vedanta Ltd&apos;s Subsidiary, ESL Steel, Faces Demand Notices for Alleged Shortfall in Fulfilling Production Targets</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vedanta+Limited&title=Vedanta+Ltd%27s+Subsidiary%2C+ESL+Steel%2C+Faces+Demand+Notices+for+Alleged+Shortfall+in+Fulfilling+Production+Targets&newsId=db96f249-6d34-45bc-90e6-b1146da4617f&token=ZGI5NmYyNDktNmQz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db96f249-6d34-45bc-90e6-b1146da4617f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 11:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vedanta Ltd&apos;s subsidiary, ESL Steel Limited, has received two Demand Notices from the office of Deputy Director of Mines, Koira Circle, Koira Steel &amp; Mines Department, Government of Odisha. The notices allege a shortfall in fulfilling Minimum Production and Dispatch Targets (MDPA Targets) for the fourth year of operation of two mining leases under the Mine Development &amp; Production Agreement dated November 15, 2021. The total demand amount is INR 12,55,37,61,591. ESL Steel is evaluating the Demand Notices and believes they are not sustainable on merits. The company plans to pursue legal remedies, seek a stay on the Demand Notices, and appropriate reliefs, including quashing of the impugned demands.</p><ul><li>Vedanta Ltd&apos;s subsidiary, ESL Steel Limited, received two Demand Notices from the office of Deputy Director of Mines, Koira Circle, Koira Steel &amp; Mines Department, Government of Odisha.</li><li>The notices allege a shortfall in fulfilling MDPA Targets for the fourth year of operation of two mining leases under the Mine Development &amp; Production Agreement dated November 15, 2021.</li><li>The total demand amount is INR 12,55,37,61,591.</li><li>ESL Steel is evaluating the Demand Notices and believes they are not sustainable on merits.</li><li>The company plans to pursue legal remedies, seek a stay on the Demand Notices, and appropriate reliefs, including quashing of the impugned demands.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8d2f73ff-3714-44db-ab09-3f311f47f207.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vedanta Limited | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PWL] Physicswallah Subsidiary Acquires Land for INR 38 Crore to Support Business Expansion</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Physicswallah+Ltd&title=Physicswallah+Subsidiary+Acquires+Land+for+INR+38+Crore+to+Support+Business+Expansion&newsId=b72ca66b-e84b-4790-ae15-ea3ba607aba0&token=YjcyY2E2NmItZTg0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b72ca66b-e84b-4790-ae15-ea3ba607aba0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 11:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Physicswallah Limited has informed the exchange about the execution of a sale deed for the acquisition of land by its wholly owned subsidiary, Penpencil Edu Services Private Limited. This is in continuation of the company&apos;s earlier intimation about fund infusion of approximately INR 400 crore in Penpencil to support its future expansion plans and strategic investments. Penpencil had previously acquired land for business expansion, and now, it has executed a Sale Deed dated January 17, 2026 for the acquisition of land admeasuring area 1.16 Acres, situated at Village - Tupudana, District Ranchi. The transaction value is INR 38,00,00,000 (Indian Rupees Thirty Eight Crore Only) excluding transfer and other applicable charges and duties.</p><ul><li>Physicswallah&apos;s subsidiary, Penpencil Edu Services Private Limited, has acquired land for business expansion.</li><li>The land is situated at Village - Tupudana, District Ranchi and measures 1.16 Acres.</li><li>The transaction value is INR 38,00,00,000 (Indian Rupees Thirty Eight Crore Only).</li><li>The acquisition is part of Physicswallah&apos;s approved expansion strategy and future business plans.</li><li>Penpencil may acquire additional parcels of land from the funds infused by the Company in the future.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/87733e89-01d1-4e47-a044-7a403cf0ed58.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Physicswallah Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BGPL] String Metaverse Ltd to Approve Q4 2025 Financial Results and Consider Share Capital Increase</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Bio+Green+Papers+Ltd&title=String+Metaverse+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+2025+Financial+Results+and+Consider+Share+Capital+Increase&newsId=e620aca4-3b68-43b3-ad00-a311f900bfda&token=ZTYyMGFjYTQtM2I2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e620aca4-3b68-43b3-ad00-a311f900bfda</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 09:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>String Metaverse Ltd (Formerly known as Bio Green Papers Limited) has scheduled a Board of Directors meeting on 22nd January 2026 to consider and approve the Standalone and Consolidated Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The meeting will also discuss increasing the company&apos;s authorized share capital, amending the Employee Stock Option Scheme(s), approving the Postal Ballot Notice, and other matters with the Chair&apos;s permission. The trading window for dealing in the company&apos;s securities has been closed for designated persons, their immediate relatives, and other connected persons from 1st December 2025 until 48 hours after the declaration of the aforesaid financial results.</p><ul><li>Approval of Q4 2025 financial results</li><li>Increase in the authorized share capital</li><li>Amendment of Employee Stock Option Scheme(s)</li><li>Approval of Postal Ballot Notice</li><li>Temporary closure of trading window for designated persons</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9cd82d35-4d6f-4801-94cf-9583256f285c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Bio Green Papers Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KPITTECH] KPIT Technologies Ltd Receives Request for Reclassification from Promoters Ajay Bhagwat &amp; Ashwini Bhagwat</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KPIT+Technologies+Ltd&title=KPIT+Technologies+Ltd+Receives+Request+for+Reclassification+from+Promoters+Ajay+Bhagwat+%26+Ashwini+Bhagwat&newsId=d60388a0-921e-48a3-9c7a-7f66a81c0e85&token=ZDYwMzg4YTAtOTIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d60388a0-921e-48a3-9c7a-7f66a81c0e85</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 08:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>KPIT Technologies Ltd has received request letters for reclassification from promoters, Mr. Ajay Bhagwat &amp; Ms. Ashwini Bhagwat. The two early founders of the company have not been associated with the day-to-day operations for the past two decades and have been pursuing their own independent business interests through Renu Electronics. Their shareholding is now purely financial in nature, with no managerial, strategic, or decision-making role in the Company. The reclassification from &apos;Promoter&apos; to &apos;Public&apos; category requires approval from the Board of Directors and both stock exchanges, BSE Limited &amp; National Stock Exchange of India Limited.</p><ul><li>KPIT Technologies Ltd received reclassification request from promoters Ajay Bhagwat &amp; Ashwini Bhagwat.</li><li>Ajay Bhagwat &amp; Ashwini Bhagwat were early founders but not involved in day-to-day operations for 20 years.</li><li>They have been focusing on their own business through Renu Electronics.</li><li>Their shareholding is purely financial with no managerial, strategic, or decision-making role.</li><li>Reclassification from &apos;Promoter&apos; to &apos;Public&apos; category is subject to Board and stock exchange approvals.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/db1cb18d-c6e3-48f4-88a2-bbb75af87600.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KPIT Technologies Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUCROSA] Super Crop Safe Ltd. Corrigendum: Changes in Relevant Dates for Extra-Ordinary General Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SUPER+CROP+SAFE+LTD.&title=Super+Crop+Safe+Ltd.+Corrigendum%3A+Changes+in+Relevant+Dates+for+Extra-Ordinary+General+Meeting&newsId=de87600a-ca61-474c-a965-2fe8fa812b99&token=ZGU4NzYwMGEtY2E2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de87600a-ca61-474c-a965-2fe8fa812b99</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 07:01:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Super Crop Safe Ltd. has issued a corrigendum to the notice of its Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) scheduled for January 19, 2026. The corrigendum includes amendments to the relevant dates for determining the minimum issue price and floor price of equity shares, and the date for calculating the trading days for the company&apos;s shares. The changes are in accordance with the ICDR Regulations and SEBI(ICDR) Regulations.</p><ul><li>Amendments to the relevant date for determining the minimum issue price of equity shares</li><li>Changes in the relevant date for calculating the floor price for the issue of equity shares</li><li>Revision in the relevant date for the purpose of calculating the trading days for the company&apos;s shares</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a9c55487-6968-4c56-ab86-22782403e450.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SUPER CROP SAFE LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SEAMECLTD] Seamec Ltd&apos;s Vessel &apos;SEAMEC PALADIN&apos; Sails to Dubai for Statutory Drydocking</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SEAMEC+LTD.&title=Seamec+Ltd%27s+Vessel+%27SEAMEC+PALADIN%27+Sails+to+Dubai+for+Statutory+Drydocking&newsId=86542403-86ce-4eb5-ab66-1df6f0e40bad&token=ODY1NDI0MDMtODZj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86542403-86ce-4eb5-ab66-1df6f0e40bad</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 07:01:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Seamec Ltd has informed that their vessel, &apos;SEAMEC PALADIN&apos;, has sailed to Dubai on 17th January 2026 at 22:05 hours for undertaking Statutory Drydocking. Upon completion of the drydock, the vessel will return to India to continue its Long Term Charter with ONGC. The event was reported at 22:50 hours on 17th January 2026.</p><ul><li>Seamec Ltd&apos;s vessel &apos;SEAMEC PALADIN&apos; has sailed to Dubai for Statutory Drydocking.</li><li>The drydocking is expected to be completed in due course.</li><li>Upon completion, the vessel will return to India to continue its Long Term Charter with ONGC.</li><li>The event was reported on 17th January 2026 at 22:50 hours.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1bf77337-e26f-4cff-a180-7c86647c0fec.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SEAMEC LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HPAL] Fire Incident at HP Adhesives Ltd Manufacturing Unit</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HP+Adhesives+Ltd&title=Fire+Incident+at+HP+Adhesives+Ltd+Manufacturing+Unit&newsId=ea4afca3-f409-44d5-b371-3d69827b55df&token=ZWE0YWZjYTMtZjQw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ea4afca3-f409-44d5-b371-3d69827b55df</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 07:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Incident</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>A fire incident occurred at HP Adhesives Ltd&apos;&apos;s manufacturing unit in Raigad, Maharashtra on Saturday, 17th January 2026. The cause of the fire is currently under investigation. There were no casualties or injuries. The company is assessing the damage and loss, and has adequate insurance coverage to cover the costs. They are taking necessary steps to restore normal operations at the plant.</p><ul><li>Fire incident at HP Adhesives Ltd manufacturing unit</li><li>No casualties or injuries reported</li><li>Company assessing damage and loss</li><li>Adequate insurance coverage in place</li><li>Company taking steps to restore normal operations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/193f1b0a-76a6-4e3e-beb2-33b873c0ddf4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HP Adhesives Ltd | Category: Incident</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>