<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:05:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[PFIZER] Pfizer Ltd Announces Changes in Senior Management: Appointment of Nilesh Pendse as Category Lead — Vaccines and Changes for Other Senior Personnel</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PFIZER+LTD.&title=Pfizer+Ltd+Announces+Changes+in+Senior+Management%3A+Appointment+of+Nilesh+Pendse+as+Category+Lead+%E2%80%94+Vaccines+and+Changes+for+Other+Senior+Personnel&newsId=e11abea6-bfce-4c1c-a11a-00217ef00eeb&token=ZTExYWJlYTYtYmZj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e11abea6-bfce-4c1c-a11a-00217ef00eeb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 03:58:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pfizer Ltd has announced changes in its senior management. Mr. Nilesh Pendse has been appointed as Category Lead — Vaccines, effective February 1, 2026. Mr. Manikantan Seshadrinathan will transition to another role within the Pfizer Group Companies, ceasing to be a Senior Management Personnel of the Company from January 31, 2026. Mr. Prashant Mahalingam will take up additional responsibility of the Hospitals Business and will be redesignated as Category Lead — Internal Medicine &amp; Hospitals, effective February 1, 2026. Mr. Pendse has a strong background in strategic growth, market access, stakeholder engagement, sales, marketing, and business transformation.</p><ul><li>Mr. Nilesh Pendse appointed as Category Lead — Vaccines of Pfizer Ltd</li><li>Mr. Manikantan Seshadrinathan to transition to another role within Pfizer Group Companies</li><li>Mr. Prashant Mahalingam to take up additional responsibility of the Hospitals Business</li><li>Mr. Pendse has a strong background in strategic growth, market access, stakeholder engagement, sales, marketing, and business transformation</li><li>Changes in senior management of Pfizer Ltd to be effective from February 1, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fcefdd38-abc4-41ea-b4fa-4db4bd11c904.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PFIZER LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LODHA] Lodha Developers Commits Additional 1L Crore Investment in Data Centre</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Macrotech+Developers+Ltd&title=Lodha+Developers+Commits+Additional+1L+Crore+Investment+in+Data+Centre&newsId=0b683dd2-fe1c-46ff-bcd2-80bd97a13758&token=MGI2ODNkZDItZmUx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b683dd2-fe1c-46ff-bcd2-80bd97a13758</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 03:36:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>MoU</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Lodha Developers Ltd has signed an MoU with the Maharashtra government for an additional 1L crore investment in a data centre. This brings the total investment to 1.3 lakh crores for a 2.5 gigawatt data centre park, making it the largest in the country. The park will create over 16,000 direct and indirect jobs and accommodate several major international and domestic players. Amazon and STT Global Data Centres have already acquired land parcels in the park.</p><ul><li>Lodha Developers commits additional 1L crore investment in data centre</li><li>Total investment now stands at 1.3 lakh crores for a 2.5 gigawatt data centre park</li><li>Data centre park to be the largest in the country</li><li>Over 16,000 direct and indirect jobs to be created</li><li>Amazon and STT Global Data Centres have already acquired land parcels in the park</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8b50719c-b2ac-475c-bb54-c7d39f3d73c4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Macrotech Developers Ltd | Category: MoU</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ECORECO] Eco Recycling Ltd &amp; BookMyJunk Initiate Nationwide E-Waste Collection with 100,000 &apos;Eco-Bins&apos;</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ECO+RECYCLING+LTD.&title=Eco+Recycling+Ltd+%26+BookMyJunk+Initiate+Nationwide+E-Waste+Collection+with+100%2C000+%27Eco-Bins%27&newsId=1f62360a-956c-4874-a05d-6a841ef0a9b9&token=MWY2MjM2MGEtOTU2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f62360a-956c-4874-a05d-6a841ef0a9b9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 03:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Eco Recycling Ltd, in collaboration with its associate brand BookMyJunk, has started a nationwide initiative to deploy 100,000 &apos;Eco-Bins&apos; across India for the collection of small electronic waste items. The &apos;Awareness cum Action&apos; drive aims to provide a seamless &amp; effortless service to environmentally conscious generators of e-waste, especially young generations and students, to facilitate scientific disposal of e-waste items. The initiative is expected to promote environmentally sound e-waste disposal, support India’s circular economy objectives, improve recovery of valuable resources, and strengthen compliance with Extended Producer Responsibility (EPR) frameworks. The proposed initiative envisages CSR &amp; EPR contribution in the range of ₹ 3200-250 crore over a period of 5 years.</p><ul><li>Eco Recycling Ltd and BookMyJunk to deploy 100,000 &apos;Eco-Bins&apos; across India for e-waste collection</li><li>Initiative targets educational institutions, corporate offices, and commercial establishments</li><li>Aims to promote environmentally sound e-waste disposal and support India’s circular economy objectives</li><li>Expected to improve recovery of valuable resources and strengthen compliance with EPR frameworks</li><li>Proposed initiative envisages CSR &amp; EPR contribution of ₹ 3200-250 crore over 5 years</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0bc6fc17-0d48-4a60-b5f8-1b07bb8eb655.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ECO RECYCLING LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ATISHAY] Atishay Ltd Secures Rs. 3.77 Crore Work Order for Digitisation of Registration Records</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Atishay+Ltd&title=Atishay+Ltd+Secures+Rs.+3.77+Crore+Work+Order+for+Digitisation+of+Registration+Records&newsId=8b153a64-e61a-4af9-9b61-a66d661c699f&token=OGIxNTNhNjQtZTYx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b153a64-e61a-4af9-9b61-a66d661c699f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 02:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Atishay Ltd has announced that it has received a work order for the digitisation of registration records from the Department of Prohibition, Excise and Registration, Government of Bihar. The order value is Rs. 3.77 Crores and it involves the digitisation of approximately 29 lakh documents from the locations Purniya and Madhubani. The completion timeline for this project is 180 days. This engagement strengthens the company&apos;s executable order book, enhances revenue visibility, and reinforces its position as a trusted implementation partner for large-scale Government digitisation projects.</p><ul><li>Atishay Ltd has received a work order for digitisation of registration records from the Department of Prohibition, Excise and Registration, Government of Bihar.</li><li>The order value is Rs. 3.77 Crores.</li><li>The project involves the digitisation of approximately 29 lakh documents from the locations Purniya and Madhubani.</li><li>The completion timeline for this project is 180 days.</li><li>This engagement strengthens the company&apos;s executable order book and reinforces its position as a trusted implementation partner for large-scale Government digitisation projects.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/63e82d5f-03d0-49a4-9798-13905a05365f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Atishay Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LGEINDIA] LG Electronics India Clarifies on No Demand of Differential Duty</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LG+Electronics+India+Ltd&title=LG+Electronics+India+Clarifies+on+No+Demand+of+Differential+Duty&newsId=7b65e346-e4fc-4fb3-b6ef-3cd159bec3f3&token=N2I2NWUzNDYtZTRm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b65e346-e4fc-4fb3-b6ef-3cd159bec3f3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 02:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>LG Electronics India Ltd has issued a clarification regarding an earlier disclosure about an Order-in-Original (OIO) passed by the Office of Commissioner of Customs. The company, upon further examination, states that no demand of differential duty amounting to Rs. 11,91,51,910/- has been raised or confirmed on LG Electronics India Limited. This clarification is to ensure accurate information is available to stakeholders and the Stock Exchanges.</p><ul><li>LG Electronics India clarifies on no demand of differential duty</li><li>The clarification is in reference to an earlier disclosure regarding an Order-in-Original passed by the Office of Commissioner of Customs</li><li>No demand of Rs. 11,91,51,910/- has been raised or confirmed on LG Electronics India Limited</li><li>This clarification is to ensure accurate information for stakeholders and the Stock Exchanges</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6b625099-4570-4aa5-804e-d7bc52d60ea0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LG Electronics India Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INOXGREEN] Inox Green Energy Services Ltd. Secures O&amp;M Contract for 625 MWp Solar Project from KEC</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Inox+Green+Energy+Services+Ltd&title=Inox+Green+Energy+Services+Ltd.+Secures+O%26M+Contract+for+625+MWp+Solar+Project+from+KEC&newsId=f9d972ec-211f-4621-aef2-7f17a010e16e&token=ZjlkOTcyZWMtMjEx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9d972ec-211f-4621-aef2-7f17a010e16e</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 02:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>O&amp;M Agreement</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Inox Green Energy Services Ltd., a leading renewables operations and maintenance (O&amp;M) service provider in India, has been awarded a Letter of Award (LoA) from KEC International Ltd. to provide O&amp;M services for a 625 MWp solar project in Bhadla, Rajasthan. This addition takes Inox Green&apos;s solar O&amp;M portfolio to over 3 GW, contributing to a total renewable O&amp;M portfolio of more than 13 GW. The company is rapidly expanding in both solar and wind segments, aiming to add more O&amp;M portfolios in the renewable energy space.</p><ul><li>Inox Green Energy Services Ltd. has been awarded a LoA from KEC International Ltd. for O&amp;M services of a 625 MWp solar project in Bhadla, Rajasthan.</li><li>This agreement expands Inox Green&apos;s solar O&amp;M portfolio to over 3 GW and its total renewable O&amp;M portfolio to more than 13 GW.</li><li>Inox Green is rapidly expanding in both solar and wind segments, aiming to add more O&amp;M portfolios in the renewable energy space.</li><li>Inox Green Energy Services Ltd. is a leading renewables O&amp;M service provider in India, part of the INOXGFL Group and a subsidiary of Inox Wind.</li><li>Inox Green has a strong and diverse portfolio base spread across 12 Indian states and an established track record of over a decade.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/18d4865d-dec7-4c97-b446-13e32a4ba74c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Inox Green Energy Services Ltd | Category: O&M Agreement</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ORIENTTR] Orient Tradelink Ltd Allots 3,90,682 Equity Shares at INR 22 Each, Increasing Paid-up Equity Share Capital</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ORIENT+TRADELINK+LTD.&title=Orient+Tradelink+Ltd+Allots+3%2C90%2C682+Equity+Shares+at+INR+22+Each%2C+Increasing+Paid-up+Equity+Share+Capital&newsId=60383891-e275-465b-9dcd-2191c0ef2825&token=NjAzODM4OTEtZTI3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60383891-e275-465b-9dcd-2191c0ef2825</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 00:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Orient Tradelink Ltd has allotted 3,90,682 equity shares of INR 10 each at a price of INR 22 per share, comprising of a premium of INR 12 per share. The allotment was made to four non-promoter allottees: Shikha, Sanjay Sinha, Bhawna Shadija, and Sunita Panwar. The allotment increased the company&apos;s paid-up equity share capital from INR 37,96,24,520 divided into 3,79,62,452 Equity Shares of INR 10/-each to INR 38,35,31,340 divided into 3,83,53,134 Equity Shares of INR 10/-each.</p><ul><li>Orient Tradelink Ltd allotted 3,90,682 equity shares at INR 22 per share with a premium of INR 12 per share.</li><li>The allotment was made to four non-promoter allottees: Shikha, Sanjay Sinha, Bhawna Shadija, and Sunita Panwar.</li><li>The allotment increased the company&apos;s paid-up equity share capital from INR 37,96,24,520 to INR 38,35,31,340.</li><li>The allotment was made in accordance with the provisions of Chapter V of the SEBI (Issue of Capital and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2018.</li><li>The allotment was approved in a Board of Directors meeting held on Monday, 19 January 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ea0cc2ac-fa20-4ad7-9626-1bf035ce51af.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ORIENT TRADELINK LTD. | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ORIENTTR] Orient Tradelink Ltd Allots 3,90,682 Equity Shares at INR 22 Each, Increasing Paid-up Equity Share Capital</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ORIENT+TRADELINK+LTD.&title=Orient+Tradelink+Ltd+Allots+3%2C90%2C682+Equity+Shares+at+INR+22+Each%2C+Increasing+Paid-up+Equity+Share+Capital&newsId=0366bec1-a93a-43f6-b42e-9d19561b40b5&token=MDM2NmJlYzEtYTkz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0366bec1-a93a-43f6-b42e-9d19561b40b5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 00:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Orient Tradelink Ltd has allotted 3,90,682 equity shares of INR 10 each at a price of INR 22 per share, comprising of a premium of INR 12 per share. The allotment was made to four non-promoter allottees: Shikha, Sanjay Sinha, Bhawna Shadija, and Sunita Panwar. The allotment increased the company&apos;s paid-up equity share capital from INR 37,96,24,520 divided into 3,79,62,452 Equity Shares of INR 10/-each to INR 38,35,31,340 divided into 3,83,53,134 Equity Shares of INR 10/-each.</p><ul><li>Orient Tradelink Ltd allotted 3,90,682 equity shares at INR 22 per share with a premium of INR 12 per share.</li><li>The allotment was made to four non-promoter allottees: Shikha, Sanjay Sinha, Bhawna Shadija, and Sunita Panwar.</li><li>The allotment increased the company&apos;s paid-up equity share capital from INR 37,96,24,520 to INR 38,35,31,340.</li><li>The decision was made in a board meeting held on Monday, 19 January 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d3d5bd32-214f-45be-8e14-ce270225817b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ORIENT TRADELINK LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SWORDEDGE] Sword-Edge Commercials Ltd Appoints Three New Independent Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sword-Edge+Commercials+Limited&title=Sword-Edge+Commercials+Ltd+Appoints+Three+New+Independent+Directors&newsId=b8ef65f9-9abf-4f2d-952f-a547f69470fe&token=YjhlZjY1ZjktOWFi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8ef65f9-9abf-4f2d-952f-a547f69470fe</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 00:08:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sword-Edge Commercials Ltd, a company based in Mumbai, Maharashtra, has announced the appointment of three new Additional Non-Executive Independent Directors: Ms. Neha Kargeti, Ms. Adithi Rathore, and Mr. Kulbir Singh Sandhu. The appointments are for a term of 5 consecutive years from January 19, 2026, to January 18, 2031, subject to the approval of the shareholders. The appointments were made based on the recommendation of the Nomination and Remuneration Committee. The new directors bring a diverse set of skills and experiences to the board, which will support effective governance, risk management, and compliance within the company.</p><ul><li>Appointment of three new Additional Non-Executive Independent Directors: Ms. Neha Kargeti, Ms. Adithi Rathore, and Mr. Kulbir Singh Sandhu</li><li>Appointments are for a term of 5 consecutive years from January 19, 2026, to January 18, 2031</li><li>Appointments are subject to the approval of the shareholders</li><li>New directors bring a diverse set of skills and experiences to the board</li><li>Reconstitution of certain committees of the Board of Directors with effect from January 19, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/75107358-931f-450d-9fe7-de45c285c5b1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sword-Edge Commercials Limited | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[OXFORDIN] Devendra Batukanath Shukla Acquires 7.09% Stake in Oxford Industries Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Oxford+Industries+Ltd&title=Devendra+Batukanath+Shukla+Acquires+7.09%25+Stake+in+Oxford+Industries+Ltd&newsId=d3bb66ed-6d50-4530-904e-5d3287cd443d&token=ZDNiYjY2ZWQtNmQ1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3bb66ed-6d50-4530-904e-5d3287cd443d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 00:07:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Devendra Batukanath Shukla has acquired 421,175 shares carrying voting rights in Oxford Industries Ltd, amounting to 7.09% of the total voting rights. This acquisition was made through a mode other than open market, public issue, rights issue, preferential allotment, inter-se transfer, or encumbrance. The acquired shares have a face value of Rs. 10 each and will rank pari-passu to the existing shares. The acquisition was made before the equity shares&apos; redemption date of 5/12/2025.</p><ul><li>Devendra Batukanath Shukla acquires 7.09% stake in Oxford Industries Ltd</li><li>Acquisition made through a mode other than open market, public issue, rights issue, preferential allotment, inter-se transfer, or encumbrance</li><li>Acquired shares have a face value of Rs. 10 each</li><li>Acquired shares will rank pari-passu to the existing shares</li><li>Acquisition made before the equity shares&apos; redemption date of 5/12/2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/AA7CC167_90F7_4F3A_AB67_D281A06A588E_193105.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Oxford Industries Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>