<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:44:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[HGS] Hinduja Global Solutions to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on Feb 10, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HINDUJA+GLOBAL+SOLUTIONS+LTD.&title=Hinduja+Global+Solutions+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+Feb+10%2C+2026&newsId=beca9c32-2035-4cb8-9c3a-3a43ebc9e63b&token=YmVjYTljMzItMjAz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">beca9c32-2035-4cb8-9c3a-3a43ebc9e63b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hinduja Global Solutions Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 10, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results (Standalone and Consolidated) for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in the equity shares of the company will remain closed for all Designated Persons and their immediate relatives from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of the Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Hinduja Global Solutions to approve Q3 and nine months financial results on Feb 10, 2026</li><li>Trading window to remain closed for Designated Persons and their immediate relatives from Jan 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the declaration of results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1041c205-3704-42f7-8fc8-b1891a1411bd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HINDUJA GLOBAL SOLUTIONS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BLUEDART] Blue Dart Express Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025-2026 with Exceptional Item of ₹ 4,423 Lakhs due to Labour Codes Implementation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BLUE+DART+EXPRESS+LTD.&title=Blue+Dart+Express+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025-2026+with+Exceptional+Item+of+%E2%82%B9+4%2C423+Lakhs+due+to+Labour+Codes+Implementation&newsId=5865bf1d-9eec-44ab-8fe5-fb545529480b&token=NTg2NWJmMWQtOWVl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5865bf1d-9eec-44ab-8fe5-fb545529480b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:42:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Blue Dart Express Ltd, an integrated air and ground transportation and distribution company, has reported its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at ₹ 1,61,616 lakhs for the quarter and ₹ 4,60,741 lakhs for the nine-month period. The total income for the quarter is ₹ 1,63,503 lakhs and ₹ 5,77,303 lakhs for the nine-month period. The company has recognized an exceptional item of ₹ 4,423 lakhs in the standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025 due to the implementation of the Labour Codes. The statutory auditors have carried out a limited review of the company&apos;s financial results for the period with no qualifications in the limited review report.</p><ul><li>Blue Dart Express Ltd reports Q3 and nine-month results for 2025-2026.</li><li>Revenue from operations stands at ₹ 1,61,616 lakhs for the quarter and ₹ 4,60,741 lakhs for the nine-month period.</li><li>Total income for the quarter is ₹ 1,63,503 lakhs and ₹ 5,77,303 lakhs for the nine-month period.</li><li>Exceptional item of ₹ 4,423 lakhs recognized due to Labour Codes implementation.</li><li>No qualifications in the limited review report issued by statutory auditors.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/90a0c063-4dbc-4290-a657-d91e010e3fc9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BLUE DART EXPRESS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TFCILTD] Tourism Finance Corporation of India Ltd. Approves Q3 &amp; Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TOURISM+FINANCE+CORPORATION+OF+INDIA+LTD.&title=Tourism+Finance+Corporation+of+India+Ltd.+Approves+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=738f1905-0e97-4655-99e6-dba0b6d50afe&token=NzM4ZjE5MDUtMGU5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">738f1905-0e97-4655-99e6-dba0b6d50afe</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:42:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Tourism Finance Corporation of India Ltd. met on January 30, 2026, and approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting was conducted in accordance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations 2015. The results will be published in newspapers as required by the SEBI regulations. The review report was issued by Rama K Gupta &amp; Company Chartered Accountants.</p><ul><li>The Board of Directors met and approved the unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The meeting was conducted in accordance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations 2015.</li><li>The results are to be published in newspapers as per SEBI regulations.</li><li>The review report was issued by Rama K Gupta &amp; Company Chartered Accountants.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4a2aa34f-67eb-4fd1-b7d1-fdef3cab8d12.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TOURISM FINANCE CORPORATION OF INDIA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LEMONTREE] Lemon Tree&apos;s Subsidiary, Fleur Hotels, Signs License Deed for a Heritage Hotel in Varanasi</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Lemon+Tree+Hotels+Ltd&title=Lemon+Tree%27s+Subsidiary%2C+Fleur+Hotels%2C+Signs+License+Deed+for+a+Heritage+Hotel+in+Varanasi&newsId=7236946c-cfb6-4dc1-b6a3-dc55501cd2a5&token=NzIzNjk0NmMtY2Zi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7236946c-cfb6-4dc1-b6a3-dc55501cd2a5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Lemon Tree Hotels Limited has announced that its material subsidiary, Fleur Hotels Limited, has entered into a License Deed for a Heritage Hotel at Varanasi. The hotel, to be branded as &apos;Aurika Varanasi&apos;, will have approximately 47 rooms and is strategically located near the river Ganges. This signing reinforces Lemon Tree Hotels&apos; focus on expanding across leisure and destination-led markets, particularly in culturally significant cities with strong tourism potential.</p><ul><li>Lemon Tree Hotels&apos; subsidiary, Fleur Hotels, signs a License Deed for a Heritage Hotel in Varanasi.</li><li>The hotel, to be branded as &apos;Aurika Varanasi&apos;, will have approximately 47 rooms.</li><li>The hotel is strategically located near the river Ganges, making it easily accessible for both domestic and international travellers.</li><li>This signing reinforces Lemon Tree Hotels&apos; focus on expanding across leisure and destination-led markets.</li><li>Lemon Tree Hotels has a growing pipeline of 130+ upcoming properties across India and abroad.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b81a1d72-5eda-43c3-9686-fd27080052de.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Lemon Tree Hotels Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RPGLIFE] RPG Life Sciences Ltd Executes Share Subscription and Shareholders&apos; Agreement with First Energy 11 Private Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RPG+LIFE+SCIENCES+LTD.&title=RPG+Life+Sciences+Ltd+Executes+Share+Subscription+and+Shareholders%27+Agreement+with+First+Energy+11+Private+Limited&newsId=fc178a3c-a0b3-4737-9b92-b16fce29ec69&token=ZmMxNzhhM2MtYTBi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc178a3c-a0b3-4737-9b92-b16fce29ec69</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:42:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>RPG Life Sciences Ltd has executed Share Subscription and Shareholders&apos; Agreement (SSSHA) and Captive Power Agreement (CPA) with First Energy 11 Private Limited. The agreements are for procuring electricity from First Energy 11 Private Limited&apos;s Wind-Solar Hybrid Power plant situated at Gujarat for the Formulation Plant of the Company at Ankleshwar, Gujarat. The Company plans to invest up to Rs.1,50,00,000 (Rupees One crore Fifty lakhs only) in one or more tranches, towards subscription of the equity shares by the Company along with other Captive Users collectively owning not less than 26% (Twenty Six percent) of the paid up equity share capital of the Captive Power Producer.</p><ul><li>RPG Life Sciences Ltd has executed Share Subscription and Shareholders&apos; Agreement (SSSHA) and Captive Power Agreement (CPA) with First Energy 11 Private Limited</li><li>The agreements are for procuring electricity from First Energy 11 Private Limited&apos;s Wind-Solar Hybrid Power plant situated at Gujarat</li><li>The Company plans to invest up to Rs.1,50,00,000 (Rupees One crore Fifty lakhs only) in one or more tranches</li><li>The power will be supplied to the Formulation Plant of the Company at Ankleshwar, Gujarat</li><li>The Company and other Captive Users will collectively own not less than 26% (Twenty Six percent) of the paid up equity share capital of the Captive Power Producer</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8d1c654a-abd4-4d02-ab6c-6a966f1ba7e5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RPG LIFE SCIENCES LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HIMTEK] Him Teknoforge Ltd. Reports Deviation in Use of Preferential Issue Proceeds</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Him+Teknoforge+Ltd&title=Him+Teknoforge+Ltd.+Reports+Deviation+in+Use+of+Preferential+Issue+Proceeds&newsId=85f6c39d-44f0-4234-9a63-5586ed751bcf&token=ODVmNmMzOWQtNDRm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85f6c39d-44f0-4234-9a63-5586ed751bcf</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:42:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Him Teknoforge Ltd. has reported a deviation in the use of proceeds from the preferential issue of share warrants. The deviation is within 10% of the earlier disclosed object of the issue and has been approved by shareholders. The deviation is reported in the statement of Deviation and Variation pursuant to Regulation 32 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The funds utilization status is as on 31st December, 2025 for the funds raised Rs. 1740.38 Lakhs, inclusive of Application Money of Rs. 717.15 Lakhs towards subscription to Share Warrants and further funds received till 31st December, 2025.</p><ul><li>Him Teknoforge Ltd. reports deviation in use of proceeds from preferential issue of share warrants</li><li>Deviation is within 10% of the earlier disclosed object of the issue and has been approved by shareholders</li><li>Deviation reported in the statement of Deviation and Variation pursuant to Regulation 32 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Funds utilization status as on 31st December, 2025 for the funds raised Rs. 1740.38 Lakhs</li><li>Inclusive of Application Money of Rs. 717.15 Lakhs towards subscription to Share Warrants and further funds received till 31st December, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5ab4689a-0180-4713-9953-c460ede8290b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Him Teknoforge Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASTEC] Astec LifeSciences Ltd. Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025, Resignation of CFO, and Appointment of New CFO</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ASTEC+LIFESCIENCES+LIMITED&title=Astec+LifeSciences+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Resignation+of+CFO%2C+and+Appointment+of+New+CFO&newsId=f3c7b58c-ac72-48ad-b1ea-29bb2ede289c&token=ZjNjN2I1OGMtYWM3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3c7b58c-ac72-48ad-b1ea-29bb2ede289c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Astec LifeSciences Ltd. announced the outcome of its Board Meeting held on 30th January, 2026. The company released the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The Board noted the limited review reports of the statutory auditors with unmodified opinions. The company&apos;s Chief Financial Officer, Ms. Mugdha Amol Khare, tendered her resignation effective from 6th March, 2026, and Mr. Deepak Jawaharlal Ochani has been appointed as the new CFO with effect from 1st April, 2026.</p><ul><li>Astec LifeSciences Ltd. released the unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December, 2025.</li><li>The Board noted the limited review reports of the statutory auditors with unmodified opinions.</li><li>Ms. Mugdha Amol Khare resigned from the position of CFO, effective from 6th March, 2026.</li><li>Mr. Deepak Jawaharlal Ochani has been appointed as the new CFO, effective from 1st April, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7dbf59e1-60d7-43d2-aea9-130fdc9bf50d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ASTEC LIFESCIENCES LIMITED | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HIMTEK] Him Teknoforge Ltd Re-Appoints Cost Auditor M/s S.k. Jain &amp; Co for FY 2026-27</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Him+Teknoforge+Ltd&title=Him+Teknoforge+Ltd+Re-Appoints+Cost+Auditor+M%2Fs+S.k.+Jain+%26+Co+for+FY+2026-27&newsId=ebb4412e-ebd9-4a19-ba8f-88e86bd5e5ef&token=ZWJiNDQxMmUtZWJk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ebb4412e-ebd9-4a19-ba8f-88e86bd5e5ef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Cost Auditor Re-Appointment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Him Teknoforge Ltd has announced the re-appointment of M/s S.k. Jain &amp; Co as the Cost Auditor for the financial year 2026-27. The decision was made at the Board of Directors&apos; meeting held on 30th January 2026, following the recommendation of the Audit Committee. Sudhir Kumar Jain, the Cost Accountant and Insolvency Professional leading M/s S.k. Jain &amp; Co, brings over 45 years of experience in financial management, strategic planning, budgeting, and fund management. He has a strong background in cost auditing, insolvency resolution, financial planning, and project financing, and has held leadership positions in various organizations. He has also contributed to academia and has authored books and study materials on finance, GST, cyber security, and business management. His technical acumen includes developing AI-based financial tools and software to streamline financial reporting and cost auditing.</p><ul><li>Him Teknoforge Ltd re-appoints M/s S.k. Jain &amp; Co as Cost Auditor for FY 2026-27</li><li>Re-appointment made following the Audit Committee&apos;s recommendation</li><li>Sudhir Kumar Jain, a seasoned Cost Accountant and Insolvency Professional, leads M/s S.k. Jain &amp; Co</li><li>Jain has over 45 years of experience in financial management and strategic planning</li><li>He has expertise in cost auditing, insolvency resolution, financial planning, and project financing</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/401ffd08-c901-490b-acc1-1e2d4be31c29.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Him Teknoforge Ltd | Category: Cost Auditor Re-Appointment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KHADIM] Khadim India Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025 on Feb 10, 2026 Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Khadim+India+Ltd&title=Khadim+India+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025+on+Feb+10%2C+2026+Board+Meeting&newsId=d2bca98c-bd47-4196-82bb-c48ca0f6f4f2&token=ZDJiY2E5OGMtYmQ0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2bca98c-bd47-4196-82bb-c48ca0f6f4f2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Khadim India Ltd, a company listed on BSE, has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 10, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. This is in accordance with Regulation 29 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Khadim India Ltd to hold a Board Meeting on February 10, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>The announcement is in accordance with Regulation 29 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/32985fbd-07fb-4c1b-936c-717e0548ec51.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Khadim India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LCCINFOTEC] LCC Infotech Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q3 and 9M Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LCC+INFOTECH+LTD.&title=LCC+Infotech+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+and+9M+Results+for+2025&newsId=c95c2204-d802-4cee-9b39-3c51d801c838&token=Yzk1YzIyMDQtZDgw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c95c2204-d802-4cee-9b39-3c51d801c838</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>LCC Infotech Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 13, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting is scheduled in accordance with the SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2013. The company has also informed that the trading window will remain closed up to February 15, 2026.</p><ul><li>LCC Infotech Ltd to hold a Board Meeting on February 13, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the unaudited financial results for Q3 and 9M ended December 31, 2025</li><li>The meeting is in accordance with the SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2013</li><li>The trading window will remain closed up to February 15, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/37d8db93-8018-4792-bdfc-a0aa366471e5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LCC INFOTECH LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>