<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 04:04:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[KERNEX] Kernex Microsystems India Ltd Secures Rs. 2,465.71 Crores Order from CLW for On-board KAVACH Loco Equipment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KERNEX+MICROSYSTEMS+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Kernex+Microsystems+India+Ltd+Secures+Rs.+2%2C465.71+Crores+Order+from+CLW+for+On-board+KAVACH+Loco+Equipment&newsId=7235ca3c-8b4d-415c-ae87-613ceecb3ed1&token=NzIzNWNhM2MtOGI0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7235ca3c-8b4d-415c-ae87-613ceecb3ed1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 04:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Kernex Microsystems India Ltd has been awarded an order valued at Rs. 2,465.71 crores by Chittaranjan Locomotive Works (CLW) for the supply, installation, testing and commissioning of 3,024 sets of On-board KAVACH Loco Equipment. This strategic order enhances the company&apos;s revenue visibility and reinforces its market position in the railway safety sector.</p><ul><li>Kernex Microsystems India Ltd secures a significant order worth Rs. 2,465.71 crores from Chittaranjan Locomotive Works (CLW).</li><li>The order is for the supply, installation, testing and commissioning of 3,024 sets of On-board KAVACH Loco Equipment.</li><li>This order is expected to enhance the company&apos;s revenue visibility and strengthen its market position in the railway safety sector.</li><li>The contract is awarded for a period of 12 months from the date of purchase order.</li><li>The order value is Rs. 2,465.71 crores.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5cd4654e-4fd7-4a36-a093-d3cb3b7ac1ba.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KERNEX MICROSYSTEMS (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BIOCON] Biocon Limited Raises Rs 4,150 Crore (~USD 460 Million) through a Qualified Institutions Placement (QIP)</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BIOCON+LTD.&title=Biocon+Limited+Raises+Rs+4%2C150+Crore+%28~USD+460+Million%29+through+a+Qualified+Institutions+Placement+%28QIP%29&newsId=8349388c-f8d4-4f8f-940a-85e00b38cbaa&token=ODM0OTM4OGMtZjhk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8349388c-f8d4-4f8f-940a-85e00b38cbaa</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Biocon Limited, an innovation-led global biopharmaceutical company, has successfully completed a Qualified Institutions Placement (QIP), raising Rs 4,150 crore (~USD 460 million) through the issuance of equity shares. The QIP saw healthy interest from all pools of capital, reflecting robust confidence in Biocon’s growth prospects. The proceeds from the QIP will be primarily utilized to meet the cash consideration payable to Mylan Inc. (Viatris) for buying out its shareholding in Biocon Biologics Limited, including repayment of debt availed in this regard. The integration of Biocon Biologics Limited, making it a wholly owned subsidiary of the Company, is expected to be completed no later than March 31, 2026. The Book Running Lead Managers to the QIP were Kotak Mahindra Capital Company Limited, HSBC Securities and Capital Markets (India) Private Limited, J.P. Morgan India Private Limited and Morgan Stanley India Company Private Limited.</p><ul><li>Biocon Limited raises Rs 4,150 crore (~USD 460 million) through a Qualified Institutions Placement (QIP)</li><li>QIP saw healthy interest from all pools of capital across Domestic Mutual Funds, Domestic Insurance Companies, and Foreign Institutional Investors</li><li>Proceeds from the QIP will be utilized to meet the cash consideration payable to Mylan Inc. (Viatris) for buying out its shareholding in Biocon Biologics Limited</li><li>Biocon Biologics Limited to become a wholly owned subsidiary of Biocon Limited</li><li>Book Running Lead Managers to the QIP were Kotak Mahindra Capital Company Limited, HSBC Securities and Capital Markets (India) Private Limited, J.P. Morgan India Private Limited and Morgan Stanley India Company Private Limited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/785e84f9-c475-4b62-8304-c8edca4b675e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BIOCON LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RPOWER] SEBI Initiates Forensic Audit of Reliance Power Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RELIANCE+POWER+LTD.&title=SEBI+Initiates+Forensic+Audit+of+Reliance+Power+Ltd&newsId=95ca012b-c190-4003-89ce-081ae4f40606&token=OTVjYTAxMmItYzE5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95ca012b-c190-4003-89ce-081ae4f40606</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pursuant to Regulation 30 of the Securities Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, Reliance Power Ltd has disclosed that the Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) has initiated a forensic audit of the Company. The audit is in relation to the alleged violations of the SEBI Act, 1992, SCRA, 1956 and Companies Act, 2013.</p><ul><li>SEBI has initiated a forensic audit of Reliance Power Ltd</li><li>The audit is in relation to the alleged violations of the SEBI Act, 1992, SCRA, 1956 and Companies Act, 2013</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3e05bd37-b4ea-4c23-9d02-ad3cfdac8dfb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RELIANCE POWER LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BIOCON] Biocon Ltd Raises ₹ 41,500 Million Through Qualified Institutions Placement</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BIOCON+LTD.&title=Biocon+Ltd+Raises+%E2%82%B9+41%2C500+Million+Through+Qualified+Institutions+Placement&newsId=b2178d9d-753b-47b6-95ce-022da6ffec73&token=YjIxNzhkOWQtNzUz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b2178d9d-753b-47b6-95ce-022da6ffec73</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Biocon Ltd has successfully completed a Qualified Institutions Placement (QIP) of equity shares, raising an amount of ₹ 41,500 million. The company issued 11,26,64,585 equity shares of face value ₹ 5 each at a price of ₹ 368.35 per share (including a premium of ₹ 363.35 per share). The shares were allotted to eligible qualified institutional buyers.</p><ul><li>Biocon Ltd raised ₹ 41,500 million through a QIP of equity shares.</li><li>11,26,64,585 equity shares of face value ₹ 5 each were issued.</li><li>The shares were issued at a price of ₹ 368.35 per share, including a premium of ₹ 363.35 per share.</li><li>The shares were allotted to eligible qualified institutional buyers.</li><li>The company&apos;s paid-up Equity Share capital has increased from ₹ 7,54,12,15,940 to ₹ 8,10,45,38,865.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/876ff8a4-9443-4991-8021-3f1eaa3bdbc8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BIOCON LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EPACKPEB] Epack Prefab Technologies Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q4 2025 Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Epack+Prefab+Technologies+Ltd&title=Epack+Prefab+Technologies+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q4+2025+Financial+Results&newsId=a5e1e970-3d4e-4da4-aca2-e5e540408866&token=YTVlMWU5NzAtM2Q0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5e1e970-3d4e-4da4-aca2-e5e540408866</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Epack Prefab Technologies Ltd has informed the BSE that its Board of Directors will meet on 21st January 2026 to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results (Standalone and Consolidated) for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will also take on record the Limited Review Report on the Un-Audited Financial Results. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company is closed and will open after 48 hours from the declaration of the aforesaid matter.</p><ul><li>Epack Prefab Technologies Ltd to consider and approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q4 2025</li><li>The meeting will take place on 21st January 2026</li><li>The Limited Review Report on the Un-Audited Financial Results will be taken on record</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company is closed and will open after 48 hours from the declaration of the aforesaid matter</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e329db23-eabd-447f-85b0-0937becad17c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Epack Prefab Technologies Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CIPLA] Cipla&apos;s Top Product in US Market, Lanreotide, Faces Supply Disruption Due to USFDA Inspection at Pharmathen&apos;s Manufacturing Facility</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CIPLA+LTD.&title=Cipla%27s+Top+Product+in+US+Market%2C+Lanreotide%2C+Faces+Supply+Disruption+Due+to+USFDA+Inspection+at+Pharmathen%27s+Manufacturing+Facility&newsId=9a19dd1e-4ddc-4cc9-8b88-0c8e4effeb25&token=OWExOWRkMWUtNGRk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a19dd1e-4ddc-4cc9-8b88-0c8e4effeb25</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>USFDA</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Cipla Ltd. has announced an update regarding the supply observations in Form 483 on Pharmathen International S.A., the manufacturer and exclusive supplier of Lanreotide Injection to Cipla USA Inc. The USFDA conducted an inspection at Pharmathen’s Rodopi, Greece manufacturing facility from 10th November 2025 to 21st November 2025, resulting in 9 inspectional observations. The redacted version of Form 483 was made public on 7th January 2026, leading to media reports and material price movement in the Company’s share price. Cipla, through its subsidiary Cipla USA Inc., has been informed that production has been temporarily paused to support ongoing remediation efforts. The re-supply of Lanreotide to the market is expected to resume in H1 of FY 2026-27, with limited supply until manufacturing restarts, subject to quality clearance.</p><ul><li>USFDA inspection at Pharmathen’s manufacturing facility resulted in 9 observations in Form 483</li><li>Lanreotide supply has been affected, it is among the top three products of Cipla in the US market</li><li>Production has been temporarily paused to support ongoing remediation efforts</li><li>Resupply of Lanreotide to the market is expected to resume in H1 of FY 2026-27</li><li>Limited supply of Lanreotide until manufacturing restarts, subject to quality clearance</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9a928645-2724-4af1-abb5-c3f8faa447a4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CIPLA LTD. | Category: USFDA</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NTPCGREEN] NTPC Green Energy Ltd Declares Commercial Operation of 300 MW out of 500 MW Bhadla Solar PV Project</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NTPC+Green+Energy+Ltd&title=NTPC+Green+Energy+Ltd+Declares+Commercial+Operation+of+300+MW+out+of+500+MW+Bhadla+Solar+PV+Project&newsId=93ce5fc7-080a-487e-812e-9543b63a6f35&token=OTNjZTVmYzctMDgw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93ce5fc7-080a-487e-812e-9543b63a6f35</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>NTPC Green Energy Limited, a subsidiary of NTPC Limited, has declared the commercial operation of the first part capacity of 300 MW out of 500 MW Bhadla Solar PV Project located in Phalodi, Rajasthan. This project is a wholly owned subsidiary of NTPC Renewable Energy Limited. The commercial operation started on 13th January 2026, following the issuance of the certificate of commissioning by SECI &amp; RRECL on 14th January 2026. This addition increases the total installed capacity of the NGEL Group to 8310.28 MW from 8010.28 MW.</p><ul><li>NTPC Green Energy Limited declares commercial operation of 300 MW out of 500 MW Bhadla Solar PV Project</li><li>Project is located in Phalodi, Rajasthan and is a subsidiary of NTPC Renewable Energy Limited</li><li>Commercial operation started on 13th January 2026</li><li>Certificate of commissioning issued by SECI &amp; RRECL on 14th January 2026</li><li>Total installed capacity of the NGEL Group increases to 8310.28 MW</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5efe05b6-6a8a-4530-bfc1-bfbba5f17178.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NTPC Green Energy Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BHARTIHEXA] Bharti Hexacom Ltd Appoints New Chief Financial Officer, Karthikeyan Velu</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Bharti+Hexacom+Ltd&title=Bharti+Hexacom+Ltd+Appoints+New+Chief+Financial+Officer%2C+Karthikeyan+Velu&newsId=96c018a5-a644-43df-8272-b467b58c685e&token=OTZjMDE4YTUtYTY0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">96c018a5-a644-43df-8272-b467b58c685e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bharti Hexacom Ltd has announced the appointment of Mr. Karthikeyan Velu as the new Chief Financial Officer (CFO) of the company, effective from January 01, 2026. This change in Key Managerial Personnel (KMP) necessitates an update in the list of KMPs responsible for determining materiality of events or information and making disclosures to the Stock Exchange(s) under Regulation 30(5) of LODR.</p><ul><li>Bharti Hexacom Ltd has appointed Mr. Karthikeyan Velu as the new Chief Financial Officer (CFO)</li><li>The appointment will be effective from January 01, 2026</li><li>This appointment results in a change in the Key Managerial Personnel (KMP) of the company</li><li>The updated list of KMPs responsible for determining materiality of events or information and making disclosures to the Stock Exchange(s) under Regulation 30(5) of LODR has been provided</li><li>Amit Chaturvedi continues to serve as the Company Secretary and Compliance Officer</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/386b9a74-9b58-4e4b-a924-beb024260a4b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Bharti Hexacom Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TANLA] Tanla Platforms Ltd: Statutory Auditors M/s. MSKA &amp; Associates Convert to LLP</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Tanla+Platforms+Ltd&title=Tanla+Platforms+Ltd%3A+Statutory+Auditors+M%2Fs.+MSKA+%26+Associates+Convert+to+LLP&newsId=69b47bd4-d8e2-4eb7-a68d-22d0ba5a7e77&token=NjliNDdiZDQtZDhl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69b47bd4-d8e2-4eb7-a68d-22d0ba5a7e77</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tanla Platforms Ltd announced that its Statutory Auditors, M/s. MSKA &amp; Associates, have converted themselves into a Limited Liability Partnership (LLP) under the provisions of the Limited Liability Partnership Act, 2008. The new name of the firm is M S K A &amp; Associates LLP, with a ICAI Firm Registration No. 105047W/W 101187. The firm will continue to function and discharge their obligations as Statutory Auditors for the remaining period of the tenure of appointment.</p><ul><li>Tanla Platforms Ltd&apos;s Statutory Auditors, M/s. MSKA &amp; Associates, have converted to a Limited Liability Partnership (LLP) under the Limited Liability Partnership Act, 2008.</li><li>The new name of the firm is M S K A &amp; Associates LLP, with a ICAI Firm Registration No. 105047W/W 101187.</li><li>The firm will continue to function and discharge their obligations as Statutory Auditors for the remaining period of the tenure of appointment.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/de20cebe-99ed-438f-bf11-f3dd8f87bddc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Tanla Platforms Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SILICON] Silicon Valley Infotech Ltd. to Consider Reduction of Share Capital</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SILICON+VALLEY+INFOTECH+LTD.&title=Silicon+Valley+Infotech+Ltd.+to+Consider+Reduction+of+Share+Capital&newsId=a38dabf1-b9bf-4a49-a1a4-b67c33d9de23&token=YTM4ZGFiZjEtYjli</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a38dabf1-b9bf-4a49-a1a4-b67c33d9de23</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:31:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Silicon Valley Infotech Ltd. has announced a Board of Directors meeting scheduled for January 27, 2026. The agenda includes the consideration and approval of a proposal for the reduction of the company&apos;s share capital. This decision is subject to approval from shareholders, stock exchanges, regulatory authorities, and the National Company Law Tribunal. The company&apos;s trading window will be closed for designated persons and their relatives in accordance with the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Silicon Valley Infotech Ltd. has scheduled a Board of Directors meeting for January 27, 2026</li><li>The agenda includes the consideration and approval of a proposal for share capital reduction</li><li>The decision is subject to approval from shareholders, stock exchanges, regulatory authorities, and the National Company Law Tribunal</li><li>The company&apos;s trading window will be closed for designated persons and their relatives as per SEBI regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c9431075-a55e-4511-8170-fe36b9c63ab7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SILICON VALLEY INFOTECH LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>