<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 21:17:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[HCLTECH] HCL Technologies Ltd Changes Record Date for Interim Dividend Payment to January 17, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HCL+TECHNOLOGIES+LTD.&title=HCL+Technologies+Ltd+Changes+Record+Date+for+Interim+Dividend+Payment+to+January+17%2C+2026&newsId=f8e25ce6-3436-4b4d-bfb5-e6fb7278b2f4&token=ZjhlMjVjZTYtMzQz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f8e25ce6-3436-4b4d-bfb5-e6fb7278b2f4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>HCL Technologies Ltd has announced a change in the Record Date for the payment of Interim Dividend that was declared on January 12, 2026. The Record Date, which was initially fixed for January 16, 2026, has been shifted to January 17, 2026 due to a trading holiday announced on account of Municipal Corporation Elections in Maharashtra. The payment date remains unchanged at January 27, 2026.</p><ul><li>HCL Technologies Ltd changes Record Date for Interim Dividend payment</li><li>Record Date shifted from January 16, 2026 to January 17, 2026</li><li>Change due to a trading holiday on account of Municipal Corporation Elections in Maharashtra</li><li>Payment date remains unchanged at January 27, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/63740c0f-dca8-44b8-aeef-970f42d7fd35.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HCL TECHNOLOGIES LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ICICIGI] ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company&apos;s Tax Litigation Appeals Allowed by CESTAT</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ICICI+Lombard+General+Insurance+Company+Ltd&title=ICICI+Lombard+General+Insurance+Company%27s+Tax+Litigation+Appeals+Allowed+by+CESTAT&newsId=e281883b-1dc5-4c4c-b384-e34527b72b08&token=ZTI4MTg4M2ItMWRj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e281883b-1dc5-4c4c-b384-e34527b72b08</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Ltd. has been informed that the appeals filed by the company with Central Excise and Service Tax Appellate Tribunal, Mumbai (CESTAT) for demand raised against the company for FY2008-09 to FY2011-12, FY2013-14 &amp; FY2014-15 and FY2011-12 have been allowed. The company is awaiting the copy of the appeal orders. This information will also be made available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company&apos;s tax litigation appeals have been allowed by CESTAT.</li><li>The company is awaiting the copy of the appeal orders.</li><li>The information will be made available on the company&apos;s website.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1d3eed17-bb56-41c5-93d3-6af3fa9ba2c8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ICICIPRULI] ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company Sells Entire Stake in ICICI Prudential Pension Funds Management to ICICI Bank</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ICICI+Prudential+Life+Insurance+Company+Ltd&title=ICICI+Prudential+Life+Insurance+Company+Sells+Entire+Stake+in+ICICI+Prudential+Pension+Funds+Management+to+ICICI+Bank&newsId=1a601741-f622-4219-b618-22b1a4810c0b&token=MWE2MDE3NDEtZjYy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a601741-f622-4219-b618-22b1a4810c0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company Ltd has sold its entire 100% equity shareholding in ICICI Prudential Pension Funds Management Company Limited to ICICI Bank Limited. The sale transaction was executed through a Share Purchase Agreement (SPA) on January 6, 2026. ICICI Bank now holds 100% shareholding in ICICI PFM, making it a wholly owned subsidiary of ICICI Bank.</p><ul><li>ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company sells its entire stake in ICICI Prudential Pension Funds Management to ICICI Bank.</li><li>The sale transaction was executed through a Share Purchase Agreement (SPA) on January 6, 2026.</li><li>ICICI Bank now holds 100% shareholding in ICICI PFM.</li><li>ICICI PFM has become a wholly owned subsidiary of ICICI Bank.</li><li>The transaction was worth 2.035 billion based on fair value determined by an independent valuer.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d87d507d-3183-47b3-b58c-e3db78c35446.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZELIO] Zelio E-Mobility&apos;s Q3 Revenue Surges 67%, Capacity Expanded by 70%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Zelio+E+Mobility+Ltd&title=Zelio+E-Mobility%27s+Q3+Revenue+Surges+67%25%2C+Capacity+Expanded+by+70%25&newsId=f646b016-f8e8-45e4-8615-6069accd6541&token=ZjY0NmIwMTYtZjhl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f646b016-f8e8-45e4-8615-6069accd6541</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:24:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Zelio E-Mobility Limited, a leading player in the slow-speed electric vehicle (EV) segment in India, reported a strong operational and financial performance for the quarter ended 31 December 2025. The company recorded a 67% year-on-year revenue growth in Q3 FY 2025-26, driven by robust festive demand, an expanding dealer footprint, increasing brand acceptance in Tier-2 and Tier-3 markets, and disciplined execution. The company&apos;s revenue increased from ₹29.6 crore in Q1 FY 2024-25 to ₹291.6 crore in Q3 FY 2025-26. Zelio also expanded its existing capacity by 70% to over 1,20,000 units per annum with a projected FY 2025-26 capacity utilization of 85%.</p><ul><li>Q3 revenue growth of 67%</li><li>Existing capacity expanded by 70% to over 1,20,000 units per annum</li><li>Strong Diwali season performance with 13,566 units sold (up 74% YoY) and revenue of ₹59 crore (up 64% YoY)</li><li>Proposed Odisha manufacturing facility targeted to commence commercial operations from February 2026</li><li>Evaluation of a potential manufacturing / assembly facility in Southern India</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2876fd3d-0897-4e3d-9161-4b1466d6fd74.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Zelio E Mobility Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[POONAWALLA] Poonawalla Fincorp Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Consider Fund Raising of up to Rs. 20,000 Crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Poonawalla+Fincorp+Ltd&title=Poonawalla+Fincorp+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Consider+Fund+Raising+of+up+to+Rs.+20%2C000+Crore&newsId=cb402ab5-6a44-49a1-a864-c5f46dd03e92&token=Y2I0MDJhYjUtNmE0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb402ab5-6a44-49a1-a864-c5f46dd03e92</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Poonawalla Fincorp Ltd has informed the BSE that the company&apos;s Board of Directors will meet on 16/01/2026. The agenda includes considering and approving an intimation under Regulation .... The Board will also consider raising funds by issuing equity shares of the company on qualified institutions placement and/or through any other permissible mode. The fundraising could be up to Rs. 20,000 Crore through the issuance of Non-Convertible Debt Securities on a private placement basis during the Financial Year 2026-2027. The Trading Window will remain closed till Sunday, January 18, 2026, as per the Company’s ‘Code of Conduct for Prohibition of Insider Trading’.</p><ul><li>Poonawalla Fincorp Ltd board meeting scheduled for 16/01/2026</li><li>Consideration of intimation under Regulation ....</li><li>Potential fundraising through equity shares issuance</li><li>Potential fundraising of up to Rs. 20,000 Crore through Non-Convertible Debt Securities</li><li>Trading Window closure till Sunday, January 18, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0d4723ca-8144-4695-9e2f-9e90b7be8b91.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Poonawalla Fincorp Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MAXESTATES] Max Estates Limited Receives Improved ESG Rating of 68 for FY 2024-2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Max+Estates+Ltd&title=Max+Estates+Limited+Receives+Improved+ESG+Rating+of+68+for+FY+2024-2025&newsId=b4f38d1a-7f33-4f9f-ac4d-8d694189ae67&token=YjRmMzhkMWEtN2Yz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4f38d1a-7f33-4f9f-ac4d-8d694189ae67</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:04:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Rating</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Max Estates Limited has been issued an improved ESG rating of 68 for the financial year 2024-2025 by SES ESG Research Private Limited. The rating was assigned based on data available in the public domain, as the company did not engage the rating provider. The rating report is available on stock exchanges, disseminated by SES ESG Research Private Limited. The event occurred on January 12, 2026, at 12:22 Hours (IST).</p><ul><li>Max Estates Limited receives an improved ESG rating of 68 for FY 2024-2025 from SES ESG Research Private Limited</li><li>The rating was assigned based on publicly available data</li><li>Max Estates Limited did not engage SES ESG Research Private Limited for this rating</li><li>The rating report is available on stock exchanges</li><li>The event occurred on January 12, 2026, at 12:22 Hours (IST)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a1218dbf-d5c8-4fae-a07e-556a45c06e23.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Max Estates Ltd | Category: Rating</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MEESHO] Meesho Ltd Appoints M/s BMP &amp; Co. LLP as Secretarial Auditors, Incorporates New Wholly Owned Subsidiary</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Meesho+Ltd&title=Meesho+Ltd+Appoints+M%2Fs+BMP+%26+Co.+LLP+as+Secretarial+Auditors%2C+Incorporates+New+Wholly+Owned+Subsidiary&newsId=8b95cd37-187d-421c-93c9-735b7febe298&token=OGI5NWNkMzctMTg3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b95cd37-187d-421c-93c9-735b7febe298</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:01:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Meesho Ltd, a Bengaluru-based company, has appointed M/s BMP &amp; Co. LLP as its Secretarial Auditors for a period of five consecutive years starting from FY 2025-26 to FY 2029-2030. The appointment is subject to the approval of the company&apos;s shareholders. Additionally, the company has approved the incorporation of a new Wholly Owned Subsidiary under the Companies Act, 2013. The detailed disclosures for both items are provided in the annexures.</p><ul><li>Meesho Ltd has appointed M/s BMP &amp; Co. LLP as its Secretarial Auditors</li><li>The appointment is for a period of five consecutive years starting from FY 2025-26 to FY 2029-2030</li><li>The appointment is subject to the approval of the company&apos;s shareholders</li><li>Meesho Ltd has approved the incorporation of a new Wholly Owned Subsidiary</li><li>The new subsidiary will be incorporated under the Companies Act, 2013</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b0ceae18-402e-40cc-9d9d-803dce8c97a8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Meesho Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MEESHO] Meesho Ltd Board Meeting: Incorporation of Wholly Owned Subsidiary &amp; Appointment of Secretarial Auditors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Meesho+Ltd&title=Meesho+Ltd+Board+Meeting%3A+Incorporation+of+Wholly+Owned+Subsidiary+%26+Appointment+of+Secretarial+Auditors&newsId=ac3787cf-9bc6-4ca9-9a0f-57185396c8a3&token=YWMzNzg3Y2YtOWJj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac3787cf-9bc6-4ca9-9a0f-57185396c8a3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Meesho Ltd, in a recent board meeting held on January 12, 2026, approved the incorporation of a new Wholly Owned Subsidiary. The company also appointed M/s BMP &amp; Co. LLP as Secretarial Auditors for a period of five consecutive years commencing from FY 2025-26 to FY 2029-2030. The new subsidiary is yet to be named and will engage in the business of logistics service provider for the movement of goods. BMP &amp; Co. LLP is a well-established firm of Practising Company Secretaries with offices in Bengaluru, Mumbai, and Delhi (NCR).</p><ul><li>Incorporation of a new Wholly Owned Subsidiary of Meesho Ltd</li><li>Appointment of M/s BMP &amp; Co. LLP as Secretarial Auditors of Meesho Ltd for five consecutive years</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1f0e9679-927f-460d-aea4-7818d352972c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Meesho Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MEESHO] Meesho Ltd. Announces Incorporation of Wholly Owned Subsidiary and Appointment of Secretarial Auditors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Meesho+Ltd&title=Meesho+Ltd.+Announces+Incorporation+of+Wholly+Owned+Subsidiary+and+Appointment+of+Secretarial+Auditors&newsId=32637943-8992-4e62-86d9-ace18e56874d&token=MzI2Mzc5NDMtODk5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32637943-8992-4e62-86d9-ace18e56874d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Meesho Ltd. has announced the incorporation of a new Wholly Owned Subsidiary under the Companies Act, 2013. The company has also appointed M/s BMP &amp; Co. LLP as Secretarial Auditors for a period of five consecutive years commencing from FY 2025-26 to FY 2029-2030. The decision was made at the Board of Directors meeting held on Monday, January 12, 2026. The new subsidiary is expected to engage in the business of logistics service provider for the movement of goods and undertake activities relating to loading, unloading, in-transit storage, and trans-shipment of goods through third-party service providers. The company will make a separate disclosure disclosing the name of the entity upon incorporation.</p><ul><li>Incorporation of a Wholly Owned Subsidiary of Meesho Ltd.</li><li>Appointment of M/s BMP &amp; Co. LLP as Secretarial Auditors for five consecutive years.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1207f17b-4413-4301-a7be-016afa7b7dc0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Meesho Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KIRLOSENG] Kirloskar Oil Engines Ltd Subsidiary&apos;s Name Change Approved by ROC</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KIRLOSKAR+OIL+ENGINES+LTD.&title=Kirloskar+Oil+Engines+Ltd+Subsidiary%27s+Name+Change+Approved+by+ROC&newsId=2e80ad01-a5dd-40e0-9ce3-7bb02d0a0177&token=MmU4MGFkMDEtYTVk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e80ad01-a5dd-40e0-9ce3-7bb02d0a0177</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 16:27:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kirloskar Oil Engines Ltd (KOEL) has announced that the Registrar of Companies, Central Processing Centre (ROC, CPC) has approved the change of name of its wholly owned subsidiary, La-Gajjar Machineries Private Limited, to KOEL Fluid Dynamics Private Limited. The new name was approved as per the Certificate of Incorporation pursuant to change of name dated 8th January 2026, issued by the ROC, CPC on 12th January 2026.</p><ul><li>Kirloskar Oil Engines Ltd (KOEL) announces name change of its wholly owned subsidiary.</li><li>The new name, KOEL Fluid Dynamics Private Limited, was approved by the ROC, CPC.</li><li>The approval was given as per the Certificate of Incorporation pursuant to change of name dated 8th January 2026.</li><li>The new name was issued by the ROC, CPC on 12th January 2026.</li><li>This update signifies a significant change in KOEL&apos;s business operations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ccafa379-bf61-48ba-b450-47e1d17e70d9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KIRLOSKAR OIL ENGINES LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>