<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:34:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[GARGI] PNGS Gargi Fashion Jewellery Ltd Opens New Exclusive Brand Store</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PNGS+Gargi+Fashion+Jewellery+Ltd&title=PNGS+Gargi+Fashion+Jewellery+Ltd+Opens+New+Exclusive+Brand+Store&newsId=f0299696-70e1-4b12-97d6-a9aa2073e719&token=ZjAyOTk2OTYtNzBl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0299696-70e1-4b12-97d6-a9aa2073e719</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 12:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>PNGS Gargi Fashion Jewellery Ltd has announced the opening of its new exclusive brand store at Unit No 4, B Wing, Ground Floor of Nyati Plaza of Project Nyati Enthral, S. No 12, Hissa No 1A, Kharadi, Pune, Maharashtra -411014. This announcement was made on January 25, 2026, in accordance with Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirement) Rules, 2015.</p><ul><li>PNGS Gargi Fashion Jewellery Ltd has opened a new exclusive brand store</li><li>The store is located at Unit No 4, B Wing, Ground Floor of Nyati Plaza of Project Nyati Enthral, S. No 12, Hissa No 1A, Kharadi, Pune, Maharashtra -411014</li><li>The opening was announced on January 25, 2026</li><li>The announcement was made in accordance with Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirement) Rules, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2124e3f4-e437-4aa3-96e9-fbd1eae366d2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PNGS Gargi Fashion Jewellery Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EVERESTIND] Everest Industries Extends Land Sale Timeline to March 31, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=EVEREST+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Everest+Industries+Extends+Land+Sale+Timeline+to+March+31%2C+2026&newsId=299e7150-622c-4e0e-953d-130beb3f2647&token=Mjk5ZTcxNTAtNjIy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">299e7150-622c-4e0e-953d-130beb3f2647</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Everest Industries Ltd. has announced an extension of the timeline for the sale of its land at Podanur. The sale, which was earlier estimated to be concluded on the day of the announcement, has been extended till March 31, 2026. This extension is due to the progress of needed government approvals and has been mutually agreed upon by the Company and G Square Realtors Private Limited. This intimation is given pursuant to Regulation 30 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Everest Industries extends the timeline for land sale at Podanur till March 31, 2026</li><li>The extension is due to the progress of needed government approvals</li><li>The decision has been mutually agreed upon by the Company and G Square Realtors Private Limited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/656f5fed-79a3-4432-a2e3-4c1d1c5f88e6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: EVEREST INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AADHARHFC] Blackstone-led Consortium to Acquire 25.82% Stake in Aadhar Housing Finance for $5.3 Billion</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Aadhar+Housing+Finance+Ltd&title=Blackstone-led+Consortium+to+Acquire+25.82%25+Stake+in+Aadhar+Housing+Finance+for+%245.3+Billion&newsId=15df204e-2fbf-4605-ac99-e28ffb672335&token=MTVkZjIwNGUtMmZi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">15df204e-2fbf-4605-ac99-e28ffb672335</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 11:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>A consortium led by BCP Asia IT Holdco VII PTE. LTD., a private limited company incorporated under the laws of Singapore, and including Blackstone Capital Partners (CYM) IX AIV-F L.P. and Blackstone Capital Partners Asia ITL.P., both exempted limited partnerships registered under the laws of Cayman Islands, has made a cash offer to acquire up to 11,35,25,761 fully paid-up equity shares of face value of INR 10 each of Aadhar Housing Finance Limited, representing 25.82% of the expanded voting share capital of the company. The offer price is INR 469.97 per equity share along with the applicable interest of INR 2.71 per equity share. The offer is not a conditional offer and is not subject to any minimum level of acceptance. It is also not a competing offer. The offer is being made in compliance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011 and subsequent amendments thereto. The offer is not subject to any statutory or regulatory approvals other than as set out in Part C (Statutory and Other Approvals) of Section VIII (Terms and Conditions of the Open Offer) which have now been received.</p><ul><li>Blackstone-led consortium to acquire 25.82% stake in Aadhar Housing Finance</li><li>Offer price is INR 469.97 per equity share along with INR 2.71 interest</li><li>Not a conditional or competing offer</li><li>Compliant with Securities and Exchange Board of India regulations</li><li>Subject to certain statutory and regulatory approvals</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ca488181-d7b3-4bdd-93ac-92cc15bf4162.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PWASML] Prakash Woollen &amp; Synthetic Mills Ltd to Approve Un-Audited Financial Results on Feb 4, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Prakash+Woollen+%26+Synthetic+Mills+Ltd&title=Prakash+Woollen+%26+Synthetic+Mills+Ltd+to+Approve+Un-Audited+Financial+Results+on+Feb+4%2C+2026&newsId=42a76f0b-bc73-4f4f-969b-969ebafbbb77&token=NDJhNzZmMGItYmM3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42a76f0b-bc73-4f4f-969b-969ebafbbb77</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 10:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Prakash Woollen &amp; Synthetic Mills Ltd has announced a Board Meeting on February 4, 2026, to consider and approve the Un-Audited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in securities of the company, which was closed on January 1, 2026, will open after 48 hours after the declaration of the Un-Audited Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Prakash Woollen &amp; Synthetic Mills Ltd to hold a Board Meeting on February 4, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the Un-Audited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities of the company was closed on January 1, 2026, and will open after 48 hours after the declaration of the Un-Audited Financial Results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4e4971f3-202e-4b24-9539-5c3e8491f88c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Prakash Woollen & Synthetic Mills Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UCOBANK] UCO Bank Branches and Offices May Be Affected by UFBU Strike on 27.01.2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=UCO+BANK&title=UCO+Bank+Branches+and+Offices+May+Be+Affected+by+UFBU+Strike+on+27.01.2026&newsId=6bd92fb9-f15e-4b0b-a2dc-95ca025f38d6&token=NmJkOTJmYjktZjE1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6bd92fb9-f15e-4b0b-a2dc-95ca025f38d6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 10:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Strike</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>UCO Bank has been informed by the Indian Banks’ Association (IBA) that the United Forum of Bank Unions (UFBU) and the All India Bank Officer&apos;s Association (AIBOA) have issued a strike notice for 27th January, 2026, to support their demands. Although the bank is taking measures to ensure smooth functioning of its branches and offices on the day of the strike, should the strike take place, the operations of these branches and offices may be impacted. This information is being shared in compliance with Regulation 30 of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>UFBU and AIBOA have issued a strike notice for 27th January, 2026</li><li>The strike is to support their demands</li><li>UCO Bank is taking steps for smooth functioning on the day of the strike</li><li>Potential impact on UCO Bank branches and offices if the strike materializes</li><li>Disclosure in compliance with Regulation 30 of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/de3e24eb-c4bf-46be-acad-19ee902e4616.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: UCO BANK | Category: Strike</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AVANTEL] Avantel Ltd. Approves Un-audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AVANTEL+LTD.&title=Avantel+Ltd.+Approves+Un-audited+Standalone+and+Consolidated+Financial+Results+for+Q3+2025&newsId=a7204990-8e70-4da9-8805-dc9860cdcfa7&token=YTcyMDQ5OTAtOGU3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a7204990-8e70-4da9-8805-dc9860cdcfa7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:02:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Avantel Ltd. approved the Un-audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the Third Quarter ended December 31, 2025. The results were reviewed by the Audit Committee and the Statutory Auditors. The company operates in a single segment and the results pertain to this segment. The financial results are available on the company&apos;s website and on the BSE and NSE websites.</p><ul><li>Avantel Ltd. approved the Un-audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 2025.</li><li>The results were reviewed by the Audit Committee and the Statutory Auditors.</li><li>The company operates in a single segment.</li><li>The financial results are available on the company&apos;s website and on the BSE and NSE websites.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/74cf51f8-a41b-4b43-8769-c4b33c7d52c7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AVANTEL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AVANTEL] Avantel Ltd. Announces Un-Audited Financial Results for Q3 2025, Revenue Up by 41.32%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AVANTEL+LTD.&title=Avantel+Ltd.+Announces+Un-Audited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+2025%2C+Revenue+Up+by+41.32%25&newsId=c14ef7da-2ce7-4eda-a7b2-2ba6d50bc7ae&token=YzE0ZWY3ZGEtMmNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c14ef7da-2ce7-4eda-a7b2-2ba6d50bc7ae</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Avantel Ltd. has announced its un-audited financial results for the third quarter ended December 31, 2025. The Board of Directors approved the un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results. The total revenue from operations has increased by 41.32% compared to the same period last year. The company operates in a single segment and the results pertain to this segment. The financial results are available on the company&apos;s website and the websites of BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange of India Limited.</p><ul><li>Un-Audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results approved for Q3 2025</li><li>Total Revenue from Operations increased by 41.32% compared to Q3 2024</li><li>Company operates in a single segment</li><li>Financial results available on company&apos;s website and stock exchange websites</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6413e3de-a3fe-4ab2-a8c3-82081168b874.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AVANTEL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JPPOWER] Jaiprakash Power Ventures Chairman Released on Interim Bail in ED Investigation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jaiprakash+Power+Ventures+Limited&title=Jaiprakash+Power+Ventures+Chairman+Released+on+Interim+Bail+in+ED+Investigation&newsId=02f6376c-fadd-4f07-98c8-4feb25bc0053&token=MDJmNjM3NmMtZmFk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02f6376c-fadd-4f07-98c8-4feb25bc0053</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 09:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jaiprakash Power Ventures Ltd. has released a disclosure stating that its Non-Executive Director and Chairman, Shri Manoj Gaur, has been granted interim bail by the Hon’ble Court of Additional Sessions Judge-7, Patiala House, New Delhi on 24th January 2026. This update comes in continuation with the previous disclosure dated 13th November, 2025 regarding the Enforcement Directorate (ED) action in connection with an ongoing investigation.</p><ul><li>Shri Manoj Gaur, Non-Executive Director and Chairman of Jaiprakash Power Ventures Ltd, has been released on interim bail</li><li>The bail was granted by the Hon’ble Court of Additional Sessions Judge-7, Patiala House, New Delhi</li><li>This update is in continuation with the previous disclosure dated 13th November, 2025 regarding ED action in an ongoing investigation</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/aa88dd2f-a370-45ff-98af-6439bfa9d24f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jaiprakash Power Ventures Limited | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CANBK] Canara Bank Branches and Offices May Be Affected by Proposed Strike on January 27, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CANARA+BANK&title=Canara+Bank+Branches+and+Offices+May+Be+Affected+by+Proposed+Strike+on+January+27%2C+2026&newsId=a1498d20-5bb3-443a-b877-e72ee687a3ee&token=YTE0OThkMjAtNWJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a1498d20-5bb3-443a-b877-e72ee687a3ee</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 08:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Strike Notice</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The United Forum of Bank Unions (U.F.B.U.) has announced a strike on Tuesday, January 27, 2026, due to various issues and demands. Canara Bank is preparing for the potential strike, but if it occurs, the bank&apos;s branches and offices may experience disruptions. This notice is to inform stock exchanges and stakeholders about the possible impact of the strike.</p><ul><li>The United Forum of Bank Unions (U.F.B.U.) has called for a strike on January 27, 2026, affecting Canara Bank branches and offices</li><li>Canara Bank is taking steps to ensure smooth functioning during the proposed strike</li><li>Potential disruptions may occur if the strike takes place</li><li>Stakeholders are informed about the possibility of branch and office disruptions</li><li>The notice is in compliance with SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4bed3b50-04d2-4a10-af63-4181a4abafbd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CANARA BANK | Category: Strike Notice</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RELTD] Ravindra Energy Revises General Business Update: Corrects Operating Swap Stations &amp; Provides Detailed Insight into Renewable Energy &amp; Electric Vehicle Business Activities</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ravindra+Energy+Ltd&title=Ravindra+Energy+Revises+General+Business+Update%3A+Corrects+Operating+Swap+Stations+%26+Provides+Detailed+Insight+into+Renewable+Energy+%26+Electric+Vehicle+Business+Activities&newsId=2843d18f-95c4-4871-911a-c7623b4ea8df&token=Mjg0M2QxOGYtOTVj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2843d18f-95c4-4871-911a-c7623b4ea8df</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 07:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Ravindra Energy Ltd. has submitted a revised business update regarding its renewable energy business and electric vehicle business activities. The company has corrected the number of operating swap stations in Q2 and Q3, which were inadvertently interchanged. The renewable energy business includes operating assets of 187 MW DC, with all 19 Mukhya Mantri Saurya Krishi Vahini Yojana (MSKVY) Phase 1 projects commissioned and generating income as per the target. MSKVY Phase 2 projects, with a capacity of 57 MW, are likely to be commissioned before 31st March 2026. The company also has a pipeline of 235 MW DC under development. In the electric vehicle business, the company has sold 125 vehicles in the nine-month period ending December 2025. Additionally, YES Bank Ltd. has sanctioned financial assistance of INR 296 Crore and a hedge facility of INR 32 Crore to Ravindra Energy Ltd.</p><ul><li>Ravindra Energy corrects the number of operating swap stations in Q2 and Q3</li><li>Company provides detailed insight into renewable energy business activities</li><li>MSKVY Phase 1 projects commissioned and generating income as per target</li><li>MSKVY Phase 2 projects with 57 MW capacity likely to be commissioned before 31st March 2026</li><li>YES Bank sanctions financial assistance of INR 296 Crore and a hedge facility of INR 32 Crore</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/17b3d109-1f5a-4cbc-baad-ef46a79f0352.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ravindra Energy Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>