<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 12:36:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[JEL] Jyotirgamya Enterprises Ltd Appoints Mr. Balkrishna K Reddy as Managing Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jyotirgamya+Enterprises+Ltd&title=Jyotirgamya+Enterprises+Ltd+Appoints+Mr.+Balkrishna+K+Reddy+as+Managing+Director&newsId=9c8b9d69-a9d9-483d-ba51-cb88cc7c2292&token=OWM4YjlkNjktYTlk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c8b9d69-a9d9-483d-ba51-cb88cc7c2292</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 12:31:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jyotirgamya Enterprises Ltd announced the outcome of their board meeting held on 15.01.2026. The board, which met via video conferencing, approved the appointment of Mr. Balkrishna K Reddy as the Managing Director of the company. This appointment is subject to the approval of shareholders in the upcoming annual general meeting. Mr. Reddy is a seasoned administrative professional with over three decades of experience in managing and streamlining administrative operations.</p><ul><li>Jyotirgamya Enterprises Ltd board approves the appointment of Mr. Balkrishna K Reddy as Managing Director</li><li>Appointment is subject to the approval of shareholders in the upcoming annual general meeting</li><li>Mr. Reddy is a seasoned administrative professional with over three decades of experience</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0af60803-279f-4418-85b3-7f9810b6e945.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jyotirgamya Enterprises Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JEL] Jyotirgamya Enterprises Ltd Appoints Mr. Balkrishna K Reddy as Managing Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jyotirgamya+Enterprises+Ltd&title=Jyotirgamya+Enterprises+Ltd+Appoints+Mr.+Balkrishna+K+Reddy+as+Managing+Director&newsId=e33d3b07-d81d-4068-8dee-f88ead967f20&token=ZTMzZDNiMDctZDgx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e33d3b07-d81d-4068-8dee-f88ead967f20</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 12:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jyotirgamya Enterprises Ltd has announced the appointment of Mr. Balkrishna K Reddy as the Managing Director of the company. The appointment is subject to the approval of shareholders in the ensuing annual general meeting. Mr. Reddy is a seasoned administrative professional with over three decades of experience.</p><ul><li>Mr. Balkrishna K Reddy appointed as Managing Director of Jyotirgamya Enterprises Ltd</li><li>Appointment is subject to shareholders&apos; approval in the annual general meeting</li><li>Mr. Reddy is a seasoned administrative professional with over three decades of experience</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8acac74d-024f-4567-9413-8938317955a4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jyotirgamya Enterprises Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VASHISHTHA] Vashishtha Luxury Fashion: No Pending Price-Sensitive Information, Price Movement Market-Driven</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vashishtha+Luxury+Fashion+Ltd&title=Vashishtha+Luxury+Fashion%3A+No+Pending+Price-Sensitive+Information%2C+Price+Movement+Market-Driven&newsId=9b54a66b-74f3-4d99-a8b2-07d4176d238d&token=OWI1NGE2NmItNzRm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b54a66b-74f3-4d99-a8b2-07d4176d238d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 12:31:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vashishtha Luxury Fashion Ltd has clarified that there is no pending price-sensitive information that could have led to the significant movement in the price of its shares. The company is in compliance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015 and has been regularly intimating the Stock Exchange of all material events, information and disclosures. The company assures that it will continue to duly inform the stock exchanges of all required information/announcements under applicable regulations.</p><ul><li>Vashishtha Luxury Fashion clarifies there is no pending price-sensitive information</li><li>Price movement of shares is market-driven</li><li>Company complies with Regulation 30 of SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Regular intimation of material events, information and disclosures to Stock Exchange</li><li>Commitment to inform stock exchanges of all required information/announcements under applicable regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/df1a8814-2d0d-4b6a-a34c-4f6551e2301c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vashishtha Luxury Fashion Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NOVIS] Nova Iron &amp; Steel Ltd to Approve Q3 and Half-Yearly Results on Jan 21, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NOVA+IRON+%26+STEEL+LTD.&title=Nova+Iron+%26+Steel+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Half-Yearly+Results+on+Jan+21%2C+2026&newsId=35c466b0-cdea-49fb-8149-786a540fb77d&token=MzVjNDY2YjAtY2Rl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">35c466b0-cdea-49fb-8149-786a540fb77d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 12:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Nova Iron &amp; Steel Ltd has announced a Board of Directors meeting on January 21, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and half-year ended on September 30, 2025, in compliance with Regulation 29 of the SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosures Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Nova Iron &amp; Steel Ltd to hold a Board of Directors meeting on January 21, 2026.</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and half-year ended on September 30, 2025.</li><li>The announcement is in compliance with Regulation 29 of the SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosures Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/95921083-4f61-483f-9f1d-691329ba22e6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NOVA IRON & STEEL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NTPCGREEN] NTPC Green Energy Ltd Approves Joint Venture Agreement with GAIL (India) Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NTPC+Green+Energy+Ltd&title=NTPC+Green+Energy+Ltd+Approves+Joint+Venture+Agreement+with+GAIL+%28India%29+Limited&newsId=c337282b-e8d3-4600-90d3-1cd38cc91ac9&token=YzMzNzI4MmItZThk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c337282b-e8d3-4600-90d3-1cd38cc91ac9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 12:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>NTPC Green Energy Ltd announced that its Board of Directors has approved a Joint Venture Agreement with GAIL (India) Limited for the formation of a 50:50 Joint Venture Company (JVC). The JVC will undertake Renewable Energy Projects, subject to approval from the Ministry of Power, DIPAM, and other statutory authorities. The details of the disclosure will be shared as per the Securities and Exchange Board of India Master Circular dated 11% November 2024.</p><ul><li>NTPC Green Energy Ltd and GAIL (India) Limited to form a 50:50 Joint Venture Company (JVC)</li><li>JVC will undertake Renewable Energy Projects</li><li>Approval from Ministry of Power, DIPAM, and other statutory authorities required</li><li>Disclosure details will be shared as per the Securities and Exchange Board of India Master Circular dated 11% November 2024</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1bf63a78-7510-46d4-9878-d2edfb08d439.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NTPC Green Energy Ltd | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TITANBIO] Titan Biotech Ltd: December 2025 Report on Re-lodgement of Transfer Requests for Physical Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TITAN+BIOTECH+LTD.&title=Titan+Biotech+Ltd%3A+December+2025+Report+on+Re-lodgement+of+Transfer+Requests+for+Physical+Shares&newsId=38429727-fb03-49d6-8e0a-14c8e0b8ece0&token=Mzg0Mjk3MjctZmIw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">38429727-fb03-49d6-8e0a-14c8e0b8ece0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 12:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Titan Biotech Ltd has released a report for December 2025, detailing the re-lodgement of transfer requests for physical shares. The report, provided by the Registrar and Share Transfer Agent of the company, BEETAL FINANCIAL &amp; COMPUTER SERVICES (P) LTD, focuses on the status of re-lodgement of transfer requests of physical shares that were previously rejected, returned, or not attended due to various deficiencies. The report indicates that Titan Biotech Ltd received 2 transfer requests in December 2025, processed all of them, approved none, and rejected 2. The average time taken for request processing was 20 days.</p><ul><li>Titan Biotech Ltd has released a report for December 2025 on the re-lodgement of transfer requests for physical shares.</li><li>The report indicates that 2 transfer requests were received in December 2025.</li><li>None of the received requests were approved in December 2025.</li><li>2 requests were rejected in December 2025.</li><li>The average time taken for request processing in December 2025 was 20 days.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/918bda8d-822f-4b78-af41-8c09b0b111a5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TITAN BIOTECH LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FAALCON] Faalcon Concepts Ltd.: No Financial Results Disclosure Required for Quarter Ended December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Faalcon+Concepts+Ltd&title=Faalcon+Concepts+Ltd.%3A+No+Financial+Results+Disclosure+Required+for+Quarter+Ended+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=c38d5e6c-22a1-4b1e-8d28-441552c8b1b8&token=YzM4ZDVlNmMtMjJh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c38d5e6c-22a1-4b1e-8d28-441552c8b1b8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 12:21:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Faalcon Concepts Ltd., a BSE SME listed company, has declared and certified the non-applicability of Integrated Filing (Financial) for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company is not required to disclose financial results, deviations from proceeds of public issues, outstanding defaults on loans and debt securities, and related party transactions for the said quarter due to specific regulations applicable to SME listed companies. The company&apos;s decision is in accordance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, as amended.</p><ul><li>Faalcon Concepts Ltd. need not disclose financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The company is exempted from disclosing deviations from proceeds of public issues, rights issues, preferential issues, and qualified institutions placements.</li><li>There is no outstanding default on loans and debt securities for the quarter.</li><li>Faalcon Concepts Ltd. does not have to disclose related party transactions for the quarter.</li><li>The decision is based on SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, as amended.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a0346587-3224-45a8-bb81-9dc352cec62d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Faalcon Concepts Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NSLNISP] NMDC Steel Ltd Assigns Additional Charge to Shri Joydeep Dasgupta as Director (Personnel)</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NMDC+Steel+Ltd&title=NMDC+Steel+Ltd+Assigns+Additional+Charge+to+Shri+Joydeep+Dasgupta+as+Director+%28Personnel%29&newsId=4d46de1f-8749-4566-9908-63a34e4ecba4&token=NGQ0NmRlMWYtODc0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d46de1f-8749-4566-9908-63a34e4ecba4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 12:21:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>NMDC Steel Ltd has assigned additional charge to Shri Joydeep Dasgupta, Director (Production), as Director (Personnel) for an initial period of 3 months starting from 01.02.2026. This decision is in accordance with the Ministry of Steel, Government of India Order No. S-14013/1/2025-BLA-Part(1) dated 14.01.2026 and Order No. 4(3)/2022-NMDC dated 20.03.2023. The assignment will continue until further orders or until 30.04.2026, whichever is earlier.</p><ul><li>NMDC Steel Ltd assigns additional charge to Shri Joydeep Dasgupta as Director (Personnel)</li><li>The assignment is for an initial period of 3 months starting from 01.02.2026</li><li>Shri Joydeep Dasgupta is currently the Director (Production) at NMDC Steel Ltd</li><li>The decision is in accordance with the Ministry of Steel, Government of India Order No. S-14013/1/2025-BLA-Part(1) dated 14.01.2026 and Order No. 4(3)/2022-NMDC dated 20.03.2023</li><li>The assignment will continue until further orders or until 30.04.2026, whichever is earlier</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/416016ab-250a-4719-9739-e898d2599f84.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NMDC Steel Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GOGIACAP] Gogia Capital Growth Ltd. Revises Board Meeting Disclosure: Includes Omitted Agenda Items &amp; Material Related Party Transaction</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Gogia+Capital+Services+Limited&title=Gogia+Capital+Growth+Ltd.+Revises+Board+Meeting+Disclosure%3A+Includes+Omitted+Agenda+Items+%26+Material+Related+Party+Transaction&newsId=5b5412e9-d6cc-4089-83eb-eda25bd7053b&token=NWI1NDEyZTktZDZj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b5412e9-d6cc-4089-83eb-eda25bd7053b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 12:21:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gogia Capital Growth Ltd. has submitted a revised outcome of the Board Meeting held on 13th January 2026. The revision includes certain inadvertently omitted agenda items from the earlier disclosure. The key highlights include the approval of a material related party transaction involving the sale of immovable property to Mr. Ankur Gogia, a Director of the Company, for a consideration of INR 5,05,00,000. This transaction qualifies as a material related party transaction under Regulation 23 of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015. The company also approved the change of its registered office and appointed M/s Arpit Garg &amp; Associates as the Scrutinizer for the upcoming EGM. The EGM is scheduled for 6th February 2026.</p><ul><li>Revised outcome of the Board Meeting held on 13th January 2026</li><li>Approval of a material related party transaction involving the sale of immovable property to a Director</li><li>Change of the company&apos;s registered office</li><li>Appointment of M/s Arpit Garg &amp; Associates as the Scrutinizer for the upcoming EGM</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/23b52e5a-8de4-4aa5-98a4-04e20d798727.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Gogia Capital Services Limited | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GVBL] Genomic Valley Biotech Ltd. Reports Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025, Announces Director&apos;s Resignation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Genomic+Valley+Biotech+Ltd&title=Genomic+Valley+Biotech+Ltd.+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025%2C+Announces+Director%27s+Resignation&newsId=1b0dbddb-72a4-4429-ba77-c180764dbd1f&token=MWIwZGJkZGItNzJh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b0dbddb-72a4-4429-ba77-c180764dbd1f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 12:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Genomic Valley Biotech Ltd. has reported its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31 December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 5,00,000 for the current quarter, a significant increase from the previous year. The total revenue for the current period is 58,80,795. The company&apos;s total expenses amount to 15,75,499, resulting in a comprehensive income of 3,84,786. The Board of Directors also accepted the resignation of Mr. Ashok Kumar from his directorship. The meeting was held on 15 January 2026.</p><ul><li>Genomic Valley Biotech Ltd. reports Q3 and nine months financial results for 2025.</li><li>Revenue from operations stands at 5,00,000 for the current quarter.</li><li>Total revenue for the current period is 58,80,795.</li><li>Total expenses amount to 15,75,499, resulting in a comprehensive income of 3,84,786.</li><li>Mr. Ashok Kumar ceases to be a Director and a Member of all Committees of the Company.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c6456aec-65ea-4371-8eb3-abeb00c0999a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Genomic Valley Biotech Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>