<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:48:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[IGCL] Indogulf Cropsciences Partners with CII, ANRF and ICAR-IARI for PM’s Fellowship for Doctoral Research</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Indogulf+Cropsciences+Ltd&title=Indogulf+Cropsciences+Partners+with+CII%2C+ANRF+and+ICAR-IARI+for+PM%E2%80%99s+Fellowship+for+Doctoral+Research&newsId=46bcff7f-55a8-4a96-851f-ffe816ac5821&token=NDZiY2ZmN2YtNTVh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">46bcff7f-55a8-4a96-851f-ffe816ac5821</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indogulf Cropsciences Limited has signed a Memorandum of Agreement (MoA) with the Confederation of Indian Industry (CII), Indian Council of Agricultural Research— Indian Agricultural Research Institute (ICAR-IARI) and Anusandhan National Research Foundation (ANRF) to implement the ‘Prime Minister’s Fellowship for Doctoral Research’. This partnership aims to promote high-quality, industry-relevant research and strengthen academia-industry collaboration in Indian agriculture. The fellowship will support a full-time PhD scholar at ICAR-IARI for a maximum period of four years starting 1st January 2026. The research will focus on mitigation strategies such as Bio-stimulants for alleviating the adverse effects of drought and heat stress, thereby encouraging young research scholars to work on scientific solutions for food security. The collaboration will be under the direct mentorship of experienced researchers with expertise in areas of Abiotic stress tolerance of Plants, Phenomics and Genome Editing.</p><ul><li>Indogulf Cropsciences partners with CII, ANRF and ICAR-IARI for PM’s Fellowship for Doctoral Research.</li><li>The partnership aims to promote high-quality, industry-relevant research and strengthen academia-industry collaboration in Indian agriculture.</li><li>The fellowship will support a full-time PhD scholar at ICAR-IARI for a maximum period of four years.</li><li>The research will focus on mitigation strategies such as Bio-stimulants for alleviating the adverse effects of drought and heat stress.</li><li>The collaboration will be under the direct mentorship of experienced researchers.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/959882a5-45df-43a2-b0e7-fd66284cd614.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Indogulf Cropsciences Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AAL] A-1 Sureja Industries Receives Orders for Electric Two-wheelers, Launches Mobile App &apos;Yellow EV&apos;</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=A-1+Acid+Ltd&title=A-1+Sureja+Industries+Receives+Orders+for+Electric+Two-wheelers%2C+Launches+Mobile+App+%27Yellow+EV%27&newsId=b4af788f-1348-48c9-b20a-9a241670c2ab&token=YjRhZjc4OGYtMTM0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4af788f-1348-48c9-b20a-9a241670c2ab</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:36:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>A-1 Sureja Industries, an associate of A-1 Ltd and part of its electric mobility initiative, announced progress on its electric mobility initiative under the brand &apos;Yellow EV&apos;. The company has received confirmed purchase orders for approximately 1400 electric two-wheelers and launched a mobile application &apos;Yellow EV&apos; for streamlined user onboarding and workflow support. The company is also evaluating a scalable rollout strategy through a partner/franchise-led operating framework and assembly/distribution expansion.</p><ul><li>Received confirmed orders for 1400+ electric two-wheelers</li><li>Launched mobile application &apos;Yellow EV&apos; for customer onboarding and workflow support</li><li>Evaluating scalable rollout strategy through a partner/franchise-led operating framework</li><li>Focused on affordable and reliable electric mobility</li><li>Assembly/distribution expansion subject to commercial feasibility and execution readiness</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d44a5ceb-a6b1-4822-97e5-389a6b7db8b3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: A-1 Acid Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SYMPHONY] Symphony Ltd to Interact with Electronic Media on Business and Sector Outlook</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Symphony+Limited&title=Symphony+Ltd+to+Interact+with+Electronic+Media+on+Business+and+Sector+Outlook&newsId=ff1912e9-0428-4c1a-8c5e-654d0e327a3e&token=ZmYxOTEyZTktMDQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff1912e9-0428-4c1a-8c5e-654d0e327a3e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:35:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Symphony Ltd has announced that the management will interact with ET Now (English) to discuss the Business and Sector Outlook of the company. The interaction is scheduled for February 26, 2026, but it is subject to change. The details of the telecast will be placed on the company&apos;s website: www.symphonylimited.com. This move aims to disseminate information widely to the members of the company.</p><ul><li>Symphony Ltd to interact with ET Now (English) on February 26, 2026</li><li>Discussion will focus on the Business and Sector Outlook of the company</li><li>The interaction may be postponed or cancelled due to exigencies</li><li>The details of the telecast will be available on the company&apos;s website: www.symphonylimited.com</li><li>This initiative aims to widely disseminate information to the members of the company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0017ba9b-0777-4270-b4fe-4da9c49e4878.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Symphony Limited | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PRIMEFRESH] Prime Fresh Ltd Allocates Shares Following Warrant Conversion by Hiren Chandrakant Ghelani</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Prime+Fresh+Ltd&title=Prime+Fresh+Ltd+Allocates+Shares+Following+Warrant+Conversion+by+Hiren+Chandrakant+Ghelani&newsId=cebd003e-0cbb-4a01-a091-f9d3fd9fab5a&token=Y2ViZDAwM2UtMGNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cebd003e-0cbb-4a01-a091-f9d3fd9fab5a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:22:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Prime Fresh Ltd has allotted 44,715 shares to Hiren Chandrakant Ghelani following the conversion of warrants into shares. The decision was made at a Finance Committee meeting held on 24th February, 2026. The disclosure, as per regulations 29 (1) of SEBI (SAST) Regulations, 2018, has been submitted.</p><ul><li>Prime Fresh Ltd has allotted 44,715 shares to Hiren Chandrakant Ghelani</li><li>The allotment is following the conversion of warrants into shares</li><li>The decision was made at a Finance Committee meeting held on 24th February, 2026</li><li>The disclosure has been submitted as per regulations 29 (1) of SEBI (SAST) Regulations, 2018</li><li>Hiren Chandrakant Ghelani&apos;s holding increased to 6.0899% from 5.8353%</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4694A0CD_94EF_46DC_A849_4A451C1BA2F1_094148.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Prime Fresh Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BALUFORGE] Balu Forge Industries Ltd Enters MoU for Large Caliber Ammunition Supply</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Balu+Forge+Industries+Ltd&title=Balu+Forge+Industries+Ltd+Enters+MoU+for+Large+Caliber+Ammunition+Supply&newsId=6dab887f-0934-45a4-b0f0-ad8309fe1b81&token=NmRhYjg4N2YtMDkz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6dab887f-0934-45a4-b0f0-ad8309fe1b81</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>MoU</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Balu Forge Industries Ltd (BSE: 531112 | NSE: BALUFORGE) has entered into a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) for the supply of empty shells from its greenfield manufacturing campus in Belgaum, Karnataka. The agreement is for a period of 5 years, covering large caliber ammunition categories such as 155 mm M107, 152 mm, and 155 mm ERFB/BT variants, with a total of 30,000 units per month for 155 mm M107 and 10,000 units per month for 152 mm. The pricing is indexed to the London Metal exchange. The commencement of supplies will be from April 2026.</p><ul><li>Balu Forge Industries Ltd enters MoU for large caliber ammunition supply</li><li>5-year agreement for the supply of empty shells from Belgaum, Karnataka campus</li><li>Covers 155 mm M107, 152 mm, and 155 mm ERFB/BT variants</li><li>Total of 40,000 units per month</li><li>Pricing indexed to London Metal exchange</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5c8f2825-567d-4078-be4f-a77b3f3ce935.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Balu Forge Industries Ltd | Category: MoU</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GALLANTT] Gallantt Industry Pvt Ltd Acquires 7,000 Shares of Gallantt Ispat Ltd via Market Purchase</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Gallantt+Ispat+Ltd&title=Gallantt+Industry+Pvt+Ltd+Acquires+7%2C000+Shares+of+Gallantt+Ispat+Ltd+via+Market+Purchase&newsId=82dc1781-4c64-4b39-935e-e54d3f7115e9&token=ODJkYzE3ODEtNGM2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">82dc1781-4c64-4b39-935e-e54d3f7115e9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gallantt Industry Pvt Ltd, a part of the Promoter Group of Gallantt Ispat Ltd, has acquired 7,000 equity shares of Gallantt Ispat Ltd by way of market purchase. This acquisition represents a 0.003% stake in the company. The shares were acquired at a price undisclosed in the document. This acquisition increases Gallantt Industry Pvt Ltd&apos;s holding to 0.980% from 0.977% of Gallantt Ispat Ltd&apos;s total voting rights and total diluted capital.</p><ul><li>Gallantt Industry Pvt Ltd, a Promoter Group company, acquires 7,000 shares of Gallantt Ispat Ltd</li><li>The acquisition represents a 0.003% stake in Gallantt Ispat Ltd</li><li>The shares were acquired via market purchase</li><li>This acquisition increases Gallantt Industry Pvt Ltd&apos;s holding to 0.980% from 0.977%</li><li>The price of the acquisition is not disclosed in the document</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/39D7DE89_ABCB_47B1_80C8_506ABEE40D73_093945.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Gallantt Ispat Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INFINITY] Infinity Infoway Ltd Secures Rs. 10.97 Crores Contract from Gujarat Education Dept.</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Infinity+Infoway+Ltd&title=Infinity+Infoway+Ltd+Secures+Rs.+10.97+Crores+Contract+from+Gujarat+Education+Dept.&newsId=4386969d-0e00-49ba-b853-0c25fc37ea45&token=NDM4Njk2OWQtMGUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4386969d-0e00-49ba-b853-0c25fc37ea45</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:13:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Infinity Infoway Ltd has been awarded a contract worth approximately Rs. 10.97 Crores from the Knowledge Consortium of Gujarat, under the Education Department, Government of Gujarat. The contract is for the provision of AI-based Data Analytics &amp; Business Intelligence Services, including the establishment of a Big Data Analytics platform, Self-Service Business Intelligence (BI) framework, Data Repository, API integration, dashboard development and reporting solutions at the Buyer’s premises. The contract tenure is 5 years. This contract is in line with the Company’s existing line of operations and is considered a part of the ordinary course of business.</p><ul><li>Contract worth approximately Rs. 10.97 Crores from the Government of Gujarat&apos;s Education Department.</li><li>5-year contract for AI-based Data Analytics &amp; Business Intelligence Services.</li><li>Involves establishment of Big Data Analytics platform, Self-Service Business Intelligence (BI) framework, Data Repository, API integration, dashboard development and reporting solutions.</li><li>In alignment with the Company’s existing line of operations.</li><li>Disclosed in the interest of transparency and good corporate governance.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8deeb33a-95f7-4d8e-b032-1d39432214d4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Infinity Infoway Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DHINDIA] Aishwarya Lunia Kakrecha Acquires 05.13% Stake in D &amp; H India Ltd&apos;s Rights Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=D%26H+India+Ltd-%24&title=Aishwarya+Lunia+Kakrecha+Acquires+05.13%25+Stake+in+D+%26+H+India+Ltd%27s+Rights+Issue&newsId=76d1b3de-c74d-4f1b-87f3-01c5515e5bc4&token=NzZkMWIzZGUtYzc0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76d1b3de-c74d-4f1b-87f3-01c5515e5bc4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:10:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Aishwarya Lunia Kakrecha has acquired 1,05,000 Equity shares of D &amp; H India Ltd, which is 05.13% of the total Rights Issue. This acquisition increases her shareholding in the company to 2.28%. The Rights Issue was for 20,47,000 shares, and Aishwarya Lunia Kakrecha has acquired 1,05,000 shares, which is 5.13% of the Rights Issue.</p><ul><li>Aishwarya Lunia Kakrecha has acquired 1,05,000 Equity shares of D &amp; H India Ltd, which is 05.13% of the total Rights Issue.</li><li>This acquisition increases her shareholding in the company to 2.28%.</li><li>The Rights Issue was for 20,47,000 shares.</li><li>Aishwarya Lunia Kakrecha has acquired 5.13% of the Rights Issue.</li><li>The total equity capital of the company after the acquisition is Rs. 10,23,50,000/-</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8C9AFFC7_898E_480C_9AB1_C8133B7E4F88_093556.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: D&H India Ltd-$ | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[OROSMITHS] B K Narula HUF Acquires 0.12% Stake in Orosil Smiths India Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=OROSIL+SMITHS+INDIA+LTD.-%24&title=B+K+Narula+HUF+Acquires+0.12%25+Stake+in+Orosil+Smiths+India+Ltd&newsId=98787d0e-966f-4c07-ab9e-7d0d41a4b4c7&token=OTg3ODdkMGUtOTY2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98787d0e-966f-4c07-ab9e-7d0d41a4b4c7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:05:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>B K Narula HUF, a Promoter/Promoter Group, has acquired 50,843 Equity Shares representing 0.12% of the total paid-up equity share capital of Orosil Smiths India Limited. This acquisition was made through the open market on 24th and 25th February 2026. The total voting rights of B K Narula HUF have increased to 14.05% after the acquisition.</p><ul><li>B K Narula HUF, a Promoter/Promoter Group, has acquired 0.12% stake in Orosil Smiths India Limited</li><li>The acquisition was made through the open market on 24th and 25th February 2026</li><li>The total voting rights of B K Narula HUF have increased to 14.05% after the acquisition</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/BA7EB5BA_B62E_48A0_B252_8A4B42EE51CB_092703.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: OROSIL SMITHS INDIA LTD.-$ | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CHAMBLFERT] CM Airtime Promotion LLP Acquires 52,000 Shares of Chambal Fertilisers &amp; Chemicals Ltd.</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CHAMBAL+FERTILISERS+%26+CHEMICALS+LTD.&title=CM+Airtime+Promotion+LLP+Acquires+52%2C000+Shares+of+Chambal+Fertilisers+%26+Chemicals+Ltd.&newsId=9b7d382f-1f26-4781-a1bd-9c57b5eafb24&token=OWI3ZDM4MmYtMWYy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b7d382f-1f26-4781-a1bd-9c57b5eafb24</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 04:05:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>CM Airtime Promotion LLP has disclosed under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI that it has purchased 52,000 equity shares of Chambal Fertilisers and Chemicals Ltd on 23-Feb-26. This has increased their aggregate shareholding to 14,093,28 equity shares. The acquisition was made in compliance with Regulations 29 (2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Take-Overs) Regulations 2011.</p><ul><li>CM Airtime Promotion LLP purchased 52,000 equity shares of Chambal Fertilisers and Chemicals Ltd.</li><li>The purchase increased CM Airtime Promotion LLP&apos;s aggregate shareholding to 14,093,28 equity shares.</li><li>The acquisition was made in compliance with Regulations 29 (2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Take-Overs) Regulations 2011.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8F1CB7DF_5855_4BDB_BEDC_9664C1ADE68F_093400.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CHAMBAL FERTILISERS & CHEMICALS LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>