<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:33:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[TEXELIN] Texel Industries Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on Feb 4, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TEXEL+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Texel+Industries+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+Feb+4%2C+2026&newsId=68bd3f98-7223-4734-938c-d9dc2c35a5af&token=NjhiZDNmOTgtNzIy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68bd3f98-7223-4734-938c-d9dc2c35a5af</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:54:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Texel Industries Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 4, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the third quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The meeting will also take on record the Limited Review Report of the Statutory Auditors.</p><ul><li>Texel Industries Ltd to approve Q3 and nine months financial results for the period ending December 31, 2025</li><li>The meeting will be held on February 4, 2026</li><li>The Board will consider and approve Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results</li><li>The Limited Review Report of the Statutory Auditors will be taken on record</li><li>The announcement is made in accordance with Regulation 29 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/10d7829d-b05c-48d4-9254-5fad187d79b4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TEXEL INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PANAENERG] Panasonic Energy India Company Ltd&apos;s Board Meeting for Q3 2025 Results Cancelled</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PANASONIC+ENERGY+INDIA+COMPANY+LTD.-%24&title=Panasonic+Energy+India+Company+Ltd%27s+Board+Meeting+for+Q3+2025+Results+Cancelled&newsId=9667fa3e-9a99-4bfc-8b5c-3641567a624f&token=OTY2N2ZhM2UtOWE5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9667fa3e-9a99-4bfc-8b5c-3641567a624f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:41:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board Meeting of Panasonic Energy India Company Ltd, originally scheduled for January 29, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, has been cancelled due to unavoidable circumstances. A new date for the meeting will be announced and shared with the Stock Exchange(s) as required by the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The updated information is also available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Panasonic Energy India Company Ltd&apos;s Board Meeting for Q3 2025 results cancelled</li><li>Unavoidable circumstances led to the cancellation</li><li>A new date for the Board Meeting will be announced in due course</li><li>The company will comply with SEBI regulations for disclosure</li><li>Updated information is available on the company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a2aa0699-9051-4a13-b306-9710a9fe7fa1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PANASONIC ENERGY INDIA COMPANY LTD.-$ | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GLOBUSSPR] Globus Spirits Ltd Commissions Distillation Plant in Uttar Pradesh</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GLOBUS+SPIRITS+LTD.&title=Globus+Spirits+Ltd+Commissions+Distillation+Plant+in+Uttar+Pradesh&newsId=91740ce0-54d1-4d16-ac25-f09ebc2d6128&token=OTE3NDBjZTAtNTRk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">91740ce0-54d1-4d16-ac25-f09ebc2d6128</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:27:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Globus Spirits Ltd has successfully commissioned its distillation plant at its Uttar Pradesh Unit, located at Abbaspur, Aurangabad, Tehsil- Matauli, Lakhimpur Kheri. The plant has an installed capacity of 80 KLPD for grain or molasses. This new facility provides internal production of ENA for the company&apos;s consumer business in the state, offering flexibility in raw material usage between molasses, broken rice, and maize.</p><ul><li>Globus Spirits Ltd commissions a distillation plant in Uttar Pradesh</li><li>The plant has an installed capacity of 80 KLPD for grain or molasses</li><li>New facility offers internal production of ENA for the company&apos;s consumer business in the state</li><li>Flexibility in raw material usage between molasses, broken rice, and maize</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2780bd8a-06f5-4ea3-b5b9-592c471f5d62.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GLOBUS SPIRITS LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NAUKRI] Info Edge (India) Ltd: Unintended Email with Draft Financial Results Sent to Outsider</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INFO+EDGE+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Info+Edge+%28India%29+Ltd%3A+Unintended+Email+with+Draft+Financial+Results+Sent+to+Outsider&newsId=ec77e012-d54e-4fc9-a281-49e62e1966fd&token=ZWM3N2UwMTItZDU0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ec77e012-d54e-4fc9-a281-49e62e1966fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:24:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>On January 28, 2026, Info Edge (India) Ltd discovered that a designated person inadvertently emailed an outsider a password-protected draft of the company&apos;s unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The email did not include the password to access the draft results. The company emphasizes that these financial results are still under review, finalization, and approval and may undergo changes during the ongoing audit. As a matter of good corporate governance, the company has informed the stock exchanges and the market about this incident under Regulation 30 of the Listing Regulations. The company advises stakeholders and investors not to rely on any information about the financial results until officially disclosed by the company. The necessary actions are being taken by the company regarding this matter.</p><ul><li>Info Edge (India) Ltd inadvertently emailed an outsider a password-protected draft of unaudited financial results.</li><li>The financial results are still under review, finalization, and approval and may change during the ongoing audit.</li><li>The company has informed the stock exchanges and the market about this incident as a good corporate governance practice.</li><li>Stakeholders and investors are advised not to rely on any information about the financial results until officially disclosed.</li><li>The company is taking necessary actions regarding this matter.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/101035b7-b975-4f2b-b97a-8f98c5355fcb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INFO EDGE (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FORCEMOT] Force Motors Ltd. to Announce Q3 and Nine Months Results on February 4, 2026; Trading Window Closed</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=FORCE+MOTORS+LTD.-%24&title=Force+Motors+Ltd.+to+Announce+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+on+February+4%2C+2026%3B+Trading+Window+Closed&newsId=eb693c1d-88f9-454c-874f-cd03441f6b9d&token=ZWI2OTNjMWQtODhm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eb693c1d-88f9-454c-874f-cd03441f6b9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:11:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Force Motors Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 4, 2026, to consider and approve the Un-Audited (Standalone and Consolidated) Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December, 2025. The Limited Review Report will also be taken on record. In accordance with the Code of Conduct of the company and SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, the Trading Window for dealing in the equity shares of the Company by the ‘Designated Persons’ and their immediate relatives, has been closed from January 15, 2026, and will remain closed until February 6, 2026.</p><ul><li>Force Motors Ltd. to announce Q3 and nine months results on February 4, 2026</li><li>Trading Window closed for Designated Persons and their immediate relatives from January 15, 2026, to February 6, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f10540da-3a00-4fe9-9e39-21ae5739719d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: FORCE MOTORS LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAMHI] Samhi Hotels to Extend Corporate Guarantee of INR 130 Crore to Axis Bank for Subsidiary&apos;s Credit Facility</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Samhi+Hotels+Ltd&title=Samhi+Hotels+to+Extend+Corporate+Guarantee+of+INR+130+Crore+to+Axis+Bank+for+Subsidiary%27s+Credit+Facility&newsId=d3c8457e-2990-43e9-967e-fa812ba50952&token=ZDNjODQ1N2UtMjk5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3c8457e-2990-43e9-967e-fa812ba50952</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:11:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Guarantee &amp; Loan</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Samhi Hotels Ltd, in accordance with the SEBI LODR Regulations, will extend a corporate guarantee, issue a non-disposal undertaking, and create a pledge over securities held in its wholly owned subsidiary, Duet India Hotels (Hyderabad) Private Limited. The total amount of the credit facility availed by the subsidiary from Axis Bank Limited is INR 130 crore. This decision was made on an arm&apos;s length basis and there is no impact on the Company.</p><ul><li>Samhi Hotels to extend a corporate guarantee of INR 130 crore to Axis Bank</li><li>The guarantee is for the credit facility availed by the wholly owned subsidiary, Duet India Hotels (Hyderabad) Private Limited</li><li>The decision is made on an arm&apos;s length basis in compliance with the applicable provisions of the Companies Act, 2013 and the SEBI LODR Regulations</li><li>Samhi Hotels to also issue a non-disposal undertaking and create a pledge over securities held in Duet India Hotels (Hyderabad) Private Limited</li><li>There is no impact of this decision on Samhi Hotels Ltd</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/430ee3d9-dc94-461e-b74f-aa270ad6c27d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Samhi Hotels Ltd | Category: Guarantee & Loan</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FORCEMOT] Force Motors Ltd. to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months of FY 2025-2026 on Feb 4, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=FORCE+MOTORS+LTD.-%24&title=Force+Motors+Ltd.+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+of+FY+2025-2026+on+Feb+4%2C+2026&newsId=ffcaa1d1-f2b2-4f23-bde7-5485c2046389&token=ZmZjYWExZDEtZjJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ffcaa1d1-f2b2-4f23-bde7-5485c2046389</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:11:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Force Motors Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 4, 2026, to consider and approve the Un-Audited (Standalone and Consolidated) Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The meeting will also take on record the Limited Review Report. The trading window for dealing in the equity shares of the company by the &apos;Designated Persons&apos; and their immediate relatives has been closed from January 15, 2026, to February 6, 2026, for the purpose of this announcement.</p><ul><li>Force Motors Ltd. to consider and approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months of FY 2025-2026 on Feb 4, 2026</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the equity shares of the company by the &apos;Designated Persons&apos; and their immediate relatives is closed from Jan 15, 2026, to Feb 6, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4f9f32ac-152c-4ca9-8714-3d7565ad8ee5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: FORCE MOTORS LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HBLPOWER] Cochin Shipyard and HBL Engineering to Form Joint Venture for Electric Mobility Technology</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HBL+POWER+SYSTEMS+LTD.-%24&title=Cochin+Shipyard+and+HBL+Engineering+to+Form+Joint+Venture+for+Electric+Mobility+Technology&newsId=845c637c-5e66-4756-9480-db6ff0cedde6&token=ODQ1YzYzN2MtNWU2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">845c637c-5e66-4756-9480-db6ff0cedde6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:11:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Cochin Shipyard Limited (CSL) and HBL Engineering Limited (HBL) have announced their proposal to form a joint venture. The joint venture aims to develop electric mobility technology and energy storage solutions in the marine space, catering to both domestic and global markets. The shareholding pattern of the proposed joint venture company will be 60% for HBL and 40% for CSL. This collaboration is expected to benefit both companies in capitalizing on the opportunities arising from the growing adoption of electric and hybrid propulsion systems in the marine space, in line with the Government of India’s vision of Aatmanirbhar Bharat.</p><ul><li>Cochin Shipyard Limited and HBL Engineering Limited to form a joint venture</li><li>Joint venture aims to develop electric mobility technology and energy storage solutions in the marine space</li><li>Shareholding pattern of the proposed joint venture company will be 60% for HBL and 40% for CSL</li><li>Collaboration aims to capitalize on the opportunities arising from the growing adoption of electric and hybrid propulsion systems in the marine space</li><li>In line with the Government of India’s vision of Aatmanirbhar Bharat</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e73d9d0e-f75a-4f6b-b5d0-0b5875fcee77.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HBL POWER SYSTEMS LTD.-$ | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SRICC] Sri Chakra Cement Ltd. to Approve Q4 Financial Results on Feb 5, 2026; Trading Window Closed</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sri+Chakra+Cement+Ltd&title=Sri+Chakra+Cement+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q4+Financial+Results+on+Feb+5%2C+2026%3B+Trading+Window+Closed&newsId=9ba55357-636b-46a9-8862-c293227886a8&token=OWJhNTUzNTctNjM2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ba55357-636b-46a9-8862-c293227886a8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:11:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sri Chakra Cement Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 5, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited quarterly financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The meeting will be held at the Corporate Office of the Company in Hyderabad, Telangana, India. In accordance with the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, the &apos;Trading Window&apos; for dealing in securities of the Company is closed for all the Directors/ Officers/ Designated Persons of the Company from January 1, 2026. The window will open after 48 hours of the announcement and intimation of the Results by the Company to the Stock Exchange.</p><ul><li>Sri Chakra Cement Ltd. to approve Q4 financial results on Feb 5, 2026</li><li>Meeting to be held at the Corporate Office in Hyderabad, Telangana, India</li><li>Trading Window closed for Directors/ Officers/ Designated Persons from Jan 1, 2026</li><li>Trading Window to open after 48 hours of results announcement</li><li>Results are for the quarter ended 31st December 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cc9342fc-d414-46f5-ae95-bf98402188ae.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sri Chakra Cement Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADITYASP] Aditya Spinners Ltd to Approve Q4 Financial Results on Feb 5, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADITYA+SPINNERS+LTD.&title=Aditya+Spinners+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+Financial+Results+on+Feb+5%2C+2026&newsId=625712e3-ca72-42bd-b37b-d3be17018bb8&token=NjI1NzEyZTMtY2E3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">625712e3-ca72-42bd-b37b-d3be17018bb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:51:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Aditya Spinners Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 5, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited quarterly financial results for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025. The meeting will be held at the corporate office in Hyderabad, Telangana, India. The &apos;Trading Window&apos; for dealing in securities of the company will be closed for all directors, officers, and designated persons from January 1, 2026, and will open after 48 hours of the announcement and intimation of the results by the company to the Stock Exchange.</p><ul><li>Aditya Spinners Ltd to approve Q4 financial results on Feb 5, 2026</li><li>Meeting to be held at the corporate office in Hyderabad, Telangana, India</li><li>Trading Window for dealing in securities to be closed from Jan 1, 2026</li><li>Trading Window to open after 48 hours of result announcement</li><li>Results to be announced for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6fc23d06-e8cc-4e47-be1e-0111356d27b2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADITYA SPINNERS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>