<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:31:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[CRIZAC] Crizac Ltd Announces Q3 Results, Interim Dividend, and Approves Employee Stock Option Plan</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Crizac+Ltd&title=Crizac+Ltd+Announces+Q3+Results%2C+Interim+Dividend%2C+and+Approves+Employee+Stock+Option+Plan&newsId=258bb457-bd16-4ee3-a3a8-3929a62ad170&token=MjU4YmI0NTctYmQx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">258bb457-bd16-4ee3-a3a8-3929a62ad170</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Crizac Ltd has announced its unaudited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company has reported a profit and has declared an interim dividend of Rs. 8.00 per share. The Board has also approved the ratification of the Amended and Restated Crizac Employee Stock Option Plan 2026 and the grant of options to employees of subsidiary/associate companies under the plan. The record date for the dividend is February 4, 2026, and the payment will be completed by February 26, 2026.</p><ul><li>Unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025, approved</li><li>Interim dividend of Rs. 8.00 per share declared</li><li>Record date for dividend payment set as February 4, 2026</li><li>Amended and Restated Crizac Employee Stock Option Plan 2026 ratified</li><li>Options to be granted to employees of subsidiary/associate companies under the plan</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/63d892bc-37db-4f7e-b609-2839e24a4b05.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Crizac Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUNLOC] Sunil Healthcare Ltd to Approve Q3 Financial Results on Feb 06, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sunil+Healthcare+Ltd&title=Sunil+Healthcare+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+Financial+Results+on+Feb+06%2C+2026&newsId=d4dca7ea-0b48-46dd-b655-b47a3f442639&token=ZDRkY2E3ZWEtMGI0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4dca7ea-0b48-46dd-b655-b47a3f442639</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sunil Healthcare Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 06, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025. The meeting will be held through video conferencing/audio visual connection as per SEBI regulations. The trading window will be closed from January 01, 2026, to February 08, 2026, under the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Sunil Healthcare Ltd to consider and approve Q3 financial results on Feb 06, 2026</li><li>Meeting to be held through video conferencing as per SEBI regulations</li><li>Trading window to be closed from Jan 01, 2026, to Feb 08, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dd5e4666-5b63-4409-90f8-4f0c05011244.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sunil Healthcare Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WARRENTEA] Warren Tea Ltd. to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended 31st December, 2025 on 10th February, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=WARREN+TEA+LTD.-%24&title=Warren+Tea+Ltd.+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+31st+December%2C+2025+on+10th+February%2C+2026&newsId=c8417c91-6279-426c-8096-c714bcd9e00b&token=Yzg0MTdjOTEtNjI3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c8417c91-6279-426c-8096-c714bcd9e00b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:26:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Warren Tea Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 10th February, 2026 to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The meeting will take place at Johar Building, P-1, Hide Lane, 8th Floor, Kolkata 700 073 at 12.30 PM. The trading window for purchase/sale/dealing in the company&apos;s shares by designated persons will remain closed from 1st January, 2026 till 12th February, 2026 in compliance with the Insider Trading Code adopted by the company pursuant to SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulation, 2015.</p><ul><li>Warren Tea Ltd. to approve unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December, 2025 on 10th February, 2026</li><li>The trading window for purchase/sale/dealing in the company&apos;s shares by designated persons will remain closed from 1st January, 2026 till 12th February, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/64acfda5-ef78-433c-b057-f4b209b5c273.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: WARREN TEA LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RISHILASE] Rishi Laser Ltd: No New Requests for Physical Shares Transfer in December 2025 - January 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RISHI+LASER+LTD.&title=Rishi+Laser+Ltd%3A+No+New+Requests+for+Physical+Shares+Transfer+in+December+2025+-+January+2026&newsId=046355fa-31e5-4ea2-938f-0e8e9eba780e&token=MDQ2MzU1ZmEtMzFl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">046355fa-31e5-4ea2-938f-0e8e9eba780e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rishi Laser Ltd has shared a report from the Registrar and Share Transfer Agent, Adroit Corporate Services Private Limited, regarding the re-lodgement of transfer requests of physical shares for the period December 2025 to January 2026. The report indicates that there were no new requests or processed requests during this period, as per the SEBI circular no. SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97 dated 2™ July 2025. This special window was opened for a period of six months from 07* July, 2025 till 06\</p><ul><li>Rishi Laser Ltd shares no new requests for physical shares transfer in December 2025 - January 2026</li><li>Report received from Registrar and Share Transfer Agent, Adroit Corporate Services Private Limited</li><li>SEBI circular no. SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97 dated 2™ July 2025 special window for re-lodgement of transfer deeds</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/08d45db6-1dda-451e-b0c6-19ebdc4d36a8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RISHI LASER LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[POLYSPIN] Polyspin Exports Ltd. to Approve Unaudited Financial Results on Feb 13, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Polyspin+Exports+Ltd&title=Polyspin+Exports+Ltd.+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+on+Feb+13%2C+2026&newsId=1412a05f-fe52-4ae0-af5c-9b23aa32855a&token=MTQxMmEwNWYtZmU1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1412a05f-fe52-4ae0-af5c-9b23aa32855a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:22:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Polyspin Exports Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 13, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The meeting is in compliance with the provisions of Regulation 29 of SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The trading window for the company’s Directors and other designated persons will remain closed till 15th February 2026.</p><ul><li>Polyspin Exports Ltd. to consider and approve Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025.</li><li>The meeting is in compliance with the provisions of Regulation 29 of SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li><li>Trading Window for the company’s Directors and other designated persons will remain closed till 15th February 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/87fd7430-e359-4098-a4b9-447d625746a1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Polyspin Exports Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CARTRADE] CarTrade Tech Ltd Approves Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025 and Postal Ballot for Increased Remuneration</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CarTrade+Tech+Ltd&title=CarTrade+Tech+Ltd+Approves+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025+and+Postal+Ballot+for+Increased+Remuneration&newsId=1c2d0292-3265-4ee9-a9fa-97cac90949ab&token=MWMyZDAyOTItMzI2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c2d0292-3265-4ee9-a9fa-97cac90949ab</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:17:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>CarTrade Tech Ltd, a leading Indian company, has approved its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s Board of Directors also approved a postal ballot notice to consider and approve an increase in remuneration of Mrs. Aneesha Bhandary, Executive Director and CFO. The financial results show the company&apos;s performance in various areas, including revenue, expenses, and profitability.</p><ul><li>Approval of unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 and nine months ended on December 31, 2025</li><li>Increase in remuneration of Mrs. Aneesha Bhandary, Executive Director and CFO approved</li><li>Revenue from operations, other income, and total income reported</li><li>Employee benefit expense, finance cost, depreciation and amortization expense, and other expenses incurred</li><li>Profit before exceptional item and tax, exceptional item, profit before tax, and tax expenses calculated</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/da9f4784-9c62-4971-8d77-bd6238679580.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CarTrade Tech Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PGIL] Pearl Global Industries Ltd to Approve Un-audited Financial Results for Q3 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Pearl+Global+Industries+Limited&title=Pearl+Global+Industries+Ltd+to+Approve+Un-audited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+2025&newsId=5d4c93f6-eeda-4b97-95cb-e41355b4ce7a&token=NWQ0YzkzZjYtZWVk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d4c93f6-eeda-4b97-95cb-e41355b4ce7a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pearl Global Industries Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 06, 2026, to consider and approve the Un-audited Financial Results (Standalone &amp; Consolidated) for the quarter and period ended December 31, 2025. This is in accordance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Pearl Global Industries Ltd to consider and approve Un-audited Financial Results for Q3 2025</li><li>The meeting is scheduled for February 06, 2026</li><li>The results to be approved are for the quarter and period ended December 31, 2025</li><li>The announcement is in accordance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/de7543ce-8b33-4080-a852-28ad6a6a3f25.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Pearl Global Industries Limited | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CARTRADE] CarTrade Tech Hits Record Q3 Revenue of 228 crores and EBITDA zooms by 56% to 78 crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CarTrade+Tech+Ltd&title=CarTrade+Tech+Hits+Record+Q3+Revenue+of+228+crores+and+EBITDA+zooms+by+56%25+to+78+crores&newsId=b374fd67-1d27-42e3-b294-48dd4a07c93c&token=YjM3NGZkNjctMWQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b374fd67-1d27-42e3-b294-48dd4a07c93c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:12:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>CarTrade Tech Limited, a leading digital marketplace ecosystem in India, announced its financial results for the quarter ended December 31st, 2025. The company reported its highest-ever quarterly revenue of 2228.37 crores, representing a 18% YoY growth. EBITDA grew 56% to 278.25 crores and Profit After Tax (PAT) of 361.52 crores, up 35% YoY. EBITDA Margins reached an all-time high of 37% in the quarter. The company operates across more than 500 physical locations and its digital platforms cater to over 150 million annual unique visitors.</p><ul><li>Q3FY26 revenue at a record 2228.37 crores, up 18% YoY</li><li>EBITDA for Q3FY26 at 278.25 crores, up 56% YoY</li><li>Profit After Tax (PAT) for Q3FY26 at 361.52 crores, up 35% YoY</li><li>EBITDA margins reached an all-time high of 37%</li><li>Company operates across more than 500 physical locations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/de283d08-466b-43c6-b849-143ccf0e4c2f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CarTrade Tech Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JAICORPLTD] Jai Corp Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q4 and Annual Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JAI+CORP+LTD.&title=Jai+Corp+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q4+and+Annual+Results+for+2025&newsId=3e992c21-6bb5-42d4-ac18-51d378e40db2&token=M2U5OTJjMjEtNmJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e992c21-6bb5-42d4-ac18-51d378e40db2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:09:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jai Corp Ltd has announced a board meeting scheduled for 13th February 2026 to consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and period ended 31st December 2025. The trading window for the company&apos;s shares, which commenced on 15th January 2026, will close 48 hours after the financial results are declared, in accordance with the Company&apos;s Code of Conduct and SEBI regulations.</p><ul><li>Jai Corp Ltd has scheduled a board meeting for 13th February 2026 to approve Q4 and annual results for 2025.</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and period ended 31st December 2025.</li><li>The trading window for the company&apos;s shares, which commenced on 15th January 2026, will close 48 hours after the financial results are declared.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1aaa3720-154a-4139-a0d9-cec6353e6ac4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JAI CORP LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JENBURPH*] Jenburkt Pharmaceuticals Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on Feb 3, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JENBURKT+PHARMACEUTICALS+LTD.&title=Jenburkt+Pharmaceuticals+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+Feb+3%2C+2026&newsId=845afc8e-cc27-4686-86c6-0da1f360d7cc&token=ODQ1YWZjOGUtY2My</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">845afc8e-cc27-4686-86c6-0da1f360d7cc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:07:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jenburkt Pharmaceuticals Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 3, 2026, to consider and approve the standalone unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. This meeting is pursuant to the company&apos;s earlier communication dated December 15, 2025.</p><ul><li>Jenburkt Pharmaceuticals Ltd is set to approve its Q3 and nine months financial results for the period ending on December 31, 2025.</li><li>The Board of Directors will meet on February 3, 2026, at the company&apos;s registered office to discuss the standalone unaudited financial results.</li><li>This meeting is a follow-up to the company&apos;s earlier communication dated December 15, 2025.</li><li>The financial results to be discussed are for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/85b1bc3c-e370-41e5-929f-3ef5a07165bc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JENBURKT PHARMACEUTICALS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>