<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 21:25:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[WAAREEENER] Waaree Energies Delivers Record-Breaking Quarterly Results with 118.81% YoY Revenue Growth and 167.16% YoY EBITDA Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Waaree+Energies+Ltd&title=Waaree+Energies+Delivers+Record-Breaking+Quarterly+Results+with+118.81%25+YoY+Revenue+Growth+and+167.16%25+YoY+EBITDA+Growth&newsId=9d5a64b1-b3b7-467d-806e-b48755c7053f&token=OWQ1YTY0YjEtYjNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d5a64b1-b3b7-467d-806e-b48755c7053f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:47:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Waaree Energies Limited, a leading renewable energy company, has reported record-breaking quarterly results for Q3 FY26. The company&apos;s revenue from operation stood at INR 7,565.05 Crores, marking an impressive 118.81% YoY growth. EBITDA for the quarter stood at INR 1,928.15 Crores, reporting a growth of 167.16% YoY with margins of 25.49%. Profit After Tax (PAT) of INR 1,106.79 Crores, reflecting a substantial 118.35% YoY surge. The company has also secured a record order inflow of INR 60,000 Crores, ensuring sustained visibility for the years ahead. Waaree is accelerating its transformation into an integrated clean energy solutions provider, strengthening adjacencies across BESS, inverter, transformer, Renewable Power Infrastructure and green hydrogen electrolyser, creating a resilient and future-ready portfolio.</p><ul><li>Achieved 3.51 GW module production in Q3 FY26, driven by robust operational focus</li><li>Achieved 0.75 GW Cell production in Q3 FY26, driven by robust operational focus</li><li>Reported quarterly revenue from operation of INR 7,565.05 Crores, marking an impressive 118.81% YoY growth</li><li>EBITDA for the quarter stood at INR 1,928.15 Crores reporting a growth of 167.16% YoY with margins of 25.49%</li><li>Profit After Tax (PAT) of INR 1,106.79 Crores, reflecting a substantial 118.35% YoY surge</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1ca2c199-3bd5-4ddf-b15d-2344c965a8ef.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Waaree Energies Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TATVA] Tatva Chintan Pharma Chem Ltd Announces Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Tatva+Chintan+Pharma+Chem+Ltd&title=Tatva+Chintan+Pharma+Chem+Ltd+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=a7992916-78f5-447b-8075-c1c4cf949741&token=YTc5OTI5MTYtNzhm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a7992916-78f5-447b-8075-c1c4cf949741</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:47:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tatva Chintan Pharma Chem Ltd, a specialty chemicals company, announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31 December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations was INR 1,385.88 million for Q3 and INR 3,636.31 million for the nine months period. The net profit before tax for Q3 was INR 187.92 million and INR 381.89 million for the nine months period. The company&apos;s net profit after tax for Q3 was INR 159.84 million and INR 300.58 million for the nine months period. The results were reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for Q3 2025 was INR 1,385.88 million</li><li>Revenue from operations for nine months ended 31 December 2025 was INR 3,636.31 million</li><li>Net profit before tax for Q3 2025 was INR 187.92 million</li><li>Net profit before tax for nine months ended 31 December 2025 was INR 381.89 million</li><li>Net profit after tax for Q3 2025 was INR 159.84 million</li><li>Net profit after tax for nine months ended 31 December 2025 was INR 300.58 million</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3712cb12-772f-43ef-be74-ffefa4c84744.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Tatva Chintan Pharma Chem Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PARMCOS-B] Paramount Cosmetics India Ltd Announces Cut-Off Date and Remote E-Voting Date for 01st Extraordinary General Meeting for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PARAMOUNT+COSMETICS+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Paramount+Cosmetics+India+Ltd+Announces+Cut-Off+Date+and+Remote+E-Voting+Date+for+01st+Extraordinary+General+Meeting+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=78add800-05c8-4558-bcbc-1e68eea9b784&token=NzhhZGQ4MDAtMDVj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78add800-05c8-4558-bcbc-1e68eea9b784</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:47:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Paramount Cosmetics India Ltd has informed the cut-off date and remote e-voting date for the 01st Extraordinary General Meeting for the Financial Year 2025-26. The Register of Members and Share Transfer Books of the Company will remain closed from Saturday, February 07, 2026 to Friday, February 13, 2026 (both days inclusive) for the purpose of the meeting. The company is providing its Members, facility to exercise their vote on the resolutions proposed through ‘Remote e-voting’ or ‘e-voting at the EGM’. The remote e-Voting facility for the Extraordinary General Meeting will commence on Tuesday, February 10, 2026, at 9:00 A.M. (IST) and end on Thursday, February 22, 2026, at 5:00 P.M. (IST).</p><ul><li>Paramount Cosmetics India Ltd announces cut-off date and remote e-voting date for 01st Extraordinary General Meeting for FY 2025-26</li><li>The Register of Members and Share Transfer Books of the Company will remain closed from February 07, 2026 to February 13, 2026</li><li>The company is providing its Members, facility to exercise their vote on the resolutions proposed through ‘Remote e-voting’ or ‘e-voting at the EGM’</li><li>The remote e-Voting facility for the Extraordinary General Meeting will commence on February 10, 2026, and end on February 22, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/42ab86f0-7cfc-45e4-80dc-1ad77ffdca40.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PARAMOUNT COSMETICS (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GRAVITA] Gravita India Ltd. Announces Q3 and Nine-Months Results for 2025, Appoints New Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GRAVITA+INDIA+LTD.&title=Gravita+India+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+Nine-Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Appoints+New+Independent+Director&newsId=82afb582-b748-4302-bbdf-6f54096bc5ea&token=ODJhZmI1ODItYjc0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">82afb582-b748-4302-bbdf-6f54096bc5ea</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:47:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gravita India Ltd. announced the outcome of their Board Meeting held on 21st January 2026. The company approved the un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. Mr. Bhupendra Kumar Dak was recommended for appointment as a Non-Executive Independent Director, subject to shareholder approval. The company&apos;s revenue from operations and total income have increased compared to the previous year&apos;s corresponding period.</p><ul><li>Gravita India Ltd. announced the Q3 and nine-months results for 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s Board approved the un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025.</li><li>Mr. Bhupendra Kumar Dak recommended for appointment as a Non-Executive Independent Director, subject to shareholder approval.</li><li>Revenue from operations and total income have increased compared to the previous year&apos;s corresponding period.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b3bc453d-b721-4ee4-b6df-dc714478277f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GRAVITA INDIA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SASHWAT] Sashwat Technocrats Ltd Announces Q3 Results for FY2025-26 with Limited Review</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sashwat+Technocrats+Limited&title=Sashwat+Technocrats+Ltd+Announces+Q3+Results+for+FY2025-26+with+Limited+Review&newsId=ce1233a4-45a8-416b-bdd6-faa937f1588e&token=Y2UxMjMzYTQtNDVh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce1233a4-45a8-416b-bdd6-faa937f1588e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:46:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sashwat Technocrats Ltd has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at INR X,XXX (previous year INR Y,XXX) and other income is INR Z,XXX (previous year INR A,XXX). The total income for the quarter is INR B,XXX (previous year INR C,XXX). The total expenses for the quarter are INR D,XXX (previous year INR E,XXX). The profit before exceptional items and tax is INR F,XXX (previous year INR G,XXX). The company has reported an exceptional item of INR H,XXX. The profit before tax is INR I,XXX (previous year INR J,XXX). The tax expenses for the quarter are INR K,XXX (previous year INR L,XXX). The net profit after tax is INR M,XXX (previous year INR N,XXX). The total comprehensive income for the period after tax is INR O,XXX (previous year INR P,XXX). The profit attributable to equityholders of the parent company is INR Q,XXX (previous year INR R,XXX). The debt equity ratio is INR S,XXX and the debt service coverage ratio is INR T,XXX. The interest service coverage ratio is INR U,XXX. The earning per share is INR V,XXX.</p><ul><li>Unaudited financial results for Q3 FY2025-26 announced</li><li>Revenue from operations stands at INR X,XXX</li><li>Profit before tax is INR I,XXX</li><li>Net profit after tax is INR M,XXX</li><li>Debt equity ratio is INR S,XXX</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7269bcd7-b870-4495-b81f-a29da548e12c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sashwat Technocrats Limited | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NETTLINX] Nettlinx Ltd to Consider Unaudited Financial Results for Q4 2025 in Board Meeting on 28th January 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NETTLINX+LTD.&title=Nettlinx+Ltd+to+Consider+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q4+2025+in+Board+Meeting+on+28th+January+2026&newsId=68cd6c44-5219-41e2-8974-12b7d51968f2&token=NjhjZDZjNDQtNTIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68cd6c44-5219-41e2-8974-12b7d51968f2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:46:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Nettlinx Ltd, a company listed on the BSE, has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 28th January 2026 to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended 31.12.2025. This includes both standalone and consolidated financial results, along with the Limited Review Report for the same period. The meeting will also consider any other business with the permission of the Chair.</p><ul><li>Nettlinx Ltd to consider unaudited financial results for Q4 2025</li><li>Board meeting scheduled on 28th January 2026</li><li>Includes standalone and consolidated financial results</li><li>Limited Review Report for Q4 2025 will also be considered</li><li>Meeting will consider any other business with the permission of the Chair</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6de80e34-ac36-4817-a797-7d2c72e4934d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NETTLINX LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAGCEM] Sagar Cements to Provide Inter Corporate Loan of up to Rs.125 Crores to Subsidiary Andhra Cements</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SAGAR+CEMENTS+LTD.-%24&title=Sagar+Cements+to+Provide+Inter+Corporate+Loan+of+up+to+Rs.125+Crores+to+Subsidiary+Andhra+Cements&newsId=4497090e-7331-4134-a0b0-84da30983f4a&token=NDQ5NzA5MGUtNzMz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4497090e-7331-4134-a0b0-84da30983f4a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:46:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Loans and Borrowings</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sagar Cements Ltd., at its board meeting held on [date], approved providing an inter corporate loan of up to Rs.125 Crores to its subsidiary, Andhra Cements Limited. The decision is in compliance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015, and is subject to necessary regulatory approvals. The company&apos;s registered office is located at Plot No.1, Road No.10, Jubilee Hills, Hyderabad - 500033, Telangana State, India.</p><ul><li>Sagar Cements to provide an inter corporate loan of up to Rs.125 Crores to Andhra Cements Limited</li><li>The decision is in compliance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Subject to necessary regulatory approvals</li><li>Loan amount is up to Rs.125 Crores</li><li>Subsidiary company is Andhra Cements Limited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7d318600-53e8-4930-9209-2122d7ddb97b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SAGAR CEMENTS LTD.-$ | Category: Loans and Borrowings</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZOMATO] Eternal Limited&apos;s QIP Proceeds Utilization in Line with Objects of the Issue: ICRA Report</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Zomato+Ltd&title=Eternal+Limited%27s+QIP+Proceeds+Utilization+in+Line+with+Objects+of+the+Issue%3A+ICRA+Report&newsId=63b05254-536e-4b09-948d-0a0b68b560ea&token=NjNiMDUyNTQtNTM2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63b05254-536e-4b09-948d-0a0b68b560ea</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:46:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Eternal Limited, formerly known as Zomato Limited, has utilized the proceeds raised through its Qualified Institutions Placement (QIP) in line with the objects of the issue, as per the monitoring agency report by ICRA Limited for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company issued 33,64,73,755 equity shares at a price of Rs 252.62 per Equity Share, raising Rs. 8,500.00 Crore. ICRA will monitor the net proceeds of INR 8,436.12 crore for Q3 FY2026.</p><ul><li>Eternal Limited&apos;s QIP proceeds utilization is in line with the objects of the issue</li><li>ICRA Limited is the monitoring agency for the QIP proceeds utilization</li><li>Eternal Limited raised Rs. 8,500.00 Crore through QIP</li><li>ICRA will monitor the net proceeds of INR 8,436.12 crore for Q3 FY2026</li><li>No material deviations or major deviations observed in the QIP proceeds utilization</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1781fa30-9b6b-4a63-8e19-c8208a4a4da9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Zomato Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VALINDIA] Valencia India Ltd Appoints New Statutory Auditor</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Valencia+India+Ltd&title=Valencia+India+Ltd+Appoints+New+Statutory+Auditor&newsId=52cbcfbe-273a-4f77-9bbb-8a96a89531ab&token=NTJjYmNmYmUtMjcz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">52cbcfbe-273a-4f77-9bbb-8a96a89531ab</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Valencia India Ltd, formerly known as Valencia India Private Limited, has called for an Extra Ordinary General Meeting on Monday, 23rd February, 2026 at 2:30 PM at its registered office in Ahmedabad, Gujarat. The meeting is to appoint M/s. Panchal S K &amp; Associates, Chartered Accountants, as the new Statutory Auditors to fill the casual vacancy caused by the resignation of M/s Doshi Doshi &amp; Co, Chartered Accountants. The new auditors will hold office from the conclusion of this meeting until the conclusion of the ensuing Annual General Meeting and will conduct the Statutory Audit for the period ended 31st March, 2026.</p><ul><li>Valencia India Ltd calls for Extra Ordinary General Meeting</li><li>M/s. Panchal S K &amp; Associates, Chartered Accountants, appointed as new Statutory Auditors</li><li>New auditors to fill the casual vacancy caused by the resignation of M/s Doshi Doshi &amp; Co, Chartered Accountants</li><li>New auditors to hold office from the conclusion of this meeting until the conclusion of the ensuing Annual General Meeting</li><li>New auditors to conduct the Statutory Audit for the period ended 31st March, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/65b17a28-5742-442f-9c96-1969b7d9077f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Valencia India Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[OFSS] Oracle Financial Services Software Ltd Announces Q3 and 9M FY2025 Results with Net Profit of ₹ 33,475 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ORACLE+FINANCIAL+SERVICES+SOFTWARE+LTD.&title=Oracle+Financial+Services+Software+Ltd+Announces+Q3+and+9M+FY2025+Results+with+Net+Profit+of+%E2%82%B9+33%2C475+Million&newsId=8ae3e120-b77e-430b-bc9f-8f5cb40bfe63&token=OGFlM2UxMjAtYjc3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ae3e120-b77e-430b-bc9f-8f5cb40bfe63</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:46:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Oracle Financial Services Software Ltd has announced its financial results for the quarter and nine-month period ended December 31, 2025. The total income for the quarter is ₹ 50,991 Million, with a net profit of ₹ 33,475 Million. The Board also approved the re-constitution of Nomination and Remuneration Committee and ORACLE Corporate Social Responsibility Committee. The Company has allotted equity shares on exercise of stock options by eligible employees under the ESOP schemes and recognized a one-time increase in provision for employee benefit expense of ₹ 489 Million due to changes in the New Labour Code. The Company received dividend of ₹ 15,199 Million from its wholly owned subsidiary company Oracle Financial Services Software America, Inc.</p><ul><li>Total income for the quarter is ₹ 50,991 Million</li><li>Net profit for the quarter is ₹ 33,475 Million</li><li>Board approved the re-constitution of Nomination and Remuneration Committee and ORACLE Corporate Social Responsibility Committee</li><li>Recognized a one-time increase in provision for employee benefit expense of ₹ 489 Million</li><li>Received dividend of ₹ 15,199 Million from its wholly owned subsidiary company Oracle Financial Services Software America, Inc.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d12295c8-e5eb-4372-97c2-df962c3617d1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ORACLE FINANCIAL SERVICES SOFTWARE LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>