<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:36:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[DHARTI] Dharti Proteins Ltd Cancels and Extinguishes 100% Outstanding Equity and Preference Shares, Allots New Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Devika+Proteins+Ltd&title=Dharti+Proteins+Ltd+Cancels+and+Extinguishes+100%25+Outstanding+Equity+and+Preference+Shares%2C+Allots+New+Shares&newsId=73a27d9e-cfb1-41e1-824e-907d5a0d8e4e&token=NzNhMjdkOWUtY2Zi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73a27d9e-cfb1-41e1-824e-907d5a0d8e4e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:36:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Dharti Proteins Ltd announced the outcome of its Board of Directors meeting held on February 20, 2026. The company has cancelled and extinguished the entire shareholding of erstwhile promoters and promoter groups. The public shareholders&apos; shareholding has been reduced and reconstituted to 5% of the post-restructured issued and paid-up share capital. The company will allot 25,000 equity shares to existing public shareholders at a face value of Rs. 10/- each. Additionally, the company will allot 4,25,000 equity shares to promoters and promoter groups, and 50,000 equity shares to Goenka Business &amp; Finance Limited.</p><ul><li>Cancellation and extinguishment of 100% presently outstanding equity and preference shares</li><li>Allotment of 25,000 equity shares to existing public shareholders</li><li>Allotment of 4,25,000 equity shares to promoters and promoter groups</li><li>Allotment of 50,000 equity shares to Goenka Business &amp; Finance Limited</li><li>Reduction and reconstitution of public shareholders&apos; shareholding to 5% of the post-restructured issued and paid-up share capital</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dd5b7c12-2fcf-4913-8849-9b996a93072a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Devika Proteins Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GULFOILLUB] Gulf Oil and Mahindra Tractors Extend Decade-Long Partnership with Multi-Year Agreement Renewal</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Gulf+Oil+Lubricants+India+Ltd&title=Gulf+Oil+and+Mahindra+Tractors+Extend+Decade-Long+Partnership+with+Multi-Year+Agreement+Renewal&newsId=28d8cb4c-b61c-4895-b8d7-65c137deddbb&token=MjhkOGNiNGMtYjYx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">28d8cb4c-b61c-4895-b8d7-65c137deddbb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Partnership</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Gulf Oil Lubricants India Ltd. (GOLIL) and Mahindra &amp; Mahindra Limited (Farm Equipment Business — Mahindra Tractors Division) have strategically renewed their partnership, extending a collaboration that has spanned more than a decade. The multi-year renewal, the longest in their journey so far, reflects the deep trust and shared vision between the two organizations. It underscores a joint commitment to advancing technological innovation, strengthening supply chain efficiency, and elevating customer service excellence across Mahindra&apos;s tractor ecosystem. Gulf Oil will hold the largest share of business for the duration of the partnership.</p><ul><li>The renewed partnership is a testament to the strength of the alliance and the shared values between Gulf Oil and Mahindra Tractors.</li><li>This extension marks a new chapter where both companies continue to innovate, enhance services for channel partners, and create lasting value for Mahindra customers.</li><li>The multi-year renewal reflects the deep trust and shared vision between the two organizations, and underscores a joint commitment to advancing technological innovation, strengthening supply chain efficiency, and elevating customer service excellence.</li><li>Gulf Oil will hold the largest share of business for the duration of the partnership, marking a significant commitment from both parties.</li><li>The partnership began in 2011 and has evolved into one of Gulf Oil&apos;s most enduring OEM relationships, built on trust, reliable product performance, excellent service, and a shared focus on innovation and market growth.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6c059f5f-3773-4f6a-8adc-4173d24c0cee.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Gulf Oil Lubricants India Ltd | Category: Partnership</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RPPINFRA] R P P Infra Projects Ltd Secures Rs. 205 Crores Work Order from Sports Development Authority of Tamil Nadu</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RPP+INFRA+PROJECTS+LTD.&title=R+P+P+Infra+Projects+Ltd+Secures+Rs.+205+Crores+Work+Order+from+Sports+Development+Authority+of+Tamil+Nadu&newsId=19fa5df7-bde3-420c-9906-128bf2c10852&token=MTlmYTVkZjctYmRl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19fa5df7-bde3-420c-9906-128bf2c10852</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>R P P Infra Projects Ltd has received a new work order from the Sports Development Authority of Tamil Nadu for the establishment of Global Sports City, Chennai. The value of the work order is Rs. 205,89,14,000 including GST @18%. The project is expected to be completed within 18 months from the date of handing over of the site. The company is required to submit a Time and Progress Chart along with quarterly milestones and resources plan within 21 days of receipt of this Work Order.</p><ul><li>R P P Infra Projects Ltd has been awarded a new work order worth Rs. 205 crores from the Sports Development Authority of Tamil Nadu.</li><li>The project involves the establishment of Global Sports City, Chennai.</li><li>The project is expected to be completed within 18 months from the date of handing over of the site.</li><li>The company is required to submit a Time and Progress Chart along with quarterly milestones and resources plan within 21 days of receipt of this Work Order.</li><li>The order includes a Performance Security Deposit of 3% of the contract value, i.e., Rs. 6,17,68,000/- Minus EMD Rs. 99,42,000/- = Rs. 5,18,26,000/- for a validity period of 36 months.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9e8429e1-da94-42b1-b157-bf415d13ec79.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RPP INFRA PROJECTS LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KAVVERITEL] Kavveri Defence &amp; Wireless Technologies Ltd Changes Company Email ID</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KAVVERI+TELECOM+PRODUCTS+LTD.-%24&title=Kavveri+Defence+%26+Wireless+Technologies+Ltd+Changes+Company+Email+ID&newsId=49b90e7a-bf5b-43b9-a3ca-fc7c1fff603c&token=NDliOTBlN2EtYmY1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">49b90e7a-bf5b-43b9-a3ca-fc7c1fff603c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kavveri Defence &amp; Wireless Technologies Ltd has announced a change in its email ID. The company&apos;s old email ID, companysecretary@kaveritelecoms.com, will be replaced with cs@kavveridefence.com. This change is being made to ensure accurate and seamless coordination for all future communications. The company requests that all stakeholders update their records accordingly and further requests the BSE and NSE to update their websites with the revised details.</p><ul><li>Kavveri Defence &amp; Wireless Technologies Ltd has changed its email ID from companysecretary@kaveritelecoms.com to cs@kavveridefence.com.</li><li>The change is being made to ensure accurate and seamless coordination for all future communications.</li><li>The company requests all stakeholders to update their records with the new email ID.</li><li>The company also requests the BSE and NSE to update their websites with the revised details.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/df758cbd-a879-4179-b7c4-1ebebb9163d3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KAVVERI TELECOM PRODUCTS LTD.-$ | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HAZOOR] Hazoor Multi Projects Ltd. Receives Work Order from Tata Steel Limited Worth INR 182.95 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HAZOOR+MULTI+PROJECTS+LTD.-%24&title=Hazoor+Multi+Projects+Ltd.+Receives+Work+Order+from+Tata+Steel+Limited+Worth+INR+182.95+Crores&newsId=ede9d23d-bb16-4ed6-81a5-d9c193b0991b&token=ZWRlOWQyM2QtYmIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ede9d23d-bb16-4ed6-81a5-d9c193b0991b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Hazoor Multi Projects Ltd. has announced that it has received a work order from Tata Steel Limited for the design, engineering, and construction of OPR and NOPR colony at TSSIJ, Bileipada, Joda. The project includes the construction of apartment blocks with a G+9 structure, complete with civil, architectural, electrical, plumbing &amp; sanitary, fire fighting, water proofing, and automated elevated lift installations. The project will deliver 288 NOPR units of approximately 900 sq. ft. each and 72 OPR units of approximately 1,100 sq. ft. each. The project is to be completed within 24 months with a total contract value of INR 182.95 crores plus applicable GST.</p><ul><li>Hazoor Multi Projects Ltd. received a work order from Tata Steel Limited worth INR 182.95 crores plus applicable GST.</li><li>The project involves the design, engineering, and construction of OPR and NOPR colony at TSSIJ, Bileipada, Joda.</li><li>The project includes the construction of apartment blocks with a G+9 structure and various installations.</li><li>The project will deliver 288 NOPR units and 72 OPR units.</li><li>The project is to be completed within 24 months.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/69dd79d6-bce4-4527-b62b-751c96120e69.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HAZOOR MULTI PROJECTS LTD.-$ | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DATAMATICS] Sameer Kanodia of Datamatics Global Services Wins CEO of the Year® Award for Second Consecutive Year!</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DATAMATICS+GLOBAL+SERVICES+LTD.&title=Sameer+Kanodia+of+Datamatics+Global+Services+Wins+CEO+of+the+Year%C2%AE+Award+for+Second+Consecutive+Year%21&newsId=2e033a53-7a90-41ba-9b99-4d607ea3d4b5&token=MmUwMzNhNTMtN2E5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e033a53-7a90-41ba-9b99-4d607ea3d4b5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:29:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Award</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sameer Kanodia, Managing Director &amp; CEO of Lumina Datamatics and Vice Chairman &amp; CEO of TNQTech, has been awarded the prestigious CEO of the Year® Award for the second consecutive year. The award, presented on 16th February 2026, recognizes his exceptional leadership, business excellence, and sustained impact. The CEO of the Year® Award is part of The Business Leader of the Year®, a leadership recognition program with a legacy of over 23 years, known for its rigorous evaluation process and uncompromising standards of excellence.</p><ul><li>Sameer Kanodia wins CEO of the Year® Award for the second consecutive year.</li><li>The award recognizes his exceptional leadership, business excellence, and sustained impact.</li><li>The Business Leader of the Year® is a prestigious leadership recognition program with a 23-year legacy.</li><li>Sameer&apos;s contribution to driving organizational growth, fostering innovation, and upholding strong values across the organization is acknowledged.</li><li>Lumina Datamatics and TNQTech are among the esteemed organizations felicitated at The Business Leader of the Year®.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0c98fa1d-8379-4184-af4d-1cc1f86dcba7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DATAMATICS GLOBAL SERVICES LTD. | Category: Award</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BHATIA] Bhatia Communications &amp; Retail (India) Ltd Changes Registered Office Address</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Bhatia+Communications+%26+Retail+%28India%29+Ltd&title=Bhatia+Communications+%26+Retail+%28India%29+Ltd+Changes+Registered+Office+Address&newsId=4974edd8-17e8-446c-bfd6-628e213adb1d&token=NDk3NGVkZDgtMTdl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4974edd8-17e8-446c-bfd6-628e213adb1d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:27:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bhatia Communications &amp; Retail (India) Ltd has informed about the change in its registered office address. The new registered office is located at Shop No. 307 to 311, First Floor, Bhatia Complex, Near Sosyo Circle, Bamroli Road, Bamroli, Surat, Chorasi, Gujarat, India, 394210. This change is effective immediately and stakeholders are requested to take note of the new address.</p><ul><li>Registered office of Bhatia Communications &amp; Retail (India) Ltd has been shifted.</li><li>New registered office is located at Shop No. 307 to 311, First Floor, Bhatia Complex, Near Sosyo Circle, Bamroli Road, Bamroli, Surat, Chorasi, Gujarat, India, 394210.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5000ccc4-4a35-49c4-be2b-2fa07f178a43.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Bhatia Communications & Retail (India) Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ICON] Icon Facilitators Ltd Secures Rs. 14,28,465.52 Electrical &amp; Mechanical Manpower Services Contract from Grandthum Facility Management</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Icon+Facilitators+Ltd&title=Icon+Facilitators+Ltd+Secures+Rs.+14%2C28%2C465.52+Electrical+%26+Mechanical+Manpower+Services+Contract+from+Grandthum+Facility+Management&newsId=d211f8fb-c27b-4789-a91b-01f4425a1d84&token=ZDIxMWY4ZmItYzI3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d211f8fb-c27b-4789-a91b-01f4425a1d84</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:22:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Icon Facilitators Ltd has announced the receipt of an order from Grandthum Facility Management Private Limited for Electrical &amp; Mechanical Manpower services. The contract, valued at Rs. 14,28,465.52, is to be completed over a period of 12 months. The order details comply with the SEBI Master Circular No. SEBI/HO/CFD/PoD2/P/0155 dated November 11, 2024 and SEBI/HO/CFD/CFD-PoD-2/P/CIR/P/2024 /185 dated December 31, 2024. This disclosure is made as per the requirements under the specified SEBI circulars.</p><ul><li>Icon Facilitators Ltd secures a contract worth Rs. 14,28,465.52 from Grandthum Facility Management Private Limited.</li><li>The contract is for Electrical &amp; Mechanical Manpower services.</li><li>The contract period is 12 months.</li><li>The transaction does not involve any related parties.</li><li>The disclosure is made as per SEBI regulations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/820312e2-90c5-4b0d-ad52-f895dcd8ba4d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Icon Facilitators Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SOBME] Sobhagya Mercantile to Raise ₹178.71 Crores for Hybrid Annuity Model Road Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SOBHAGYA+MERCHANTILE+LTD.&title=Sobhagya+Mercantile+to+Raise+%E2%82%B9178.71+Crores+for+Hybrid+Annuity+Model+Road+Projects&newsId=8d510184-65f1-407b-8ba0-59cd8165dd52&token=OGQ1MTAxODQtNjVm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d510184-65f1-407b-8ba0-59cd8165dd52</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Sobhagya Mercantile Ltd. plans to raise approximately ₹178.71 Crores through a Preferential Issue of Convertible Warrants. The funds will be utilized for investing in promoter group Special Purpose Vehicles (SPVs) executing road infrastructure projects under the Hybrid Annuity Model (HAM) awarded by the Department of Public Works, Government of Maharashtra. The company intends to deploy around ₹154.30 Crores for equity and/or quasi-equity investment in the SPVs. The HAM model ensures sovereign-linked credit strength and minimizes traffic and revenue risks, providing predictable cash flows through annuity and interest income, O&amp;M revenue, and equity upside.</p><ul><li>Sobhagya Mercantile to raise ₹178.71 Crores for infrastructure projects</li><li>Investment in promoter group SPVs executing HAM road projects</li><li>Expected IRR of approximately 16% on the company&apos;s investment</li><li>Minimal demand/traffic risk and government-backed cash flows</li><li>Additional O&amp;M revenue overlay for the company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a5a015af-e705-4d76-a1b5-f8f032f24cc4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SOBHAGYA MERCHANTILE LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SANOFICONR] Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd. to Approve Audited Financial Statements and Consider Dividend Recommendation for FY 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sanofi+Consumer+Healthcare+India+Ltd&title=Sanofi+Consumer+Healthcare+India+Ltd.+to+Approve+Audited+Financial+Statements+and+Consider+Dividend+Recommendation+for+FY+2025&newsId=0095bdeb-31e2-4398-a3d9-def1b5be0953&token=MDA5NWJkZWItMzFl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0095bdeb-31e2-4398-a3d9-def1b5be0953</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:11:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd. has announced a meeting of its Board of Directors on 25th February 2026. The agenda includes the approval of the Audited Financial Statements for the quarter and financial year ended 31st December 2025. Additionally, the Board may consider the recommendation of a dividend for the Financial Year 2025 at the same meeting.</p><ul><li>Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd. to hold Board Meeting on 25th February 2026</li><li>Approval of Audited Financial Statements for Q4 and FY 2025 on the agenda</li><li>Board may consider dividend recommendation for FY 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/49590aae-8f43-4aea-84ab-5023865e0fab.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>