<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:17:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[PBAINFRA] PBA Infrastructure Ltd. to Appoint Suresh Kumar Sunderlal Bothra as Managing Director for 2 Years</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PBA+INFRASTRUCTURE+LTD.&title=PBA+Infrastructure+Ltd.+to+Appoint+Suresh+Kumar+Sunderlal+Bothra+as+Managing+Director+for+2+Years&newsId=a9decbdf-561b-4ee4-85b2-36922c1e447a&token=YTlkZWNiZGYtNTYx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a9decbdf-561b-4ee4-85b2-36922c1e447a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>PBA Infrastructure Ltd. has scheduled an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) on 12th February 2026 at 4.00 p.m. through Video Conferencing and Other Audio Visual Means. The EGM will transact the special business of appointing Suresh Kumar Sunderlal Bothra as Managing Director for a term of 2 years.</p><ul><li>PBA Infrastructure Ltd. has called for an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM)</li><li>The EGM will be held on 12th February 2026 at 4.00 p.m.</li><li>The EGM will be conducted through Video Conferencing and Other Audio Visual Means</li><li>Suresh Kumar Sunderlal Bothra is proposed to be appointed as Managing Director for a term of 2 years</li><li>The appointment is subject to the approval of the Members of the Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5bb687f8-7ab4-4808-b699-d87ca037b071.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PBA INFRASTRUCTURE LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[POWERGRID] POWERGRID Bhadla Sikar Transmission Limited Commissions 8.1GW Solar Energy Transmission Project</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=POWER+GRID+CORPORATION+OF+INDIA+LTD.&title=POWERGRID+Bhadla+Sikar+Transmission+Limited+Commissions+8.1GW+Solar+Energy+Transmission+Project&newsId=6923bcb4-771f-463c-bf00-b8ec97feff24&token=NjkyM2JjYjQtNzcx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6923bcb4-771f-463c-bf00-b8ec97feff24</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:47:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>POWERGRID Bhadla Sikar Transmission Limited, a Wholly Owned Subsidiary of Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd., has successfully commissioned a transmission system strengthening scheme for evacuation of Power from Solar energy Zones in Rajasthan under Phase II — Part E. The project, secured through Tariff Based Competitive Bidding, has a capacity of 8.1GW. The project received the Notification for Commercial Operation (DOCO) via email on 16th January, 2026.</p><ul><li>POWERGRID Bhadla Sikar Transmission Limited has commissioned an 8.1GW solar energy transmission project in Rajasthan.</li><li>The project was secured through Tariff Based Competitive Bidding.</li><li>The project is a part of the transmission system strengthening scheme under Phase II — Part E.</li><li>The project received the Notification for Commercial Operation (DOCO) via email on 16th January, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/de8d8bd5-85b6-4256-bdb5-8d19d6484397.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: POWER GRID CORPORATION OF INDIA LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VICTMILL] Victoria Mills Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q4 Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VICTORIA+MILLS+LTD.&title=Victoria+Mills+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q4+Results+for+2025&newsId=e97cb04e-555e-40b8-8c83-0bfef6f18900&token=ZTk3Y2IwNGUtNTU1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e97cb04e-555e-40b8-8c83-0bfef6f18900</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Victoria Mills Ltd has announced a board meeting scheduled for February 13, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. This meeting is in accordance with Regulation 29 and other applicable regulations of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Victoria Mills Ltd has scheduled a board meeting on February 13, 2026</li><li>The meeting aims to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for Q4 2025</li><li>This meeting is in compliance with SEBI regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e9b2abcc-1ad6-45a0-8296-17a858a03357.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VICTORIA MILLS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AEQUS] Aequs Ltd Enters Joint Venture with Accel India VIII, Vagus Defence Tech &amp; Aerospace Fund I, and Ajna Aerospace &amp; Defence</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Aequs+Ltd&title=Aequs+Ltd+Enters+Joint+Venture+with+Accel+India+VIII%2C+Vagus+Defence+Tech+%26+Aerospace+Fund+I%2C+and+Ajna+Aerospace+%26+Defence&newsId=91a37530-d101-4362-b4c0-bfe7c1c03254&token=OTFhMzc1MzAtZDEw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">91a37530-d101-4362-b4c0-bfe7c1c03254</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:37:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Aequs Limited has executed a Joint Venture Agreement and Shareholders Agreement with Accel India VIII (Mauritius) Ltd, Vagus Defence Tech &amp; Aerospace Fund I, and Ajna Aerospace &amp; Defence Private Limited. The joint venture aims to source, acquire, license intellectual property rights for unmanned aerial vehicles from overseas licensors and owners, develop and manufacture, assemble, test, market and sell unmanned aerial vehicles (&apos;UAVs&apos;) and related products in India and internationally. Aequs, Accel and Vagus will have equal shareholding in the JV Company and will have special rights such as right to appoint directors, first right of refusal, and right of first offer in case of issuance of shares. This is not a related party transaction.</p><ul><li>Aequs Ltd enters into a joint venture with Accel India VIII (Mauritius) Ltd, Vagus Defence Tech &amp; Aerospace Fund I, and Ajna Aerospace &amp; Defence Private Limited</li><li>The joint venture aims to source, acquire, license intellectual property rights for unmanned aerial vehicles from overseas licensors and owners</li><li>Aequs, Accel and Vagus will have equal shareholding in the JV Company</li><li>Special rights such as right to appoint directors, first right of refusal, and right of first offer in case of issuance of shares</li><li>This is not a related party transaction</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0a1fa4dd-5944-4b0f-b459-2440ec3070e5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Aequs Ltd | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASMTEC] ASM Technologies Ltd Registers Wholly Owned Subsidiary in Vietnam</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ASM+TECHNOLOGIES+LTD.&title=ASM+Technologies+Ltd+Registers+Wholly+Owned+Subsidiary+in+Vietnam&newsId=b4aca517-401d-42e4-b917-8749cebcb089&token=YjRhY2E1MTctNDAx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4aca517-401d-42e4-b917-8749cebcb089</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>ASM Technologies Ltd has registered a Wholly Owned Subidiary (WOS) named ‘ASM Technologies VIET NAM CO. Ltd.’ in Vietnam. The company is in the process of completing the preliminary set up. The WOS is expected to support customers in the areas of Engineering Design led Manufacturing. ASM Technologies Ltd will invest 5,247,800,000 VND as initial capital. The WOS is a newly incorporated company in Vietnam and has no turnover since it is not yet operational.</p><ul><li>ASM Technologies Ltd has registered a Wholly Owned Subsidiary (WOS) in Vietnam.</li><li>The WOS, named ‘ASM Technologies VIET NAM CO. Ltd.’ is expected to support customers in the areas of Engineering Design led Manufacturing.</li><li>ASM Technologies Ltd will invest 5,247,800,000 VND as initial capital.</li><li>The WOS is a newly incorporated company in Vietnam and has no turnover since it is not yet operational.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9aa2d253-481e-4f5a-8396-66a9697e2ef4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ASM TECHNOLOGIES LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DALBHARAT] Dalmia Bharat Ltd Disposes Entire Stake in Associate O2 Renewable Energy V Private Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Dalmia+Bharat+Ltd&title=Dalmia+Bharat+Ltd+Disposes+Entire+Stake+in+Associate+O2+Renewable+Energy+V+Private+Limited&newsId=bc8829b8-c885-4ee8-96b8-72df90c2ede1&token=YmM4ODI5YjgtYzg4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc8829b8-c885-4ee8-96b8-72df90c2ede1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Disposal of stake in an Associate</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dalmia Bharat Ltd announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, Dalmia Cement (Bharat) Limited (DCBL), has disposed of the entire 25.44% equity stake in O2 Renewable Energy V Private Limited (OREV). OREV was an associate of DCBL, but since DCBL did not exercise any control over OREV, its financials were not consolidated with the financials of the Company. The stake was transferred to third parties, namely SW Neo Energy Limited, Goldman Sachs Services Pvt Ltd, and Syngene International Limited, for a consideration of Rs. 10.82 Crore. The disposal was completed on January 16, 2026.</p><ul><li>Dalmia Bharat Ltd&apos;s subsidiary, Dalmia Cement (Bharat) Limited, disposes of entire 25.44% stake in O2 Renewable Energy V Private Limited</li><li>O2 Renewable Energy V Private Limited was an associate of Dalmia Cement (Bharat) Limited, but its financials were not consolidated with the Company&apos;s financials</li><li>The stake was transferred to third parties for a consideration of Rs. 10.82 Crore</li><li>The disposal was completed on January 16, 2026</li><li>The transaction does not fall under related party transactions and is not covered by any Scheme of Arrangement</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/05b84d92-48bc-4000-946b-99c6187aeeaa.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Dalmia Bharat Ltd | Category: Disposal of stake in an Associate</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAILANI] Sailani Tours N Travels Ltd Announces No Deviation in Public Issue Proceeds Use</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sailani+Tours+N+Travels+Ltd&title=Sailani+Tours+N+Travels+Ltd+Announces+No+Deviation+in+Public+Issue+Proceeds+Use&newsId=6b91c583-a170-4e3b-9000-c49f6bd14465&token=NmI5MWM1ODMtYTE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6b91c583-a170-4e3b-9000-c49f6bd14465</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:21:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sailani Tours N Travels Ltd has announced that there has been no deviation or variation in the use of the Public Issue Proceeds raised from the Initial Public Issue (IPO). This information is for the record.</p><ul><li>Sailani Tours N Travels Ltd has not deviated from the intended use of Public Issue Proceeds from the IPO.</li><li>This announcement is for informational and record-keeping purposes.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5a64d697-e445-4030-9187-73dd3ed47311.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sailani Tours N Travels Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NH] Narayana Hrudayalaya Ltd Incorporates Wholly Owned Subsidiary &apos;Narayana Healthcare North Private Limited&apos;</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Narayana+Hrudayalaya+Ltd&title=Narayana+Hrudayalaya+Ltd+Incorporates+Wholly+Owned+Subsidiary+%27Narayana+Healthcare+North+Private+Limited%27&newsId=b5b39eb5-436d-4901-bd1f-dd832ee73714&token=YjViMzllYjUtNDM2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5b39eb5-436d-4901-bd1f-dd832ee73714</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:11:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Narayana Hrudayalaya Ltd, a leading healthcare service provider, has incorporated a Wholly Owned Subsidiary named &apos;Narayana Healthcare North Private Limited&apos; on January 16, 2026. The new subsidiary, with a paid-up capital of Rs. 5,00,000, is aimed at optimizing the company&apos;s presence in the Northern part of the country and carrying on the business of healthcare services in the field of hospitals, health, and wellness management.</p><ul><li>Narayana Hrudayalaya Ltd has incorporated a Wholly Owned Subsidiary named &apos;Narayana Healthcare North Private Limited&apos;</li><li>The new subsidiary is registered under the Companies Act, 2013 with CIN: U86100KA2026PTC214296</li><li>The subsidiary is authorized with a capital of Rs. 10,00,000 and a paid-up capital of Rs. 5,00,000</li><li>The new subsidiary is aimed at optimizing the company&apos;s presence in the Northern part of the country</li><li>The subsidiary&apos;s main object is to operate and run hospitals and to provide healthcare services in the field of health and wellness management</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ad59ac69-d54f-4fa6-bec3-b7221329b4bf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Narayana Hrudayalaya Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SFL] Sheela Foam Ltd. Receives Approval for Composite Scheme of Arrangement</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sheela+Foam+Ltd&title=Sheela+Foam+Ltd.+Receives+Approval+for+Composite+Scheme+of+Arrangement&newsId=a648b767-1ad9-40f8-84c1-d4b42c118eba&token=YTY0OGI3NjctMWFk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a648b767-1ad9-40f8-84c1-d4b42c118eba</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:04:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sheela Foam Ltd. has announced that a certified copy of the Order of the Hon’ble National Company Law Tribunal, Mumbai Bench, approving the Composite Scheme of Arrangement involving Belvedore International Limited, Kanvas Concepts Private Limited, Kurlon Retail Limited, Komfort Universe Products and Services Limited, Starship Value Chain and Manufacturing Private Limited into Kurlon Enterprise Limited, and further into Sheela Foam Limited and their respective shareholders and creditors, has been filed with the Registrar of Companies, Mumbai. The shareholders of Kurlon Enterprise Limited holding equity share as on Friday, 30th January, 2026, being the Record Date, shall be allotted 52 (Fifty-Two) equity shares of Sheela Foam Limited for every 100 (One Hundred) equity shares held in Kurlon Enterprise Limited, in accordance with the provisions of the Scheme.</p><ul><li>Sheela Foam Ltd. receives approval for a Composite Scheme of Arrangement</li><li>The Scheme involves Belvedore International Limited, Kanvas Concepts Private Limited, Kurlon Retail Limited, Komfort Universe Products and Services Limited, Starship Value Chain and Manufacturing Private Limited into Kurlon Enterprise Limited, and further into Sheela Foam Limited</li><li>The Order of the Hon’ble National Company Law Tribunal, Mumbai Bench has been approved</li><li>The shareholders of Kurlon Enterprise Limited will be allotted 52 equity shares of Sheela Foam Limited for every 100 equity shares held</li><li>The Record Date for this arrangement is 30th January, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9e1a5d41-b699-4beb-ab17-7f756d742781.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sheela Foam Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASIANHOTNR] Asian Hotels (North) Ltd. Fined for Non-Compliance with Board Composition Regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Asian+Hotels+%28North%29+Limited&title=Asian+Hotels+%28North%29+Ltd.+Fined+for+Non-Compliance+with+Board+Composition+Regulations&newsId=d4a8a0cd-b6fa-436c-8792-f1e061090452&token=ZDRhOGEwY2QtYjZm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4a8a0cd-b6fa-436c-8792-f1e061090452</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Asian Hotels (North) Ltd. has been fined by BSE and NSE for non-compliance with Regulation 17(1) of the Listing Regulations, which pertains to the composition of the Board of Directors, including the failure to appoint a woman director. The fine, amounting to Rs. 1,06,200/- each (inclusive of GST), was imposed on November 28, 2025. The company has since appointed Ms. Karishma Kaur Gill as an Additional Director acting in the capacity of an Independent Non-executive Woman Director on December 16, 2025, for a period of one year, subject to shareholder approval within three months. The company has assured that the non-compliance was not intentional and was due to the non-availability of the right candidate. The company has an optimum mix of Board of Directors, with 7 members, 4 of whom are Independent Directors, including a woman director. The Chairperson of the Board is also an Independent Director. The company has stated that it has always endeavored to comply with applicable regulations and has taken steps to strengthen its processes to avoid such delays in the future.</p><ul><li>Asian Hotels (North) Ltd. fined for non-compliance with Regulation 17(1) of the Listing Regulations.</li><li>Fine imposed by BSE and NSE amounting to Rs. 1,06,200/- each (inclusive of GST).</li><li>Ms. Karishma Kaur Gill appointed as Additional Director on December 16, 2025.</li><li>Company assures non-compliance was not intentional.</li><li>Company has an optimum mix of Board of Directors, including 4 Independent Directors and a woman director.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f0f7ebda-e519-4770-b568-c58c92f971dc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Asian Hotels (North) Limited | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>