<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:36:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[IFINSEC] India Finsec Ltd: Release of Pledge of Equity Shares Disclosed Under SEBI Regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDIA+FINSEC+LTD.&title=India+Finsec+Ltd%3A+Release+of+Pledge+of+Equity+Shares+Disclosed+Under+SEBI+Regulations&newsId=3b6c5454-eb58-4029-90f4-693707fcaea8&token=M2I2YzU0NTQtZWI1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b6c5454-eb58-4029-90f4-693707fcaea8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Pledge</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Exchange has received disclosures from India Finsec Ltd regarding the release of pledge of Equity Shares under Regulation 31(1) and 31(2) of the SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeover) Regulations, 2011. This disclosure contains detailed information about the release of pledge, including the number of shares, percentage of shareholding, and other relevant particulars.</p><ul><li>India Finsec Ltd discloses release of pledge of Equity Shares under SEBI regulations.</li><li>Disclosure made pursuant to Regulation 31(1) and 31(2) of the SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeover) Regulations, 2011.</li><li>Detailed information about the release of pledge, including the number of shares and percentage of shareholding provided.</li><li>Disclosure aims to ensure transparency and compliance with relevant regulations.</li><li>Investors and stakeholders are advised to take note of this development.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/C9C7D2DF_9C31_4FFA_A09B_A115AABA2889_114923.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDIA FINSEC LTD. | Category: Pledge</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IFINSEC] Pledge of Equity Shares of India Finsec Limited Released by Promoter</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDIA+FINSEC+LTD.&title=Pledge+of+Equity+Shares+of+India+Finsec+Limited+Released+by+Promoter&newsId=d4ad67ee-8d3f-46c1-ad10-c901e10ec9a9&token=ZDRhZDY3ZWUtOGQz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4ad67ee-8d3f-46c1-ad10-c901e10ec9a9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Exchange has received disclosures of reasons for encumbrance by the promoter of India Finsec Ltd. A disclosure regarding the release of pledge of Equity Shares of M/s India Finsec Limited has been made in the prescribed format under Regulation 31(1) and 31(2) of the SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeover) Regulations, 2011. The promoter has released the pledge of equity shares of India Finsec Limited.</p><ul><li>Disclosure of reasons for encumbrance by the promoter of India Finsec Ltd.</li><li>Release of pledge of Equity Shares of M/s India Finsec Limited.</li><li>Regulation 31(1) and 31(2) of the SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeover) Regulations, 2011 applied.</li><li>Pledge of equity shares of India Finsec Limited released by the promoter.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/C3AA4F08_B06E_4280_832E_AAFC433888BD_114935.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDIA FINSEC LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NCLIND] Kalidindi Ravi Acquires Shares of NCL Industries Ltd. Through Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NCL+INDUSTRIES+LTD.-%24&title=Kalidindi+Ravi+Acquires+Shares+of+NCL+Industries+Ltd.+Through+Open+Market&newsId=21212f08-3a94-41a7-99e2-f09b41983d3f&token=MjEyMTJmMDgtM2E5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21212f08-3a94-41a7-99e2-f09b41983d3f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>According to a disclosure made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011, Kalidindi Ravi, through Kakatiya Industries Pvt Ltd, has acquired shares of NCL Industries Ltd. The acquisition was made through the open market. The total equity shares of NCL Industries Ltd. stand at 4,52,32,790, with a face value of Rs.10/- each. The total diluted share/voting capital of the company after the acquisition is also Rs.45,23,27,900/-.</p><ul><li>Kalidindi Ravi acquires shares of NCL Industries Ltd.</li><li>Acquisition made through the open market.</li><li>Total equity shares of NCL Industries Ltd. stand at 4,52,32,790.</li><li>Face value of Rs.10/- each.</li><li>Total diluted share/voting capital of the company after the acquisition is Rs.45,23,27,900/-.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/AD8D1AB8_E126_4D14_9CA3_5763B71D6EE1_114837.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NCL INDUSTRIES LTD.-$ | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ACIIN] ACI Infocom Ltd Appoints Aviation Entrepreneur Sanjay Natvarlal Mandavia as Additional Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ACI+INFOCOM+LTD.&title=ACI+Infocom+Ltd+Appoints+Aviation+Entrepreneur+Sanjay+Natvarlal+Mandavia+as+Additional+Director&newsId=dc5944d4-f07c-4add-8111-bd2e73ba5296&token=ZGM1OTQ0ZDQtZjA3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc5944d4-f07c-4add-8111-bd2e73ba5296</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:31:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>At a Board Meeting on 21st February, 2026, ACI Infocom Ltd approved the appointment of Mr. Sanjay Natvarlal Mandavia as an Additional Director (Executive) with effect from the same date. Mandavia, an Indian aviation entrepreneur and former Senior Pilot and DGCA-approved Check Pilot at Kingfisher Airlines, founded Flight Simulation Techniques Centre (FSTC) and launched FlyBig to enhance regional connectivity across tier-2 and tier-3 cities. He has no relations with any member of the ACI Infocom Ltd Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>ACI Infocom Ltd appointed Sanjay Natvarlal Mandavia as Additional Director (Executive)</li><li>Mandavia is an Indian aviation entrepreneur and former Senior Pilot at Kingfisher Airlines</li><li>He founded Flight Simulation Techniques Centre (FSTC) and launched FlyBig</li><li>Mandavia&apos;s appointment is effective from 21st February, 2026</li><li>Mandavia has no relations with any ACI Infocom Ltd Board members</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fd9e7649-19f4-43c6-b975-6680eaa78f7e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ACI INFOCOM LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CENTRALBK] Central Bank of India Signs Distribution Agreement with SBI Funds Management Limited for Mutual Fund Products</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CENTRAL+BANK+OF+INDIA&title=Central+Bank+of+India+Signs+Distribution+Agreement+with+SBI+Funds+Management+Limited+for+Mutual+Fund+Products&newsId=6dd13fd8-a5b5-4874-a1cc-5e1827865edd&token=NmRkMTNmZDgtYTVi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6dd13fd8-a5b5-4874-a1cc-5e1827865edd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:31:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Central Bank of India has entered into a distributorship agreement with M/s SBI Funds Management Limited for the distribution of their Mutual Fund Products to its customers. This partnership offers Central Bank of India&apos;s customers an opportunity to unlock the value of their savings through various mutual fund products offered by SBI Funds Management Limited. SBI Funds Management Limited, a joint venture between SBI and AMUNDI (France), is one of the leading asset management companies in India, servicing around 25 crore above investor folios and has a total AUM of X 12,41,000 crore as on December 2025 under its suite of investment offerings.</p><ul><li>Central Bank of India has signed a distributorship agreement with SBI Funds Management Limited</li><li>The agreement allows Central Bank of India to distribute SBI Funds Management Limited&apos;s Mutual Fund Products to its customers</li><li>SBI Funds Management Limited is a joint venture between SBI and AMUNDI (France)</li><li>SBI Funds Management Limited is one of the leading asset management companies in India</li><li>SBI Funds Management Limited has a total AUM of X 12,41,000 crore as on December 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/08d4c9eb-5426-41a4-b645-4d8902c71a04.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CENTRAL BANK OF INDIA | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RBLBANK] RBL Bank Ltd Announces Retirement of Executive Director and Appointment of New Whole-time Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RBL+Bank+Ltd&title=RBL+Bank+Ltd+Announces+Retirement+of+Executive+Director+and+Appointment+of+New+Whole-time+Director&newsId=c9c976fb-04d8-4c7d-be30-597980850805&token=YzljOTc2ZmItMDRk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9c976fb-04d8-4c7d-be30-597980850805</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>RBL Bank Limited has informed the exchange about the Change in Directors of the Bank. Mr. Rajeev Ahuja, Executive Director of the Bank, has retired from the services of the Bank upon completion of his term and has ceased to be the Whole-time Director and Key Managerial Personnel of the Bank. Mr. Jaideep lyer has assumed charge as a Whole-time Director and a Key Managerial Personnel of the Bank effective February 21, 2026, for a term of three years i.e. till February 20, 2029. The Bank has also approved the names of the Key Managerial Personnel (KMP) authorised under Regulation 30 (5) of the SEBI Listing Regulations.</p><ul><li>Mr. Rajeev Ahuja has retired from the services of the Bank and ceased to be the Whole-time Director and Key Managerial Personnel of the Bank.</li><li>Mr. Jaideep lyer has assumed charge as a Whole-time Director and a Key Managerial Personnel of the Bank.</li><li>Mr. Jaideep lyer&apos;s term as approved by the Reserve Bank of India and Shareholders is for a period of three years i.e. till February 20, 2029.</li><li>The Bank has approved the names of the Key Managerial Personnel (KMP) authorised under Regulation 30 (5) of the SEBI Listing Regulations.</li><li>The Bank has reviewed and approved the amendments to the ‘Code of Practices and Procedures for Fair Disclosure of Unpublished Price Sensitive Information’.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d0d39c64-e3a0-4163-b81c-730ecebf6dcc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RBL Bank Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RBLBANK] RBL Bank&apos;s Executive Director, Mr. Rajeev Ahuja, Retires; Mr. Jaideep Lyer Appointed as New Executive Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RBL+Bank+Ltd&title=RBL+Bank%27s+Executive+Director%2C+Mr.+Rajeev+Ahuja%2C+Retires%3B+Mr.+Jaideep+Lyer+Appointed+as+New+Executive+Director&newsId=535ae0fc-31b4-4655-ae8a-9bd0be66684b&token=NTM1YWUwZmMtMzFi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">535ae0fc-31b4-4655-ae8a-9bd0be66684b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>RBL Bank Limited has informed the exchange about the retirement of Mr. Rajeev Ahuja, Executive Director, with effect from the close of business hours of February 20, 2026. Mr. Jaideep Lyer has assumed charge as a Whole-time Director (designated as Executive Director) and a Key Managerial Personnel of the Bank effective February 21, 2026, for a term of three years i.e. till February 20, 2029. The Bank&apos;s Board of Directors has also approved the names of the Key Managerial Personnel (KMP) authorized under Regulation 30 (5) of the SEBI Listing Regulations. The Bank has also reviewed and approved the amendments to the ‘Code of Practices and Procedures for Fair Disclosure of Unpublished Price Sensitive Information’ effective February 21, 2026.</p><ul><li>Mr. Rajeev Ahuja retires as Executive Director of RBL Bank.</li><li>Mr. Jaideep Lyer appointed as new Executive Director and Key Managerial Personnel.</li><li>Mr. Lyer&apos;s term is for three years, i.e., from February 21, 2026, to February 20, 2029.</li><li>Board of Directors approved the names of KMP authorized under Regulation 30 (5) of the SEBI Listing Regulations.</li><li>Bank approved the amendments to the ‘Code of Practices and Procedures for Fair Disclosure of Unpublished Price Sensitive Information’.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/27269b9d-ec8f-4d88-890a-c9907b981238.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RBL Bank Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HITECHGEAR] Hi-Tech Gears&apos; Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process Stayed by NCLAT Until April 20, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=The+Hi-Tech+Gears+Ltd&title=Hi-Tech+Gears%27+Corporate+Insolvency+Resolution+Process+Stayed+by+NCLAT+Until+April+20%2C+2026&newsId=3fe84c15-bfce-440c-a763-58503fe09c48&token=M2ZlODRjMTUtYmZj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3fe84c15-bfce-440c-a763-58503fe09c48</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>The Hi-Tech Gears Ltd. has informed its stakeholders that the National Company Law Appellate Tribunal (NCLAT) has continued the interim stay on the Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP) until April 20, 2026. The decision came in light of the paucity of time, which led to the adjournment of the matter hearing to the aforementioned date. The order was passed by Hon&apos;ble NCLAT on September 03, 2024, and a copy of the order is available on the NCLAT website.</p><ul><li>Hi-Tech Gears&apos; Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process stay extended until April 20, 2026</li><li>NCLAT hearing adjourned to April 20, 2026</li><li>Interim stay order passed by Hon&apos;ble NCLAT on September 03, 2024</li><li>Order available on NCLAT website</li><li>Paucity of time led to the adjournment of the matter hearing</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c95dd164-6471-45cf-bd2c-e036ebb6404a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: The Hi-Tech Gears Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LAXMIMACH] LMW Ltd Receives ESG Rating from SES ESG Research Private Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LAKSHMI+MACHINE+WORKS+LTD.&title=LMW+Ltd+Receives+ESG+Rating+from+SES+ESG+Research+Private+Limited&newsId=db8a8673-b9cf-4a2b-9692-efbea9e8d560&token=ZGI4YTg2NzMtYjlj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db8a8673-b9cf-4a2b-9692-efbea9e8d560</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>LMW Ltd has received an ESG Rating from SES ESG Research Private Limited. The rating was independently prepared by SES ESG based on data available in the public domain. The company did not engage SES ESG for this rating. This disclosure is being made in accordance with Regulation 30 of SEBI(LODR) Regulations, 2015 and is also available on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>LMW Ltd receives ESG Rating from SES ESG Research Private Limited</li><li>The rating was independently prepared by SES ESG based on publicly available data</li><li>LMW Ltd did not engage SES ESG for this rating</li><li>Disclosure is being made in accordance with SEBI regulations</li><li>The information is also available on the company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9f1db951-f51d-4456-95cb-607c22354719.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LAKSHMI MACHINE WORKS LTD. | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PASHUPATI] Pashupati Cotspin Ltd. Announces Board Meeting to Consider Stock Split and Memorandum Amendment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Pashupati+Cotspin+Ltd&title=Pashupati+Cotspin+Ltd.+Announces+Board+Meeting+to+Consider+Stock+Split+and+Memorandum+Amendment&newsId=e23f127a-6a3b-4e21-b298-87f939def47f&token=ZTIzZjEyN2EtNmEz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e23f127a-6a3b-4e21-b298-87f939def47f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:59:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Split</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pashupati Cotspin Ltd. has informed the BSE that its Board of Directors will meet on February 26, 2026, to consider several matters. The agenda includes the consideration of a sub-division (split) of the company&apos;s equity shares, subject to shareholder and regulatory approvals. The proposed split would require an amendment to the company&apos;s Memorandum of Association, which will also be considered in the meeting. Any other matter with the permission of the Chair and majority of the Directors will also be discussed.</p><ul><li>Pashupati Cotspin Ltd. to hold a Board Meeting on February 26, 2026</li><li>The agenda includes the consideration of a stock split of equity shares</li><li>The proposed split is subject to shareholder and regulatory approvals</li><li>An amendment to the Memorandum of Association will be considered</li><li>The company will discuss any other matter with the permission of the Chair and majority of the Directors</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fd0f513f-0043-4624-802a-7af7bf053083.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Pashupati Cotspin Ltd | Category: Split</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>