<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:25:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[OIL] Oil India Ltd Clarifies on Recent Increase in Volume of Company&apos;s Scrip</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=OIL+INDIA+LTD.&title=Oil+India+Ltd+Clarifies+on+Recent+Increase+in+Volume+of+Company%27s+Scrip&newsId=063c72b5-f18f-475b-a243-a0185d085903&token=MDYzYzcyYjUtZjE4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">063c72b5-f18f-475b-a243-a0185d085903</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:19:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Oil India Ltd has issued a clarification regarding the increase in volume of the company&apos;s scrip in the recent past. The company stated that there is no information or announcement from their side that may have an impact on the price or volume of the scrip. However, they mentioned that the price of crude oil, which is dependent on the world market and geopolitics, has seen an increase from ~ USD 60 to ~USD 68 in the last 3 weeks, which may have an influence on the price/volume of the company’s scrip.</p><ul><li>Oil India Ltd clarifies on recent increase in volume of company&apos;s scrip</li><li>No information or announcement from the company&apos;s side affecting the scrip&apos;s price or volume</li><li>Increase in crude oil price by more than 13% in the last 3 weeks may affect the scrip&apos;s price/volume</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d3016aa7-444a-4986-b107-89928b454a88.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: OIL INDIA LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GRSE] GRSE Q3 Results: Consistent Performance &amp; Strong Numbers with 74% Y-o-Y Growth in PAT</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Garden+Reach+Shipbuilders+%26+Engineers+Ltd&title=GRSE+Q3+Results%3A+Consistent+Performance+%26+Strong+Numbers+with+74%25+Y-o-Y+Growth+in+PAT&newsId=77b3dfbd-235e-4548-b1e4-cab462a2535d&token=NzdiM2RmYmQtMjM1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77b3dfbd-235e-4548-b1e4-cab462a2535d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Garden Reach Shipbuilders &amp; Engineers Ltd. (GRSE) has announced its financial results for the third quarter &amp; nine months ended December 31, 2025. The key highlights of the financial performance include a 46% Y-o-Y growth in Total Income for Q3 FY26, 49% Y-o-Y growth in Revenue from Operation, 59% increase in EBITDA, 63% growth in PBT, and 74% growth in PAT compared to Q3 FY25. The 9MFY26 results showed a 39% growth in Total Income, 42% growth in Revenue from Operation, 53% growth in EBITDA, 56% growth in PBT, and 57% growth in PAT compared to 9MFY25. The company declared a 2nd interim dividend for the Financial Year 2025-26 @ Rs. 7.15 per equity share.</p><ul><li>GRSE reported a 46% Y-o-Y growth in Total Income for Q3 FY26.</li><li>Revenue from Operation increased by 49% Y-o-Y in Q3 FY26.</li><li>EBITDA for Q3 FY26 increased by 59% compared to Q3 FY25.</li><li>PBT for Q3 FY26 grew by 63% Y-o-Y.</li><li>PAT for Q3 FY26 registered a growth of 74% Y-o-Y.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8bb06258-ae24-4bc2-9e11-554ec1f79dbb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Garden Reach Shipbuilders & Engineers Ltd | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INFY*] Infosys and Tennis Australia Bring Al-First Experiences and Accessibility to Australian Open 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INFOSYS+LTD.&title=Infosys+and+Tennis+Australia+Bring+Al-First+Experiences+and+Accessibility+to+Australian+Open+2026&newsId=56efbb1d-72e2-43e5-99a8-89f1b9b7d6d6&token=NTZlZmJiMWQtNzJl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56efbb1d-72e2-43e5-99a8-89f1b9b7d6d6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Infosys and Tennis Australia have unveiled innovations for Australian Open 2026, powered by Infosys Topaz™. These advancements aim to redefine fan engagement, empower players and coaches, and push the boundaries of digital accessibility in tennis. The new innovations include MatchFeel, a tactile experience for visually impaired audiences, and Rally, an interactive Al mascot. The existing AO technology experiences will also have enhancements like Keys to the Match, Infosys Gen Al Stadium, and Infosys Match Centre.</p><ul><li>MatchFeel: A tactile experience for visually impaired fans</li><li>Rally: An interactive Al mascot</li><li>Keys to the Match: Al-powered feature giving fans match insights</li><li>Infosys Gen Al Stadium: An immersive experience for fans</li><li>Infosys Match Centre: Offers a suite of Al-powered experiences</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/27e25394-8d0e-4031-b825-318564ba0747.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INFOSYS LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HINDPETRO] HPCL Denies Negotiations for Venezuelan Crude Oil Procurement</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HINDUSTAN+PETROLEUM+CORPORATION+LTD.&title=HPCL+Denies+Negotiations+for+Venezuelan+Crude+Oil+Procurement&newsId=0606a3bb-e405-4762-b914-2d1260bf88bd&token=MDYwNmEzYmItZTQw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0606a3bb-e405-4762-b914-2d1260bf88bd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 04:06:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Clarification</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Hindustan Petroleum Corporation Ltd (HPCL) has denied any negotiations or events regarding the procurement of Venezuelan crude oil. The company is not aware of any unannounced information that could explain the trading movement of its scrip. There are no regulatory/legal proceedings or material impact related to the news article. HPCL believes the movement in its scrip is market-driven, attributable to general market conditions and investor sentiment.</p><ul><li>HPCL denies negotiations for Venezuelan crude oil</li><li>No unannounced information that could explain trading movement</li><li>No regulatory/legal proceedings or material impact related to the news article</li><li>Movement in HPCL&apos;s scrip believed to be market-driven</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/711540d4-51aa-4364-bf2b-a733ff2c93f3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HINDUSTAN PETROLEUM CORPORATION LTD. | Category: Clarification</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BHARTIARTL] Airtel Provides 360 Million Indians with Free Access to Adobe Express Premium</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BHARTI+AIRTEL+LTD.&title=Airtel+Provides+360+Million+Indians+with+Free+Access+to+Adobe+Express+Premium&newsId=21550165-b998-475d-bdcc-dd067ce22d80&token=MjE1NTAxNjUtYjk5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21550165-b998-475d-bdcc-dd067ce22d80</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 03:56:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Bharti Airtel, one of India’s largest telecommunication service providers, has partnered with Adobe to provide free access to Adobe Express Premium for all its 360 million customers across India. This partnership aims to empower millions of Indians with cutting-edge AI tools to create and innovate, regardless of their design experience. The Adobe Express Premium subscription, worth approximately INR 4,000, will be available for free for a year to all Airtel customers, including mobile, Wi-Fi, and DTH customers.</p><ul><li>Airtel provides free access to Adobe Express Premium for all its 360 million customers across India.</li><li>The partnership aims to empower Indians with cutting-edge AI tools to create and innovate.</li><li>Adobe Express Premium subscription worth approximately INR 4,000 is available for free for a year to all Airtel customers.</li><li>The subscription is available to all Airtel customers, including mobile, Wi-Fi, and DTH customers.</li><li>Adobe Express Premium provides access to thousands of professional design templates, Al-powered features, premium Adobe Stock assets, over 30,000 professional fonts, 100GB cloud storage, and advanced features with no watermarks.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/545450ee-0eae-4f53-9ecf-34799e22689f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BHARTI AIRTEL LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GREENPOWER] Orient Green Power Company Ltd. Signs Contract with Suzlon Energy for 6.3 MW Wind Energy Generators</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ORIENT+GREEN+POWER+COMPANY+LTD.&title=Orient+Green+Power+Company+Ltd.+Signs+Contract+with+Suzlon+Energy+for+6.3+MW+Wind+Energy+Generators&newsId=0ae3d323-f16b-41d3-9643-abba090477c8&token=MGFlM2QzMjMtZjE2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ae3d323-f16b-41d3-9643-abba090477c8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 03:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Orient Green Power Company Ltd. has signed a contract with Suzlon Energy Limited for the supply of 3 Nos Wind Energy Generators of 2.1 MW capacity each, aggregating to 6.3 MW. The contract is for re-powering an existing wind farm at Devarkulam site, Tamil Nadu. The contract value is approximately Rs. 32.87 Crores (inclusive of GST). The contract is to be executed on or before June 30, 2026.</p><ul><li>Orient Green Power Company Ltd. has signed a contract with Suzlon Energy Limited for 6.3 MW Wind Energy Generators</li><li>The contract is for re-powering an existing wind farm at Devarkulam site, Tamil Nadu</li><li>The contract value is approximately Rs. 32.87 Crores (inclusive of GST)</li><li>The contract is to be executed on or before June 30, 2026</li><li>The contract is not a related party transaction</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/648b9a91-9369-433b-86f7-a6bc40b3a46b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ORIENT GREEN POWER COMPANY LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ORGANICREC] ORSL Officially Empaneled as Execution Partner by Indraprastha Gas Limited for Joint Development of CBG Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Organic+Recycling+Systems+Ltd&title=ORSL+Officially+Empaneled+as+Execution+Partner+by+Indraprastha+Gas+Limited+for+Joint+Development+of+CBG+Projects&newsId=f278a458-f21a-4268-af4e-43223e6dfc2a&token=ZjI3OGE0NTgtZjIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f278a458-f21a-4268-af4e-43223e6dfc2a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 03:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Organic Recycling Systems Limited (ORSL) has formalized its empanelment as an execution partner with Indraprastha Gas Limited (IGL) for the joint development of Compressed Biogas (CBG) projects across India. The formalization was marked by the exchange of a non-binding Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) during India Energy Week (IEW) 2026. The partnership is expected to strengthen ORSL’s national project pipeline and accelerate project development across multiple feedstocks and geographies.</p><ul><li>ORSL officially empaneled as execution partner by Indraprastha Gas Limited for joint development of CBG projects</li><li>Formalization marked by exchange of non-binding MoU during India Energy Week 2026</li><li>Partnership expected to strengthen ORSL’s national project pipeline and accelerate project development</li><li>Collaboration across multiple feedstocks and geographies</li><li>ORSL creating a clear pathway for sustained revenue growth and long-term expansion in the Bio-CNG sector</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/df659be7-16e8-4e9b-9969-5e22ccf0f433.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Organic Recycling Systems Ltd | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LUCENT] Mobavenue AI Tech Ltd Receives In-Principle Approval for Preferential Issue of Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Lucent+Industries+Ltd&title=Mobavenue+AI+Tech+Ltd+Receives+In-Principle+Approval+for+Preferential+Issue+of+Equity+Shares&newsId=4148a72a-2518-492d-a332-af30c3c925cb&token=NDE0OGE3MmEtMjUx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4148a72a-2518-492d-a332-af30c3c925cb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 03:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mobavenue AI Tech Ltd has received in-principle approval from BSE Limited for the proposed preferential issue of equity shares. The issue involves raising of funds up to Rs. 99,99,99,296/- by way of issuance of up to 9,19,117 equity shares of face value of Rs. 10/- each at an issue price of Rs. 1,088/- per equity share. The approval is subject to compliance with various regulations and obtaining necessary approvals.</p><ul><li>Mobavenue AI Tech Ltd has received in-principle approval from BSE Limited for a proposed preferential issue of equity shares.</li><li>The preferential issue involves raising of funds aggregating up to Rs. 99,99,99,296/-.</li><li>The issue will be of up to 9,19,117 equity shares of face value of Rs. 10/- each at an issue price of Rs. 1,088/- per equity share.</li><li>The approval is subject to compliance with various regulations and obtaining necessary approvals.</li><li>The company is advised to strengthen internal controls and obtain an undertaking from the allottee(s) to avoid any non-compliances.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/465b5463-f314-4f69-bfae-28142feb24b3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Lucent Industries Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHANTIGURU] Sarthak Sanghvi and Shripal Sanghvi Acquire 3.46% Stake in Shanti Guru Industries Ltd via Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shanti+Guru+Industries+Ltd&title=Sarthak+Sanghvi+and+Shripal+Sanghvi+Acquire+3.46%25+Stake+in+Shanti+Guru+Industries+Ltd+via+Open+Market&newsId=2a357cb6-ff00-4d74-873f-a38d3224bf12&token=MmEzNTdjYjYtZmYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a357cb6-ff00-4d74-873f-a38d3224bf12</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 02:56:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sarthak Sanghvi and Shripal Sanghvi have acquired a 3.46% stake in Shanti Guru Industries Ltd through the open market. The acquisition was made in two tranches, with the first on 07-03-2025 for 12,000 shares and the second on 10-03-2025 for Rs. 12,31,00,000 divided into 1,23,10,000 shares. This acquisition increased their holding from no shares to 4,26,000 shares, representing 3.46% of the company&apos;s total voting rights.</p><ul><li>Sarthak Sanghvi and Shripal Sanghvi acquire 3.46% stake in Shanti Guru Industries Ltd</li><li>Acquisition made through open market</li><li>Two tranches of acquisition: 12,000 shares on 07-03-2025 and Rs. 12,31,00,000 on 10-03-2025</li><li>Post-acquisition holding: 4,26,000 shares representing 3.46% of the company&apos;s total voting rights</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/FB4516B9_D08B_4AC6_9313_4F3ABCD190E4_082119.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shanti Guru Industries Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ALLCARGO] ACACIA Banyan Partners Acquires 3.62% Stake in Allcargo Logistics Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ALLCARGO+LOGISTICS+LTD.&title=ACACIA+Banyan+Partners+Acquires+3.62%25+Stake+in+Allcargo+Logistics+Ltd&newsId=8745320b-9685-4637-95ff-2f9004d9e4f5&token=ODc0NTMyMGItOTY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8745320b-9685-4637-95ff-2f9004d9e4f5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 02:52:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>ACACIA Banyan Partners, along with ACACIA INSTITUTIONAL PARTNERS LP, ACACIA Il PARTNERS LP, ACACIA CONSERVATION FUND LP, and ACACIA PARTNERS LP, have acquired a 3.62% stake in Allcargo Logistics Ltd. This acquisition was made through shares carrying voting rights, and the total number of shares acquired amounts to 54189500. The shares were acquired on the open market. This acquisition is subject to the Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Take over Regulations, 2011 of Securities &amp; Exchange Board of India.</p><ul><li>ACACIA Banyan Partners acquires 3.62% stake in Allcargo Logistics Ltd</li><li>Total of 54189500 shares carrying voting rights acquired</li><li>Shares acquired through open market</li><li>Acquisition subject to Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Take over Regulations, 2011 of Securities &amp; Exchange Board of India</li><li>Allcargo Logistics Ltd share price fluctuated by 3.68% after the acquisition</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5D9FF473_C4BE_4F00_8DF4_AE4B4F01B629_081448.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ALLCARGO LOGISTICS LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>