<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:33:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[NRBBEARING] NRB Bearings Ltd Subsidiary to Acquire Aerospace Component Manufacturer for INR 27.5 Crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NRB+BEARINGS+LTD.&title=NRB+Bearings+Ltd+Subsidiary+to+Acquire+Aerospace+Component+Manufacturer+for+INR+27.5+Crore&newsId=0c37e83d-d243-4824-96ac-821a3a1307c4&token=MGMzN2U4M2QtZDI0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c37e83d-d243-4824-96ac-821a3a1307c4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>NRB Bearings Ltd announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, Mahant Tool Room Private Limited (MTRPL), has agreed to acquire the business of M/s. Mahant Tool Room (MTR), a sole proprietorship concern based out of Bangalore, engaged in the manufacturing of precision machined components for engine and fuel systems for the aerospace industry. The acquisition is subject to completion of certain conditions precedent with a cash consideration of INR 27,50,00,000. This acquisition will mark NRB Bearings Ltd&apos;s entry in the aerospace industry.</p><ul><li>NRB Bearings Ltd&apos;s subsidiary, MTRPL, to acquire MTR for INR 27.5 crore</li><li>MTR is engaged in the manufacturing of precision machined components for the aerospace industry</li><li>The acquisition is subject to completion of certain conditions precedent</li><li>MTR has an annual turnover of INR 1,88,30,000 and a confirmed order book of over INR 25 crore</li><li>This acquisition will mark NRB Bearings Ltd&apos;s entry in the aerospace industry</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e778c9db-9175-4c99-a659-53481c9a118f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NRB BEARINGS LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ALLSEC] Alldigi Tech Ltd Declares 2nd Interim Dividend of INR 30 per Share for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ALLSEC+TECHNOLOGIES+LTD.&title=Alldigi+Tech+Ltd+Declares+2nd+Interim+Dividend+of+INR+30+per+Share+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=767d36a6-a686-4f96-8f3d-c15b6284b850&token=NzY3ZDM2YTYtYTY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">767d36a6-a686-4f96-8f3d-c15b6284b850</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Alldigi Tech Ltd announced the declaration of a 2nd interim dividend of INR 30 per equity share for the financial year 2025-26. The dividend is subject to approval at the Board of Directors meeting held on January 27, 2026. The dividend payment is expected to be made on or before February 20, 2026, to the equity shareholders whose names appear on the Register of Members or in the records of the Depositories as beneficial owners as on the record date, i.e., February 04, 2026. The announcement came after the consideration of the unaudited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</p><ul><li>Alldigi Tech Ltd declares 2nd interim dividend of INR 30 per equity share for FY 2025-26</li><li>The dividend payment is expected to be made on or before February 20, 2026</li><li>The record date for the dividend payment is February 04, 2026</li><li>The announcement came after the review of unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ending December 31, 2025</li><li>The Board meeting commenced at 6:30 P.M. (IST) and concluded at 7:50 P.M. (IST)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/761f3962-488b-405a-886c-300592220e3a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ALLSEC TECHNOLOGIES LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PFOCUS] Prime Focus Ltd. Approves Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PRIME+FOCUS+LTD.&title=Prime+Focus+Ltd.+Approves+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=7466b24b-694f-40b5-9da0-663623fb2a34&token=NzQ2NmIyNGItNjk0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7466b24b-694f-40b5-9da0-663623fb2a34</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Prime Focus Limited approved the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a total income of INR 5,050.50 Lakhs for the nine months ended December 31, 2025. The results are available on the company&apos;s website and will be published in newspapers as required under the LODR Regulations.</p><ul><li>Prime Focus Ltd. approved the unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>Total income for the nine months ended December 31, 2025, is INR 5,050.50 Lakhs.</li><li>The results are available on the company&apos;s website and will be published in newspapers as required under the LODR Regulations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5619bc39-cabd-4631-a93c-ef54a406ed40.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PRIME FOCUS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ACEMEN] Ace Men Engg Works Ltd: Statutory Auditor M/s. Singh &amp; Associates Resigns</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ace+Men+Engg+Works+Ltd&title=Ace+Men+Engg+Works+Ltd%3A+Statutory+Auditor+M%2Fs.+Singh+%26+Associates+Resigns&newsId=af65d21d-e604-4149-bbc6-b67f9d8c268f&token=YWY2NWQyMWQtZTYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">af65d21d-e604-4149-bbc6-b67f9d8c268f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Auditor</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ace Men Engg Works Ltd announced the resignation of its statutory auditor, M/s. Singh &amp; Associates, due to the resignation of a key partner and acute staff constraints. The auditor was unable to allocate the necessary team strength required to ensure timely and quality completion of the audit within the stipulated timelines.</p><ul><li>M/s. Singh &amp; Associates resigns as statutory auditor of Ace Men Engg Works Ltd.</li><li>Resignation triggered by the departure of a key partner and staff shortages.</li><li>Auditor unable to complete the audit within the prescribed timelines.</li><li>Ace Men Engg Works Ltd to appoint a new auditor to avoid delays and inconvenience.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9d59c4e4-1a75-47fd-a7f2-c5e7c78d16f0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ace Men Engg Works Ltd | Category: Auditor</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NRBBEARING] NRB Bearings Acquires Aerospace Component Manufacturer Mahant Tool Room for ₹27.5 Crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NRB+BEARINGS+LTD.&title=NRB+Bearings+Acquires+Aerospace+Component+Manufacturer+Mahant+Tool+Room+for+%E2%82%B927.5+Crore&newsId=7894ff0a-c863-4746-bf6c-ed1007800d7a&token=Nzg5NGZmMGEtYzg2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7894ff0a-c863-4746-bf6c-ed1007800d7a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>NRB Bearings Limited, a leading manufacturer of bearings and friction solutions, has announced the acquisition of Mahant Tool Room (MTR), a Bengaluru-based sole proprietorship that specializes in the manufacturing of precision machined components for the aerospace industry. The acquisition, valued at ₹27.5 crore, will provide NRB with immediate scalability and revenue visibility in the aerospace sector. MTR has an order book of over ₹25 Crores and has been recognized with HAL’s Best Performance Award for technical excellence and delivery track record. This strategic entry into the aerospace segment aligns with NRB’s high growth and diversified strategy, expanding its customer base and moving closer towards its aspirational growth plan.</p><ul><li>NRB Bearings Limited has acquired Mahant Tool Room Private Limited, a sole proprietorship concern based out of Bangalore, for ₹27.5 crore.</li><li>Mahant Tool Room specializes in the manufacture of sophisticated mission-critical engine and fuel systems for the aerospace industry.</li><li>MTR has an order book of over ₹25 Crores, providing NRB with immediate scalability and revenue visibility in the aerospace sector.</li><li>As part of the transaction, Mr Mallappa, a recognized industry expert will join NRB Group and support the expansion of the aerospace business.</li><li>This acquisition marks NRB’s strategic entry into the aerospace segment, further broad-basing its business model in line with its high growth and diversified strategy.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0a7d5fe2-b419-49e8-a26d-7e04e0e32594.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NRB BEARINGS LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ALLSEC] Alldigi Tech Ltd Declares 2nd Interim Dividend of INR 30 per Share for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ALLSEC+TECHNOLOGIES+LTD.&title=Alldigi+Tech+Ltd+Declares+2nd+Interim+Dividend+of+INR+30+per+Share+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=0977a9a3-b846-4d00-9fa1-6c3e5feec3f2&token=MDk3N2E5YTMtYjg0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0977a9a3-b846-4d00-9fa1-6c3e5feec3f2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Alldigi Tech Ltd, at their meeting held on Tuesday, January 27, 2026, approved the unaudited financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The Board also declared a 2nd interim dividend of INR 30 per equity share of face value INR 10/- each for the financial year 2025-26. The dividend will be paid on or before February 20, 2026, to the equity shareholders whose names appear on the Register of Members or in the records of the Depositories as beneficial owners of the shares as on the record date, i.e., February 04, 2026.</p><ul><li>Board approves 2nd Interim Dividend of INR 30 per share for FY 2025-26</li><li>Unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025, approved</li><li>Dividend payment date set for on or before February 20, 2026</li><li>Record date for dividend payment set as February 04, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9bef6777-9323-44c2-8409-ccbe063cc6cd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ALLSEC TECHNOLOGIES LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HYUNDAI] Hyundai Motor India Ltd. to Approve Un-audited Financial Results for Q3 &amp; Nine Months of FY2025-26 on Feb 2, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Hyundai+Motor+India+Ltd&title=Hyundai+Motor+India+Ltd.+to+Approve+Un-audited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+of+FY2025-26+on+Feb+2%2C+2026&newsId=9039c314-ca0c-4bad-aad4-fda706116546&token=OTAzOWMzMTQtY2Ew</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9039c314-ca0c-4bad-aad4-fda706116546</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hyundai Motor India Ltd. has announced a Board of Directors meeting on February 2, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results (standalone and consolidated) for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting is held in compliance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. In accordance with the Company&apos;s Code of Conduct, the trading window for dealing in the shares of the company is closed for designated persons, their immediate relatives, and persons with whom such designated persons share a material financial relationship from January 1, 2026, and will remain closed for 48 hours after the declaration of the un-audited financial results.</p><ul><li>Hyundai Motor India Ltd. to approve un-audited financial results for Q3 and nine months of FY2025-26 on Feb 2, 2026</li><li>Meeting held in compliance with SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Trading window closed for designated persons, their immediate relatives, and persons with material financial relationships from Jan 1, 2026</li><li>Trading window to remain closed for 48 hours after the declaration of un-audited financial results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e84d3018-3264-4ecf-82ee-d2dd23f52765.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Hyundai Motor India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZAPPFRESH] Promoter Deepanshu Manchanda Purchases Shares of DSM Fresh Foods Ltd Worth INR 27.66%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DSM+Fresh+Foods+Ltd&title=Promoter+Deepanshu+Manchanda+Purchases+Shares+of+DSM+Fresh+Foods+Ltd+Worth+INR+27.66%25&newsId=4e4125e0-14d5-406e-8fd4-3ed54775f9f4&token=NGU0MTI1ZTAtMTRk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4e4125e0-14d5-406e-8fd4-3ed54775f9f4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pursuant to Regulation 7(2)(b) of SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, DSM Fresh Foods Ltd has received a disclosure from Mr. Deepanshu Manchanda, Promoter, regarding the purchase of equity shares of the company. The purchase was made in compliance with Form-C and the transaction details are as follows: Mr. Manchanda purchased 12,57,300 shares on 20th January 2026, 23rd January 2026, and 27th January 2026, through the BSE Limited platform. The total value of shares acquired amounts to INR 27.66%.</p><ul><li>Promoter Deepanshu Manchanda purchased shares worth INR 27.66%</li><li>Purchase made in three transactions on different dates in January 2026</li><li>Transactions executed through BSE Limited platform</li><li>DSM Fresh Foods Ltd shares purchased in compliance with Form-C</li><li>Total of 12,57,300 shares acquired by the promoter</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d9eae70a-9f4f-4e88-838a-93e6fd1a4832.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DSM Fresh Foods Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PFOCUS] Prime Focus Ltd Authorizes Key Managerial Personnel to Determine Materiality of Events or Information</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PRIME+FOCUS+LTD.&title=Prime+Focus+Ltd+Authorizes+Key+Managerial+Personnel+to+Determine+Materiality+of+Events+or+Information&newsId=f8bbee52-3c8f-4560-8ae6-d5de97576df0&token=ZjhiYmVlNTItM2M4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f8bbee52-3c8f-4560-8ae6-d5de97576df0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Prime Focus Limited has informed the Exchange about the authorization of Key Managerial Personnel to determine the materiality of an event or information and disclose the same to the Stock Exchanges. The Board of Directors has authorized Mr. Naresh Malhotra, Chairman and Whole-Time Director, Mr. Vikas Rathee, Chief Financial Officer, and Ms. Parina Shah, Company Secretary and Compliance Officer for this purpose. The contact details of these individuals and the company are provided in the document.</p><ul><li>Prime Focus Ltd has authorized Key Managerial Personnel to determine the materiality of events or information</li><li>The authorized personnel include Mr. Naresh Malhotra, Mr. Vikas Rathee, and Ms. Parina Shah</li><li>The decision was made at a Board of Directors meeting on January 27, 2026</li><li>The authorized personnel are responsible for making disclosures to the Stock Exchanges</li><li>The contact details of the authorized personnel are provided in the document</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/75e4ac5f-a9b3-4e9c-943b-376c27398f20.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PRIME FOCUS LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KTKBANK] Karnataka Bank Ltd. Re-appoints Non-Executive Independent Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KARNATAKA+BANK+LTD.&title=Karnataka+Bank+Ltd.+Re-appoints+Non-Executive+Independent+Directors&newsId=2cf32c8e-1495-4a2e-8b4b-3084ef1aeae8&token=MmNmMzJjOGUtMTQ5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2cf32c8e-1495-4a2e-8b4b-3084ef1aeae8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Karnataka Bank Ltd. has announced the re-appointment of two Non-Executive Independent Directors, Dr. DS Ravindran and Mr. Balakrishna Alse S, for a further period of three years. The re-appointment is subject to the approval of the shareholders of the Bank as per SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015 and applicable provisions of the Companies Act, 2013. The directors have not been debarred from holding the office of a Director by virtue of any order passed by the SEBI or any other such authority. The Board Meeting commenced at 10.30 AM and concluded at 08.15 PM.</p><ul><li>Re-appointment of Dr. DS Ravindran for three years</li><li>Re-appointment of Mr. Balakrishna Alse S for three years</li><li>Re-appointments subject to shareholders&apos; approval</li><li>No debarment orders against the directors</li><li>Board Meeting held on 27.01.2026 from 10.30 AM to 08.15 PM</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/de94fc7b-0feb-48c2-93fc-9149f6d6bf5c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KARNATAKA BANK LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>