<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:43:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[AADHARHFC] BCP Topco VII Pte. Ltd. Acquires Major Stake in Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Aadhar+Housing+Finance+Ltd&title=BCP+Topco+VII+Pte.+Ltd.+Acquires+Major+Stake+in+Aadhar+Housing+Finance+Ltd&newsId=26af4ac0-22d4-4c37-a7aa-45be8bc6c2e2&token=MjZhZjRhYzAtMjJk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26af4ac0-22d4-4c37-a7aa-45be8bc6c2e2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:43:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>BCP Topco VII Pte. Ltd., in concert with BCP Asia (SG) Holdings Co. Pte Ltd. and Singapore VII Holding Co. Pte. Ltd., has acquired a significant stake in Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd. The acquisition was made through an off-market sale, with the disclosure made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. The total shares acquired represent 75.19% of the total voting shares and 73.29% of the total diluted capital of the company.</p><ul><li>BCP Topco VII Pte. Ltd. acquires a significant stake in Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd.</li><li>The acquisition was made in concert with BCP Asia (SG) Holdings Co. Pte Ltd. and Singapore VII Holding Co. Pte. Ltd.</li><li>The acquisition represents 75.19% of the total voting shares and 73.29% of the total diluted capital of the company.</li><li>The acquisition was made through an off-market sale.</li><li>The disclosure was made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/EB133A6E_E861_4DD1_BEEA_2F68DFA74C5A_100801.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STEELXIND] Catalyst Trusteeship Ltd Releases Pledged Equity Shares of Steel Exchange India Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=STEEL+EXCHANGE+INDIA+LTD.&title=Catalyst+Trusteeship+Ltd+Releases+Pledged+Equity+Shares+of+Steel+Exchange+India+Ltd&newsId=186ff6d0-c52c-4a1a-b3b3-fc6f7278225d&token=MTg2ZmY2ZDAtYzUy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">186ff6d0-c52c-4a1a-b3b3-fc6f7278225d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:39:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Pledge</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Catalyst Trusteeship Ltd, acting as Debenture Trustee on behalf of Debenture Holder(s) of Vizag Profiles Private Limited, has released pledged equity shares of Steel Exchange India Ltd. The release of pledged shares was disclosed under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. The total number of shares carrying voting rights before and after the release of pledged shares remains the same at 18,61,55,375, representing 14.93% of the total voting rights.</p><ul><li>Catalyst Trusteeship Ltd releases pledged equity shares of Steel Exchange India Ltd.</li><li>The release of pledged shares was disclosed under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</li><li>The total number of shares carrying voting rights before and after the release of pledged shares remains the same at 18,61,55,375, representing 14.93% of the total voting rights.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/02A5EC23_20F0_4DC5_920B_13F02C259BD3_100406.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: STEEL EXCHANGE INDIA LTD. | Category: Pledge</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GOKUL] Arjunsinh Rajput Acquires 0.025% Stake in Gokul Refoils &amp; Solvent Ltd via Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GOKUL+REFOILS+%26+SOLVENT+LTD.&title=Arjunsinh+Rajput+Acquires+0.025%25+Stake+in+Gokul+Refoils+%26+Solvent+Ltd+via+Open+Market&newsId=8cbe517e-35b3-47fd-bc1b-a592c8cf0e9f&token=OGNiZTUxN2UtMzVi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8cbe517e-35b3-47fd-bc1b-a592c8cf0e9f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:38:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Arjunsinh Rajput, along with Persons Acquirer (PAC), has acquired 25,000 shares of Gokul Refoils &amp; Solvent Ltd on February 25, 2026, through the open market. This acquisition has increased their collective stake to 1.27% from the previous 1.25%. The total equity share capital of the company remains unchanged at Rs.19,79,90,000 divided into 9,89,95,000 equity shares of Rs. 2/- each.</p><ul><li>Arjunsinh Rajput and PAC acquired 25,000 shares of Gokul Refoils &amp; Solvent Ltd on February 25, 2026.</li><li>The acquisition was made through the open market.</li><li>This increased their collective stake from 1.25% to 1.27%.</li><li>The total equity share capital of the company remains unchanged at Rs.19,79,90,000 divided into 9,89,95,000 equity shares of Rs. 2/- each.</li><li>Arjunsinh Rajput, Balvantsinh Chandansinh Rajput, Bhikhiben Balvantsinh Rajput, Dharmendrasinh Balvantsinh Rajput, Profitline Securities Pvt. Ltd., and M/s. BSELtd. are the acquirers.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9BA61775_F732_46F6_94C9_9A9B36A88156_100615.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GOKUL REFOILS & SOLVENT LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HRMNYCP] Ascentedge Advisors LLP Sells 2,00,000 Shares of Harmony Capital Service Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HARMONY+CAPITAL+SERVICES+LTD.&title=Ascentedge+Advisors+LLP+Sells+2%2C00%2C000+Shares+of+Harmony+Capital+Service+Ltd&newsId=b4f19692-8cec-49f4-815d-8381d71e819b&token=YjRmMTk2OTItOGNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4f19692-8cec-49f4-815d-8381d71e819b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:35:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Sale</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ascentedge Advisors LLP has sold 2,00,000 shares of Harmony Capital Service Ltd, reducing their holding from 3,50,000 to 1,50,000 shares, as per a disclosure made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. The sale represents approximately 11.66% of the total voting rights and capital of the target company.</p><ul><li>Ascentedge Advisors LLP sells 2,00,000 shares of Harmony Capital Service Ltd</li><li>Pre-sale holding was 3,50,000 shares, post-sale holding is 1,50,000 shares</li><li>Sale represents approximately 11.66% of the total voting rights and capital</li><li>Harmony Capital Service Ltd shares are listed on BSE Limited</li><li>No warrants, convertible securities or encumbrances were reported in this transaction</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ADE5D8C3_ED51_4A53_9D88_FD8A0C76A7E0_095133.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HARMONY CAPITAL SERVICES LTD. | Category: Sale</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDSWFTLAB] Essix Biosciences Acquires 51 Lakh Shares of Ind-Swift Laboratories via Fully Convertible Warrants</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IND-SWIFT+LABORATORIES+LTD.&title=Essix+Biosciences+Acquires+51+Lakh+Shares+of+Ind-Swift+Laboratories+via+Fully+Convertible+Warrants&newsId=ed29aee3-2992-4e78-8c48-839c1b16ee77&token=ZWQyOWFlZTMtMjk5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed29aee3-2992-4e78-8c48-839c1b16ee77</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:32:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Essix Biosciences Limited, on behalf of the promoter and promoter group of Ind-Swift Laboratories Limited, has acquired 51,00,000 Equity Shares of Ind-Swift Laboratories on February 24, 2026. The acquisition was made pursuant to the conversion of Fully Convertible Warrants into Equity Shares. The total voting rights of Essix Biosciences Limited now stands at 40.05% post-acquisition.</p><ul><li>Essix Biosciences acquires 51 Lakh shares of Ind-Swift Laboratories</li><li>Acquisition made pursuant to the conversion of Fully Convertible Warrants into Equity Shares</li><li>Essix Biosciences&apos; voting rights stand at 40.05% post-acquisition</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/D60BA1D1_B629_4615_A37D_43E065176565_100037.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IND-SWIFT LABORATORIES LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JUSTO] Promoter Puspamitra Das Acquires 5,000 Equity Shares of Justo Realfintech Ltd Through Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Justo+Realfintech+Ltd&title=Promoter+Puspamitra+Das+Acquires+5%2C000+Equity+Shares+of+Justo+Realfintech+Ltd+Through+Open+Market&newsId=2bd44995-b610-44f7-a487-e0abe9d2ad35&token=MmJkNDQ5OTUtYjYx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2bd44995-b610-44f7-a487-e0abe9d2ad35</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Puspamitra Das, a promoter of Justo Realfintech Ltd, has acquired 5,000 equity shares of the company through the open market. This acquisition is in line with the SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. The total share capital of the company remains unchanged at INR 18,79,81,420 consisting of 1,87,98,142 Equity Shares of Rs. 10 each. This acquisition increases the promoter&apos;s stake to 39.26% from 39.24%.</p><ul><li>Puspamitra Das, a promoter of Justo Realfintech Ltd, has acquired 5,000 equity shares of the company.</li><li>The acquisition was made through the open market.</li><li>The total share capital of the company remains unchanged at INR 18,79,81,420 consisting of 1,87,98,142 Equity Shares of Rs. 10 each.</li><li>This acquisition increases the promoter&apos;s stake to 39.26% from 39.24%.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/F2593447_DC56_40CE_B2F3_9D661B908575_095726.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Justo Realfintech Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VIPUL] Vipul Limited Allots 8,89,00,000 Fully Convertible Warrants on Preferential Basis</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VIPUL+LTD.&title=Vipul+Limited+Allots+8%2C89%2C00%2C000+Fully+Convertible+Warrants+on+Preferential+Basis&newsId=4dd4aeea-07e4-4c96-a676-de5c6df3d454&token=NGRkNGFlZWEtMDdl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4dd4aeea-07e4-4c96-a676-de5c6df3d454</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:28:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Vipul Limited has allotted 8,89,00,000 Fully Convertible Warrants on a preferential basis to various allottees, including Promoter &amp; Promoter Group and Public categories. The warrants were issued at a price of Rs. 9.20/- per Warrant, amounting to a total of Rs.81,78,80,000/-. The allottees include individuals and entities such as Punit Beriwala, Om Aggarwal, Karnica Gupta, Blma Pay Technology Private Limited, Kapil Agrawal, Gourav Kumar, Manju Rani, Sourav Gupta, Ashok Kumar, Pinki Gupta, KSJ Estates Private Limited, Pine Emergence LLP, Vinita Jain, Pramod Kumar Jain, Aryaman Jain, and Renu Goyal. This allotment does not affect the Un-diluted Paid-up Equity Share Capital of the Company, which remains at Rs.14,09,59,480/- comprising of 14,09,59,480 Equity Shares of face value of Re. 1/- each.</p><ul><li>Vipul Limited allots 8,89,00,000 Fully Convertible Warrants on preferential basis</li><li>Warrants issued at a price of Rs. 9.20/- per Warrant</li><li>Total amount payable towards subscription of the warrants is Rs.81,78,80,000/-</li><li>Allottees include Promoter &amp; Promoter Group and Public categories</li><li>Un-diluted Paid-up Equity Share Capital of the Company remains unaffected</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c10ad888-b230-4883-a52c-74d757c7fe95.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VIPUL LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HRMNYCP] Harmony Capital Service Ltd: Nyra Business Development LLP Acquires 11.66% Shares via Open Offer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HARMONY+CAPITAL+SERVICES+LTD.&title=Harmony+Capital+Service+Ltd%3A+Nyra+Business+Development+LLP+Acquires+11.66%25+Shares+via+Open+Offer&newsId=116d0a0f-0e8e-442b-9571-015fa5ac1ab4&token=MTE2ZDBhMGYtMGU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">116d0a0f-0e8e-442b-9571-015fa5ac1ab4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Nyra Business Development LLP has acquired 11.66% shares of Harmony Capital Service Ltd through an open offer, as per the disclosure under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. The transaction involved 3,50,000 shares carrying voting rights, and the total diluted share/voting capital of the TC after the acquisition is 30,00,900 Equity Shares.</p><ul><li>Nyra Business Development LLP acquires 11.66% shares of Harmony Capital Service Ltd</li><li>The acquisition involves 3,50,000 shares carrying voting rights</li><li>The total diluted share/voting capital of the TC after the acquisition is 30,00,900 Equity Shares</li><li>The transaction is disclosed under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011</li><li>The mode of sale is an open offer</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8435F52B_3505_4C38_88CC_9576B3C0E39C_095353.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HARMONY CAPITAL SERVICES LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LATIMMETAL] La Tim Lifestyle &amp; Resorts Acquires La Tim Metal &amp; Industries Shares Through Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=La+Tim+Metal+%26+Industries+Ltd&title=La+Tim+Lifestyle+%26+Resorts+Acquires+La+Tim+Metal+%26+Industries+Shares+Through+Open+Market&newsId=8fac5e60-de5b-4b29-b327-832c575fa49a&token=OGZhYzVlNjAtZGU1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8fac5e60-de5b-4b29-b327-832c575fa49a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:18:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>La Tim Lifestyle &amp; Resorts Limited, a promoter and promoter group of La Tim Metal &amp; Industries Limited, has acquired shares of La Tim Metal &amp; Industries Limited through the open market. The acquisition was made on 26th February 2026. The total shares acquired by La Tim Lifestyle &amp; Resorts Limited are 5,71,600, which is 13.06% of the total diluted share/voting capital of La Tim Metal &amp; Industries Limited.</p><ul><li>La Tim Lifestyle &amp; Resorts Limited, a promoter and promoter group of La Tim Metal &amp; Industries Limited, has acquired shares of La Tim Metal &amp; Industries Limited.</li><li>The acquisition was made through the open market on 26th February 2026.</li><li>The total shares acquired by La Tim Lifestyle &amp; Resorts Limited are 5,71,600, which is 13.06% of the total diluted share/voting capital of La Tim Metal &amp; Industries Limited.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8C7C7C5F_E471_4AF4_B2D1_DB824A02969D_094015.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: La Tim Metal & Industries Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CUPID] Aditya Kumar Halwasiya Acquires 0.08% Stake in Cupid Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CUPID+LTD.-%24&title=Aditya+Kumar+Halwasiya+Acquires+0.08%25+Stake+in+Cupid+Limited&newsId=0746b6a6-9fa2-45d6-815f-911bee461124&token=MDc0NmI2YTYtOWZh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0746b6a6-9fa2-45d6-815f-911bee461124</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 04:18:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>According to a disclosure made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011, Aditya Kumar Halwasiya has acquired 2,27,000 equity shares of Cupid Limited, a company listed on BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange Limited. This acquisition represents 0.08% of the total voting rights of the company. The total voting rights of the company before the acquisition was 45.71% and after the acquisition, it stands at 45.79%. The acquisition was made through the open market on Thursday, February 26, 2026. The equity share capital of the company before the acquisition was Rs.26,89,32,140 divided into 26,89,32,140 Equity Shares of Re. 1/- each and after the acquisition, it is Rs.26,94,00,000 divided into 26,94,00,000 Equity Shares of Re. 1/- each.</p><ul><li>Aditya Kumar Halwasiya acquires 0.08% stake in Cupid Limited</li><li>The acquisition was made through the open market</li><li>The total voting rights of the company before the acquisition was 45.71%</li><li>After the acquisition, the total voting rights of the company stands at 45.79%</li><li>The equity share capital of the company has been altered post-acquisition</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9B8D3C96_F8C6_499C_B0A4_8C85217C20D6_094656.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CUPID LTD.-$ | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>