<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 04:50:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[TIRUFOAM] Tirupati Foam Ltd: Transmission of Shares from Smt Kamla Mehta to Mr Takhatmal Mehta</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Tirupati+Foam+Ltd&title=Tirupati+Foam+Ltd%3A+Transmission+of+Shares+from+Smt+Kamla+Mehta+to+Mr+Takhatmal+Mehta&newsId=b0758465-3ea0-43a6-b0d8-b7b5d7584e97&token=YjA3NTg0NjUtM2Vh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b0758465-3ea0-43a6-b0d8-b7b5d7584e97</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 04:43:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tirupati Foam Ltd has informed about the transmission of shares of Smt Kamla Mehta, a part of the Promoter Group, to her husband Mr Takhatmal Mehta. This transmission is due to the sad demise of Smt Kamla Mehta and is in compliance with the SEBI LODR Regulations 2015. The shares have been transferred from Smt Kamla Mehta to Mr Takhatmal Mehta, who is now a part of the Promoter Individual Group with a 0.17% shareholding.</p><ul><li>Smt Kamla Mehta, a part of the Promoter Group, has ceased to be a part of the promoter and promoter group of Tirupati Foam Ltd.</li><li>Smt Kamla Mehta&apos;s shares have been transmitted to her husband Mr Takhatmal Mehta.</li><li>Mr Takhatmal Mehta is now a part of the Promoter Individual Group with a 0.17% shareholding.</li><li>The transmission is in compliance with the SEBI LODR Regulations 2015.</li><li>The date of transmission is 17.02.2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/75aa63f1-0399-44a3-9567-3afe9da29b41.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Tirupati Foam Ltd | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[7TEC] Saven Technologies Declares Interim Dividend FY 2025-26 of Rs.1.50 Per Share</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SAVEN+TECHNOLOGIES+LTD.&title=Saven+Technologies+Declares+Interim+Dividend+FY+2025-26+of+Rs.1.50+Per+Share&newsId=2d16fa7a-0296-4a80-b442-e8cce50722d1&token=MmQxNmZhN2EtMDI5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2d16fa7a-0296-4a80-b442-e8cce50722d1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 04:39:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Saven Technologies Ltd. has declared an interim dividend of Rs.1.50 per equity share for the Financial Year 2025-26. The record date for determining the eligibility of shareholders for the payment of interim dividend is 16th February, 2026. The dividend shall be paid to eligible shareholders on or before 7th March, 2026. The company will deduct tax at source (TDS) at the time of making the payment of the said Dividend. The withholding tax rate would vary depending on the residential status, category of the shareholder and is subject to provision of requisite declarations / documents to the Company. The last date to provide the documents /information is 16th February, 2026.</p><ul><li>Saven Technologies has declared an interim dividend of Rs.1.50 per equity share for the Financial Year 2025-26.</li><li>The record date for determining the eligibility of shareholders for the payment of interim dividend is 16th February, 2026.</li><li>The dividend shall be paid to eligible shareholders on or before 7th March, 2026.</li><li>The company will deduct tax at source (TDS) at the time of making the payment of the said Dividend.</li><li>The last date to provide the documents /information is 16th February, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/349d20fa-00bb-41d3-9251-c6267874277a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SAVEN TECHNOLOGIES LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TRISHAKT] Shalini Jhawar Acquires 1,600 Shares of Trishakti Industries Ltd via Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TRISHAKTI+ELECTRONICS+%26+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Shalini+Jhawar+Acquires+1%2C600+Shares+of+Trishakti+Industries+Ltd+via+Open+Market&newsId=2a114b47-c2dd-4eba-8019-2605c4bed50b&token=MmExMTRiNDctYzJk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a114b47-c2dd-4eba-8019-2605c4bed50b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 04:34:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shalini Jhawar has acquired 1,600 shares of Trishakti Industries Ltd through the open market, according to a disclosure made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. This acquisition represents 0.01% of the total diluted share capital of Trishakti Industries Ltd.</p><ul><li>Shalini Jhawar acquires 1,600 shares of Trishakti Industries Ltd.</li><li>Acquisition represents 0.01% of the total diluted share capital.</li><li>Shares were acquired through the open market.</li><li>Trishakti Industries Ltd shares are listed on BSE and CSE.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/106FD71B_0FE0_4F3D_80D2_CE47C88F551C_094701.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TRISHAKTI ELECTRONICS & INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RGF] Nishad Jitendra Shah Acquires 2.95% Stake in RGF Capital Markets Ltd via Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RGF+Capital+Markets+Ltd&title=Nishad+Jitendra+Shah+Acquires+2.95%25+Stake+in+RGF+Capital+Markets+Ltd+via+Open+Market&newsId=54cd3eae-cbcf-4c0b-b9af-e1764e5afcf6&token=NTRjZDNlYWUtY2Jj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54cd3eae-cbcf-4c0b-b9af-e1764e5afcf6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 04:28:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Nishad Jitendra Shah has acquired 44,27,548 shares carrying voting rights of RGF Capital Markets Ltd, amounting to 2.95% of the total voting rights. The acquisition was made via the open market. The total equity share capital and total voting capital of the company remains unchanged at Rs. 15,00,24,000/- (15,00,24,000) Equity shares of Re.1/- each, both before and after the acquisition.</p><ul><li>Nishad Jitendra Shah acquires 2.95% stake in RGF Capital Markets Ltd</li><li>Acquisition made via open market</li><li>44,27,548 shares carrying voting rights acquired</li><li>No change in the total equity share capital and total voting capital of the company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7409E948_C217_46F8_8F19_EECA5B04BB7C_095540.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RGF Capital Markets Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MRO-TEK] Umiya Holding Pvt Ltd Acquires 38.06% Stake in Umiya Buildcon Ltd Through Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MRO-TEK+Realty+Ltd&title=Umiya+Holding+Pvt+Ltd+Acquires+38.06%25+Stake+in+Umiya+Buildcon+Ltd+Through+Open+Market&newsId=b3da84e6-8125-4913-a741-821f185c368d&token=YjNkYTg0ZTYtODEy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3da84e6-8125-4913-a741-821f185c368d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 04:23:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Umiya Holding Pvt Ltd, a non-promoter entity, has acquired a significant stake in Umiya Buildcon Ltd (formerly MRO-TEK Realty Limited) through the open market. The acquisition was made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. The total voting rights of Umiya Buildcon Ltd stand at 1,86,84,602 shares before and after the acquisition. The total diluted share/voting capital of Umiya Buildcon Ltd after the acquisition is 1:80,84,602. The acquisition was made by Aniruddha Bhanuprasad Mehta, Director of Umiya Holding Pvt Ltd.</p><ul><li>Umiya Holding Pvt Ltd acquires 38.06% stake in Umiya Buildcon Ltd</li><li>Acquisition made under SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011</li><li>Acquirer is a non-promoter entity</li><li>Total voting rights of Umiya Buildcon Ltd stand at 1,86,84,602 shares before and after the acquisition</li><li>Acquisition made through open market</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/D248AD1B_EC95_4209_B60F_B5DBBC0A69E2_094607.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MRO-TEK Realty Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FIRSTCRY] ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund Acquires 2,00,210 Shares of Brainbees Solutions Ltd, Exceeding 5% Shareholding</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Brainbees+Solutions+Ltd&title=ICICI+Prudential+Mutual+Fund+Acquires+2%2C00%2C210+Shares+of+Brainbees+Solutions+Ltd%2C+Exceeding+5%25+Shareholding&newsId=7bb7973f-edd1-4739-ac50-2188169b0eaf&token=N2JiNzk3M2YtZWRk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7bb7973f-edd1-4739-ac50-2188169b0eaf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 04:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund has acquired 2,00,210 shares of Brainbees Solutions Ltd on February 16, 2026, which has resulted in the Fund&apos;s shareholding exceeding 5% of the paid-up capital of the Company. This acquisition is from an investment perspective and not with the objective of seeking any controlling interest. The Fund holds these shares under various schemes listed on the BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange of India Limited.</p><ul><li>ICICI Prudential Mutual Fund has acquired 2,00,210 shares of Brainbees Solutions Ltd.</li><li>The acquisition has resulted in the Fund&apos;s shareholding exceeding 5% of the paid-up capital of the Company.</li><li>The acquisition is from an investment perspective and not with the objective of seeking any controlling interest.</li><li>The Fund holds these shares under various schemes listed on the BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange of India Limited.</li><li>The total voting capital of Brainbees Solutions Ltd after the acquisition is 1,04,40,83,968 comprising of 52,20,41,984 shares of face value %2/- each.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0FBD1ABD_01BF_49DA_BF01_B38AA56C62D8_095110.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Brainbees Solutions Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GBLOGISTIC] Rajasthan Global Securities Acquires 1.62% Shares in GB Logistics Commerce Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GB+Logistics+Commerce+Ltd&title=Rajasthan+Global+Securities+Acquires+1.62%25+Shares+in+GB+Logistics+Commerce+Ltd&newsId=77b66dff-5284-44cc-a770-ca1c2c922c8e&token=NzdiNjZkZmYtNTI4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77b66dff-5284-44cc-a770-ca1c2c922c8e</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 04:21:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rajasthan Global Securities Pvt Ltd has acquired 1,33,200 shares of GB Logistics Commerce Ltd, which amounts to 1.62% of the company&apos;s total voting rights. This acquisition was made through a disclosure under Regulation 29(1) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. The shares were acquired through a specified mode, but the exact method is not mentioned in the text. The acquisition date and the date of receipt of intimation are also not provided in the text.</p><ul><li>Rajasthan Global Securities Pvt Ltd acquires 1.62% shares in GB Logistics Commerce Ltd</li><li>The acquisition was made through a disclosure under Regulation 29(1) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011</li><li>The total number of shares acquired is 1,33,200</li><li>The acquisition does not involve any encumbrance or voting rights otherwise than by equity shares</li><li>The exact mode of acquisition and the dates are not provided in the text</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/DED8C7F2_0CC9_4042_A907_CDA8F199041A_094921.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GB Logistics Commerce Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VARDMNPOLY] Pine Oak Global Fund Acquires 2.18% Stake in Vardhman Polytex Ltd from Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VARDHMAN+POLYTEX+LTD.&title=Pine+Oak+Global+Fund+Acquires+2.18%25+Stake+in+Vardhman+Polytex+Ltd+from+Open+Market&newsId=09157773-f181-4d82-973d-6175db4de246&token=MDkxNTc3NzMtZjE4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09157773-f181-4d82-973d-6175db4de246</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 04:19:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pine Oak Global Fund has acquired 1,00,00,000 shares of Vardhman Polytex Ltd from the open market, which amounts to 2.18% of the company&apos;s total shares and 1.97% of the total voting rights. This acquisition has increased Pine Oak Global Fund&apos;s total holding to 3.32% of the company&apos;s total shares and 3.00% of the total voting rights.</p><ul><li>Pine Oak Global Fund has acquired 1,00,00,000 shares of Vardhman Polytex Ltd from the open market.</li><li>This acquisition amounts to 2.18% of the company&apos;s total shares and 1.97% of the total voting rights.</li><li>Pine Oak Global Fund&apos;s total holding has increased to 3.32% of the company&apos;s total shares and 3.00% of the total voting rights.</li><li>The acquisition was made on 16.02.2026.</li><li>Vardhman Polytex Ltd has a total equity share capital of Rs. 45,88,94,004/- and a total voting capital of 45,88,94,004 Equity shares of Re. 1 each.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/127C9734_2B49_4CA0_B5A8_231E7836730B_094424.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VARDHMAN POLYTEX LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SPORTKING] Anil Kumar Goel Acquires Shares in Sportking India Ltd: SEBI Disclosure</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sportking+India+Ltd&title=Anil+Kumar+Goel+Acquires+Shares+in+Sportking+India+Ltd%3A+SEBI+Disclosure&newsId=7d8bba41-bf3a-4c9c-af30-e5d04b9b99be&token=N2Q4YmJhNDEtYmYz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7d8bba41-bf3a-4c9c-af30-e5d04b9b99be</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 04:16:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Anil Kumar Goel has acquired equity shares in Sportking India Ltd, as per a disclosure made under Regulation 29(1) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. The acquisition was made through open market purchases, as detailed in the disclosure. The total voting capital of the company remains unchanged at Rs. 12,70,72,000 consisting of 12,70,72,000 equity shares of face value of Rs. 1 (one) each fully paid, both before and after the acquisition.</p><ul><li>Anil Kumar Goel acquires shares in Sportking India Ltd</li><li>Acquisition made through open market purchases</li><li>Total voting capital of the company remains unchanged</li><li>Acquirer does not belong to the Promoter/Promoter group</li><li>Acquisition details submitted under Regulation 29(1) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4B679ADC_8606_42B3_8980_6779CA158A00_093908.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sportking India Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PMCFIN] Stellant Securities Acquires 7.98% Fully Diluted Post-Issue Paid-Up Equity Share Capital of PMC Fincorp Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PMC+Fincorp+Limited&title=Stellant+Securities+Acquires+7.98%25+Fully+Diluted+Post-Issue+Paid-Up+Equity+Share+Capital+of+PMC+Fincorp+Limited&newsId=d54d6709-386e-4323-b7a8-54c9c146be4d&token=ZDU0ZDY3MDktMzg2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d54d6709-386e-4323-b7a8-54c9c146be4d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 04:14:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Stellant Securities (India) Limited and Mr. Subhash Phootarmal Rathod, as Person Acting in Concert, have acquired 2,00,00,000 and 4,40,00,000 Fully Convertible Warrants respectively. This represents 7.98% of the fully diluted post-issue paid-up equity share capital of PMC Fincorp Limited. The acquisition was made on February 17, 2026, pursuant to a preferential allotment by the Target Company.</p><ul><li>Stellant Securities and Mr. Subhash Phootarmal Rathod have acquired 2,00,00,000 and 4,40,00,000 Fully Convertible Warrants respectively.</li><li>The acquisition represents 7.98% of the fully diluted post-issue paid-up equity share capital of PMC Fincorp Limited.</li><li>The acquisition was made on February 17, 2026.</li><li>The acquisition was pursuant to a preferential allotment by PMC Fincorp Limited.</li><li>The total diluted share/voting capital of the TC after the said acquisition is INR 8,02,08,16,000/- comprising of 80,20,81,600 Equity Shares of INR 1/- each.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/48A12807_7CF6_413C_8510_C89F4CFF508A_094138.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PMC Fincorp Limited | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>