<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:38:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SEQUENT] Viyash Scientific Ltd Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025, Approves New ESOP Scheme, and Changes in Senior Management</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SEQUENT+SCIENTIFIC+LTD.&title=Viyash+Scientific+Ltd+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Approves+New+ESOP+Scheme%2C+and+Changes+in+Senior+Management&newsId=db22c5f4-d24e-4464-899e-dc5bd58183cb&token=ZGIyMmM1ZjQtZDI0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db22c5f4-d24e-4464-899e-dc5bd58183cb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:37:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Viyash Scientific Ltd announced the outcome of its Board Meeting held on February 05, 2026. The company reported its Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The Board also approved the introduction and adoption of a new employee stock option scheme, &apos;Viyash Scientific Limited Employee Stock Option Scheme 2026&apos; (VSL ESOP Scheme 2026), subject to necessary approvals. Additionally, the Board approved changes in the Senior Management Personnel (SMP) of the company, aligning with post-merger strategic objectives and operational requirements.</p><ul><li>Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025, approved</li><li>Introduction and adoption of new employee stock option scheme, &apos;Viyash Scientific Limited Employee Stock Option Scheme 2026&apos; (VSL ESOP Scheme 2026), approved</li><li>Changes in Senior Management Personnel (SMP) of the company approved</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/81023014-d34b-4a81-9acf-854511a20210.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SEQUENT SCIENTIFIC LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EBGNG] GNG Electronics Reports 102.8% YoY Rise in Q3 FY26 PAT to INR 38.7 Cr</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GNG+Electronics+Ltd&title=GNG+Electronics+Reports+102.8%25+YoY+Rise+in+Q3+FY26+PAT+to+INR+38.7+Cr&newsId=cc9e8f24-25ec-43ea-8174-89a4b9339f65&token=Y2M5ZThmMjQtMjVl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cc9e8f24-25ec-43ea-8174-89a4b9339f65</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>GNG Electronics Limited, India’s largest refurbisher of laptops and desktops, has announced its un-audited financial results for the quarter and the Nine Months ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a 40.3% YoY increase in revenue from operations to INR 487.2 Cr, a 70.5% YoY increase in EBITDA to INR 54.6 Cr, and a 102.8% YoY increase in PAT to INR 38.7 Cr. The company&apos;s EBITDA margin stood at 11.2% and PAT margin at 7.9%.</p><ul><li>Revenue up by 40.3% YoY to INR 487.2 Cr</li><li>EBITDA up by 70.5% YoY to INR 54.6 Cr</li><li>PAT up by 102.8% YoY to INR 38.7 Cr</li><li>EBITDA margin at 11.2%</li><li>PAT margin at 7.9%</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e004a4c8-7ad5-476f-8d92-8107f0fdf24f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GNG Electronics Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[THOMASCOOK] Thomas Cook (India) Ltd Approves Vesting of 46,196 Stock Options Under ESOP 2018 - Execom</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=THOMAS+COOK+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Thomas+Cook+%28India%29+Ltd+Approves+Vesting+of+46%2C196+Stock+Options+Under+ESOP+2018+-+Execom&newsId=13900d87-29c3-4d7b-8720-536b5d8464f9&token=MTM5MDBkODctMjlj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13900d87-29c3-4d7b-8720-536b5d8464f9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:32:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>ESOP</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Thomas Cook (India) Ltd has approved the vesting of 46,196 stock options under the Thomas Cook Employees Stock Option Scheme 2018 - Execom (ESOP 2018 - Execom). The options were granted at an exercise price of Re 1/- per stock option and are exercisable within a period of 20 years from vesting. The ESOP 2018 - Execom is in compliance with the SEBI (Share Based Employee Benefits and Sweat Equity) Regulations, 2021. Upon exercise of the vested options, 46,196 Equity Shares of the Company will be transferred from Thomas Cook (India) Limited ESOP Trust to the eligible employee(s) subject to the approval of the Nomination and Remuneration Committee.</p><ul><li>Thomas Cook (India) Ltd approves vesting of 46,196 stock options under ESOP 2018 - Execom.</li><li>Options granted at an exercise price of Re 1/- per stock option.</li><li>Options are exercisable within a period of 20 years from vesting.</li><li>ESOP 2018 - Execom is in compliance with the SEBI (Share Based Employee Benefits and Sweat Equity) Regulations, 2021.</li><li>Upon exercise of the vested options, 46,196 Equity Shares of the Company will be transferred to the eligible employee(s).</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d92a9bf3-9287-491a-8f18-438064384b21.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: THOMAS COOK (INDIA) LTD. | Category: ESOP</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SKFINDIA] SKF India Ltd Appoints M/s. Samdani and Co. as Tax and GST Auditors for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SKF+India+Ltd&title=SKF+India+Ltd+Appoints+M%2Fs.+Samdani+and+Co.+as+Tax+and+GST+Auditors+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=0279e6e9-7ca5-42c8-8e81-62aa23a3839d&token=MDI3OWU2ZTktN2Nh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0279e6e9-7ca5-42c8-8e81-62aa23a3839d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:31:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SKF India Ltd has appointed M/s. Samdani and Co., Chartered Accountants as Tax and GST Auditors for the financial year 2025-26. The appointment was made at the board meeting held on 05th February 2026, based on the recommendation of the Audit Committee. The firm, formed in 2016, provides audit and litigation services and helps businesses increase their efficiency and reduce finance cost.</p><ul><li>SKF India Ltd appoints M/s. Samdani and Co. as Tax and GST Auditors for FY 2025-26</li><li>Appointment made at the board meeting held on 05th February 2026</li><li>Samdani and Co. provides audit and litigation services</li><li>Formed in 2016, the firm helps businesses increase their efficiency and reduce finance cost</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6f9a0dda-4ef9-43b0-94bd-e50408bce4b5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SKF India Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NUTRA] Nutraplus India Ltd: Q3 FY2025 Financial Results Delayed Due to Non-Compliance with Listing Regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Nutraplus+India+Ltd&title=Nutraplus+India+Ltd%3A+Q3+FY2025+Financial+Results+Delayed+Due+to+Non-Compliance+with+Listing+Regulations&newsId=4695a5ea-3ded-4a03-b4c0-eed5f647424a&token=NDY5NWE1ZWEtM2Rl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4695a5ea-3ded-4a03-b4c0-eed5f647424a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Nutraplus India Ltd, a company involved in Active Pharmaceutical Ingredient (API) operations, announced its unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter ended September 30, 2025, and year-to-date period from April 1, 2025, to September 30, 2025. The results were approved by the Board of Directors and Audit Committee in a meeting on October 25, 2025. However, the company did not comply with the listing requirements under the Companies Act, 2013, and the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, causing delays in submitting the limited review report and quarterly results within the prescribed timelines. The company&apos;s property, plant, and equipment were lost under the SARFAESI Act, 2002, as it was declared a Non-Performing Asset in FY-2019-20, with the auction process delayed due to the COVID-19 pandemic. The company&apos;s net profit for the period shows a loss.</p><ul><li>Nutraplus India Ltd announced its Q3 FY2025 and year-to-date financial results.</li><li>The results were approved by the Board of Directors and Audit Committee on October 25, 2025.</li><li>The company did not comply with listing requirements, causing delays in submitting the limited review report and quarterly results.</li><li>Property, plant, and equipment lost under the SARFAESI Act, 2002 due to being declared a Non-Performing Asset.</li><li>The company reported a net loss for the period.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8c4aa287-cfab-422f-a00f-2c54e358625f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Nutraplus India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ALKALI] Alkali Metals Ltd to Approve Un-Audited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months of FY2025-2026 on 14th February 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ALKALI+METALS+LTD.&title=Alkali+Metals+Ltd+to+Approve+Un-Audited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+of+FY2025-2026+on+14th+February+2026&newsId=90e97369-2b6e-40f7-b3ae-69ad98175a66&token=OTBlOTczNjktMmI2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90e97369-2b6e-40f7-b3ae-69ad98175a66</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Alkali Metals Ltd has announced a Board of Directors meeting on 14th February 2026. The agenda includes the consideration and approval of the Un-Audited Financial Results for the Third Quarter and Nine Months ended on 31st December 2025. This meeting is in compliance with regulation 29 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Alkali Metals Ltd scheduled a Board of Directors meeting on 14th February 2026</li><li>The meeting aims to consider and approve the Un-Audited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months of FY2025-2026</li><li>The meeting is in accordance with regulation 29 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d7bfb60c-5a33-4d9f-8ef3-3fe956f3b1a7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ALKALI METALS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PWL] PhysicsWallah Maintains Market Stronghold with PAT-Positive Q3 and 9M; Surpasses Full FY25 Revenue in 9M FY26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Physicswallah+Ltd&title=PhysicsWallah+Maintains+Market+Stronghold+with+PAT-Positive+Q3+and+9M%3B+Surpasses+Full+FY25+Revenue+in+9M+FY26&newsId=9985a1e9-2443-44a6-86fd-fe5104bb750f&token=OTk4NWExZTktMjQ0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9985a1e9-2443-44a6-86fd-fe5104bb750f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:24:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>PhysicsWallah Limited, a leading tech-enabled education company, announced its financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company surpassed its full FY25 revenue within nine months of FY26, demonstrating another PAT-positive quarter with profits of ₹1,023 Mn and revenue from operations growing 34% YoY to ₹210,824 Mn. The online business continued to gain strong traction with over 3.96 million enrollments in 9M FY26, a 20% increase compared to 9M FY25. Offline enrollments grew by 36% YoY in 9M FY26. Key metrics for 9M FY26 include revenue growth of 31% YoY, driven by an increase in unique paid users, and positive 9M FY26 PAT.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations grew 34% YoY to ₹210,824 Mn in Q3 and 9M FY26</li><li>PAT stood at ₹450 Mn for 9M FY26, after adjusting for one-time expenses of ₹236 Mn</li><li>Pre-IndAS EBITDA for Q3FY26 grew 42% YoY to ₹2,188 Mn</li><li>Strong treasury with robust capital efficiency, cash flow from operations for 9M FY26 is ₹6,429 Mn</li><li>PW’s newer exam category, State Boards, has seen strong early traction with 175k enrollments in its first year</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a759a619-3043-4c3e-9fab-b11340a0ca17.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Physicswallah Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TIMESGREEN] Times Green Energy (India) Ltd Appoints M/s TRAK &amp; Associates as New Statutory Auditor</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Times+Green+Energy+%28India%29+Ltd&title=Times+Green+Energy+%28India%29+Ltd+Appoints+M%2Fs+TRAK+%26+Associates+as+New+Statutory+Auditor&newsId=53de1289-b319-41a9-82c3-3044f8f0b2fc&token=NTNkZTEyODktYjMx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53de1289-b319-41a9-82c3-3044f8f0b2fc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Times Green Energy (India) Ltd has appointed M/s TRAK &amp; Associates as the new Statutory Auditor of the company, following the resignation of M/s. VASG &amp; Associates, Chartered Accountants. The appointment will take effect from February 05, 2026 and will continue until the conclusion of the ensuing AGM, subject to shareholder approval. TRAK &amp; Associates is a Hyderabad-based firm of Chartered Accountants with offices in Hyderabad, Chennai, and Kadapa, offering a wide range of professional services.</p><ul><li>Times Green Energy (India) Ltd has appointed M/s TRAK &amp; Associates as the new Statutory Auditor.</li><li>The appointment follows the resignation of M/s. VASG &amp; Associates, Chartered Accountants.</li><li>The appointment will take effect from February 05, 2026 and will continue until the conclusion of the ensuing AGM, subject to shareholder approval.</li><li>TRAK &amp; Associates is a Hyderabad-based firm of Chartered Accountants with offices in Hyderabad, Chennai, and Kadapa.</li><li>TRAK &amp; Associates offers a wide range of professional services, focusing on integrity, transparency, and value creation.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a631b32c-bbed-4c47-8a4e-0234d2ebacae.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Times Green Energy (India) Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CTE] Cambridge Technology Enterprises Ltd: Dharani Swaroop Raghurama Resigns as Whole-Time Director and CFO, Raj Kumar Sehgal Appointed</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CAMBRIDGE+TECHNOLOGY+ENTERPRISES+LTD.&title=Cambridge+Technology+Enterprises+Ltd%3A+Dharani+Swaroop+Raghurama+Resigns+as+Whole-Time+Director+and+CFO%2C+Raj+Kumar+Sehgal+Appointed&newsId=26871a5d-f332-4468-97d2-b4b7fc7499c6&token=MjY4NzFhNWQtZjMz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26871a5d-f332-4468-97d2-b4b7fc7499c6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cambridge Technology Enterprises Ltd announced the resignation of Dharani Swaroop Raghurama as Whole-Time Director and Chief Financial Officer (CFO) with effect from close of business hours on February 05, 2026. Mr. Raghurama will continue as a Non-Executive and Non-Independent Director of the Company. The Company has appointed Raj Kumar Sehgal as Whole-Time Director for a period of five (5) years and as Chief Financial Officer with effect from February 05, 2026, subject to the approval of the shareholders.</p><ul><li>Dharani Swaroop Raghurama resigns as Whole-Time Director and CFO of Cambridge Technology Enterprises Ltd.</li><li>Raghurama to continue as a Non-Executive and Non-Independent Director of the Company.</li><li>Raj Kumar Sehgal appointed as Whole-Time Director for a period of five (5) years.</li><li>Sehgal also appointed as Chief Financial Officer of the Company with effect from February 05, 2026.</li><li>Appointments subject to the approval of the shareholders.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3743bd74-6f43-4420-918b-28f97da45461.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CAMBRIDGE TECHNOLOGY ENTERPRISES LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TIMESGREEN] Resignation of Statutory Auditor at Times Green Energy (India) Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Times+Green+Energy+%28India%29+Ltd&title=Resignation+of+Statutory+Auditor+at+Times+Green+Energy+%28India%29+Ltd&newsId=8bfa01c4-be0b-4af6-8467-d6634812a15b&token=OGJmYTAxYzQtYmUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8bfa01c4-be0b-4af6-8467-d6634812a15b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 15:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Times Green Energy (India) Ltd has announced the resignation of its statutory auditor, M/s. VASG &amp; Associates, Chartered Accountants. The resignation is due to non-availability of staff and resources. There are no concerns raised by the resigning auditor regarding the management of the company, nor is there a material reason for the resignation. The company has disclosed the details as required under SEBI regulations.</p><ul><li>Resignation of statutory auditor, M/s. VASG &amp; Associates, Chartered Accountants</li><li>Resignation due to non-availability of staff and resources</li><li>No concerns raised by the resigning auditor regarding the management of the company</li><li>No material reason for the resignation</li><li>Disclosure of details as required under SEBI regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/73eaca56-5ed6-4336-89e5-432bfeb05523.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Times Green Energy (India) Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>