<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:32:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[MSCTC] Mardia Samyoung Capillary Tubes Company Ltd Approves Unaudited Standalone Financial Results for Q3 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MARDIA+SAMYOUNG+CAPILLARY+TUBES+COMPANY+LTD.&title=Mardia+Samyoung+Capillary+Tubes+Company+Ltd+Approves+Unaudited+Standalone+Financial+Results+for+Q3+2025&newsId=eb2cc64b-ffcb-43e4-a6c3-3f2278a87ccc&token=ZWIyY2M2NGItZmZj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eb2cc64b-ffcb-43e4-a6c3-3f2278a87ccc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mardia Samyoung Capillary Tubes Company Ltd announced the approval of their unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025 during the Board of Directors meeting held on January 24, 2026. The meeting was held in accordance with Regulation 30 and 33 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The Board approved the unaudited standalone financial results and the limited review report from the statutory auditors.</p><ul><li>Approval of unaudited standalone financial results for Q3 2025</li><li>The results were reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors</li><li>Statutory auditors carried out a limited review report of the financial results</li><li>The financial results were prepared in accordance with Ind AS 34, prescribed under section 133 of the Companies Act, 2013</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/424a4623-7df8-4c60-8ce5-62bef8cc0971.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MARDIA SAMYOUNG CAPILLARY TUBES COMPANY LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NILACHAL] Nilachal Refractories Ltd. Announces Q3 Results with Net Loss and Negative Net Worth</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NILACHAL+REFRACTORIES+LTD.&title=Nilachal+Refractories+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+Results+with+Net+Loss+and+Negative+Net+Worth&newsId=f070c7ea-d021-4178-a7cd-d6973a5efe29&token=ZjA3MGM3ZWEtZDAy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f070c7ea-d021-4178-a7cd-d6973a5efe29</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Nilachal Refractories Ltd. has announced its unaudited standalone financial results for the third quarter ended 31st December 2025. The company has reported a net loss of Rs. 449.01 lakhs and a negative net worth of Rs. 3242.91 lakhs. The board has approved the results and the limited review report submitted by the statutory auditors, Jain Saraogi &amp; Co. LLP. The company has recognized impairment losses on Capital Work in Progress and Plant &amp; Machinery. There are material uncertainties related to the company&apos;s ability to continue as a going concern. The company is taking measures to improve its financial position, including roping in strategic investors, diversifying into new businesses, optimizing resource utilization, reducing costs, expanding product lines, and entering new markets.</p><ul><li>Net loss of Rs. 449.01 lakhs for Q3 2025</li><li>Negative net worth of Rs. 3242.91 lakhs as of 31st December 2025</li><li>Impairment losses recognized on Capital Work in Progress and Plant &amp; Machinery</li><li>Material uncertainties related to going concern</li><li>Measures taken to improve financial position, including strategic investments, diversification, cost reduction, and market expansion</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b23a2c56-b8ba-4c69-8e69-0b5e79cd4201.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NILACHAL REFRACTORIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IMPEXFERRO] Impex Ferro Tech Ltd Invites Expression of Interest Under IBC Regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IMPEX+FERRO+TECH+LTD.&title=Impex+Ferro+Tech+Ltd+Invites+Expression+of+Interest+Under+IBC+Regulations&newsId=56fec8f1-07ed-425e-952f-dca467c87392&token=NTZmZWM4ZjEtMDdl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56fec8f1-07ed-425e-952f-dca467c87392</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:22:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Insolvency and Bankruptcy</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Impex Ferro Tech Limited, a company operating in iron and steel at Burdwan, West Bengal, has invited expressions of interest (EOI) for its Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP) under the Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code, 2016. The company, which is currently undergoing CIRP, has published Form G in accordance with the IBBI regulations. The plant was operational until October 2022, but as of March 2025, there were no employees or workmen on the payroll. The last available financial statements of the two preceding years are available on the company&apos;s website. The EOI process document and the provisional list of resolution applicants can be found on the company&apos;s website or by sending an email to the provided address.</p><ul><li>Impex Ferro Tech Limited has invited expressions of interest under the Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code, 2016.</li><li>The company is operating in iron and steel at Burdwan, West Bengal.</li><li>The plant was operational until October 2022, but as of March 2025, there were no employees or workmen on the payroll.</li><li>The EOI process document and the provisional list of resolution applicants can be found on the company&apos;s website or by sending an email to the provided address.</li><li>The last available financial statements of the two preceding years are available on the company&apos;s website.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a8f8c24c-da2b-4b5e-a2ae-0b699ebf9a34.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IMPEX FERRO TECH LTD. | Category: Insolvency and Bankruptcy</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SWITCHTE] BBU Enterprise, Touristas Horizons, and Nikhil Pujari to Acquire 26% Stake in Switching Technologies Gunther Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SWITCHING+TECHNOLOGIES+GUNTHER+LTD.&title=BBU+Enterprise%2C+Touristas+Horizons%2C+and+Nikhil+Pujari+to+Acquire+26%25+Stake+in+Switching+Technologies+Gunther+Ltd&newsId=63dfc8b2-202b-4b0f-a1d8-242692d084f5&token=NjNkZmM4YjItMjAy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63dfc8b2-202b-4b0f-a1d8-242692d084f5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>BBU Enterprise, Touristas Horizons, and Nikhil Pujari have signed a share purchase agreement to acquire 37.63% of Switching Technologies Gunther Ltd, which includes 26% from public shareholders. The offer price is Rs. 66.00 per equity share. This is a triggered offer in compliance with Regulation 3(1) and 4 of the Takeover Regulations.</p><ul><li>BBU Enterprise, Touristas Horizons, and Nikhil Pujari to acquire 26% stake in Switching Technologies Gunther Ltd from public shareholders</li><li>Offer price is Rs. 66.00 per equity share</li><li>Acquirers to acquire 37.63% of the company&apos;s fully paid-up equity share capital</li><li>This is a triggered offer in compliance with Regulation 3(1) and 4 of the Takeover Regulations</li><li>Acquirers do not hold any equity shares of the target company presently</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/C74F7EC7-48A7-43E9-97A0-5AFC88C6366A-174629.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SWITCHING TECHNOLOGIES GUNTHER LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAINDUS] Sai Industries Ltd. Approves Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SAI+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Sai+Industries+Ltd.+Approves+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+2026&newsId=4bc09696-b459-4095-a72a-8b55fc1b9c2d&token=NGJjMDk2OTYtYjQ1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4bc09696-b459-4095-a72a-8b55fc1b9c2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sai Industries Ltd. has announced the approval of its unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2026, by the Board of Directors. The meeting was held on January 24, 2026, and the results show the company&apos;s financial performance during the quarter. The net sales/income from operations stands at Rs. XXXX Lacs, with total expenses of Rs. XXXX Lacs. The company reported a profit before finance costs and exceptional items of Rs. XXXX Lacs, and a profit after taxes, minority interest, and share of profit/(loss) of associates of Rs. XXXX Lacs.</p><ul><li>Sai Industries Ltd. approved the unaudited financial results for Q3 2026.</li><li>The results showed a net sales/income from operations of Rs. XXXX Lacs.</li><li>Total expenses were reported at Rs. XXXX Lacs.</li><li>The company had a profit before finance costs and exceptional items of Rs. XXXX Lacs.</li><li>The profit after taxes, minority interest, and share of profit/(loss) of associates stood at Rs. XXXX Lacs.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ed069b40-600a-4f5d-8e63-a0ffb4bfb08d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SAI INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IMPEXFERRO] Impex Ferro Tech Ltd. Holds Successful 23rd CoC Meeting: Key Discussions on CIRP Progress, EOI, and CIRP Cost Approval</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IMPEX+FERRO+TECH+LTD.&title=Impex+Ferro+Tech+Ltd.+Holds+Successful+23rd+CoC+Meeting%3A+Key+Discussions+on+CIRP+Progress%2C+EOI%2C+and+CIRP+Cost+Approval&newsId=2fd1b779-a004-48d4-be0c-f2800a7ee0d4&token=MmZkMWI3NzktYTAw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2fd1b779-a004-48d4-be0c-f2800a7ee0d4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Impex Ferro Tech Limited, currently undergoing Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP), held its 23rd Committee of Creditors (CoC) meeting on January 22, 2026. The meeting, which lasted from 17:00 to 17:15 hours, discussed several key matters including the steps taken by the Resolution Professional, invocation of bank guarantees, finalization of fresh Expression of Interest (EOI) and Form G, and criteria for Prospective Resolution Applicants (PRA). The CoC also approved the CIRP cost up to November 25 and December 25, and noted the extension of the CIRP period by the Hon’ble NCLT, Kolkata. The minutes of the meeting were circulated via email on January 24, 2026.</p><ul><li>Successful 23rd CoC meeting of Impex Ferro Tech Ltd.</li><li>Discussion on steps taken by the Resolution Professional in CIRP.</li><li>Discussion and finalization on fresh EOI and Form G.</li><li>Approval of CIRP cost up to November 25 and December 25.</li><li>Noting of extension of CIRP period by Hon’ble NCLT, Kolkata.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5376f4cf-2e5b-4127-baa9-b7a09f83c8ef.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IMPEX FERRO TECH LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UDS] Updater Services Ltd Receives Order from Commercial Tax Officer for Rs. 40,83,637 under Sec 74 of CGST Act, 2017</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Updater+Services+Ltd&title=Updater+Services+Ltd+Receives+Order+from+Commercial+Tax+Officer+for+Rs.+40%2C83%2C637+under+Sec+74+of+CGST+Act%2C+2017&newsId=4ba8e29d-66c8-47c9-adb1-59fdfd0d744a&token=NGJhOGUyOWQtNjZj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4ba8e29d-66c8-47c9-adb1-59fdfd0d744a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:11:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Updater Services Limited has received an order from the Office of the Commercial Tax Officer, Chennai, Tamil Nadu for an amount of Rs. 40,83,637/- under Sec 74 of the CGST Act, 2017. The order has been passed without considering the response submitted by the company against the notice. The company is exploring legal options and is hopeful that there will be no significant financial impact. The order is based on turnover difference between GSTR 3B vs GSTR 9, wrongly availed ITC on travelling expenses, insurance expenses, and ineligible ITC on unamortized uniform and shoe cost.</p><ul><li>Order received from Commercial Tax Officer for Rs. 40,83,637 under Sec 74 of the CGST Act, 2017</li><li>Order passed without considering the company&apos;s response</li><li>Company exploring legal options</li><li>Order based on turnover difference and wrongly availed ITC</li><li>Company hopeful of no significant financial impact</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c263839a-51b4-40d2-a107-558426c1f617.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Updater Services Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[20MICRONS] 20 Microns Ltd: Board Approves Advancing Loans, Appointment of Ms. Vedika Parikh, and Unaudited Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=20+MICRONS+LTD.&title=20+Microns+Ltd%3A+Board+Approves+Advancing+Loans%2C+Appointment+of+Ms.+Vedika+Parikh%2C+and+Unaudited+Financial+Results&newsId=f7bec49f-65df-48eb-bce8-59a880c87d68&token=ZjdiZWM0OWYtNjVk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7bec49f-65df-48eb-bce8-59a880c87d68</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of 20 Microns Limited approved the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The Board also approved the proposal to authorize the Company to advance loans, give guarantees and/or provide securities up to an aggregate amount not exceeding ¥50 Crores, and the appointment of Ms. Vedika Parikh as Strategy &amp; Transformation Associate (AI + Finance). These decisions are subject to the approval of the Members of the Company through Postal Ballot.</p><ul><li>Approval of Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Proposal to advance loans, give guarantees and/or provide securities up to ¥50 Crores</li><li>Appointment of Ms. Vedika Parikh as Strategy &amp; Transformation Associate (AI + Finance)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0ef2b3aa-a605-471a-b639-868ca98a33f1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: 20 MICRONS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UDS] Updater Services Ltd Receives Order from Commercial Tax Officer for Rs. 21,99,560 under Sec 74 of CGST Act, 2017</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Updater+Services+Ltd&title=Updater+Services+Ltd+Receives+Order+from+Commercial+Tax+Officer+for+Rs.+21%2C99%2C560+under+Sec+74+of+CGST+Act%2C+2017&newsId=7b163327-725d-4bcf-95f1-def5d2a5ddbc&token=N2IxNjMzMjctNzI1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b163327-725d-4bcf-95f1-def5d2a5ddbc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:11:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Updater Services Limited has received an order from the Office of the Commercial Tax Officer, Chennai, Tamil Nadu for an amount of Rs. 21,99,560/- under Sec 74 of the CGST Act, 2017. The order has been passed without considering the response submitted by the company against the notice. The company is exploring legal options and is hopeful that there will be no significant financial impact.</p><ul><li>Order received from Commercial Tax Officer, Chennai, Tamil Nadu for Rs. 21,99,560 under Sec 74 of the CGST Act, 2017</li><li>The order has been passed without considering the company&apos;s response</li><li>The company is exploring legal options including filing writ / appeal before the Appellant authority</li><li>The company is hopeful that there will be no significant financial impact</li><li>The order is based on wrongly availed ITC on Insurance Expenses</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a3af6d92-a6d9-40fb-92fd-820c90b4e991.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Updater Services Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UDS] Updater Services Ltd Receives Rs. 1,30,34,703/- Order from Commercial Tax Officer, Chennai</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Updater+Services+Ltd&title=Updater+Services+Ltd+Receives+Rs.+1%2C30%2C34%2C703%2F-+Order+from+Commercial+Tax+Officer%2C+Chennai&newsId=d703b1c1-f1cb-42c2-9ba9-615e47da4cc5&token=ZDcwM2IxYzEtZjFj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d703b1c1-f1cb-42c2-9ba9-615e47da4cc5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Updater Services Limited has received an order from the Office of the Commercial Tax Officer, Chennai, Tamil Nadu for an amount of Rs. 1,30,34,703/- under Sec 74 of the CGST Act, 2017. The order has been passed without considering the company&apos;s response to the notice. The company is exploring legal options and is hopeful that there will be no significant financial impact.</p><ul><li>Order received from the Office of the Commercial Tax Officer, Chennai for Rs. 1,30,34,703/- under Sec 74 of the CGST Act, 2017</li><li>The order has been passed without considering the company&apos;s response to the notice</li><li>The company is exploring legal options including filing writ / appeal before the Appellant authority</li><li>The company is hopeful that there will be no significant financial impact</li><li>The order is devoid of merits and the financial amount is expected to be NIL</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f50e79e2-6d4a-4b61-bcfa-9dceaa3ad07c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Updater Services Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>