<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:39:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[RAUNAQEPC] Raunaq International Ltd. to Approve Q4 Results for 2025 in February Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Raunaq+EPC+International+Ltd&title=Raunaq+International+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q4+Results+for+2025+in+February+Board+Meeting&newsId=9985e8f2-9934-4ec5-85c5-2e1f78d01911&token=OTk4NWU4ZjItOTkz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9985e8f2-9934-4ec5-85c5-2e1f78d01911</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:38:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Raunaq International Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 12, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The meeting is scheduled in accordance with Regulation 29 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. Additionally, the company has informed that the &apos;Trading Window&apos; for dealing in the shares of the company for Promoters/Promoter Group/Directors/Key Managerial Personnel/Designated Persons/Connected Persons/Connected Persons of the Company will be closed till Saturday, February 14, 2026, in compliance with the Code for Prevention of Insider Trading and the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Raunaq International Ltd. to approve Q4 results for 2025 in February Board Meeting</li><li>Meeting scheduled in accordance with Regulation 29 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Trading Window for dealing in the shares of the company to be closed till February 14, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d9cd42e3-06f3-4728-9945-63c13274d596.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Raunaq EPC International Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GHCLTEXTIL] GHCL Textiles Ltd Announces Unaudited Q3 Results for FY2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GHCL+Textiles+Ltd&title=GHCL+Textiles+Ltd+Announces+Unaudited+Q3+Results+for+FY2025-26&newsId=96e10ad9-78d6-479a-b6ea-1b368eabc99a&token=OTZlMTBhZDktNzhk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">96e10ad9-78d6-479a-b6ea-1b368eabc99a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:37:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>GHCL Textiles Ltd has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s total income stands at ₹ 1,10,483 lakhs, with a profit before tax of ₹ 6,329 lakhs. The company has no outstanding default on loans and debt securities. The results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>GHCL Textiles Ltd has reported a total income of ₹ 1,10,483 lakhs for Q3 FY2025-26.</li><li>The company&apos;s profit before tax stands at ₹ 6,329 lakhs.</li><li>The Statutory Auditors have conducted a limited review of these unaudited financial results.</li><li>The company has no outstanding default on loans and debt securities.</li><li>The results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d0b9e189-4c78-4496-aa1a-2d356b92ef3f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GHCL Textiles Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IRIS] IRIS RegTech Solutions Ltd Receives Award from NEC Corporation India for DRR Solution Development</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IRIS+Business+Services+Ltd&title=IRIS+RegTech+Solutions+Ltd+Receives+Award+from+NEC+Corporation+India+for+DRR+Solution+Development&newsId=4577659e-53f4-4d82-9e5b-f57f5cc653de&token=NDU3NzY1OWUtNTNm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4577659e-53f4-4d82-9e5b-f57f5cc653de</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:37:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Award</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>IRIS RegTech Solutions Ltd has announced that it has received an award from NEC Corporation India Private Limited for the design, development, and maintenance of the DRR (Digital Regulatory Reporting) solution for International Financial Services Centres Authority (IFSCA). The project is in the ordinary course of business for the company. The required disclosure as per SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/CFD/CFD-PoD-1/P/CIR/2023/123 dated July 13, 2023, is enclosed as Annexure-A.</p><ul><li>IRIS RegTech Solutions Ltd received an award from NEC Corporation India Private Limited</li><li>The award is for the design, development, and maintenance of the DRR (Digital Regulatory Reporting) solution for International Financial Services Centres Authority (IFSCA)</li><li>The project is in the ordinary course of business for the company</li><li>The required disclosure as per SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/CFD/CFD-PoD-1/P/CIR/2023/123 dated July 13, 2023, is enclosed as Annexure-A</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/13c21166-8138-4630-a8b3-4f6b2202472e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IRIS Business Services Ltd | Category: Award</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JJFINCOR] JJ Finance Corporation Ltd Submits Limited Review Report with Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 &amp; Nine Months Ended 31 December 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=J.J.FINANCE+CORPORATION+LTD.&title=JJ+Finance+Corporation+Ltd+Submits+Limited+Review+Report+with+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Ended+31+December+2025&newsId=866fbbf6-73f6-49f9-95f1-e66e50112758&token=ODY2ZmJiZjYtNzNm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">866fbbf6-73f6-49f9-95f1-e66e50112758</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:37:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>JJ Finance Corporation Ltd has submitted the Limited Review Report along with the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31 December 2025 under Regulation 33 of SEBI LODR. The company&apos;s revenue from operations, total income, and expenses are stated in the report. The financial results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee, audited by the Statutory Auditor, and approved by the Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>JJ Finance Corporation Ltd has submitted the Limited Review Report along with the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31 December 2025.</li><li>The financial results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee, audited by the Statutory Auditor, and approved by the Board of Directors.</li><li>Revenue from operations, total income, and expenses are stated in the report.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7fd4cef3-80ab-4114-92e9-85d5767e9686.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: J.J.FINANCE CORPORATION LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SIDDHA] Siddha Ventures Ltd. to Approve Q3 Results and Appoint New Secretarial Auditor</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SIDDHA+VENTURES+LTD.&title=Siddha+Ventures+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q3+Results+and+Appoint+New+Secretarial+Auditor&newsId=50f1db1c-9eb6-4170-a3ba-c9e3ef4b45fa&token=NTBmMWRiMWMtOWVi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50f1db1c-9eb6-4170-a3ba-c9e3ef4b45fa</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:36:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Siddha Ventures Ltd. has announced a Board of Directors meeting on 06/02/2026 to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The company will also consider the appointment of M/s. Vidhya Baid &amp; Co as the new Secretarial Auditor for the financial year 2025-2026, following the resignation of M/s Dash M &amp; Associates.</p><ul><li>Siddha Ventures Ltd. to approve Q3 results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025</li><li>New Secretarial Auditor, M/s. Vidhya Baid &amp; Co, to be appointed for the financial year 2025-2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7267fe0b-3a9a-4f53-85e5-0fe95e5bdb1d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SIDDHA VENTURES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GOCOLORS] Go Fashion (India) Ltd Announces Q4 2025 Results and Buy Back of Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Go+Fashion+%28India%29+Ltd&title=Go+Fashion+%28India%29+Ltd+Announces+Q4+2025+Results+and+Buy+Back+of+Shares&newsId=047d7599-965e-42d3-bebb-1a24f429a548&token=MDQ3ZDc1OTktOTY1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">047d7599-965e-42d3-bebb-1a24f429a548</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:36:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Go Fashion (India) Ltd has announced its quarterly results for the period ended December 31, 2025, and a buyback of up to 14,13,000 equity shares. The buyback, which is 9.44% of the company&apos;s total paid-up equity share capital and free reserves, will be conducted at a price of 460 Rupees per share, amounting to 64,99,80,000 Rupees. The record date for the buyback is February 9, 2026. The company has also fixed the record date for ascertaining the eligibility of shareholders for the buyback of equity shares.</p><ul><li>Go Fashion (India) Ltd has announced its quarterly results for Q4 2025.</li><li>The company has proposed a buyback of up to 14,13,000 equity shares.</li><li>The buyback price is set at 460 Rupees per share, amounting to 64,99,80,000 Rupees.</li><li>The record date for the buyback is February 9, 2026.</li><li>The company has fixed the record date for ascertaining the eligibility of shareholders for the buyback of equity shares.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c511f2ab-dd09-4046-96b1-97973c1417d4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Go Fashion (India) Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ORIENTCQ] AG Ventures Ltd. to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 &amp; 9M Ended Dec 31, 2025 on Feb 4, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ORIENTAL+CARBON+%26+CHEMICALS+LTD.-%24&title=AG+Ventures+Ltd.+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+%26+9M+Ended+Dec+31%2C+2025+on+Feb+4%2C+2026&newsId=fddf4a5a-bd04-423c-bc12-856e0741ae1f&token=ZmRkZjRhNWEtYmQw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fddf4a5a-bd04-423c-bc12-856e0741ae1f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:34:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>AG Ventures Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 4, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. In accordance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, and the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, the Trading Window will be closed for Designated Persons and their immediate relatives from January 1, 2026, and will reopen after 48 hours of submitting the financial results to the Stock Exchanges.</p><ul><li>AG Ventures Ltd. to approve unaudited financial results for Q3 and 9M ended Dec 31, 2025.</li><li>Board meeting scheduled on Feb 4, 2026, to consider and approve the results.</li><li>Trading Window closed for Designated Persons and their immediate relatives from Jan 1, 2026.</li><li>Trading Window to reopen after 48 hours of submitting the financial results to Stock Exchanges.</li><li>Meeting held in accordance with SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, and SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, and the Company’s Code of Conduct for Prohibition of Insider Trading.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2523613d-029d-465c-be1d-8e5c0c0b3081.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ORIENTAL CARBON & CHEMICALS LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NOVARTIND] Novartis India Clarifies Incorrect Q3 2025-26 Financial Figures in Free Press Journal Article</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NOVARTIS+INDIA+LTD.&title=Novartis+India+Clarifies+Incorrect+Q3+2025-26+Financial+Figures+in+Free+Press+Journal+Article&newsId=8d9f50d6-21be-4043-ac9f-8d7b5de4b3b8&token=OGQ5ZjUwZDYtMjFi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d9f50d6-21be-4043-ac9f-8d7b5de4b3b8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:33:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Clarification</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Novartis India Ltd has issued a clarification regarding incorrect financial figures of the company for Q3 2025-26 that were reported in a Free Press Journal article dated January 28, 2026. The article, which has now been taken down, contained inaccurate financial information that was not released, verified, or endorsed by the company. Novartis India has taken measures to notify the Free Press Journal about the mistake, resulting in the removal of the article. The company requests that investors, shareholders, and the public refer only to the official financial results and disclosures published on the BSE Limited website, the company’s official website, and in newspaper advertisements published in the Financial Express and Navshakti.</p><ul><li>Novartis India clarifies incorrect financial figures for Q3 2025-26</li><li>Inaccurate information was published in a Free Press Journal article</li><li>The company has taken measures to notify Free Press Journal about the mistake</li><li>The article has been removed from the E-Newspaper</li><li>Novartis India requests referring to official financial results and disclosures</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/15f37fd6-c1a5-439e-b91a-b9386518386f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NOVARTIS INDIA LTD. | Category: Clarification</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BMW] BMW Industries Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine-months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BMW+Industries+Ltd&title=BMW+Industries+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine-months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=ccde43a1-1469-4abc-b0d9-0c5bd17c1dba&token=Y2NkZTQzYTEtMTQ2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ccde43a1-1469-4abc-b0d9-0c5bd17c1dba</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>BMW Industries Limited has announced its financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 16,186.25 lakhs for the quarter and 45,490.38 lakhs for the nine-month period. The total income, after considering other income, expenses, and taxes, is 14,223.45 lakhs for the quarter and 2,105.88 lakhs for the nine-month period. The company&apos;s earnings per equity share (basic and diluted) are not explicitly stated in the document.</p><ul><li>BMW Industries Ltd has reported its financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>Revenue From Operations for the quarter is 16,186.25 lakhs, and for the nine-month period is 45,490.38 lakhs.</li><li>Profit before tax for the quarter is 14,223.45 lakhs, and for the nine-month period is 2,105.88 lakhs.</li><li>The company has reported an earnings per equity share, but the exact figures are not provided in the document.</li><li>The financial results have been reviewed by the Audit Committee and approved by the Board of Directors.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d41422e7-747f-4053-a74f-4a69d8deb2db.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BMW Industries Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MRPL] Mangalore Refinery and Petrochemicals Ltd: Transfer of Shares and Airport Upgrade</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MANGALORE+REFINERY+%26+PETROCHEMICALS+LTD.&title=Mangalore+Refinery+and+Petrochemicals+Ltd%3A+Transfer+of+Shares+and+Airport+Upgrade&newsId=93b3b6ee-97ff-4a15-93e0-9bced5bbb94e&token=OTNiM2I2ZWUtOTdm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93b3b6ee-97ff-4a15-93e0-9bced5bbb94e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 09:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mangalore Refinery and Petrochemicals Ltd has updated on the re-lodgement of transfer requests for physical shares for a specific folio. The transfer has been approved after a 30-day period with no objections. The shares will remain under lock-in for six months. Meanwhile, the MP for Dakshina Kannada, Dhiraj Bhalla, has urged for Point of Call (PoC) status to Mangaluru International Airport to enable direct international connectivity, expand airline operations, and significantly ease travel for overseas workers and their families.</p><ul><li>Transfer of shares approved for Mangalore Refinery and Petrochemicals Ltd</li><li>Shares to remain under lock-in for six months</li><li>MP urges for Point of Call (PoC) status to Mangaluru International Airport</li><li>PoC status would enable direct international connectivity</li><li>PoC status would expand airline operations and ease travel for overseas workers</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0cedb9df-6a7d-4998-bfd1-473740fb019e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MANGALORE REFINERY & PETROCHEMICALS LTD. | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>