<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 01:19:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ORIENTTR] Orient Tradelink Ltd Allots 3,90,682 Equity Shares at INR 22 Each, Increasing Paid-up Equity Share Capital</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ORIENT+TRADELINK+LTD.&title=Orient+Tradelink+Ltd+Allots+3%2C90%2C682+Equity+Shares+at+INR+22+Each%2C+Increasing+Paid-up+Equity+Share+Capital&newsId=60383891-e275-465b-9dcd-2191c0ef2825&token=NjAzODM4OTEtZTI3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60383891-e275-465b-9dcd-2191c0ef2825</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 00:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Orient Tradelink Ltd has allotted 3,90,682 equity shares of INR 10 each at a price of INR 22 per share, comprising of a premium of INR 12 per share. The allotment was made to four non-promoter allottees: Shikha, Sanjay Sinha, Bhawna Shadija, and Sunita Panwar. The allotment increased the company&apos;s paid-up equity share capital from INR 37,96,24,520 divided into 3,79,62,452 Equity Shares of INR 10/-each to INR 38,35,31,340 divided into 3,83,53,134 Equity Shares of INR 10/-each.</p><ul><li>Orient Tradelink Ltd allotted 3,90,682 equity shares at INR 22 per share with a premium of INR 12 per share.</li><li>The allotment was made to four non-promoter allottees: Shikha, Sanjay Sinha, Bhawna Shadija, and Sunita Panwar.</li><li>The allotment increased the company&apos;s paid-up equity share capital from INR 37,96,24,520 to INR 38,35,31,340.</li><li>The allotment was made in accordance with the provisions of Chapter V of the SEBI (Issue of Capital and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2018.</li><li>The allotment was approved in a Board of Directors meeting held on Monday, 19 January 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ea0cc2ac-fa20-4ad7-9626-1bf035ce51af.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ORIENT TRADELINK LTD. | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ORIENTTR] Orient Tradelink Ltd Allots 3,90,682 Equity Shares at INR 22 Each, Increasing Paid-up Equity Share Capital</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ORIENT+TRADELINK+LTD.&title=Orient+Tradelink+Ltd+Allots+3%2C90%2C682+Equity+Shares+at+INR+22+Each%2C+Increasing+Paid-up+Equity+Share+Capital&newsId=0366bec1-a93a-43f6-b42e-9d19561b40b5&token=MDM2NmJlYzEtYTkz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0366bec1-a93a-43f6-b42e-9d19561b40b5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 00:08:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Equity Issuance</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Orient Tradelink Ltd has allotted 3,90,682 equity shares of INR 10 each at a price of INR 22 per share, comprising of a premium of INR 12 per share. The allotment was made to four non-promoter allottees: Shikha, Sanjay Sinha, Bhawna Shadija, and Sunita Panwar. The allotment increased the company&apos;s paid-up equity share capital from INR 37,96,24,520 divided into 3,79,62,452 Equity Shares of INR 10/-each to INR 38,35,31,340 divided into 3,83,53,134 Equity Shares of INR 10/-each.</p><ul><li>Orient Tradelink Ltd allotted 3,90,682 equity shares at INR 22 per share with a premium of INR 12 per share.</li><li>The allotment was made to four non-promoter allottees: Shikha, Sanjay Sinha, Bhawna Shadija, and Sunita Panwar.</li><li>The allotment increased the company&apos;s paid-up equity share capital from INR 37,96,24,520 to INR 38,35,31,340.</li><li>The decision was made in a board meeting held on Monday, 19 January 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d3d5bd32-214f-45be-8e14-ce270225817b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ORIENT TRADELINK LTD. | Category: Equity Issuance</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SWORDEDGE] Sword-Edge Commercials Ltd Appoints Three New Independent Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sword-Edge+Commercials+Limited&title=Sword-Edge+Commercials+Ltd+Appoints+Three+New+Independent+Directors&newsId=b8ef65f9-9abf-4f2d-952f-a547f69470fe&token=YjhlZjY1ZjktOWFi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8ef65f9-9abf-4f2d-952f-a547f69470fe</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 00:08:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sword-Edge Commercials Ltd, a company based in Mumbai, Maharashtra, has announced the appointment of three new Additional Non-Executive Independent Directors: Ms. Neha Kargeti, Ms. Adithi Rathore, and Mr. Kulbir Singh Sandhu. The appointments are for a term of 5 consecutive years from January 19, 2026, to January 18, 2031, subject to the approval of the shareholders. The appointments were made based on the recommendation of the Nomination and Remuneration Committee. The new directors bring a diverse set of skills and experiences to the board, which will support effective governance, risk management, and compliance within the company.</p><ul><li>Appointment of three new Additional Non-Executive Independent Directors: Ms. Neha Kargeti, Ms. Adithi Rathore, and Mr. Kulbir Singh Sandhu</li><li>Appointments are for a term of 5 consecutive years from January 19, 2026, to January 18, 2031</li><li>Appointments are subject to the approval of the shareholders</li><li>New directors bring a diverse set of skills and experiences to the board</li><li>Reconstitution of certain committees of the Board of Directors with effect from January 19, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/75107358-931f-450d-9fe7-de45c285c5b1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sword-Edge Commercials Limited | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[OXFORDIN] Devendra Batukanath Shukla Acquires 7.09% Stake in Oxford Industries Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Oxford+Industries+Ltd&title=Devendra+Batukanath+Shukla+Acquires+7.09%25+Stake+in+Oxford+Industries+Ltd&newsId=d3bb66ed-6d50-4530-904e-5d3287cd443d&token=ZDNiYjY2ZWQtNmQ1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3bb66ed-6d50-4530-904e-5d3287cd443d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 00:07:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Devendra Batukanath Shukla has acquired 421,175 shares carrying voting rights in Oxford Industries Ltd, amounting to 7.09% of the total voting rights. This acquisition was made through a mode other than open market, public issue, rights issue, preferential allotment, inter-se transfer, or encumbrance. The acquired shares have a face value of Rs. 10 each and will rank pari-passu to the existing shares. The acquisition was made before the equity shares&apos; redemption date of 5/12/2025.</p><ul><li>Devendra Batukanath Shukla acquires 7.09% stake in Oxford Industries Ltd</li><li>Acquisition made through a mode other than open market, public issue, rights issue, preferential allotment, inter-se transfer, or encumbrance</li><li>Acquired shares have a face value of Rs. 10 each</li><li>Acquired shares will rank pari-passu to the existing shares</li><li>Acquisition made before the equity shares&apos; redemption date of 5/12/2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/AA7CC167_90F7_4F3A_AB67_D281A06A588E_193105.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Oxford Industries Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GALAGEX] Galaxy Agrico Exports Ltd. Fixes Record Date for Rights Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GALAXY+AGRICO+EXPORTS+LTD.&title=Galaxy+Agrico+Exports+Ltd.+Fixes+Record+Date+for+Rights+Issue&newsId=e04c0ef1-80c2-47cc-9650-42aa6ace2303&token=ZTA0YzBlZjEtODBj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e04c0ef1-80c2-47cc-9650-42aa6ace2303</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 00:07:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Rights Issue</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Galaxy Agrico Exports Ltd. has announced Friday, 23rd January, 2026, as the Record Date for the purpose of determining the eligibility of shareholders for the proposed Rights Issue. The Rights Equity Shares are being offered to the Eligible Equity Shareholders of the Company on a rights basis in the ratio of Five (5) Rights Equity Shares for every One (1) fully paid-up Equity Share (5:1) held by them as on the Record Date. The Company&apos;s decision is in accordance with the applicable SEBI Circulars governing Rights Issues.</p><ul><li>Record Date for Rights Issue fixed for 23rd January, 2026</li><li>Rights Equity Shares offered in the ratio of 5:1</li><li>Offer only for fully paid-up Equity Shareholders</li><li>Eligibility determined as on the Record Date</li><li>In accordance with SEBI Circulars governing Rights Issues</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6778c6c4-15dd-4757-8036-5e0f4296912a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GALAXY AGRICO EXPORTS LTD. | Category: Rights Issue</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ONGC] ONGC Appoints Four New Executive Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Oil+and+Natural+Gas+Corporation+Ltd&title=ONGC+Appoints+Four+New+Executive+Directors&newsId=2ca01823-3b68-4913-a93b-44508835e5bc&token=MmNhMDE4MjMtM2I2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ca01823-3b68-4913-a93b-44508835e5bc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 00:06:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Oil and Natural Gas Corporation Ltd (ONGC) has appointed four new Executive Directors, Balraj Kumar Kotta, Pawan Kumar Jalutharia, Hemant Ramlu Mulka, and Vivek Chand Singh. Balraj Kumar Kotta, an engineering graduate in Electronics Engineering from Indian Institute of Technology (Banaras Hindu University), Varanasi, has 36 years of experience. Pawan Kumar Jalutharia, an engineering graduate in Mechanical Engineering from Rajasthan University and a Master of Human Resource Management from Sikkim Manipal University, has 36 years of experience. Hemant Ramlu Mulka, an engineering graduate in chemical engineering from Nagpur University &amp; MBA from Sikkim Manipal University, has 35 years of experience. Vivek Chand Singh, an engineering graduate in Electrical Engineering from Punjab University &amp; MBA (International Business) from Indian Institute of Foreign Trade, has 36 years of experience. All four will join ONGC as Executive Directors (one level below the Board) with effect from 19.01.2026.</p><ul><li>ONGC appoints four new Executive Directors</li><li>Balraj Kumar Kotta has 36 years of experience in Electronics Engineering</li><li>Pawan Kumar Jalutharia has 36 years of experience in Mechanical Engineering and Human Resource Management</li><li>Hemant Ramlu Mulka has 35 years of experience in Chemical Engineering and Business Administration</li><li>Vivek Chand Singh has 36 years of experience in Electrical Engineering and International Business</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0b0bafba-ebe7-4f4b-b9c5-f145038a4319.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Oil and Natural Gas Corporation Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHARDFI] Eco Hotels and Resorts Limited Delivers Strong Q3 FY 2025-26 Performance: Revenues at 179.31 lakh, High Occupancies, and Expansion Pipeline Support Positive Outlook</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHARAD+FIBRES+%26+YARN+PROCESSORS+LTD.&title=Eco+Hotels+and+Resorts+Limited+Delivers+Strong+Q3+FY+2025-26+Performance%3A+Revenues+at+179.31+lakh%2C+High+Occupancies%2C+and+Expansion+Pipeline+Support+Positive+Outlook&newsId=38e3cd87-df7c-461c-9a0c-1e2c4c6093cb&token=MzhlM2NkODctZGY3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">38e3cd87-df7c-461c-9a0c-1e2c4c6093cb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 00:06:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Eco Hotels and Resorts Limited, a sustainable hospitality company, reported a strong operating performance during Q3 FY 2025-26. The Company witnessed robust operating momentum following the successful launch of new properties in Varanasi and Vadodara towards the end of September 2025. The Varanasi property delivered exceptional performance, achieving 100% occupancy on multiple days and maintaining an average occupancy of approximately 85% in December 2025. The Kochi property also continued to perform steadily, recording around 80% occupancy in November and December 2025. The Company reported revenue from operations of 3179.31 lakh for Q3 FY 2025-26, with total income of 3182.34 lakh. The performance during the period reflects the Company’s ongoing investment and expansion phase, including new property additions, initial ramp-up of recently launched hotels, and restructuring initiatives aimed at creating a scalable, asset-light and sustainable hospitality platform. These strategic initiatives are expected to support improving operating leverage and financial performance as occupancies stabilise and new properties mature. During the quarter, the Board approved the addition of a new property to the Company’s portfolio. In addition, two to three new properties are expected to become operational in Q4 FY 2025-26, further strengthening the Company’s expansion pipeline.</p><ul><li>Revenues for Q3 FY 2025-26 stood at 179.31 lakh</li><li>New properties launched in Varanasi and Vadodara performed exceptionally with high occupancies</li><li>Company&apos;s location strategy and brand positioning in key travel destinations proved strong</li><li>Two to three new properties expected to become operational in Q4 FY 2025-26</li><li>Strategic initiatives aimed at creating a scalable, asset-light and sustainable hospitality platform</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/545f43eb-90bd-42e6-a32b-ae5f095bc010.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHARAD FIBRES & YARN PROCESSORS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDOCITY] Indo City Infotech Ltd. to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results on Feb 11, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDO-CITY+INFOTECH+LTD.-%24&title=Indo+City+Infotech+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+on+Feb+11%2C+2026&newsId=bf468ef4-fc87-4fe3-bc87-58e969cbe229&token=YmY0NjhlZjQtZmM4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf468ef4-fc87-4fe3-bc87-58e969cbe229</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 00:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indo City Infotech Ltd. has announced a Board Meeting scheduled for 11th February, 2026. The meeting will consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December, 2025. The company&apos;s srip code is 532100.</p><ul><li>Indo City Infotech Ltd. scheduled a Board Meeting on 11th February, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3802f2da-295f-45a6-9eb2-4475b07bb3cd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDO-CITY INFOTECH LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BAJAJELEC] Bajaj Electricals Ltd to Enter &apos;Wires&apos; Industry Under &apos;Lighting Solutions&apos; Segment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BAJAJ+ELECTRICALS+LTD.-%24&title=Bajaj+Electricals+Ltd+to+Enter+%27Wires%27+Industry+Under+%27Lighting+Solutions%27+Segment&newsId=1954dd46-b268-4ced-92f7-6d1521f7d9b6&token=MTk1NGRkNDYtYjI2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1954dd46-b268-4ced-92f7-6d1521f7d9b6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 00:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Bajaj Electricals Ltd has decided to expand and diversify its business operations by entering into &apos;Wires&apos; as a new business line under its &apos;Lighting Solutions&apos; segment. This decision is driven by the growing demand in the Wires Industry. The company plans to launch the product shortly and will assess the market to determine the investment required, which will be based on various factors such as scale of business, operational requirements, and other prevailing external factors. The company will continue to update the Stock Exchanges on any further material developments as required under the applicable regulatory framework.</p><ul><li>Bajaj Electricals Ltd to enter &apos;Wires&apos; industry</li><li>New business line under &apos;Lighting Solutions&apos; segment</li><li>Decision driven by growing demand in the Wires Industry</li><li>Investment to be determined based on various factors</li><li>Company to update Stock Exchanges on further developments</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/04e12f4f-5c2c-4c14-a775-49624c126bec.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BAJAJ ELECTRICALS LTD.-$ | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JONJUA] Promoter Harjinder Singh Jonjua Transfers Shares in Jonjua Overseas Ltd via Gift and Off-market Sale</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jonjua+Overseas+Ltd&title=Promoter+Harjinder+Singh+Jonjua+Transfers+Shares+in+Jonjua+Overseas+Ltd+via+Gift+and+Off-market+Sale&newsId=ea25db87-a3a1-4d20-9dfa-6d6ef89dbd86&token=ZWEyNWRiODctYTNh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ea25db87-a3a1-4d20-9dfa-6d6ef89dbd86</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 00:01:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Harjinder Singh Jonjua, a promoter of Jonjua Overseas Ltd, has transferred a portion of his holding in the company on 19th January 2026. The transfer was made through a gift and off-market sale. The total shares transferred represent 18.30% of the total voting rights and total diluted share capital of the company.</p><ul><li>Promoter Harjinder Singh Jonjua transfers shares in Jonjua Overseas Ltd</li><li>Transfer made through gift and off-market sale</li><li>Total shares transferred represent 18.30% of total voting rights</li><li>Transfer affects 18.30% of total diluted share capital</li><li>Transaction disclosed in compliance with Regulation 29 (2) of SEBI (SAST) Regulations, 2011</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/feeb3b0b-9961-45b4-883b-bfb916b482c9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jonjua Overseas Ltd | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>