<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:50:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[HONAUT] Honeywell Automation India Ltd: CFO Mr. Pulkit Goyal Resigns Effective April 30, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HONEYWELL+AUTOMATION+INDIA+LTD.&title=Honeywell+Automation+India+Ltd%3A+CFO+Mr.+Pulkit+Goyal+Resigns+Effective+April+30%2C+2026&newsId=cd239f50-619d-479c-8083-c15306487652&token=Y2QyMzlmNTAtNjE5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd239f50-619d-479c-8083-c15306487652</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:47:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Auditor</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Honeywell Automation India Ltd announced that its Chief Financial Officer (CFO), Mr. Pulkit Goyal, has resigned from his position effective April 30, 2026. The Board accepted his resignation at its meeting held on February 2, 2026, and acknowledged his valuable contributions during his tenure. Mr. Goyal is leaving to pursue other opportunities.</p><ul><li>Mr. Pulkit Goyal resigns as Chief Financial Officer of Honeywell Automation India Ltd.</li><li>Resignation takes effect from the close of business hours on April 30, 2026.</li><li>The Board accepted the resignation and appreciated Mr. Goyal&apos;s contributions.</li><li>Mr. Goyal is leaving to pursue other opportunities.</li><li>The company will ensure a smooth transition of duties.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7abd5e01-2976-4b76-8d8b-17305e837f84.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HONEYWELL AUTOMATION INDIA LTD. | Category: Auditor</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TASHIND] Tashi India Ltd to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months of FY2025-2026 on Feb 7, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TASHI+INDIA+LTD.&title=Tashi+India+Ltd+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+of+FY2025-2026+on+Feb+7%2C+2026&newsId=19ad10a8-2c77-40a4-b019-0ce0c9473787&token=MTlhZDEwYTgtMmM3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19ad10a8-2c77-40a4-b019-0ce0c9473787</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:44:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tashi India Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 7, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the Third Quarter and Nine months ended 31° December, 2025. In accordance with SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, the Trading Window for dealing in shares/securities of the Company, by the Designated /Connected Persons and their immediate relatives is closed from January 1, 2026, and will continue to remain closed till 48 hours after the declaration of the Results.</p><ul><li>Tashi India Ltd to approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine months of FY2025-2026 on Feb 7, 2026</li><li>Trading Window closed from January 1, 2026, for Designated/Connected Persons and their immediate relatives</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2b2e121e-b515-4b63-ab62-52145a6b686d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TASHI INDIA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DELPHIFX] Delphi World Money Ltd Announces 5:1 Stock Split and 2:1 Bonus Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Delphi+World+Money+Ltd&title=Delphi+World+Money+Ltd+Announces+5%3A1+Stock+Split+and+2%3A1+Bonus+Issue&newsId=1781ecd0-5ead-4e8f-aabc-66042d84e567&token=MTc4MWVjZDAtNWVh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1781ecd0-5ead-4e8f-aabc-66042d84e567</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:44:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Split</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Delphi World Money Ltd has announced a sub-division/split of the face value of its equity shares from Rs. 10/- to Rs. 2/- each, with a record date of February 14, 2026. Additionally, the company will issue bonus shares in the ratio of 2:1, with the deemed date of allotment on February 16, 2026. These bonus shares will be available for trading on the next working day i.e. February 17, 2026.</p><ul><li>Delphi World Money Ltd announces a 5:1 stock split of its equity shares face value.</li><li>The company also announces a 2:1 bonus issue of fully paid-up equity shares.</li><li>The record date for both corporate actions is February 14, 2026.</li><li>The deemed date of allotment for bonus shares is February 16, 2026.</li><li>Bonus shares will be available for trading from February 17, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a4d0a14c-ff9a-4fc9-8b17-bb4960b0e027.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Delphi World Money Ltd | Category: Split</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GCCLINP] GCCL Infrastructure &amp; Projects Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q4 Results and Director&apos;s Continuation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GCCL+Infrastructure+%26+Projects+Ltd&title=GCCL+Infrastructure+%26+Projects+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q4+Results+and+Director%27s+Continuation&newsId=416317fe-dc45-40a6-a2c2-cffa94bad34f&token=NDE2MzE3ZmUtZGM0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">416317fe-dc45-40a6-a2c2-cffa94bad34f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:44:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>GCCL Infrastructure &amp; Projects Ltd has announced a board meeting scheduled for 10th February 2026. The agenda includes approving the un-audited financial results for the quarter ended on 31st December 2025, discussing the continuation of Mr. Dhirendra Ansukhlal Avashia&apos;s directorship post 75 years, approving the draft Notice of Extra-Ordinary General Meeting, appointing a scrutinizer for the e-voting process, and considering any other business with the chairman&apos;s permission. The trading window for dealing in the company&apos;s securities has been closed for all designated persons and their immediate relatives till the end of 48 hours after the announcement of the un-audited financial results.</p><ul><li>GCCL Infrastructure &amp; Projects Ltd to approve Q4 results on 10th February 2026</li><li>Discussion on continuation of Mr. Dhirendra Ansukhlal Avashia&apos;s directorship post 75 years</li><li>Appointment of scrutinizer for the e-voting process for the Extra-Ordinary General Meeting</li><li>Trading window closed for all designated persons and their immediate relatives</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/debf2fae-f017-4efc-b943-81f02fc0558a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GCCL Infrastructure & Projects Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EMUDHRA] eMudhra Ltd. Approves Unaudited Financial Statements for Q3 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=eMudhra+Ltd&title=eMudhra+Ltd.+Approves+Unaudited+Financial+Statements+for+Q3+2026&newsId=cafa61c0-1755-4777-b00b-31ad4e1fe705&token=Y2FmYTYxYzAtMTc1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cafa61c0-1755-4777-b00b-31ad4e1fe705</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>eMudhra Ltd. has approved the unaudited financial statements (both standalone &amp; consolidated) prepared in accordance with Indian Accounting Standards (IndAS) for the quarter ended December 31, 2026. The company&apos;s total revenue for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025 is Rs. 1,974.24 million and Rs. 211233 million respectively. The profit before exceptional items, share of net profit of associates accounted under equity method &amp; tax for the same period is Rs. 981.88 million and Rs. 804.69 million respectively.</p><ul><li>eMudhra Ltd. has approved the unaudited financial statements for the quarter ended December 31, 2026.</li><li>The company&apos;s total revenue for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025 is Rs. 1,974.24 million and Rs. 211233 million respectively.</li><li>The profit before exceptional items, share of net profit of associates accounted under equity method &amp; tax for the same period is Rs. 981.88 million and Rs. 804.69 million respectively.</li><li>The consolidated financial results include the Group’s share of profit after tax of Rs. (0.07) million and Rs. (0.05) million for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025 respectively in respect of one associate.</li><li>The review report was conducted by Suri &amp; Co., Chartered Accountants.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bc3c15f5-7062-496e-a2e0-9cd3d6b4d2b3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: eMudhra Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SAMBHV] Sambhv Steel Tubes Ltd Reports Utilization of IPO Gross Proceeds as of December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sambhv+Steel+Tubes+Ltd&title=Sambhv+Steel+Tubes+Ltd+Reports+Utilization+of+IPO+Gross+Proceeds+as+of+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=9ac55a35-fbdb-43e1-901f-8d960b32bcc5&token=OWFjNTVhMzUtZmJk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ac55a35-fbdb-43e1-901f-8d960b32bcc5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:42:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sambhv Steel Tubes Ltd has provided a Monitoring Agency Report, prepared by CARE Ratings Limited, detailing the utilization of gross proceeds from their IPO as of December 31, 2025. The report highlights that there have been no deviations from the intended objects and no range of deviation. The company has not utilized any IPO proceeds in Q3 FY26 and has not observed any major deviations over the earlier monitoring agency reports. The report also mentions that all Government/statutory approvals related to the objects have been obtained.</p><ul><li>Sambhv Steel Tubes Ltd provided a Monitoring Agency Report for the quarter ended December 31, 2025</li><li>The report was prepared by CARE Ratings Limited</li><li>No deviations from the intended objects and no range of deviation</li><li>No utilization of IPO proceeds in Q3 FY26</li><li>All Government/statutory approvals related to the objects have been obtained</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b0db2207-5f83-41f5-8b1a-0b89f4b8ddc7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sambhv Steel Tubes Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AADHARHFC] JM Financial Discloses Zero Equity Shares Tendered in Aadhar Housing Finance Open Offer</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Aadhar+Housing+Finance+Ltd&title=JM+Financial+Discloses+Zero+Equity+Shares+Tendered+in+Aadhar+Housing+Finance+Open+Offer&newsId=057b22c2-96e0-4629-b463-986d82316855&token=MDU3YjIyYzItOTZl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">057b22c2-96e0-4629-b463-986d82316855</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:41:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Open Offer</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>JM Financial Limited, the Manager to the Open Offer of Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd, has disclosed that no Equity Shares were tendered in the Open Offer as of 2 February 2026. The disclosure is based on the Open Offer Escrow Demat Account statement received from Ventura Securities Limited. The Equity Shares tendered by the Public Shareholders are subject to validation and verification of submitted documents. The &apos;validly tendered&apos; Equity Shares will be accepted in accordance with the SEBI (SAST) Regulations and the Letter of Offer dated 24 January 2026.</p><ul><li>JM Financial discloses zero Equity Shares tendered in Aadhar Housing Finance Open Offer</li><li>The disclosure is based on the Open Offer Escrow Demat Account statement as of 2 February 2026</li><li>Tendered Equity Shares are subject to validation and verification of submitted documents</li><li>Acceptance of &apos;validly tendered&apos; Equity Shares is in accordance with SEBI (SAST) Regulations and Letter of Offer</li><li>No Equity Shares were held in the Open Offer Escrow Demat Account as of the stated date</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/42A9D151-4504-4728-827B-1EAF41514AA3-180905.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Aadhar Housing Finance Ltd | Category: Open Offer</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WILLIMFI] Williamson Financial Services Ltd to Approve Q4 2025 Unaudited Financial Results on Feb 10, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=WILLIAMSON+FINANCIAL+SERVICES+LTD.&title=Williamson+Financial+Services+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+2025+Unaudited+Financial+Results+on+Feb+10%2C+2026&newsId=c221cd36-f72e-419d-856e-b6369da8feef&token=YzIyMWNkMzYtZjcy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c221cd36-f72e-419d-856e-b6369da8feef</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:41:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Williamson Financial Services Ltd has announced a Board of Directors meeting on February 10, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The meeting is in accordance with Regulation 29 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The trading window for dealing in securities of the company will remain closed till the end of 48 hours after the announcement of the un-audited financial results.</p><ul><li>Williamson Financial Services Ltd to consider and approve unaudited financial results for Q4 2025</li><li>Board of Directors meeting scheduled for February 10, 2026</li><li>Meeting in accordance with Regulation 29 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Trading window for securities dealings to remain closed till 48 hours after un-audited financial results announcement</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a4823c3a-cb22-4a14-9913-489a2a13eaf2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: WILLIAMSON FINANCIAL SERVICES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GOLKONDA] Golkonda Aluminium Extrusions Ltd. Announces Q3 FY2025 Financial Results with 25.57% Profit Before Tax</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Golkonda+Aluminium+Extrusions+Ltd-%24&title=Golkonda+Aluminium+Extrusions+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+FY2025+Financial+Results+with+25.57%25+Profit+Before+Tax&newsId=134b7256-31af-4cde-8b4c-f63063f47b56&token=MTM0YjcyNTYtMzFh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">134b7256-31af-4cde-8b4c-f63063f47b56</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Golkonda Aluminium Extrusions Ltd. has announced its unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December 2025. The company reported a profit before tax of 25.57%, an increase from the previous quarter&apos;s 6.47%. The Board of Directors also approved the resignation of Mr. Narender as an Independent Director. The financial results have been prepared in compliance with the Companies (India Accounting Standards) Rules, 2015.</p><ul><li>Profit before tax at 25.57%</li><li>Resignation of Mr. Narender as an Independent Director</li><li>Financial results prepared in compliance with Companies (India Accounting Standards) Rules, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/46ea1555-3835-445e-ae2c-60074faac273.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Golkonda Aluminium Extrusions Ltd-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GOVNOW] SAB Events &amp; Governance Now Media Ltd Announces 4th Meeting of Committee of Creditors for Pre-Packaged Insolvency Resolution Process</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SAB+Events+%26+Governance+Now+Media+Ltd&title=SAB+Events+%26+Governance+Now+Media+Ltd+Announces+4th+Meeting+of+Committee+of+Creditors+for+Pre-Packaged+Insolvency+Resolution+Process&newsId=60906db8-f916-43bc-99d5-27f140e92d63&token=NjA5MDZkYjgtZjkx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60906db8-f916-43bc-99d5-27f140e92d63</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SAB Events &amp; Governance Now Media Limited has announced the 4th Meeting of the Committee of Creditors for the ongoing Pre-Packaged Insolvency Resolution Process. The meeting is scheduled for Friday, February 06, 2026, at 04:00 P.M. The agenda includes voting and approving the Binding Resolution Plan submitted by the Resolution Applicant, approving the appointment of an Advocate for filing the Application before Adjudicating Authority for approval of the Binding Resolution Plan and their Professional fees, and approving and ratifying the PPIRP costs incurred by the Resolution Professional from the 3rd CoC Meeting till the date of this Meeting.</p><ul><li>4th Meeting of Committee of Creditors scheduled for February 06, 2026</li><li>Voting and approval of the Binding Resolution Plan submitted by the Resolution Applicant</li><li>Approval of the appointment of an Advocate for filing the Application before Adjudicating Authority</li><li>Approval and ratification of the PPIRP costs incurred by the Resolution Professional</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d3490194-ab0d-40ec-b02b-022efd607690.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SAB Events & Governance Now Media Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>