<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:54:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[GALACTICO] Galactico Corporate Services Ltd. to Restructure Non-core Activities in Compliance with SEBI Regulations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Galactico+Corporate+Services+Ltd&title=Galactico+Corporate+Services+Ltd.+to+Restructure+Non-core+Activities+in+Compliance+with+SEBI+Regulations&newsId=8e55d0ac-33fe-4dff-bb7c-d94ed0b24ae8&token=OGU1NWQwYWMtMzNm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8e55d0ac-33fe-4dff-bb7c-d94ed0b24ae8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:50:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Galactico Corporate Services Ltd. held a meeting on 25th February, 2026, to discuss the implications of the SEBI (Merchant Bankers) Amendment Regulations, 2025. The Board noted that the Company will ensure ongoing compliance with the revised capital adequacy and minimum liquid net worth requirements. The Company will undertake Non-core activities at arm&apos;s length through separate business units, segregated by a Chinese wall and ring-fenced from SEBI- regulated operations. The Board is reviewing the regulatory framework, operational requirements, and implementation of a Grievance Redressal Mechanism for such activities. The Company has decided to take all necessary steps to ensure compliance with the SEBI (Merchant Bankers) Amendment Regulations, and will undergo corporate restructuring in accordance with SEBI Regulations, and all requisite approvals shall be obtained and accorded in due course.</p><ul><li>Galactico Corporate Services Ltd. to ensure ongoing compliance with revised capital adequacy and minimum liquid net worth requirements</li><li>Company to undertake Non-core activities at arm&apos;s length through separate business units</li><li>Board reviewing regulatory framework, operational requirements, and implementation of a Grievance Redressal Mechanism for non-SEBI regulated activities</li><li>Company to take necessary steps to ensure compliance with SEBI (Merchant Bankers) Amendment Regulations</li><li>Corporate restructuring to be undertaken in accordance with SEBI Regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e1e8794d-30fe-43eb-a226-bc923ed0cc9c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Galactico Corporate Services Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DMR] DMR Engineering Secures Rs. 4 Crore Solar PV EPC Contract in Bihar</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DMR+Hydroengineering+%26+Infrastructures+Ltd&title=DMR+Engineering+Secures+Rs.+4+Crore+Solar+PV+EPC+Contract+in+Bihar&newsId=d17c3397-b8d8-423b-beb6-adacbcf7d786&token=ZDE3YzMzOTctYjhk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d17c3397-b8d8-423b-beb6-adacbcf7d786</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:45:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>DMR Engineering Limited has announced the receipt of a work order for EPC Execution of 1.00 MW (AC) Solar PV at PSS-Kharagpur, Munger, in the state of Bihar. The contract is worth Rs. 4,00,00,000/- (Rupees Four Crore only), inclusive of GST, and the contract period is 6 months.</p><ul><li>DMR Engineering Limited has been awarded a work order for EPC Execution of 1.00 MW (AC) Solar PV in Bihar.</li><li>The contract is worth Rs. 4,00,00,000/- (Rupees Four Crore only), inclusive of GST.</li><li>The contract period is 6 months for the project.</li><li>The project is located at PSS-Kharagpur, Munger, in the state of Bihar.</li><li>This is a significant step for DMR Engineering Limited in the renewable energy sector.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/78c2a078-2095-448a-9ef1-e7660c703ba6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DMR Hydroengineering & Infrastructures Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KSB] KSB Ltd Recommends Final Dividend of INR 4.40 /- (220%) per Equity Share for FY 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KSB+Ltd&title=KSB+Ltd+Recommends+Final+Dividend+of+INR+4.40+%2F-+%28220%25%29+per+Equity+Share+for+FY+2025&newsId=a750708a-5db7-4e51-9bd1-554b4c84c5d1&token=YTc1MDcwOGEtNWRi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a750708a-5db7-4e51-9bd1-554b4c84c5d1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:44:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>KSB Ltd has approved and recommended a final dividend of INR 4.40 /- (220%) per equity share for the financial year ended on December 31, 2025. This dividend is subject to approval by the members at the Annual General Meeting (AGM). The record date for the AGM and payment of final dividend is 8th May, 2026. The company&apos;s registered office is located at Office No. 601, Runwal R-Square, L.B.S. Marg, Mulund (West), Mumbai- 400 080, India.</p><ul><li>KSB Ltd has recommended a final dividend of INR 4.40 /- (220%) per equity share for the financial year 2025.</li><li>The dividend is subject to approval by the members at the Annual General Meeting (AGM).</li><li>The record date for the AGM and payment of final dividend is 8th May, 2026.</li><li>The company&apos;s registered office is located at Office No. 601, Runwal R-Square, L.B.S. Marg, Mulund (West), Mumbai- 400 080, India.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8555ed2a-2b1d-462d-abc7-30864960cf6b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KSB Ltd | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GICHSGFIN] GIC Housing Finance Ltd Allots NCDs Worth Rs. 150 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GIC+HOUSING+FINANCE+LTD.&title=GIC+Housing+Finance+Ltd+Allots+NCDs+Worth+Rs.+150+Crores&newsId=7526f7ea-94d6-4bcf-8630-965e98a0fa1d&token=NzUyNmY3ZWEtOTRk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7526f7ea-94d6-4bcf-8630-965e98a0fa1d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:44:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>GIC Housing Finance Ltd has allotted Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs) amounting to Rs. 150 Crores on a private placement basis. The allotment was made on February 25, 2026, with each NCD having a face value of Rs. 1,00,000. The allotment includes 15,000 NCDs, issued to ICICI Bank and Reliance General Insurance Company Ltd. The NCDs are proposed to be listed on BSE Limited.</p><ul><li>GIC Housing Finance Ltd allots NCDs worth Rs. 150 Crores</li><li>NCDs issued on a private placement basis</li><li>Each NCD has a face value of Rs. 1,00,000</li><li>ICICI Bank and Reliance General Insurance Company Ltd are the allottees</li><li>NCDs proposed to be listed on BSE Limited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5b7d72af-1474-4e11-b666-6d703c2bfd57.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GIC HOUSING FINANCE LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KAYPOWR] Kay Power and Paper Ltd Announces EGM with Remote e-Voting Facility for Members</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KAY+POWER+AND+PAPER+LTD.&title=Kay+Power+and+Paper+Ltd+Announces+EGM+with+Remote+e-Voting+Facility+for+Members&newsId=2e789d97-3e2f-4607-807c-fec2002964b2&token=MmU3ODlkOTctM2Uy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e789d97-3e2f-4607-807c-fec2002964b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:34:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kay Power and Paper Ltd has announced an Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) to be held on Monday, 23 March 2026 at 3.00 p.m. at the company&apos;s registered office in Satara, Maharashtra. The company is providing an electronic voting (Remote e-voting) facility to the members through the electronic voting platform of Central Depository Services Limited (CDSL). Members holding shares either in physical or demat mode as on the cut-off date, i.e., March 16th, 2026, can cast their votes electronically on the businesses set out in the Notice of Extra Ordinary General Meeting. The e-voting will commence from 9.00 a.m. on March 20th, 2026, and will end at 5.00 p.m. on March 22nd, 2026.</p><ul><li>Kay Power and Paper Ltd announces Extra Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) on 23 March 2026</li><li>Electronic voting (Remote e-voting) facility provided through CDSL platform</li><li>Cut-off date for members to participate is 16 March 2026</li><li>Members can cast votes electronically on businesses outlined in the Notice of EGM</li><li>E-voting to commence on 20 March 2026 and end on 22 March 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ee3ba97b-dcf1-42f6-b802-f50fd5cb67b1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KAY POWER AND PAPER LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADANIGREEN] Adani Green Energy Ltd Incorporates Wholly-Owned Subsidiary - Adani Renewable Energy Middle East Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Adani+Green+Energy+Ltd&title=Adani+Green+Energy+Ltd+Incorporates+Wholly-Owned+Subsidiary+-+Adani+Renewable+Energy+Middle+East+Ltd&newsId=dd9577fb-93ff-4e2b-868d-a82dbecf26f3&token=ZGQ5NTc3ZmItOTNm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd9577fb-93ff-4e2b-868d-a82dbecf26f3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Adani Green Energy Limited (AGEL), a leading player in the renewable energy sector, has incorporated a wholly-owned subsidiary named Adani Renewable Energy Middle East Ltd (AREMEL) on February 25, 2026, in the United Arab Emirates. This strategic move is expected to bolster AGEL&apos;s presence in the renewable energy sector and strengthen its global footprint. AREMEL, with an authorized capital of AED 10000, is a 100% subsidiary of AGEL, and its incorporation does not require any governmental or regulatory approvals.</p><ul><li>Adani Green Energy Limited has incorporated a wholly-owned subsidiary, Adani Renewable Energy Middle East Ltd, in the United Arab Emirates.</li><li>AREMEL has been incorporated with an authorized capital of AED 10000.</li><li>AGEL holds 100% of the shareholding of AREMEL.</li><li>The incorporation of AREMEL is expected to strengthen AGEL&apos;s presence in the renewable energy sector.</li><li>The incorporation does not require any governmental or regulatory approvals.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a1140e9f-4c61-4041-b9e9-b5d2fa2d3bcf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Adani Green Energy Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHRINGARMS] Prominent Promoter Group Member, Shri Natwarlal Thadeshwar, Passes Away at 86</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shringar+House+of+Mangalsutra+Ltd&title=Prominent+Promoter+Group+Member%2C+Shri+Natwarlal+Thadeshwar%2C+Passes+Away+at+86&newsId=a10b11a6-5b47-4ef3-a228-32263389ea19&token=YTEwYjExYTYtNWI0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a10b11a6-5b47-4ef3-a228-32263389ea19</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Reclassification of Shareholding</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shringar House of Mangalsutra Ltd has announced the demise of Shri Natwarlal Thadeshwar, a member of the Promoter Group, who passed away on 24th February 2026 at the age of 86. He held no equity shares in the company. The sudden and unexpected passing away of Shri Natwarlal Thadeshwar will be an irreparable loss to the company, and the board members and employees convey deep sorrow and condolences to the family. As a result of his demise, he will cease to be part of the Promoter Group of the company in accordance with Regulation 31 A (6) (c) of the SEBI LODR regulations, 2015. The new list of the Promoter and Promoter group of the company is provided in the document.</p><ul><li>Shri Natwarlal Thadeshwar, a member of the Promoter Group, has passed away at the age of 86.</li><li>He held no equity shares in the company.</li><li>His demise will result in his cessation from the Promoter Group of the company.</li><li>The new list of the Promoter and Promoter group of the company is provided in the document.</li><li>The board members and employees convey deep sorrow and condolences to the family.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/38b9658e-8a9f-4669-b6ec-31517d7d412e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shringar House of Mangalsutra Ltd | Category: Reclassification of Shareholding</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KSB] KSB Ltd Recommends Final Dividend of INR 4.40 (220%) per Equity Share for FY 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KSB+Ltd&title=KSB+Ltd+Recommends+Final+Dividend+of+INR+4.40+%28220%25%29+per+Equity+Share+for+FY+2025&newsId=16d09836-5874-4400-a111-af12136ac30c&token=MTZkMDk4MzYtNTg3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">16d09836-5874-4400-a111-af12136ac30c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>KSB Ltd has announced a final dividend recommendation of INR 4.40 (220%) per equity share for the financial year ending December 31, 2025. The dividend is subject to approval by the members at the Annual General Meeting (AGM) scheduled for May 20, 2026. The record date for the AGM and dividend payment is set for May 8, 2026. The final dividend will be paid on 17,40,39,220 equity shares with a face value of INR 2/- each, fully paid up.</p><ul><li>KSB Ltd recommends a final dividend of INR 4.40 (220%) per equity share for FY 2025.</li><li>The dividend recommendation is subject to approval by the members at the AGM on May 20, 2026.</li><li>The record date for the AGM and dividend payment is May 8, 2026.</li><li>The final dividend will be paid on 17,40,39,220 equity shares with a face value of INR 2/- each.</li><li>The announcement has been made in accordance with SEBI Regulations and is signed by the Company Secretary, Shraddha Kavathekar.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6bb5198d-96fe-46df-889b-04f135eae6dc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KSB Ltd | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EMBASSY] Embassy Office Parks REIT Participates in Kotak Chasing Growth 2026 Conference</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Embassy+Office+Parks+REIT&title=Embassy+Office+Parks+REIT+Participates+in+Kotak+Chasing+Growth+2026+Conference&newsId=f162abcd-9e97-47d0-938e-37aa564acebf&token=ZjE2MmFiY2QtOWU5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f162abcd-9e97-47d0-938e-37aa564acebf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Embassy Office Parks REIT, managed by Embassy Office Parks Management Services Private Limited, participated in the Kotak Chasing Growth 2026 Conference hosted by Kotak Institutional Equities on February 24, 2026. The event included one-on-one senior management update meetings, with the focus on Q3 FY2026 results.</p><ul><li>Embassy Office Parks REIT participated in the Kotak Chasing Growth 2026 Conference</li><li>The event was hosted by Kotak Institutional Equities on February 24, 2026</li><li>The participation included one-on-one senior management update meetings</li><li>The focus of the meetings was on Q3 FY2026 results</li><li>The event is a part of the regular updates provided by the REIT to the stakeholders</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4b4edc07-5499-4d0a-9fe2-f98be68507e4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Embassy Office Parks REIT | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EIGHTY] Eighty Jewellers Ltd Declares Interim Dividend of 1% for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Eighty+Jewellers+Ltd&title=Eighty+Jewellers+Ltd+Declares+Interim+Dividend+of+1%25+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=c4730f76-2513-4d68-9c81-8079aa33e2be&token=YzQ3MzBmNzYtMjUx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4730f76-2513-4d68-9c81-8079aa33e2be</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 12:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Eighty Jewellers Ltd has fixed Saturday, 7th March, 2026 as the record date for interim dividend for the FY 2025-26. The company declared an interim dividend of Z0.1/- (i.e. 1%) per equity share of face value of ¥10/- each. The dividend will be paid to the equity shareholders whose names appear on the Register of Members or in the records of the Depositories as beneficial owners of the shares as on the Record Date.</p><ul><li>Eighty Jewellers Ltd declares interim dividend of 1% for FY 2025-26</li><li>Record date for dividend is Saturday, 7th March, 2026</li><li>Interim dividend of Z0.1/- per equity share</li><li>Dividend to be paid on or before Tuesday, 24th March, 2026</li><li>Names of shareholders as on the Record Date will be considered for dividend payment</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/977be4aa-c60a-4ffb-9f9a-22ed6dbf6cda.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Eighty Jewellers Ltd | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>