<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:49:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ITCONS] ITCONS E-Solutions Ltd Secures INR 4314220.86 Contract from Uranium Corporation of India Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ITCONS+E-Solutions+Ltd&title=ITCONS+E-Solutions+Ltd+Secures+INR+4314220.86+Contract+from+Uranium+Corporation+of+India+Limited&newsId=89374db5-35d3-4ba2-9916-b787611c55e2&token=ODkzNzRkYjUtMzVk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">89374db5-35d3-4ba2-9916-b787611c55e2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>ITCONS E-Solutions Ltd has been awarded a new contract by Uranium Corporation of India Limited, Department of Atomic Energy, PMO. The contract, valued at INR 4314220.86, is for the deployment of 10 resources for a period of one year. The contract is set to commence on February 26, 2026, and will remain in force until February 25, 2027, unless extended further by mutual agreement between the parties. This contract marks a significant milestone for the company, reflecting the continued trust placed in them by Government agencies.</p><ul><li>Contract value: INR 4314220.86</li><li>Contract period: One year</li><li>Resources to be deployed: 10</li><li>Awarded by: Uranium Corporation of India Limited, Department of Atomic Energy, PMO</li><li>Significant milestone for the company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b7e27e0d-7c54-491b-afb3-020165051b48.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ITCONS E-Solutions Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZYDUSLIFE] Zydus Launches India&apos;s First Indigenously Developed Aflibercept 2 mg Biosimilar ANYRA™</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Zydus+Lifesciences+Ltd&title=Zydus+Launches+India%27s+First+Indigenously+Developed+Aflibercept+2+mg+Biosimilar+ANYRA%E2%84%A2&newsId=2f64ed80-5454-49a7-a19a-e54303134098&token=MmY2NGVkODAtNTQ1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2f64ed80-5454-49a7-a19a-e54303134098</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:23:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Zydus Lifesciences Ltd., an innovation-led global life sciences company, announced the launch of Anyra™, India’s first indigenously developed biosimilar of Aflibercept 2 mg. The biosimilar is indicated for the treatment of various ophthalmic conditions including neovascular (wet) Age-related Macular Degeneration (AMD), visual impairment due to macular edema secondary to Retinal Vein Occlusion (Branch RVO or Central RVO), visual impairment due to Diabetic Macular Edema (DME), Diabetic Retinopathy (DR), and visual impairment due to Myopic Choroidal Neovascularization (mCNV). This launch reinforces Zydus&apos; commitment to advancing ophthalmic care and expanding access to high-quality, affordable biologics for patients across India. With over 100 million people in India living with diabetes, the biosimilar is expected to improve treatment adherence, reduce preventable blindness, and lower long-term disease burden.</p><ul><li>Zydus launches India’s first indigenously developed Aflibercept 2 mg biosimilar ANYRA™.</li><li>ANYRA™ is indicated for the treatment of various ophthalmic conditions.</li><li>Launch aims to advance ophthalmic care and expand access to affordable biologics in India.</li><li>Over 100 million people in India live with diabetes, making it one of the largest diabetic populations globally.</li><li>Biosimilar expected to improve treatment adherence, reduce preventable blindness, and lower long-term disease burden.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/92f7e54f-ba77-47df-bf72-b1ed59b54905.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Zydus Lifesciences Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[REFEXRENEW] Refex Renewables &amp; Infrastructure Ltd: No Official Communication from Income-Tax Department on Search and Seizure Outcome</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Refex+Renewables+%26+Infrastructure+Ltd&title=Refex+Renewables+%26+Infrastructure+Ltd%3A+No+Official+Communication+from+Income-Tax+Department+on+Search+and+Seizure+Outcome&newsId=02cd76d4-a17c-430c-9cf3-08f298258b2a&token=MDJjZDc2ZDQtYTE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02cd76d4-a17c-430c-9cf3-08f298258b2a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Refex Renewables &amp; Infrastructure Ltd has clarified that there is no official communication from the Income-Tax Department regarding the outcome of the search and seizure operations conducted in December 2025. This confirmation comes in response to an RTI application filed by the company&apos;s legal team. The company assures stakeholders of its commitment to ethical conduct and legal compliance.</p><ul><li>Refex Renewables &amp; Infrastructure Ltd confirms no official communication from the Income-Tax Department on search and seizure outcome.</li><li>The confirmation comes in response to an RTI application filed by the company&apos;s legal team.</li><li>The Income-Tax Department confirmed no press release(s), official statement(s), press communication(s) or public communications(s) were issued.</li><li>Refex Renewables &amp; Infrastructure Ltd is a law-abiding company and will cooperate with the authorities.</li><li>The company is committed to ethical conduct and legal compliance.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/842c2de7-db14-4eb0-a7ef-6b837df9928c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Refex Renewables & Infrastructure Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NCLIND] Kakatiya Industries Pvt Ltd Acquires Shares of NCL Industries Ltd Worth Rs. 45,23,27,900</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NCL+INDUSTRIES+LTD.-%24&title=Kakatiya+Industries+Pvt+Ltd+Acquires+Shares+of+NCL+Industries+Ltd+Worth+Rs.+45%2C23%2C27%2C900&newsId=4a0216aa-2be8-4bc7-93ee-e87a2ae64278&token=NGEwMjE2YWEtMmJl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a0216aa-2be8-4bc7-93ee-e87a2ae64278</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>According to a disclosure made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011, Kakatiya Industries Pvt Ltd has acquired shares of NCL Industries Ltd. The acquisition was made through the open market and amounted to Rs. 45,23,27,900. Post-acquisition, Kakatiya Industries Pvt Ltd holds 527,193 shares of NCL Industries Ltd, which constitutes 0.00% of the total share and voting capital. The acquisition took place on 31/12/2025, 16/02/2026, and 17/02/2026.</p><ul><li>Kakatiya Industries Pvt Ltd acquires shares of NCL Industries Ltd worth Rs. 45,23,27,900</li><li>The acquisition was made through the open market</li><li>Post-acquisition, Kakatiya Industries Pvt Ltd holds 0.00% of the total share and voting capital</li><li>The acquisition took place on 31/12/2025, 16/02/2026, and 17/02/2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/977D6C31_D4AB_44E1_882F_087D999BAC97_091329.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NCL INDUSTRIES LTD.-$ | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[REFEXRENEW] Securities Appellate Tribunal Grants Stay on Penalty for Refex Renewables Promoter</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Refex+Renewables+%26+Infrastructure+Ltd&title=Securities+Appellate+Tribunal+Grants+Stay+on+Penalty+for+Refex+Renewables+Promoter&newsId=977a7a6a-12cf-45b7-bce3-4fad4ecdc66e&token=OTc3YTdhNmEtMTJj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">977a7a6a-12cf-45b7-bce3-4fad4ecdc66e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Securities Appellate Tribunal (SAT) has granted a stay on the penalty imposed on Mr. Anil Jain, Promoter &amp; Non-Executive Director of Refex Renewables &amp; Infrastructure Limited, by SEBI. The penalty was levied in a matter of alleged insider trading activities in the scrip of Refex Industries Limited. The stay is subject to the deposit of 50% of the penalty amount with the SEBI within four weeks from the date of the order passed by SAT. This order was passed by SAT on February 13, 2026, and uploaded on the portal on February 18, 2026.</p><ul><li>Securities Appellate Tribunal grants stay on penalty for Refex Renewables Promoter</li><li>Stay subject to deposit of 50% of the penalty amount with the SEBI within four weeks</li><li>Penalty imposed by SEBI in a matter of alleged insider trading activities</li><li>Order passed by SAT on February 13, 2026, and uploaded on February 18, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/52aa4914-3962-4ac0-87df-bbb4e66456cf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Refex Renewables & Infrastructure Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KALLAM] Kallam Textiles Ltd. Receives Notice from NCLT Amaravati Bench Regarding Union Bank of India Case</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kallam+Textiles+Ltd-%24&title=Kallam+Textiles+Ltd.+Receives+Notice+from+NCLT+Amaravati+Bench+Regarding+Union+Bank+of+India+Case&newsId=0d3cb733-46c6-4516-9356-9c70c6fff7a7&token=MGQzY2I3MzMtNDZj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d3cb733-46c6-4516-9356-9c70c6fff7a7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 04:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kallam Textiles Ltd. has received a Notice from the NCLT Amaravati Bench regarding a case filed by Union Bank of India. The Notice, dated 18-02-2026, informs of the next hearing date on 11-03-2026 for Case No: C.P. (IB)/3(AM)2026. The Company Secretary &amp; Compliance Officer, Golagani Ramesh Kumar, has been directed to issue a notice to the Respondent and file a Counter affidavit within four weeks of receiving the Notice. The matter is listed for further consideration on 11.03.2026.</p><ul><li>Kallam Textiles Ltd. received a Notice from the NCLT Amaravati Bench</li><li>The Notice is regarding a case filed by Union Bank of India</li><li>The next hearing date is set for 11-03-2026</li><li>Company Secretary &amp; Compliance Officer directed to issue a notice to the Respondent</li><li>The Respondents are required to file a Counter affidavit within four weeks of receiving the Notice</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1c455154-c3a2-4f43-ba23-6f98b30308ad.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kallam Textiles Ltd-$ | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ARMAN] Varigate Advisory Services Disposes Equity Shares in Arman Holdings Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Arman+Holdings+Ltd&title=Varigate+Advisory+Services+Disposes+Equity+Shares+in+Arman+Holdings+Limited&newsId=d8689312-c68b-4c47-a189-095a63e5a0d8&token=ZDg2ODkzMTItYzY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d8689312-c68b-4c47-a189-095a63e5a0d8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:57:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Sale</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Varigate Advisory Services (P) Ltd, a non-promoter entity, has disclosed the disposal of equity shares in Arman Holdings Limited. The disposal was made by Varigate Advisory Services (P) Ltd and Sanjay Otawat, who are Persons Acting in Concert (PACs). The disclosure was made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011. The disposal took place on the open market. The total share capital of Arman Holdings Limited remains at Rs. 5,21,05,000 comprising of 52,10,500 equity shares of face value of Rs. 10/- each.</p><ul><li>Varigate Advisory Services (P) Ltd and Sanjay Otawat, Persons Acting in Concert (PACs), dispose equity shares in Arman Holdings Limited.</li><li>The disposal was made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</li><li>The disposal took place on the open market.</li><li>Arman Holdings Limited&apos;s total share capital remains at Rs. 5,21,05,000 comprising of 52,10,500 equity shares of face value of Rs. 10/- each.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/986A8F03_E8AC_4FA2_A167_83D42DED98A6_092221.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Arman Holdings Ltd | Category: Sale</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KWIL] Unilever Acquires Majority Shares in Kwality Walls (India) Ltd Through Scheme of Arrangement</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=KWIL&title=Unilever+Acquires+Majority+Shares+in+Kwality+Walls+%28India%29+Ltd+Through+Scheme+of+Arrangement&newsId=4d221aa4-a930-4d6e-b1ec-ab4b5ca42dfe&token=NGQyMjFhYTQtYTkz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d221aa4-a930-4d6e-b1ec-ab4b5ca42dfe</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:55:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Unilever PLC and other promoters have acquired a majority stake in Kwality Walls (India) Ltd. The acquisition was made pursuant to a Scheme of Arrangement for the demerger of the Ice Cream Business Undertaking between Hindustan Unilever Limited and Kwality Wall’s (India) Limited. The demerger was approved by the National Company Law Tribunal, Mumbai Bench, on 30th October, 2025 and took effect from 1st December, 2025. Unilever PLC, along with other promoters, now holds 1,45,44,12,858 shares, which is 61.90% of the total voting rights in Kwality Walls (India) Ltd.</p><ul><li>Unilever PLC and other promoters have acquired a majority stake in Kwality Walls (India) Ltd.</li><li>The acquisition was made pursuant to a Scheme of Arrangement for the demerger of the Ice Cream Business Undertaking between Hindustan Unilever Limited and Kwality Wall’s (India) Limited.</li><li>The demerger was approved by the National Company Law Tribunal, Mumbai Bench, on 30th October, 2025 and took effect from 1st December, 2025.</li><li>Unilever PLC, along with other promoters, now holds 1,45,44,12,858 shares, which is 61.90% of the total voting rights in Kwality Walls (India) Ltd.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9A2B4CCB_7308_4C7F_B7CF_B25E67566C60_092404.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: KWIL | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[STARCEMENT] SBI Mutual Fund Reduces Star Cement Shareholding by 1.0103%</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Star+Cement+Ltd&title=SBI+Mutual+Fund+Reduces+Star+Cement+Shareholding+by+1.0103%25&newsId=70523bb3-75e6-4b35-8acf-b56354c89678&token=NzA1MjNiYjMtNzVl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70523bb3-75e6-4b35-8acf-b56354c89678</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:53:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Sale</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>SBI Mutual Fund has sold 40,83,331 shares representing 1.0103% of the paid-up share capital of Star Cement Ltd. The final holding of SBI Mutual Fund, under its various schemes, as at the close of business hours on February 17, 2026, was 2.5811% of the paid-up share capital of Star Cement Ltd.</p><ul><li>SBI Mutual Fund sold 40,83,331 shares of Star Cement Ltd.</li><li>The sale represents 1.0103% of the paid-up share capital of Star Cement Ltd.</li><li>The final holding of SBI Mutual Fund is now 2.5811% of the paid-up share capital of Star Cement Ltd.</li><li>The sale was made on February 17, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/67F0817A_2A3A_4998_8895_EFBABF1C4027_092108.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Star Cement Ltd | Category: Sale</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[REFEX] Securities Appellate Tribunal Grants Stay on Penalty for Refex Industries&apos; Chairman</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Refex+Industries+Limited&title=Securities+Appellate+Tribunal+Grants+Stay+on+Penalty+for+Refex+Industries%27+Chairman&newsId=37807f40-9287-4b9f-aa4e-7646da1660d8&token=Mzc4MDdmNDAtOTI4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37807f40-9287-4b9f-aa4e-7646da1660d8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 03:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Securities Appellate Tribunal (SAT) has granted a stay on the recovery of penalty imposed by the Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) on Mr. Anil Jain, Promoter, Chairman, and Managing Director of Refex Industries Limited. The penalty was imposed due to alleged insider trading activities of certain entities in the scrip of Refex Industries Limited. The stay is subject to the deposit of 50% of the penalty amount within four weeks from the date of the order passed by SAT.</p><ul><li>Securities Appellate Tribunal grants stay on SEBI&apos;s penalty order</li><li>Stay subject to deposit of 50% of the penalty amount within four weeks</li><li>Penalty imposed on Mr. Anil Jain, Promoter, Chairman, and Managing Director of Refex Industries Limited</li><li>Alleged insider trading activities in Refex Industries Limited&apos;s scrip</li><li>Order passed by SAT on February 13, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c72aa0d8-2442-4402-9fa9-8c844feb52fc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Refex Industries Limited | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>