<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:49:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[NBCC] NBCC (India) Ltd Receives Tax Demand from CGST Authorities; Anticipates No Material Impact</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NBCC+%28India%29+Ltd&title=NBCC+%28India%29+Ltd+Receives+Tax+Demand+from+CGST+Authorities%3B+Anticipates+No+Material+Impact&newsId=164bc231-7d4b-4deb-b57d-580d1fab42db&token=MTY0YmMyMzEtN2Q0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">164bc231-7d4b-4deb-b57d-580d1fab42db</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:42:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>NBCC (India) Ltd, a Government of India Enterprise, has received a tax demand from Central Goods &amp; Service Tax authorities under the Goods and Services Tax (CGST) Act, 2017. The demand includes tax, penalty, and interest totaling approximately 79.95 crores INR for two overseas projects. The company is in the process of filing an appeal against the orders before the appropriate authority and does not anticipate any material impact on its financial, operational, or other business activities. The demand is primarily due to the alleged reversal of proportional ITC attributable to exempt supplies and ITC claimed from cancelled dealers, return defaulters, and tax non-payers. NBCC executed both projects as a Project Management Consultant (PMC) in overseas countries and handed them over. The company is taking necessary steps to file an appeal and evaluating the matter in accordance with the SEBI LODR Regulations and Industry Standards.</p><ul><li>NBCC (India) Ltd received a tax demand from CGST authorities under the GST Act, 2017</li><li>The demand includes tax, penalty, and interest totaling approximately 79.95 crores INR</li><li>The demand is primarily due to the alleged reversal of proportional ITC and ITC claimed from cancelled dealers, return defaulters, and tax non-payers</li><li>NBCC executed both projects as a Project Management Consultant (PMC) in overseas countries</li><li>The company is in the process of filing an appeal against the orders before the appropriate authority</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/33a2318c-9d2b-4d08-8144-4b7d7f1ce36c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NBCC (India) Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[OXYGENTAPH] Oxygenta Pharmaceutical Reports Q3 and Nine Months Results with a Loss of Rs. 632.65 Lakhs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Oxygenta+Pharmaceutical+Ltd&title=Oxygenta+Pharmaceutical+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+with+a+Loss+of+Rs.+632.65+Lakhs&newsId=5938b8e1-81d9-480d-81d9-71052d6b2efb&token=NTkzOGI4ZTEtODFk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5938b8e1-81d9-480d-81d9-71052d6b2efb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:42:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Oxygenta Pharmaceutical Limited has reported its un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31.12.2025. The company reported a loss of Rs. 632.65 Lakhs for the quarter. The re-constitution of the Internal Complaints Committee (ICC) was also approved at the meeting. The company is committed to achieving full compliance and transparency in its reporting.</p><ul><li>Loss of Rs. 632.65 Lakhs for the quarter</li><li>Revenue of Rs. 3393.09 Lakhs for the quarter</li><li>Re-constitution of the Internal Complaints Committee (ICC)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f1e823da-80e2-4519-9e48-3d18d3ab06c0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Oxygenta Pharmaceutical Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WELENT] Welspun Enterprises Ltd Receives 25% of Issue Proceeds from Preferential Issue of Convertible Warrants</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Welspun+Enterprises+Ltd&title=Welspun+Enterprises+Ltd+Receives+25%25+of+Issue+Proceeds+from+Preferential+Issue+of+Convertible+Warrants&newsId=45d8b777-e419-4ce6-be76-6aed86375a40&token=NDVkOGI3NzctZTQx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">45d8b777-e419-4ce6-be76-6aed86375a40</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:41:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Welspun Enterprises Ltd has received 25% of the issue proceeds from the Preferential Issue (PI) of convertible warrants. The issue size was Rs 1,000.002 crore, out of which Rs 250.00 crore was received during the period from November 26, 2025 to December 01, 2025. The remaining Rs 750.00 crore is yet to be received from the warrant holders. The warrants can be converted into equity shares within 18 months from the date of allotment. The Monitoring Agency Report for the quarter ended December 31, 2025 has been considered by the Audit Committee and Board of Directors.</p><ul><li>Welspun Enterprises Ltd received 25% of the issue proceeds from the Preferential Issue of convertible warrants.</li><li>The issue size was Rs 1,000.002 crore, out of which Rs 250.00 crore was received during the period from November 26, 2025 to December 01, 2025.</li><li>The remaining Rs 750.00 crore is yet to be received from the warrant holders.</li><li>The warrants can be converted into equity shares within 18 months from the date of allotment.</li><li>The Monitoring Agency Report for the quarter ended December 31, 2025 has been considered by the Audit Committee and Board of Directors.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1524e5b1-5165-4598-85e2-d6ef540f1c7d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Welspun Enterprises Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SCILAL] Shipping Corporation of India Land and Assets Ltd Approves Unaudited Standalone Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months of FY2025-2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shipping+Corporation+of+India+Land+and+Assets+Ltd&title=Shipping+Corporation+of+India+Land+and+Assets+Ltd+Approves+Unaudited+Standalone+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+of+FY2025-2026&newsId=d48e2f12-360d-488d-86ed-db7efd831466&token=ZDQ4ZTJmMTItMzYw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d48e2f12-360d-488d-86ed-db7efd831466</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:41:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Shipping Corporation of India Land and Assets Ltd considered and approved the unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31.12.2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 1,749 crores for the nine months ended 31.12.2025. The profit before tax for the quarter is 167 crores, while the profit before tax for the nine months is 518 crores. The total comprehensive income for the period is 1,25,452 crores.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the nine months ended 31.12.2025 is 1,749 crores.</li><li>Profit before tax for the quarter is 167 crores and 518 crores for the nine months.</li><li>Total comprehensive income for the period is 1,25,452 crores.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b0854a15-cc9d-40b5-b5a2-8f4db1f37c54.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shipping Corporation of India Land and Assets Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PURVA] Puravankara Ltd Provides Corporate Guarantee of Rs. 440 Crores to Wholly Owned Subsidiary</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Puravankara+Ltd&title=Puravankara+Ltd+Provides+Corporate+Guarantee+of+Rs.+440+Crores+to+Wholly+Owned+Subsidiary&newsId=b860ac9b-5f66-44ec-8ab5-8bcf5480b40a&token=Yjg2MGFjOWItNWY2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b860ac9b-5f66-44ec-8ab5-8bcf5480b40a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:41:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Puravankara Limited has provided a corporate guarantee on behalf of Purva Oak Private Limited, a wholly owned subsidiary of the Company. The guarantee is towards the issuance of Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs) of Rs. 440,00,00,000/- (Rupees Four Hundred and Forty Crores only) in favour of Catalyst Trusteeship Limited. The guarantee is a liability for the Company, but at this point, there is no impact of this guarantee on the Company.</p><ul><li>Puravankara Ltd provides corporate guarantee to Purva Oak Private Limited</li><li>Guarantee is for an aggregate amount of Rs. 440,00,00,000/-</li><li>Guarantee is towards the issuance of Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs)</li><li>Catalyst Trusteeship Limited is the trustee for the NCDs</li><li>No impact of this guarantee on the Company at this point</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/610482db-9d3b-422b-9129-dcce5cc00e3f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Puravankara Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ONESOURCE] Tenshi Pharmaceuticals Acquires 2,05,000 Shares of Onesource Specialty Pharma Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Onesource+Specialty+Pharma+Ltd&title=Tenshi+Pharmaceuticals+Acquires+2%2C05%2C000+Shares+of+Onesource+Specialty+Pharma+Ltd&newsId=3ae226bf-237f-4746-ae26-068d9cce01f5&token=M2FlMjI2YmYtMjM3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ae226bf-237f-4746-ae26-068d9cce01f5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tenshi Pharmaceuticals Private Limited has acquired 2,05,000 shares of Onesource Specialty Pharma Ltd. This acquisition increases Tenshi Pharmaceuticals&apos; holding to 3,48,55,105 shares, which is 30.41% of the total diluted share/voting capital of Onesource Specialty Pharma Ltd. The acquisition was made through the open market on February 02, 2026.</p><ul><li>Tenshi Pharmaceuticals Private Limited has acquired 2,05,000 shares of Onesource Specialty Pharma Ltd</li><li>This acquisition increases Tenshi Pharmaceuticals&apos; holding to 3,48,55,105 shares</li><li>The acquisition is 30.41% of the total diluted share/voting capital of Onesource Specialty Pharma Ltd</li><li>The acquisition was made through the open market</li><li>The acquisition date was February 02, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6EE80CC0_C801_4A48_952D_5BCFE9293E65_174519.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Onesource Specialty Pharma Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ASIANHOTNR] Elana Holdings Pte Ltd Acquires 39.42% Stake in Asian Hotels (North) Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Asian+Hotels+%28North%29+Limited&title=Elana+Holdings+Pte+Ltd+Acquires+39.42%25+Stake+in+Asian+Hotels+%28North%29+Ltd&newsId=85d9ecfb-6114-4e65-828b-f6c54af3d864&token=ODVkOWVjZmItNjEx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85d9ecfb-6114-4e65-828b-f6c54af3d864</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:34:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Elana Holdings Pte Ltd has acquired 1,68,05,943 equity shares of Asian Hotels (North) Limited through preferential allotment, representing 39.42% of the total issued and paid-up equity share capital of the company. This acquisition was made in compliance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</p><ul><li>Elana Holdings Pte Ltd has acquired 39.42% stake in Asian Hotels (North) Ltd.</li><li>The acquisition was made through preferential allotment of 1,68,05,943 equity shares.</li><li>This acquisition increases Elana Holdings Pte Ltd&apos;s holding to 54.37% from 24.68% of the total issued and paid-up equity share capital.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/DF7D325C_5778_4160_9DB6_AAAB7BC53AE8_172459.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Asian Hotels (North) Limited | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[APTANN] Andhra Pradesh Tanneries Ltd to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months of FY2025-26 on Feb 13, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Andhra+Pradesh+Tanneries+Ltd&title=Andhra+Pradesh+Tanneries+Ltd+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+nine+months+of+FY2025-26+on+Feb+13%2C+2026&newsId=a05eaa7d-e2bd-48bc-98cc-58439d1764e2&token=YTA1ZWFhN2QtZTJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a05eaa7d-e2bd-48bc-98cc-58439d1764e2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Andhra Pradesh Tanneries Ltd has announced that a Board Meeting will be held on February 13, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 30, 2025. The trading window for dealing in the company’s securities will be closed from January 01, 2026, till closure of business hours on February 15, 2026, in accordance with the Company’s Code of Internal Procedures and Conduct for Regulating, Monitoring and Reporting of Trading by Insiders.</p><ul><li>Andhra Pradesh Tanneries Ltd to consider and approve unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months of FY2025-26 on Feb 13, 2026</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the company’s securities to be closed from Jan 1, 2026, to Feb 15, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bd2ceb7e-4609-4bdc-99b0-f8822f202f61.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Andhra Pradesh Tanneries Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RIR] RIR Power Electronics Ltd to Approve Q3 Financial Results on 09/02/2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RIR+Power+Electronics+Ltd&title=RIR+Power+Electronics+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+Financial+Results+on+09%2F02%2F2026&newsId=ffdb01b3-46ab-4c56-a2eb-8999bc927221&token=ZmZkYjAxYjMtNDZh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ffdb01b3-46ab-4c56-a2eb-8999bc927221</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>RIR Power Electronics Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 9 February 2026 to consider and approve the Un-audited Standalone Financial Results for the third quarter and nine months ended 31% December, 2025. The Trading Window has been closed since 1°* January, 2026 and will open 48 hours after the announcement of the financial results.</p><ul><li>RIR Power Electronics Ltd to consider and approve Un-audited Standalone Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended 31% December, 2025</li><li>Trading Window closed since 1°* January, 2026 and will open 48 hours after the announcement of financial results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/aebfb5c5-b3e6-46ed-971f-443f1268be8a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RIR Power Electronics Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BGWTATO] Bhagwati Autocast Ltd. Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BHAGWATI+AUTOCAST+LTD.&title=Bhagwati+Autocast+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025&newsId=9f3e95ab-babf-49c3-8cdc-7bbe238f9aeb&token=OWYzZTk1YWItYmFi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9f3e95ab-babf-49c3-8cdc-7bbe238f9aeb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bhagwati Autocast Ltd. has announced its unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The total income for the nine months stood at Rs. 12,634.50 Lakhs with a net profit of Rs. 989.09 Lakhs. The company operates in a single segment, manufacturing of castings. The financial results have been prepared in accordance with the Companies (Indian Accounting Standards) Rules, 2015 and other recognized accounting practices. The company has made an additional provision of Rs. 38.72 Lakhs towards past service cost due to the implementation of new Labour Codes by the Government of India.</p><ul><li>Total income for the nine months ended 31st December 2025: Rs. 12,634.50 Lakhs</li><li>Net profit for the nine months ended 31st December 2025: Rs. 989.09 Lakhs</li><li>The company operates in a single segment - manufacturing of castings</li><li>Financial results prepared in accordance with Companies (Indian Accounting Standards) Rules, 2015</li><li>Additional provision of Rs. 38.72 Lakhs towards past service cost due to new Labour Codes implementation</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/64307487-9b43-4565-9d65-920fbbe55cad.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BHAGWATI AUTOCAST LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>