<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:26:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[WILLIMFI] Williamson Financial Services Ltd Updates Email Id</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=WILLIAMSON+FINANCIAL+SERVICES+LTD.&title=Williamson+Financial+Services+Ltd+Updates+Email+Id&newsId=7c2c8d59-6a35-43e3-bcc9-48c712f8fdc6&token=N2MyYzhkNTktNmEz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c2c8d59-6a35-43e3-bcc9-48c712f8fdc6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Williamson Financial Services Ltd has updated its email id from administrator@mcleodrussel.com to administrator@williamsonfinancial.co. The company has also requested to remove the old email id from the database and update the new one in the records.</p><ul><li>Email id of Williamson Financial Services Ltd has been changed</li><li>The new email id is administrator@williamsonfinancial.co</li><li>The old email id has been requested to be removed from the database</li><li>Companies are requested to update their records with the new email id</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/be46415c-d5b0-4697-84d7-44e923ac805a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: WILLIAMSON FINANCIAL SERVICES LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DIXON] Dixon Technologies to Approve Un-Audited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months of FY 2025-2026 on Jan 29, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Dixon+Technologies+%28India%29+Ltd&title=Dixon+Technologies+to+Approve+Un-Audited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+of+FY+2025-2026+on+Jan+29%2C+2026&newsId=84449bf1-4d9d-4feb-a83e-aec448f2e3de&token=ODQ0NDliZjEtNGQ5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">84449bf1-4d9d-4feb-a83e-aec448f2e3de</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dixon Technologies (India) Ltd has informed BSE that their Board of Directors will meet on 29th January 2026 to consider and approve the Un-Audited Financial Results (Standalone and Consolidated) for the Quarter and Nine Months ended on 31st December 2025. The Trading Window for dealing in securities of the Company has been closed since 1st January 2026 and will reopen 48 hours after the declaration of the Financial results.</p><ul><li>Dixon Technologies to approve Un-Audited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months of FY 2025-2026 on Jan 29, 2026</li><li>The meeting will be held on 29th January 2026</li><li>Financial Results to be approved are for the Quarter and Nine Months ended on 31st December 2025</li><li>Trading Window for dealing in securities of the Company has been closed since 1st January 2026</li><li>The Trading Window will reopen 48 hours after the declaration of the Financial results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/499e1a72-ec7d-475e-8372-70e1fde0912a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Dixon Technologies (India) Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BELRISE] Belrise Industries Acquires Aerospace Equipment in Liquidation Process for Euro 350,000</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Belrise+Industries+Ltd&title=Belrise+Industries+Acquires+Aerospace+Equipment+in+Liquidation+Process+for+Euro+350%2C000&newsId=f9439414-f352-4cbd-9f86-125018a71c96&token=Zjk0Mzk0MTQtZjM1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9439414-f352-4cbd-9f86-125018a71c96</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Belrise Industries Limited has acquired certain aerospace-related equipment for a total consideration of Euro 350,000 through its subsidiaries. The acquisition was carried out pursuant to an Order of Private Sale on January 21, 2026, passed by the Commercial Court of Arras, France, in accordance with the provisions of Article L.642-19 of the French Commercial Code. This transaction will enable the company to expand into the domain of aerospace and defence by immediately partnering with existing aerospace OEMs and Tier-1 suppliers in Europe. The transaction does not fall within the related party transactions and has been undertaken in the ordinary course of business of the subsidiary.</p><ul><li>Belrise Industries acquires aerospace equipment for Euro 350,000</li><li>Acquisition carried out through subsidiaries pursuant to an Order of Private Sale</li><li>Transaction to enable company to expand into aerospace and defence domain</li><li>Immediate partnership with existing aerospace OEMs and Tier-1 suppliers in Europe</li><li>Transaction not related to party transactions and undertaken in ordinary course of business</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5d805620-7c29-49f4-9d2e-d73e34986c72.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Belrise Industries Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NISMGMT] NIS Management Ltd. Voluntarily Discloses Unaudited Financial Results, Closes Trading Window</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NIS+Management+Ltd&title=NIS+Management+Ltd.+Voluntarily+Discloses+Unaudited+Financial+Results%2C+Closes+Trading+Window&newsId=2620540a-5356-4c62-bfd5-7e2ee16a18ed&token=MjYyMDU0MGEtNTM1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2620540a-5356-4c62-bfd5-7e2ee16a18ed</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>NIS Management Ltd., a company listed on the SME Platform, has proposed to voluntarily disclose its Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the period ended December 31, 2025. As a measure of good governance and in compliance with the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, the company has closed the trading window for directors, officers, designated employees, and their immediate relatives until 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results.</p><ul><li>NIS Management Ltd. to disclose Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the period ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>Trading window closed for directors, officers, designated employees, and their immediate relatives until 48 hours after the financial results declaration.</li><li>Disclosure is a voluntary measure for good governance.</li><li>Company is listed on the SME Platform and governed by the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7eccd969-114e-4c65-8198-92d6a899423a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NIS Management Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INFOBEAN] Infobeans Technologies Ltd Approves Q3 2025 Financial Statements &amp; Announces Bonus Issue of Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Infobeans+Technologies+Ltd&title=Infobeans+Technologies+Ltd+Approves+Q3+2025+Financial+Statements+%26+Announces+Bonus+Issue+of+Shares&newsId=53cf1631-3120-4742-afda-16948ed584c8&token=NTNjZjE2MzEtMzEy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53cf1631-3120-4742-afda-16948ed584c8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Infobeans Technologies Ltd, a company formerly known as Infobeans Systems India Private Limited, announced the approval of its un-audited financial statement for the quarter ended on 31st Dec, 2025 during a board meeting held on 22nd January, 2026. The company&apos;s board also approved a bonus issue of shares in the ratio of 3:1, i.e 3 bonus equity shares for every 1 fully paid-up Equity Share held, subject to approval of the members of the company and statutory and regulatory approvals. The record date for determining the entitlement of the members of the company to receive bonus equity shares is 27th February, 2026.</p><ul><li>Approval of un-audited financial statement for Q3 2025</li><li>Bonus issue of shares in the ratio of 3:1</li><li>Record date for bonus share entitlement set to 27th February, 2026</li><li>Subject to approval of members and statutory authorities</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f3f46ae9-519b-41f4-b05d-59dfb379ff61.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Infobeans Technologies Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADANIENT] Adani Enterprises&apos; Subsidiary to Acquire Remaining Stake in IANS India Private Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADANI+ENTERPRISES+LTD.&title=Adani+Enterprises%27+Subsidiary+to+Acquire+Remaining+Stake+in+IANS+India+Private+Limited&newsId=6b6a7e35-70b9-4548-818d-d8d37f5600ce&token=NmI2YTdlMzUtNzBi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6b6a7e35-70b9-4548-818d-d8d37f5600ce</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:01:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Adani Enterprises Ltd. announced that its wholly owned subsidiary, AMG Media Networks Limited (AMNL), has signed a Share Purchase Agreement (SPA) to acquire the remaining stake in IANS India Private Limited. Upon completion of the proposed transaction, IANS will become a wholly owned step-down subsidiary of Adani Enterprises Ltd. The transaction is subject to customary conditions and was received by the company on January 21, 2026 at 10:28 PM.</p><ul><li>Adani Enterprises&apos; subsidiary, AMG Media Networks Limited, to acquire remaining stake in IANS India Private Limited.</li><li>Upon completion, IANS will become a wholly owned step-down subsidiary of Adani Enterprises Ltd.</li><li>Transaction is subject to customary conditions.</li><li>IANS is a subsidiary of AMNL.</li><li>Transaction does not involve issuance of shares or other related party transactions.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e4b75819-f2cb-452a-82d9-4b87da86b5b6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADANI ENTERPRISES LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MANAPPURAM] Manappuram Finance Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025, Considers Interim Dividend</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MANAPPURAM+FINANCE+LTD.&title=Manappuram+Finance+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025%2C+Considers+Interim+Dividend&newsId=7c123b9e-258e-45d2-83d6-4247a349dc8b&token=N2MxMjNiOWUtMjU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c123b9e-258e-45d2-83d6-4247a349dc8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Manappuram Finance Ltd has announced a meeting of its Board of Directors on January 29, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company is also considering the declaration of an interim dividend. This notice is in accordance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The company&apos;s Trading Window for dealing in securities will remain closed till the end of 48 hours after the declaration of financial results and will reopen on February 02, 2026.</p><ul><li>Manappuram Finance Ltd to consider and approve Q3 and nine months financial results for 2025</li><li>Company considering declaration of interim dividend</li><li>Trading Window for dealing in securities to remain closed till February 02, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9bba2da5-2414-494e-a4f1-278b79665147.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MANAPPURAM FINANCE LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TELECANOR] TeleCanor Global Ltd. Approves Remuneration Hike for Managing Director and Whole-Time Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TELECANOR+GLOBAL+LTD.&title=TeleCanor+Global+Ltd.+Approves+Remuneration+Hike+for+Managing+Director+and+Whole-Time+Director&newsId=082ab4a0-fd32-45b2-8738-da1db2101fae&token=MDgyYWI0YTAtZmQz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">082ab4a0-fd32-45b2-8738-da1db2101fae</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:47:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of TeleCanor Global Ltd., at its meeting held on January 22, 2026, approved the remuneration for the Managing Director and Whole-Time Director. The Managing Director, Mr. Marutiram Praturi, is set to receive a monthly remuneration of Rs. 15,00,000/- (Rupees Fifteen Lakhs only) effective from January 1, 2026, along with an advance salary of three months and a bonus at the rate of 5% on sales. The Whole-Time Director, Ms. Pilli Swetha, will be paid a monthly remuneration of Rs. 1,50,000/- (Rupees One Lakh Fifty Thousand only) from the same date. The remuneration is subject to shareholder approval and necessary compliances.</p><ul><li>TeleCanor Global Ltd. Board approves remuneration for Managing Director and Whole-Time Director</li><li>Managing Director&apos;s monthly remuneration set at Rs. 15,00,000</li><li>Whole-Time Director&apos;s monthly remuneration set at Rs. 1,50,000</li><li>Remuneration subject to shareholder approval and necessary compliances</li><li>Advance salary and bonus approved for the Managing Director</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/701940ca-ee65-4d63-96d3-73329b11b954.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TELECANOR GLOBAL LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IRONWOOD] Ironwood Education Ltd. Approves Allotment of 17,11,670 Equity Shares on Preferential Basis</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ironwood+Education+Ltd&title=Ironwood+Education+Ltd.+Approves+Allotment+of+17%2C11%2C670+Equity+Shares+on+Preferential+Basis&newsId=77cbac96-cc2d-4464-98dd-658b1a1a3fe4&token=NzdjYmFjOTYtY2My</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77cbac96-cc2d-4464-98dd-658b1a1a3fe4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ironwood Education Ltd. has approved the allotment of 17,11,670 equity shares of Rs. 10/- each at an issue price of Rs. 45/- on preferential basis. The Board of Directors made this decision at their meeting held on January 22, 2026. The shares will be issued to non-promoters and non-promoter groups in accordance with the SEBI (Issue of Capital and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2018 and the Companies Act, 2013. The total consideration for the shares is Rs. 7,70,25,150.</p><ul><li>Ironwood Education Ltd. approves allotment of 17,11,670 equity shares on preferential basis</li><li>The shares are issued at an issue price of Rs. 45/- each, with a premium of Rs. 35/-</li><li>The total consideration for the shares is Rs. 7,70,25,150</li><li>The allotment is made to non-promoters and non-promoter groups</li><li>The decision is made in accordance with the SEBI (Issue of Capital and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2018 and the Companies Act, 2013</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a4c84bef-fe83-4a23-9943-e41842ddefa9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ironwood Education Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AMAGI] Amagi Media Labs Ltd. Becomes First Cloud-Native SaaS Company to List on Indian Stock Exchanges</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Amagi+Media+Labs+Ltd&title=Amagi+Media+Labs+Ltd.+Becomes+First+Cloud-Native+SaaS+Company+to+List+on+Indian+Stock+Exchanges&newsId=134c7ab3-62dd-49ac-8502-adf0adafb197&token=MTM0YzdhYjMtNjJk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">134c7ab3-62dd-49ac-8502-adf0adafb197</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Amagi Media Labs Limited, the only cloud-native SaaS provider offering end-to-end solutions across live production, content preparation, distribution, and monetization in the global broadcasting and streaming ecosystem, has successfully listed its equity shares on Indian stock exchanges (BSE and NSE). The company is the largest cloud-native software solution provider in cloud playout for the broadcasting and streaming industry, and has reported revenue from operations of 21,162.64 crore (Rs. 11,626.37 mn) in FY25. Amagi proposes to utilize the net proceeds from the fresh issue primarily towards expenses in technology and cloud infrastructure, funding inorganic growth through unidentified acquisitions, and general corporate purposes.</p><ul><li>Amagi Media Labs Ltd. listed on Indian stock exchanges (BSE and NSE) as the first cloud-native SaaS company in the broadcasting and streaming ecosystem.</li><li>Amagi is the largest cloud-native software solution provider in cloud playout for the broadcasting and streaming industry.</li><li>The company reported revenue from operations of 21,162.64 crore (Rs. 11,626.37 mn) in FY25.</li><li>Amagi proposes to utilize the net proceeds from the fresh issue primarily towards expenses in technology and cloud infrastructure, funding inorganic growth through unidentified acquisitions, and general corporate purposes.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c25824bf-0fba-471e-bc61-0936b0a1a8ef.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Amagi Media Labs Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>