<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:29:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[PGCRL] Nanvi Hemantsingh Jhala Sells 0.90% Shares of Pearl Green Clubs and Resorts Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Pearl+Green+Clubs+and+Resorts+Ltd&title=Nanvi+Hemantsingh+Jhala+Sells+0.90%25+Shares+of+Pearl+Green+Clubs+and+Resorts+Limited&newsId=5797ce3a-fb17-4a3d-8a71-811ba4fcdf6c&token=NTc5N2NlM2EtZmIx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5797ce3a-fb17-4a3d-8a71-811ba4fcdf6c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:28:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Nanvi Hemantsingh Jhala has sold 24000 equity shares of Pearl Green Clubs and Resorts Limited, amounting to 0.90% of the company&apos;s total share capital. The sale took place in the open market on January 9, 2026. The total equity share capital of the company before the sale was Rs. 2,67,71,000, which has now been reduced to Rs. 2,63,04,000 after the sale.</p><ul><li>Nanvi Hemantsingh Jhala sold 24000 equity shares of Pearl Green Clubs and Resorts Limited.</li><li>The sale represents 0.90% of the company&apos;s total share capital.</li><li>The sale took place in the open market on January 9, 2026.</li><li>The total equity share capital of the company was reduced to Rs. 2,63,04,000 after the sale.</li><li>The sale was made in compliance with Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7159F1F6_43BA_497D_B77F_11AD0EA468E2_145019.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Pearl Green Clubs and Resorts Ltd | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MAPMYINDIA] C.E. Info Systems Ltd. to Acquire 6.06% Stake in Iwayplus Private Limited for Rs. 2 Crore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=C.E.+Info+Systems+Ltd&title=C.E.+Info+Systems+Ltd.+to+Acquire+6.06%25+Stake+in+Iwayplus+Private+Limited+for+Rs.+2+Crore&newsId=aad4b0b3-bfca-4a4b-b3a2-551b2b3ed677&token=YWFkNGIwYjMtYmZj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aad4b0b3-bfca-4a4b-b3a2-551b2b3ed677</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:28:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>C.E. Info Systems Ltd. has approved an investment of Rs. 2 Crore in the form of Compulsorily Convertible Preference Shares (CCPS) to acquire 6.06% stake in Iwayplus Private Limited. Iwayplus is an indoor navigation start-up that provides digital indoor mapping solutions, indoor positioning systems, and location-based services. The proposed investment is part of the company’s strategic initiatives to support innovative technologies and enhance its business portfolio.</p><ul><li>C.E. Info Systems Ltd. to invest Rs. 2 Crore in Iwayplus Private Limited</li><li>Investment to be made in the form of Compulsorily Convertible Preference Shares (CCPS)</li><li>Iwayplus is an indoor navigation start-up</li><li>Proposed investment is part of the company’s strategic initiatives to support innovative technologies</li><li>Iwayplus provides digital indoor mapping solutions, indoor positioning systems, and location-based services</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4d1c9459-4cc4-49d8-9d38-32efe0cf06bd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: C.E. Info Systems Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PGCRL] Karamvirsingh Hemantsingh Jhala Sells 0.90% Shares of Pearl Green Clubs and Resorts Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Pearl+Green+Clubs+and+Resorts+Ltd&title=Karamvirsingh+Hemantsingh+Jhala+Sells+0.90%25+Shares+of+Pearl+Green+Clubs+and+Resorts+Limited&newsId=308a404a-01ab-42e0-b923-774a25d2e6a9&token=MzA4YTQwNGEtMDFh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">308a404a-01ab-42e0-b923-774a25d2e6a9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:25:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>According to a disclosure made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011, Karamvirsingh Hemantsingh Jhala has sold 24000 (0.90%) equity shares of Pearl Green Clubs and Resorts Limited in the open market. This disclosure was made to the stock exchange where the shares of the company are listed.</p><ul><li>Karamvirsingh Hemantsingh Jhala sells 0.90% shares of Pearl Green Clubs and Resorts Limited</li><li>The sale took place in the open market</li><li>The sale amounted to 24000 equity shares</li><li>The sale was made as per Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011</li><li>Pearl Green Clubs and Resorts Limited is listed on the stock exchange</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5C2FD763_2E41_42F6_B9C6_5D066B3C9E5B_145311.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Pearl Green Clubs and Resorts Ltd | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LKPFIN] LKP Finance Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Consider Bonus Shares Issue and Authorized Share Capital Increase</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LKP+Finance+Limited&title=LKP+Finance+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Consider+Bonus+Shares+Issue+and+Authorized+Share+Capital+Increase&newsId=b6a624f1-0549-4812-b3a4-2f40a2eea8dd&token=YjZhNjI0ZjEtMDU0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6a624f1-0549-4812-b3a4-2f40a2eea8dd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:23:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>LKP Finance Ltd has informed the BSE about a scheduled Board of Directors meeting on January 19, 2026. The agenda includes considering and approving a proposal for the issue of Bonus Shares, subject to necessary approvals, and a proposal for an increase in the company&apos;s Authorized Share Capital. This disclosure is in compliance with the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>LKP Finance Ltd has scheduled a Board of Directors meeting for January 19, 2026</li><li>The agenda includes considering and approving a bonus share issue proposal</li><li>The bonus share issue is subject to necessary approvals</li><li>Another agenda item is a proposal to increase the company&apos;s Authorized Share Capital</li><li>The disclosure is in compliance with SEBI Listing Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2045d54a-ee02-4e43-9b5b-a15d3a605cca.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LKP Finance Limited | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DDIL] Bhavishya Ecommerce Sells 1.69% Shares in Deep Diamond India Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Deep+Diamond+India+Ltd&title=Bhavishya+Ecommerce+Sells+1.69%25+Shares+in+Deep+Diamond+India+Ltd&newsId=70ea331f-4177-4ede-8996-418b3d28908d&token=NzBlYTMzMWYtNDE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70ea331f-4177-4ede-8996-418b3d28908d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:22:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bhavishya Ecommerce Pvt Ltd, a shareholder of Deep Diamond India Limited, has sold 2429142 equity shares, which is 1.69% of the total shares, from January 06, 2026 to January 09, 2026. The sale has reduced their shareholding to 3.80% from the previous 5.49%.</p><ul><li>Bhavishya Ecommerce sold 1.69% shares of Deep Diamond India Ltd</li><li>The sale took place from January 06, 2026 to January 09, 2026</li><li>Bhavishya Ecommerce&apos;s shareholding reduced to 3.80% from 5.49%</li><li>The total shares sold were 2429142</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/BF129EA1_EEDA_4F82_928B_962DEFE3DEFD_144621.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Deep Diamond India Ltd | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JSLL] Jeena Sikho Lifecare Ltd Publishes Case Study and Research Article on Ayurvedic Management of Chronic Kidney Disease and Type 2 Diabetes Mellitus</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jeena+Sikho+Lifecare+Ltd&title=Jeena+Sikho+Lifecare+Ltd+Publishes+Case+Study+and+Research+Article+on+Ayurvedic+Management+of+Chronic+Kidney+Disease+and+Type+2+Diabetes+Mellitus&newsId=493a68a9-dbe4-4916-bba9-10973e276373&token=NDkzYTY4YTktZGJl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">493a68a9-dbe4-4916-bba9-10973e276373</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:21:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Jeena Sikho Lifecare Ltd has announced the publication of a case study and a research article in the European Journal of Pharmaceutical and Medical Research and International Journal of Advanced Research (IJAR). These publications focus on the Ayurvedic management of chronic kidney disease and type 2 diabetes mellitus. The case study details the treatment of a patient with type 2 diabetes mellitus, hyperlipidemia, and a history of multiple abdominal surgeries. The research article discusses the Ayurvedic management of type 2 diabetes mellitus and its impact on blood glucose levels, HbA1c, fecal elastase, and lipid profile.</p><ul><li>Jeena Sikho Lifecare Ltd has published a case study and a research article in the European Journal of Pharmaceutical and Medical Research and International Journal of Advanced Research (IJAR).</li><li>The case study focuses on the Ayurvedic management of a patient with type 2 diabetes mellitus, hyperlipidemia, and a history of multiple abdominal surgeries.</li><li>The research article discusses the Ayurvedic management of type 2 diabetes mellitus and its impact on blood glucose levels, HbA1c, fecal elastase, and lipid profile.</li><li>The publications reflect the company’s continued commitment towards advancement of Ayurvedic research and promotion of evidence-based clinical practices.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3b06209f-ef4f-455c-b3e2-0e93b5742e31.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jeena Sikho Lifecare Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LT] Larsen &amp; Toubro Ltd Acquires Stake in L&amp;T Sapura Shipping Private Limited from Sapura Nautical Power Pte Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LARSEN+%26+TOUBRO+LTD.&title=Larsen+%26+Toubro+Ltd+Acquires+Stake+in+L%26T+Sapura+Shipping+Private+Limited+from+Sapura+Nautical+Power+Pte+Ltd&newsId=b6c93e2f-23da-4e2f-b870-319d68a51286&token=YjZjOTNlMmYtMjNk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6c93e2f-23da-4e2f-b870-319d68a51286</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:19:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Larsen &amp; Toubro Ltd (L&amp;T) has executed a Share Purchase Agreement for the acquisition of Sapura Nautical Power Pte Ltd&apos;s (Sapura) shareholding in L&amp;T Sapura Shipping Private Limited (LTSSPL), a subsidiary of L&amp;T. Post completion of the acquisition, LTSSPL will become a wholly owned subsidiary of L&amp;T. The acquisition will further strengthen L&amp;T&apos;s operational flexibility and asset availability for execution of offshore projects, particularly in India and the Middle East. LTSSPL operates in the offshore marine construction segment, which is complementary to L&amp;T&apos;s core engineering and construction businesses. The acquisition is expected to be completed by 31st January 2026.</p><ul><li>L&amp;T to acquire 40% stake in LTSSPL from Sapura Nautical Power Pte Ltd.</li><li>LTSSPL will become a wholly owned subsidiary of L&amp;T upon completion of the acquisition.</li><li>The acquisition strengthens L&amp;T&apos;s operational flexibility and asset availability for offshore projects.</li><li>LTSSPL operates in the offshore marine construction segment.</li><li>The acquisition is expected to be completed by 31st January 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/73f18691-6e73-4803-8ea3-9e4ebf6e3367.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LARSEN & TOUBRO LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FRUTION] Fruition Venture Ltd Allots 25,00,000 Warrants to Promoters and Non-Promoters</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Fruition+Venture+Ltd&title=Fruition+Venture+Ltd+Allots+25%2C00%2C000+Warrants+to+Promoters+and+Non-Promoters&newsId=8524a08c-63bb-455f-a078-34e0446d4d08&token=ODUyNGEwOGMtNjNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8524a08c-63bb-455f-a078-34e0446d4d08</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:19:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Fruition Venture Ltd has allotted 25,00,000 warrants on a preferential basis to promoters and non-promoters at an issue price of Rs. 20/- per warrant. The warrants are convertible into or exchangeable for one fully paid-up equity share of face value of Re. 10/- each. The allotment is pursuant to the approval of the Board of Directors and members in their respective meetings and the in-principle approval granted by BSE Limited. The allottees include KRISHAN KUMAR AGGARWAL, NITIN AGGARWAL, AAYUSH AGGARWAL, LALIT GARG, KUSUM GARG, GANESH MAL JANGIR, HRISHIKESH JANGIR, CHHATRA SINGH BAID, PRIYANKA CHOPRA, SAURABH KALIA, SAMEER CHAUDHARY, PRERNA JINDAL, PUSHPA JINDAL, TARUN JINDAL, NEHA KALIA, GAURAV BAID, RAJU DEVI BAID, SUPRIYA BAID, MANISH UPPAL, NISHA UPPAL, NITIN GOEL, and others. The company has also approved the application to the Registrar and Transfer Agent for the extension of lock-in of pre-preferential equity shareholding of the promoters.</p><ul><li>Fruition Venture Ltd allots 25,00,000 warrants to promoters and non-promoters</li><li>Warrants are convertible into or exchangeable for one fully paid-up equity share</li><li>Allotment is pursuant to the approval of the Board of Directors and members</li><li>In-principle approval granted by BSE Limited</li><li>Company has approved the application to the Registrar and Transfer Agent for the extension of lock-in of pre-preferential equity shareholding of the promoters</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2e8d7eff-bdc5-48c5-b8ef-e58d211ccdb2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Fruition Venture Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AARTIPHARM] Aarti Pharmalabs Clarifies Recent Surge in Trading Volume is Market-Driven</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Aarti+Pharmalabs+Ltd&title=Aarti+Pharmalabs+Clarifies+Recent+Surge+in+Trading+Volume+is+Market-Driven&newsId=617d46be-5733-4bb7-9864-f53024e5bbfc&token=NjE3ZDQ2YmUtNTcz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">617d46be-5733-4bb7-9864-f53024e5bbfc</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:16:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Aarti Pharmalabs Ltd. has issued a clarification regarding the significant increase in trading volume of its securities across exchanges. The company has been disclosing all required information to the Stock Exchanges as per Regulation 30 of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. There is no undisclosed information that could influence the price or volume behavior of the company&apos;s scrip. Therefore, the increase in volume is attributed to market dynamics.</p><ul><li>Aarti Pharmalabs has issued a clarification regarding the increase in trading volume of its securities.</li><li>The company has been disclosing all required information to the Stock Exchanges as per regulations.</li><li>There is no undisclosed information that could influence the price or volume behavior of the company&apos;s scrip.</li><li>The increase in volume is attributed to market dynamics.</li><li>The clarification is issued in response to an email dated January 12, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/45302cb7-bac5-4709-8c43-2b975629058f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Aarti Pharmalabs Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PRERINFRA] Prerna Infrabuild Ltd to Consider and Approve Un-audited Results for H1 2026 in Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PRERNA+INFRABUILD+LTD.&title=Prerna+Infrabuild+Ltd+to+Consider+and+Approve+Un-audited+Results+for+H1+2026+in+Board+Meeting&newsId=b1462c37-10f2-43f0-bfdb-4b5e196d2fbe&token=YjE0NjJjMzctMTBm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b1462c37-10f2-43f0-bfdb-4b5e196d2fbe</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 09:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Prerna Infrabuild Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 21st January 2026 to consider and approve the un-audited results for the half year/quarter ended 31st December 2025. The meeting will also consider any other business with the permission of the chair.</p><ul><li>Prerna Infrabuild Ltd to consider and approve un-audited results for H1 2026</li><li>Meeting scheduled on 21st January 2026</li><li>Un-audited results pertain to the half year/quarter ended 31st December 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/eb8327b2-a40d-4466-b089-50bb899ecf8f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PRERNA INFRABUILD LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>