<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:21:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[BBOX] Black Box Ltd Denies Rumors of Promoters Selling Shareholding</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Black+Box+Ltd&title=Black+Box+Ltd+Denies+Rumors+of+Promoters+Selling+Shareholding&newsId=0b56d601-0a07-4459-8775-fb4f1c086ffd&token=MGI1NmQ2MDEtMGEw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b56d601-0a07-4459-8775-fb4f1c086ffd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Clarification</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Black Box Ltd has issued a clarification regarding a market rumor that the company&apos;s promoters intend to sell a large part of their shareholding. The company has categorically stated that this &apos;news item&apos; is absolutely untrue and there is no truth whatsoever in the claim of any change in the promoter holding. The company also mentioned a preferential issue of compulsorily convertible warrants in 2024, in which the promoters participated, subscribing 51.76% of the issue. The company is committed to adhering to the highest standards of corporate governance and will continue to inform the exchanges of any material events in a timely manner.</p><ul><li>Black Box Ltd denies rumors of promoters selling shareholding</li><li>The news item regarding promoters selling shareholding is absolutely untrue</li><li>Company participated in a preferential issue of compulsorily convertible warrants in 2024</li><li>Company is committed to adhering to the highest standards of corporate governance</li><li>Company will continue to inform the exchanges of any material events in a timely manner</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b11287af-386f-4d93-9fb6-ce22345bdd4b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Black Box Ltd | Category: Clarification</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BEL] Bharat Electronics Ltd. to Form Joint Venture with Safran Electronics and Defense, France</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BHARAT+ELECTRONICS+LTD.&title=Bharat+Electronics+Ltd.+to+Form+Joint+Venture+with+Safran+Electronics+and+Defense%2C+France&newsId=f8c16523-742c-4c40-87d0-470166e7d061&token=ZjhjMTY1MjMtNzQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f8c16523-742c-4c40-87d0-470166e7d061</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Bharat Electronics Limited (BEL) has announced that its Board of Directors has approved the signing of a Joint Venture Agreement (JVA) with M/s. Safran Electronics and Defence (SED), France for Project HAMMER. The JV will incorporate a Private Limited Company under the Companies Act, 2013, with the primary purpose of operating a &apos;Center of Excellence&apos; for the manufacturing, supply, maintenance, and repair of the Guidance Kit (GK) of HAMMER Weapon System. The registered office and principal place of business will be in Pune or any other mutually agreed location. The primary &apos;End Users&apos; are the Indian Air Force and Indian Navy. The equity will be split 50:50 between BEL and SED. The Board will consist of 4 Directors; 2 nominated by BEL and 2 by SED. The Chairman is appointed by the nominees but does not have a casting vote. The operationalisation of the provisions of JV agreement is subject to regulatory and administrative approvals from both the Countries.</p><ul><li>BEL and SED to form a Joint Venture for Project HAMMER</li><li>JV to incorporate a Private Limited Company under the Companies Act, 2013</li><li>Center of Excellence to be set up in Pune or mutually agreed location</li><li>Primary End Users are Indian Air Force and Indian Navy</li><li>Equity to be split 50:50 between BEL and SED</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5c8357ca-dec6-49e6-a96e-2af60b8108f8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BHARAT ELECTRONICS LTD. | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ARROWGREEN] Arrow Greentech Reports Q3 FY26 Revenue of Rs. 561 Millions with 1.7% YoY Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Arrow+Greentech+Ltd&title=Arrow+Greentech+Reports+Q3+FY26+Revenue+of+Rs.+561+Millions+with+1.7%25+YoY+Growth&newsId=c13726ff-00de-4855-9882-3aedf529c5ce&token=YzEzNzI2ZmYtMDBk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c13726ff-00de-4855-9882-3aedf529c5ce</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Arrow Greentech Ltd, a leader in green packaging technology, announced its un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st Dec 2025. The company reported a revenue from operations of Rs. 561 Millions in Q3 FY26, with a marginal growth of 1.7% YoY. The EBITDA stood at Rs. 192 Millions, with an EBITDA margin of 34.3%, increased by 175 bps YoY. The Profit After Tax (PAT) came at Rs. 133 Millions, with a PAT margin of 22.8%, witnessing a margin expansion of 19 bps YoY.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for Q3 FY26 stood at Rs. 561 Millions, as compared to Rs. 551 Millions in Q3 FY25</li><li>EBITDA for Q3 FY26 is Rs. 192 Millions, as compared to Rs. 179 Millions in Q3 FY25</li><li>PBT for Q3 FY26 is Rs. 193 Millions, as compared to Rs. 175 Millions in Q3 FY25</li><li>PAT for Q3 FY26 is at Rs. 133 Millions as compared to Rs. 128 Millions in Q3 FY25, with PAT margins of 23.1% in Q3 FY26</li><li>Green Products segment delivered revenue of Rs. 103 million as compared to 53 million, growth of 94% YoY</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/42220f68-9210-4374-bdb1-80d5931af8b6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Arrow Greentech Ltd | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ARROWGREEN] Arrow Greentech Ltd. Addresses Noncompliance, Assures Future Compliance</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Arrow+Greentech+Ltd&title=Arrow+Greentech+Ltd.+Addresses+Noncompliance%2C+Assures+Future+Compliance&newsId=ebadc8f9-8584-4716-b058-dca6f862ab92&token=ZWJhZGM4ZjktODU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ebadc8f9-8584-4716-b058-dca6f862ab92</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In response to the NSE Letter and BSE Email dated December 16, 2025, Arrow Greentech Ltd. addressed the matter of noncompliance/delayed compliance of Regulation 23(9) of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The Board of Directors, in its meeting held on February 13, 2026, took note of the matter, acknowledging that the delay was not intentional and advised to ensure future compliance. The Company has paid the fine levied by the Stock Exchanges and is committed to strengthening its processes to avoid such delays in the future.</p><ul><li>Arrow Greentech Ltd. addresses noncompliance with SEBI regulations</li><li>The delay in compliance was not intentional, as per the Board</li><li>The Company has paid the fine imposed by the Stock Exchanges</li><li>The Board advised to ensure future compliance with regulations</li><li>Company to strengthen processes to avoid such delays in the future</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1cc1c416-df2c-4e5f-884a-2bdd2b97a9e3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Arrow Greentech Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GNFC] Gujarat Narmada Valley Fertilizers &amp; Chemicals Ltd: No Loss of Life or Property Damage in Chlorine Gas Leak Incident</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GUJARAT+NARMADA+VALLEY+FERTILIZERS+%26+CHEMICALS+LTD.&title=Gujarat+Narmada+Valley+Fertilizers+%26+Chemicals+Ltd%3A+No+Loss+of+Life+or+Property+Damage+in+Chlorine+Gas+Leak+Incident&newsId=b239a4e7-4b21-4ba2-80eb-611992533ce1&token=YjIzOWE0ZTctNGIy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b239a4e7-4b21-4ba2-80eb-611992533ce1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 13:04:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>On February 14, 2026, a sudden leakage of Chlorine gas occurred at the TDI-I Plant of GNFC Ltd. at Bharuch. The incident led to an automatic shutdown of the plant as per the in-built safety system, and remained confined within the plant premises with no adverse impact on the surrounding area. No loss of life or damage to property was reported, and normal plant operations were safely restored by 02:12 hours.</p><ul><li>Sudden Chlorine gas leak at GNFC Ltd.&apos;s TDI-I Plant in Bharuch</li><li>Automatic shutdown of the plant due to in-built safety system</li><li>No loss of life or damage to property reported</li><li>Normal plant operations safely restored by 02:12 hours</li><li>Incident remained confined within the plant premises with no adverse impact on the surrounding area</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7590bab0-4b81-4dde-a765-75228cfaf731.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GUJARAT NARMADA VALLEY FERTILIZERS & CHEMICALS LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CENTUM] Centum Electronics Sharpens Strategic Focus, Exits Loss-Making Canadian Operations, and Plans Restructuring of French Subsidiaries</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CENTUM+ELECTRONICS+LTD.&title=Centum+Electronics+Sharpens+Strategic+Focus%2C+Exits+Loss-Making+Canadian+Operations%2C+and+Plans+Restructuring+of+French+Subsidiaries&newsId=bd02c658-7255-4de7-bd72-6673c089971d&token=YmQwMmM2NTgtNzI1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd02c658-7255-4de7-bd72-6673c089971d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 12:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Centum Electronics Limited, a leading Electronics System Design &amp; Manufacturing (ESDM) company, has announced strategic actions to sharpen its focus on high-growth, high-reliability electronics opportunities and strengthen its financial foundation. This includes the discontinuation of loss-making operations in Canada and the restructuring of French subsidiaries. The company is streamlining its global footprint to reinforce its long-term strategy of building scale and leadership in advanced defence, space and aerospace systems, and Electronics Manufacturing Services (EMS).</p><ul><li>Centum Electronics is exiting its loss-making operations in Canada.</li><li>The company is planning to restructure its French subsidiaries, considering options like divestment, sale, or transfer of businesses, and judicial reorganisation.</li><li>These actions are part of Centum&apos;s ongoing portfolio optimization and disciplined capital allocation strategy.</li><li>Centum Electronics continues to experience robust growth in its core ESDM business in India.</li><li>The company is focusing on high-reliability electronics products and services, and expanding its EMS business across new products, customers, and segments.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/84abb8b1-1de2-49e6-bcef-a7c028d390fe.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CENTUM ELECTRONICS LTD. | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HFCL] HFCL Secures Export Order Worth ~USD 4.67 Million for Optical Fiber Cables</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HFCL+Ltd&title=HFCL+Secures+Export+Order+Worth+~USD+4.67+Million+for+Optical+Fiber+Cables&newsId=2042f6e1-9c00-4475-b8bc-321b28960609&token=MjA0MmY2ZTEtOWMw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2042f6e1-9c00-4475-b8bc-321b28960609</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 12:01:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>HFCL Ltd has announced that it has secured an export order worth ~USD 4.67 million (equivalent to ~INR 42.34 crore) for the supply of optical fiber cables from a renowned international customer. This significant order reaffirms the trust global customers place in the Company’s manufacturing capabilities, technological excellence and product quality. The order is to be executed by May 2026.</p><ul><li>HFCL secures export order worth ~USD 4.67 million for optical fiber cables</li><li>Order from a renowned international customer</li><li>Reaffirms trust in Company’s manufacturing capabilities, technological excellence and product quality</li><li>Order to be executed by May 2026</li><li>Significant order from international customer in the normal course of business</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4eb5afb4-afaa-4a2b-b317-b4590ceb555f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HFCL Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MEHAI] Mehai Technology Ltd Receives Order for Shifting Registered Office from Rajasthan to West Bengal</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Mehai+Technology+Ltd&title=Mehai+Technology+Ltd+Receives+Order+for+Shifting+Registered+Office+from+Rajasthan+to+West+Bengal&newsId=e0c302ac-f6db-47dc-9119-17725f258852&token=ZTBjMzAyYWMtZjZk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0c302ac-f6db-47dc-9119-17725f258852</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 08:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mehai Technology Ltd has announced that it has received an order from the Regional Director, North-West regarding the shifting of its registered office from Rajasthan to West Bengal. This decision comes in accordance with section 13 of the Companies Act, 2013. The company can now proceed to make changes in the Master Data on the MCA Portal regarding the shifting of the registered office.</p><ul><li>Mehai Technology Ltd has received an order for shifting its registered office from Rajasthan to West Bengal.</li><li>The order is in accordance with section 13 of the Companies Act, 2013.</li><li>The company can now proceed to make changes in the Master Data on the MCA Portal.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a9b9089c-8a9a-407d-a330-41513a44a73a.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Mehai Technology Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IGIL] International Gemmological Institute India Ltd Completes Acquisition of AGL Holdco Inc by Subsidiary</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=International+Gemmological+Institute+India+Ltd&title=International+Gemmological+Institute+India+Ltd+Completes+Acquisition+of+AGL+Holdco+Inc+by+Subsidiary&newsId=1a735169-faeb-47cf-b9a9-bb156e7e575b&token=MWE3MzUxNjktZmFl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a735169-faeb-47cf-b9a9-bb156e7e575b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 08:09:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>International Gemmological Institute India Ltd (IGI India) has announced the completion of the acquisition of AGL Holdco Inc by its step-down wholly owned subsidiary, International Gemmological Institute Inc (IGI USA). This acquisition was initially approved by the Board of Directors of IGI India in January 2026 and involved an investment in International Gemmological Institute BV (IGI Belgium), a wholly-owned subsidiary of IGI India, and investment by IGI Belgium in IGI USA. The acquisition of AGL Holdco Inc from Christopher P Smith and Helene Smith has resulted in AGL Holdco becoming a wholly-owned subsidiary of IGI USA and a step-down wholly-owned subsidiary of IGI Belgium and IGI India. Additionally, American Gemological Laboratories, LLC, a wholly-owned subsidiary of AGL Holdco, has become a step-down wholly-owned subsidiary of IGI USA, IGI Belgium, and IGI India.</p><ul><li>International Gemmological Institute India Ltd completes the acquisition of AGL Holdco Inc by its step-down wholly owned subsidiary, International Gemmological Institute Inc</li><li>AGL Holdco Inc becomes wholly-owned subsidiary of IGI USA and step-down wholly-owned subsidiary of IGI Belgium and IGI India</li><li>American Gemological Laboratories, LLC becomes a step-down wholly-owned subsidiary of IGI USA, IGI Belgium, and IGI India</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5ace7647-7013-41d5-8539-de8ddd9ce023.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: International Gemmological Institute India Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SOMATEX] Supreme Court Orders National Highways Authority of India to Deposit 50% of Awarded Amount in Arbitration Matter Involving Soma Textiles &amp; Industries&apos; Promoter</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SOMA+TEXTILES+%26+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Supreme+Court+Orders+National+Highways+Authority+of+India+to+Deposit+50%25+of+Awarded+Amount+in+Arbitration+Matter+Involving+Soma+Textiles+%26+Industries%27+Promoter&newsId=b82391c3-03c9-4db3-93cb-ed4d5926197c&token=YjgyMzkxYzMtMDNj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b82391c3-03c9-4db3-93cb-ed4d5926197c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 08:01:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Hon&apos;ble Supreme Court of India, in an arbitration-related matter involving Roadways Solutions India Infra Limited, the Promoter and Holding Company of Soma Textiles &amp; Industries Ltd, has passed directions for the National Highways Authority of India to deposit 50% of the total awarded amount before the Registry of the Hon’ble Delhi High Court within eight weeks. The matter arises out of a Concession Agreement relating to the Vadodara— Mumbai Expressway Project (Packages VIII &amp; IX). Soma Textiles &amp; Industries Ltd is not a party to the proceedings and based on the information currently available, the order does not have any direct material impact on its financial or operational activities.</p><ul><li>Supreme Court orders National Highways Authority of India to deposit 50% of the total awarded amount in an arbitration matter involving Soma Textiles &amp; Industries&apos; Promoter.</li><li>The matter pertains to disputes arising out of a Concession Agreement relating to the Vadodara— Mumbai Expressway Project (Packages VIII &amp; IX).</li><li>Soma Textiles &amp; Industries Ltd is not a party to the proceedings.</li><li>The awarded amount is Rs. 1,019,02,63,440/- plus interest aggregating to Rs. 1,197,72,60,596/- as on 09.02.2026.</li><li>Based on the information currently available, the order does not have any direct material impact on Soma Textiles &amp; Industries Ltd&apos;s financial or operational activities.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/78a273f9-18e4-453d-9fe6-ce422c41add7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SOMA TEXTILES & INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>