<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:11:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[STUDDS] Studds Accessories Ltd Delays Commercial Production at Manufacturing Facility-V Due to GRAP Standards Implementation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Studds+Accessories+Ltd&title=Studds+Accessories+Ltd+Delays+Commercial+Production+at+Manufacturing+Facility-V+Due+to+GRAP+Standards+Implementation&newsId=d3b3565b-b4f6-4966-bc83-1a339ff90e6f&token=ZDNiMzU2NWItYjRm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3b3565b-b4f6-4966-bc83-1a339ff90e6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:07:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Studds Accessories Ltd, a leading manufacturer of helmets and accessories, has reported a delay in the commencement of commercial production at its Manufacturing Facility-V located in Faridabad, Haryana, India. The delay is due to the implementation of GRAP standards as an emergency measure to combat severe air pollution in the Delhi-NCR region. The company expects the commercial production to begin before the end of Q2 of FY 2027, subject to receipt of requisite approvals and improvement in prevailing conditions. The update was reviewed and noted in the Board Meeting held on January 31, 2026. The company&apos;s financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, were also approved in the same meeting.</p><ul><li>Studds Accessories Ltd delays commercial production at Manufacturing Facility-V due to GRAP standards implementation.</li><li>The delay is expected to be resolved before the end of Q2 of FY 2027.</li><li>The decision was reviewed and noted in the Board Meeting held on January 31, 2026.</li><li>The company&apos;s financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, were also approved in the meeting.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/087fe751-25b8-4caf-8fb3-edcdcf8266ac.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Studds Accessories Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UTLSOLAR] Fujiyama Power Systems Reports 73.8% YoY Growth in Q3 FY26 Revenue from Operations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Fujiyama+Power+Systems+Ltd&title=Fujiyama+Power+Systems+Reports+73.8%25+YoY+Growth+in+Q3+FY26+Revenue+from+Operations&newsId=91e6c4f1-66e7-4bcc-8ec0-dbf7a5372a4d&token=OTFlNmM0ZjEtNjZl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">91e6c4f1-66e7-4bcc-8ec0-dbf7a5372a4d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Fujiyama Power Systems Limited, a leading provider of rooftop solar solutions in India, has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The company reported a 73.8% YoY growth in Q3 FY26 Revenue from Operations, with EBITDA more than doubling and expanding to 18.7%. The company added over 60 distributors, 400 dealers, and 20 exclusive Shoppes during the quarter, taking the total channel partner base to over 8,200. Fujiyama also commissioned a 1 GW solar cell manufacturing facility at Dadri, Uttar Pradesh, based on Mono PERC technology, with an investment of around Rs. 300 crore.</p><ul><li>Q3 FY26 Revenue from Operations at Rs. 5,885 Mn; up 73.8% YoY</li><li>Q3 FY26 EBITDA at Rs. 1,099 Mn; up 110.1% YoY with a margin of 18.7%</li><li>Q3 FY26 PAT at Rs. 673 Mn; up 124.3% YoY with a margin of 11.4%</li><li>Commissioned a 1 GW solar cell manufacturing facility at Dadri, Uttar Pradesh</li><li>Added over 60 distributors, 400 dealers and 20 exclusive Shoppes in Q3 FY2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cc50d304-53d5-406c-94eb-bd492dd0c7aa.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Fujiyama Power Systems Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZENTEC] Zen Technologies Announces Q3 &amp; 9MFY26 Financial Results, Reports 177.82 Crore Revenue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ZEN+TECHNOLOGIES+LTD.&title=Zen+Technologies+Announces+Q3+%26+9MFY26+Financial+Results%2C+Reports+177.82+Crore+Revenue&newsId=144e6cd0-b450-4402-b9ce-f3596db8e7f7&token=MTQ0ZTZjZDAtYjQ1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">144e6cd0-b450-4402-b9ce-f3596db8e7f7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 15:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Zen Technologies, a leading anti-drone technology and defence training solutions provider, has announced its financial results for Q3 &amp; IMFY26. The company reported a revenue of 177.82 crore, with an operational EBITDA of 54.77 crore and a profit after tax of 47.82 crore. The revenue was impacted due to delays in procurement orders, but the company witnessed a sharp acceleration in order inflows during and after the quarter, with cumulative order inflows of 931 crore. The company expects a stronger financial performance in FY27, supported by higher execution across both the standalone business and subsidiaries.</p><ul><li>Revenue of 177.82 crore in Q3 FY26</li><li>Operational EBITDA of 54.77 crore</li><li>Profit after tax of 47.82 crore</li><li>Cumulative order inflows of 931 crore</li><li>Expected stronger financial performance in FY27</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d5fef45f-e633-465f-8162-1268313195b1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ZEN TECHNOLOGIES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FILATEX] Filatex India Ltd. to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on Feb 7, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=FILATEX+INDIA+LTD.-%24&title=Filatex+India+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+Feb+7%2C+2026&newsId=3abc3c3f-abaa-4e61-86a2-8090fdbebddb&token=M2FiYzNjM2YtYWJh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3abc3c3f-abaa-4e61-86a2-8090fdbebddb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:56:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Filatex India Ltd. has informed BSE that the meeting of the Board of Directors of the Company is scheduled on 07/02/2026. The meeting will consider and approve the standalone and consolidated Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31° December, 2025. The &apos;Trading Window&apos; for dealing in the Equity Shares of the Company has been closed from January 01, 2026 till the end of 48 hours after declaration of above financial results for the Directors/Promoters/KMPs/Designated Employees/ Auditor / law firms, etc. of the Company.</p><ul><li>Filatex India Ltd. to consider and approve Q3 and nine months financial results on Feb 7, 2026</li><li>Trading Window closed from Jan 1, 2026 till 48 hours after financial results declaration</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0f48c306-f348-4ed9-9824-8c3c3782f77d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: FILATEX INDIA LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ELLEN] Ellenbarrie Industrial Gases Commissions New 220 TPD Plant in Uluberia, West Bengal</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ellenbarrie+Industrial+Gases+Ltd&title=Ellenbarrie+Industrial+Gases+Commissions+New+220+TPD+Plant+in+Uluberia%2C+West+Bengal&newsId=b1e9d043-68b3-4c30-8eec-929c5ee59447&token=YjFlOWQwNDMtNjhi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b1e9d043-68b3-4c30-8eec-929c5ee59447</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:51:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Ellenbarrie Industrial Gases Limited has announced the commissioning of a new plant, Uluberia-II, at Uluberia, West Bengal. The plant, which has a capacity of 220 TPD, has begun its operations. The announcement was made at a Board of Directors meeting and has been disseminated on the company&apos;s website.</p><ul><li>Ellenbarrie Industrial Gases has commissioned a new plant, Uluberia-II, in Uluberia, West Bengal</li><li>The new plant has a capacity of 220 TPD</li><li>The plant has started its operations</li><li>The announcement was made at a Board of Directors meeting</li><li>The information has been shared on the company&apos;s website</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a0f9e5b5-3cc9-4628-ac3c-86e3e2740539.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ellenbarrie Industrial Gases Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ELLEN] Ellenbarrie Industrial Gases Approves Q3 Results and Commissions New Plant</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ellenbarrie+Industrial+Gases+Ltd&title=Ellenbarrie+Industrial+Gases+Approves+Q3+Results+and+Commissions+New+Plant&newsId=b40d550e-fb09-4466-ac51-8cffd1319303&token=YjQwZDU1MGUtZmIw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b40d550e-fb09-4466-ac51-8cffd1319303</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:47:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Ellenbarrie Industrial Gases Ltd. has approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, and announced the commissioning of its new plant, Uluberia - II, at Uluberia, West Bengal, with a capacity of 220 TPD. The plant commenced operations on January 31, 2026. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 813.46 million for the quarter and 2,541.49 million for the nine-month period ended December 31, 2025.</p><ul><li>Ellenbarrie Industrial Gases approved the unaudited financial results for Q3 2025</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue from operations for Q3 2025 is 813.46 million</li><li>The company has commissioned a new plant, Uluberia - II, with a capacity of 220 TPD</li><li>The Uluberia - II plant commenced operations on January 31, 2026</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue from operations for the nine-month period ended December 31, 2025, is 2,541.49 million</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8a46981f-5a21-4c35-8961-5833a117a6de.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ellenbarrie Industrial Gases Ltd | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GANECOS] Ganesha Ecosphere Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on February 07, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GANESHA+ECOSPHERE+LTD.&title=Ganesha+Ecosphere+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+February+07%2C+2026&newsId=07ad108c-bf95-44ad-9921-f6a181a8c0b9&token=MDdhZDEwOGMtYmY5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07ad108c-bf95-44ad-9921-f6a181a8c0b9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:44:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ganesha Ecosphere Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 07, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results (Provisional) for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for the company&apos;s equity shares has been closed from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the announcement of the Unaudited Financial Results on February 07, 2026.</p><ul><li>Ganesha Ecosphere Ltd to consider and approve Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled for February 07, 2026.</li><li>Trading window for the company&apos;s equity shares is closed from January 1, 2026, till 48 hours after the financial results announcement.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/66023410-9084-4cd7-88e3-99dbf9a0f974.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GANESHA ECOSPHERE LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ELLEN] Ellenbarrie Industrial Gases Reports Q3 Results with 28.18% YoY Growth in Profit Before Tax</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ellenbarrie+Industrial+Gases+Ltd&title=Ellenbarrie+Industrial+Gases+Reports+Q3+Results+with+28.18%25+YoY+Growth+in+Profit+Before+Tax&newsId=da04e189-d086-4a69-bc1e-a70bce0ee1de&token=ZGEwNGUxODktZDA4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">da04e189-d086-4a69-bc1e-a70bce0ee1de</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:44:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Ellenbarrie Industrial Gases Ltd. has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine-months ended on December 31, 2025. The company has recorded a 28.18% YoY growth in profit before tax at INR 1,020.09 million. The revenue from operations stands at INR 2,541.49 million with a 25.78% YoY growth. The total expenses for the quarter were INR 631.91 million.</p><ul><li>28.18% YoY growth in profit before tax</li><li>Revenue from operations stands at INR 2,541.49 million with a 25.78% YoY growth</li><li>Total expenses for the quarter were INR 631.91 million</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1b1dd4f5-6f00-4e5a-829e-daab444fa75d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ellenbarrie Industrial Gases Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RRKABEL] R R Kabel Ltd Reports Highest Ever Nine-Month Revenue, EBIDTA &amp; PAT</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=R+R+Kabel+Ltd&title=R+R+Kabel+Ltd+Reports+Highest+Ever+Nine-Month+Revenue%2C+EBIDTA+%26+PAT&newsId=bfa7041f-9753-413d-8bfc-049f1901d6f3&token=YmZhNzA0MWYtOTc1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bfa7041f-9753-413d-8bfc-049f1901d6f3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:42:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>R R Kabel Ltd, India&apos;s No.1 exporter of Wires and Cables, has declared its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The company reported a significant increase in revenue, EBIDTA, and PAT for the nine-month period. The Wires &amp; Cables segment delivered robust growth, while the FMEG segment recorded steady performance despite a challenging operating environment. The company remains focused on sustaining growth momentum and delivering long-term value to stakeholders.</p><ul><li>Revenue from Operations for the quarter increased by 42.3% YoY to INR 2,535.9 crores</li><li>Operating EBITDA for the quarter increased by 86.0% YoY to INR 206.4 crores</li><li>Profit Before Tax for the quarter increased by 75.5% YoY to INR 158.8 crores</li><li>Profit After Tax for the quarter increased by 72.4% YoY to INR 118.2 crores</li><li>For the nine months ended, Revenue from Operations increased by 25.1% YoY to INR 6,758.2 crores</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/48bb509a-3de1-4901-8c1d-345f8c6c69c8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: R R Kabel Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IKIO] IKIO Technologies Ltd: Board Approves Q3 Results, Re-designates Director in Subsidiaries</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IKIO+Lighting+Ltd&title=IKIO+Technologies+Ltd%3A+Board+Approves+Q3+Results%2C+Re-designates+Director+in+Subsidiaries&newsId=424edc07-3f10-45cb-be74-0887e1d41b92&token=NDI0ZWRjMDctM2Yx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">424edc07-3f10-45cb-be74-0887e1d41b92</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 14:41:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>IKIO Technologies Ltd announced the outcome of its Board Meeting held on 31st January, 2026. The Board approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The meeting also resulted in the re-designation of Mr. Hardeep Singh as Non-Executive Director in IKIO Solutions Private Limited and as Managing Director in Royalux Lighting Private Limited, subject to shareholders&apos; approval. The changes are aimed at ensuring compliance with the Companies Act, 2013.</p><ul><li>Board approved unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December, 2025</li><li>Mr. Hardeep Singh re-designated as Non-Executive Director in IKIO Solutions Private Limited</li><li>Mr. Hardeep Singh re-designated as Managing Director in Royalux Lighting Private Limited, subject to shareholders&apos; approval</li><li>Changes aimed at ensuring compliance with the Companies Act, 2013</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/68b3204a-e92e-47a5-8557-056f120d2e88.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IKIO Lighting Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>