<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:54:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[TIMESGTY] Team India Guaranty Ltd Receives In-Principle Approval for Preferential Issue of Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TIMES+GUARANTY+LTD.&title=Team+India+Guaranty+Ltd+Receives+In-Principle+Approval+for+Preferential+Issue+of+Equity+Shares&newsId=a6424bf4-7ff5-4075-9bd9-ec5700ad4c0a&token=YTY0MjRiZjQtN2Zm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a6424bf4-7ff5-4075-9bd9-ec5700ad4c0a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:52:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Team India Guaranty Ltd has received in-principle approval from the National Stock Exchange of India Limited (NSE) and BSE Limited for the proposed preferential issue of 22,48,270 equity shares of Rs. 10/- each to non-promoter, public category at an issue price of Rs. 285/- (including a premium of Rs. 275/-) per equity share. The approval is subject to certain conditions and compliance with regulations. The company is advised to strengthen internal controls and obtain undertakings from the allottees regarding trade restrictions.</p><ul><li>Team India Guaranty Ltd has received in-principle approval for preferential issue of equity shares from NSE and BSE.</li><li>The issue is for 22,48,270 equity shares at an issue price of Rs. 285/- each, including a premium of Rs. 275/-.</li><li>The approval is subject to certain conditions and compliance with regulations.</li><li>The company is advised to strengthen internal controls and obtain undertakings from the allottees regarding trade restrictions.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7714862a-45b1-44ec-9b12-0f9be33f0fa4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TIMES GUARANTY LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BOSCHLTD] Bosch Ltd Announces Resignation of CFO Ms. Karin Gilges and Appointment of Mr. Tillmann Olsen as New CFO</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BOSCH+LTD.&title=Bosch+Ltd+Announces+Resignation+of+CFO+Ms.+Karin+Gilges+and+Appointment+of+Mr.+Tillmann+Olsen+as+New+CFO&newsId=c331065b-8876-4a33-b602-ba554b9d484c&token=YzMzMTA2NWItODg3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c331065b-8876-4a33-b602-ba554b9d484c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:52:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bosch Ltd announced the resignation of its Chief Financial Officer (CFO), Ms. Karin Gilges, due to her appointment to a global role outside India. The Board of Directors has approved the appointment of Mr. Tillmann Olsen as the new CFO and Key Managerial Personnel (KMP) of the company, effective from June 01, 2026. Mr. Olsen has extensive experience in various leadership roles within the Bosch Group. The outgoing CFO, Ms. Gilges, has served as the CFO of Bosch Ltd since May 01, 2022, and her resignation has been accepted by the Board, which expressed gratitude for her contributions.</p><ul><li>Resignation of Ms. Karin Gilges as CFO due to global role within the Group</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Tillmann Olsen as the new CFO and KMP with effect from June 01, 2026</li><li>Mr. Olsen&apos;s extensive experience in various leadership roles within the Bosch Group</li><li>Ms. Gilges&apos; contributions as CFO from May 01, 2022, acknowledged by the Board</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4b3c1743-a3cc-4167-bc77-46549b505800.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BOSCH LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BOSCHLTD] Bosch Ltd. Announces Changes in Management: New CFO Appointed, Current CFO Resigns</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BOSCH+LTD.&title=Bosch+Ltd.+Announces+Changes+in+Management%3A+New+CFO+Appointed%2C+Current+CFO+Resigns&newsId=43aa8ec9-6c44-4d32-9609-c8102b8696b7&token=NDNhYThlYzktNmM0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43aa8ec9-6c44-4d32-9609-c8102b8696b7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:52:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bosch Ltd. has announced changes in its management at the Board Meeting held on February 17, 2026. The company has appointed Mr. Tillmann Olsen as the new Chief Financial Officer (CFO) and Key Managerial Personnel (KMP) with effect from June 01, 2026. Ms. Karin Gilges, the current CFO, has resigned from her position with effect from the close of business hours on May 31, 2026, due to her appointment to a global role within the Group, which will be based outside India.</p><ul><li>Mr. Tillmann Olsen appointed as the new Chief Financial Officer and Key Managerial Personnel of Bosch Ltd. with effect from June 01, 2026.</li><li>Ms. Karin Gilges resigns from her position as Chief Financial Officer and Key Managerial Personnel with effect from May 31, 2026, due to her appointment to a global role within the Group.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fd2cbc34-10ec-4f81-9c09-db030f81ae39.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BOSCH LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ENGINERSIN] Engineers India Ltd. Announces Board Meeting to Consider Interim Dividend for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ENGINEERS+INDIA+LTD.&title=Engineers+India+Ltd.+Announces+Board+Meeting+to+Consider+Interim+Dividend+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=b3283684-5a67-461f-9e11-afba9ccdce57&token=YjMyODM2ODQtNWE2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3283684-5a67-461f-9e11-afba9ccdce57</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:51:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Engineers India Ltd. has informed the BSE that a Board Meeting is scheduled on 26/02/2026. The meeting will consider and approve the Notice of Board Meeting and inter alia, consider and approve the Interim Dividend, if any, for the financial year 2025-26. The Record Date for the purpose of ascertaining the eligibility of shareholders for payment of interim dividend has been fixed for Friday, 6th March, 2026. The Trading Window for trading in EIL’s securities has been closed from 17.02.2026 to 28.02.2026 and will re-open on 02.03.2026.</p><ul><li>Engineers India Ltd. scheduled a Board Meeting on 26/02/2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve Interim Dividend for the financial year 2025-26</li><li>The Record Date for the purpose of ascertaining the eligibility of shareholders for payment of interim dividend is 6th March, 2026</li><li>The Trading Window for trading in EIL’s securities is closed from 17.02.2026 to 28.02.2026</li><li>The Trading Window will re-open on 02.03.2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/59bd16b7-0db1-4cea-830c-e076d99ab504.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ENGINEERS INDIA LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[COSYN] COSYN Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Discuss Fund Raising Proposal</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=COSYN+Ltd&title=COSYN+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Discuss+Fund+Raising+Proposal&newsId=15b6fcec-4cb2-405e-98f9-f9e433043627&token=MTViNmZjZWMtNGNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">15b6fcec-4cb2-405e-98f9-f9e433043627</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:51:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>COSYN Ltd has informed the BSE that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on February 20, 2026. The agenda includes considering a proposal for fund raising by way of issue of equity shares/convertible warrants and or/any other instruments through preferential issue. This is in accordance with the SEBI (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, and is subject to the approval of the shareholders of the Company and any necessary regulatory/statutory approvals.</p><ul><li>COSYN Ltd scheduled a Board Meeting on February 20, 2026</li><li>The agenda includes a proposal for fund raising</li><li>The fund raising will be through the issuance of equity shares/convertible warrants and or/any other instruments through preferential issue</li><li>The proposal is subject to the approval of the shareholders of the Company</li><li>The proposal is also subject to necessary regulatory/statutory approvals</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6e7abb32-69e0-4c3c-9ff6-2271604b9e4e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: COSYN Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HUDCO] HUDCO Extends Tenure of Chief Risk Officer for One More Year</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Housing+%26+Urban+Development+Corporation+Ltd&title=HUDCO+Extends+Tenure+of+Chief+Risk+Officer+for+One+More+Year&newsId=06e47f70-d660-4f96-8866-5b00ae05df26&token=MDZlNDdmNzAtZDY2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06e47f70-d660-4f96-8866-5b00ae05df26</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Housing &amp; Urban Development Corporation Ltd. has announced the extension of the tenure of its Chief Risk Officer, Smt. Madhu Nagrani, General Manager (Finance), for a further period of one year starting from 1st March, 2026. This decision aligns with the Reserve Bank of India (Non-Banking Financial Companies - Governance) Directions.</p><ul><li>HUDCO extends the tenure of its Chief Risk Officer, Smt. Madhu Nagrani, for one more year.</li><li>The extension is in compliance with the Reserve Bank of India (Non-Banking Financial Companies - Governance) Directions.</li><li>Smt. Madhu Nagrani is the General Manager (Finance) at HUDCO.</li><li>The extended tenure will commence from 1st March, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d60e6610-d149-4e04-8dce-090c57c208ce.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Housing & Urban Development Corporation Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NITINFIRE] Nitin Fire Protection Industries Ltd Appoints New CFO &amp; KMP, Changes Registered Office Address, and Announces Other Key Appointments</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Nitin+Fire+Protection+Industries+Ltd&title=Nitin+Fire+Protection+Industries+Ltd+Appoints+New+CFO+%26+KMP%2C+Changes+Registered+Office+Address%2C+and+Announces+Other+Key+Appointments&newsId=544c6f83-ab75-4f91-bf30-3a5d916a3c4c&token=NTQ0YzZmODMtYWI3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">544c6f83-ab75-4f91-bf30-3a5d916a3c4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:51:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Nitin Fire Protection Industries Ltd has announced several key appointments and changes in its latest board meeting held on 17th February 2026. The company has appointed Mr. Bharat Shah as the Chief Financial Officer and Key Managerial Personnel with effect from 17th February 2026. Mr. Shah holds a B.Com. (Hons.), a degree in Law from the University of Mumbai, and a Diploma in Business Management from the Indian Merchants&apos; Chamber, bringing with him over 47 years of experience in legal, taxation, and financial matters. The company has also changed its registered office address from &apos;501, Delta, Technology Street, Powai, Mumbai, Maharashtra, India - 400076&apos; to &apos;C-801, Neelkanth Business Park, Kirol, Vidyavihar (West), Mumbai - 400086.&apos; Additionally, Nitin Fire Protection Industries Ltd has appointed M/s. AVS &amp; Associates, Company Secretaries as Secretarial Auditors for the financial years 2024-25 and 2025-26, and M/s. Jimit Kamdar &amp; Associates, Chartered Accountants as Internal Auditors for the financial years 2025-26 and 2026-27. The company has also accepted consent terms and filed for Cancellation of sale certificate in DRT and is looking at organic &amp; inorganic growth opportunities as well as potential investors for recapitalising the company.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Bharat Shah as CFO &amp; Key Managerial Personnel</li><li>Change in Registered Office Address</li><li>Appointment of M/s. AVS &amp; Associates as Secretarial Auditors</li><li>Appointment of M/s. Jimit Kamdar &amp; Associates as Internal Auditors</li><li>Company looking for growth opportunities and potential investors</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0fc512a2-32fe-4ad1-ae2f-fc0ed356a5d7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Nitin Fire Protection Industries Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MRCAGRO] MRC Agrotech Ltd: Director Resigns, Additional Director Appointed</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MRC+Agrotech+Ltd&title=MRC+Agrotech+Ltd%3A+Director+Resigns%2C+Additional+Director+Appointed&newsId=8d83a454-fd0c-4faf-b353-98ba3bdb1216&token=OGQ4M2E0NTQtZmQw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d83a454-fd0c-4faf-b353-98ba3bdb1216</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>MRC Agrotech Ltd has announced that a meeting of the Board of Directors will be held on February 24, 2026. The agenda includes the acceptance of the resignation of Mr. Sanjay Kumar Singh due to personal obligations and other commitments. The board will also consider the appointment of Mr. Vishal Surendra Parmar as an Additional Director. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the company will be closed for all designated persons and their immediate relatives from the close of business hours of February 18, 2026 until 48 hours after the conclusion of the board meeting.</p><ul><li>Mr. Sanjay Kumar Singh has resigned from his position as Non-Executive Director.</li><li>The resignation is due to personal obligations and other commitments.</li><li>Mr. Vishal Surendra Parmar is being considered for appointment as an Additional Director.</li><li>The trading window for dealing in the securities of the company will be closed from February 18, 2026 until 48 hours after the board meeting.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6b5469f9-5b34-4a0e-97e4-494e3d73dac4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MRC Agrotech Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RPPINFRA] R P P Infra Projects Ltd Receives Notice of Investigation from ROC, Coimbatore</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RPP+INFRA+PROJECTS+LTD.&title=R+P+P+Infra+Projects+Ltd+Receives+Notice+of+Investigation+from+ROC%2C+Coimbatore&newsId=158e6a57-6371-4957-9fe7-c096112005e2&token=MTU4ZTZhNTctNjM3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">158e6a57-6371-4957-9fe7-c096112005e2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:44:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>R P P Infra Projects Ltd has received a notice of investigation from the Registrar of Companies (ROC), Coimbatore. The company is required to provide data, documents, and information for examination as per Regulation 30 and Para A Part A of Schedule III of the SEBI [Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations 2015. The company will cooperate with the ROC/MCA during the investigation and submission of necessary information/documents.</p><ul><li>R P P Infra Projects Ltd has received a notice of investigation from the Registrar of Companies (ROC), Coimbatore.</li><li>The company is required to provide data, documents, and information for examination as per Regulation 30 and Para A Part A of Schedule III of the SEBI [Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations 2015.</li><li>R P P Infra Projects Ltd will cooperate with the ROC/MCA during the investigation and submission of necessary information/documents.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/81f0154b-cf5b-4ea9-ad0c-c7929ce37081.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RPP INFRA PROJECTS LTD. | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BOSCHLTD] Bosch Ltd Appoints New Chief Financial Officer, Mr. Tillmann Olsen</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BOSCH+LTD.&title=Bosch+Ltd+Appoints+New+Chief+Financial+Officer%2C+Mr.+Tillmann+Olsen&newsId=08dd72c8-672a-4bee-bc44-32b6ffae8ff2&token=MDhkZDcyYzgtNjcy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08dd72c8-672a-4bee-bc44-32b6ffae8ff2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 12:44:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bosch Ltd has announced the appointment of Mr. Tillmann Olsen as the new Chief Financial Officer and Key Managerial Personnel (KMP) with effect from June 01, 2026. Mr. Olsen has extensive experience in financial management and leadership, having held various positions in Bosch Rexroth AG and Bosch Rexroth Africa. The current Chief Financial Officer, Ms. Karin Gilges, has resigned from her position with effect from May 31, 2026, upon her appointment to a global role within the Group, based outside India.</p><ul><li>Mr. Tillmann Olsen appointed as the new Chief Financial Officer and Key Managerial Personnel (KMP) of Bosch Ltd with effect from June 01, 2026.</li><li>Ms. Karin Gilges has resigned from her position as Chief Financial Officer due to her appointment to a global role within the Group, based outside India.</li><li>Mr. Olsen has extensive experience in financial management and leadership, having held various positions in Bosch Rexroth AG and Bosch Rexroth Africa.</li><li>Ms. Gilges has been the Chief Financial Officer of Bosch Ltd since May 01, 2022.</li><li>The resignation of Ms. Gilges is purely on account of her new professional opportunity and there are no other material reasons for her resignation.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e3ad2c44-4b19-4c29-a026-f7014f4e8d16.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BOSCH LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>