<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:52:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[DSSL] Dynacons Systems &amp; Solutions Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on Feb 14, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=DYNACONS+SYSTEMS+%26+SOLUTIONS+LTD.&title=Dynacons+Systems+%26+Solutions+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+Feb+14%2C+2026&newsId=fdcfbdc0-f4fc-4b36-8213-dd7e0e4150fa&token=ZmRjZmJkYzAtZjRm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fdcfbdc0-f4fc-4b36-8213-dd7e0e4150fa</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Dynacons Systems &amp; Solutions Ltd has announced a Board of Directors meeting on February 14, 2026, to consider and approve the Un-Audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The trading window for insiders, which was closed on January 1, 2026, will remain closed till 48 hours after the dissemination of the Un-Audited financial results.</p><ul><li>Dynacons Systems &amp; Solutions Ltd to consider and approve Un-Audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended on December 31, 2025.</li><li>Trading window for insiders to remain closed till 48 hours after the dissemination of the Un-Audited financial results.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/113b60b6-375a-41fd-ad3d-1cfbfdec2361.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: DYNACONS SYSTEMS & SOLUTIONS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NRBBEARING] NRB Bearings Ltd Declares Interim Dividend of Rs. 3.20 per Share for F.Y 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NRB+BEARINGS+LTD.&title=NRB+Bearings+Ltd+Declares+Interim+Dividend+of+Rs.+3.20+per+Share+for+F.Y+2025-26&newsId=9f245b00-138f-4cc6-8cb2-d02e71304b96&token=OWYyNDViMDAtMTM4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9f245b00-138f-4cc6-8cb2-d02e71304b96</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>NRB Bearings Ltd has declared an interim dividend of Rs. 3.20 (160% of the Face Value) per equity share for the financial year 2025-26. The Record Date (Cut-off Date) for determining the entitlement of payment of Interim Dividend is Friday, February 13, 2026. Dividend payments will be subject to deduction of tax at source as per the Income Tax Act, 1961. The Trading Window for dealing in the Securities of the Company is closed from January 1, 2026 till 48 hours after the announcement of financial results for the quarter ended as on 31°&apos;December, 2025. Shareholders are requested to update their PAN and bank account details with the RTA/Depositories to facilitate smooth dividend payment and TDS compliance.</p><ul><li>NRB Bearings Ltd declares interim dividend of Rs. 3.20 per equity share for F.Y 2025-26</li><li>Record Date for determining the entitlement of payment of Interim Dividend is Friday, February 13, 2026</li><li>Dividend payments will be subject to deduction of tax at source as per the Income Tax Act, 1961</li><li>Trading Window for dealing in the Securities of the Company is closed from January 1, 2026 till 48 hours after the announcement of financial results</li><li>Shareholders are requested to update their PAN and bank account details with the RTA/Depositories</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8103415b-7fdf-4311-bcac-9bf5977f3d31.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NRB BEARINGS LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SWADEIN] Swadeshi Industries &amp; Leasing Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SWADESHI+INDUSTRIES+LEASING+CO.LTD.&title=Swadeshi+Industries+%26+Leasing+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=d0093ca4-f9cd-490d-9c4b-30c5cefc6174&token=ZDAwOTNjYTQtZjlj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d0093ca4-f9cd-490d-9c4b-30c5cefc6174</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:32:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Swadeshi Industries &amp; Leasing Ltd has reported its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 1,578.63 crores for the quarter and 3,529.97 crores for the nine months. The total income for the quarter is 1,578.63 crores and 3,529.97 crores for the nine months. The company&apos;s expenses for the quarter are 1,520.64 crores and 3,400.41 crores for the nine months. The profit before tax for the quarter is 57.99 crores and 199.56 crores for the nine months. The tax expenses for the quarter are 41.20 crores and 132.73 crores for the nine months. The profit for the quarter is 16.79 crores and 66.83 crores for the nine months.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter is 1,578.63 crores</li><li>Total income for the quarter is 1,578.63 crores</li><li>Expenses for the quarter are 1,520.64 crores</li><li>Profit before tax for the quarter is 57.99 crores</li><li>Profit for the quarter is 16.79 crores</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9c892f17-1885-4903-b1cb-23850f134f2c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SWADESHI INDUSTRIES LEASING CO.LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SIGNPOST] Signpost India Ltd. Announces Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025, Appoints New Company Secretary, and Re-appoints Internal Auditor</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Signpost+India+Ltd&title=Signpost+India+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Appoints+New+Company+Secretary%2C+and+Re-appoints+Internal+Auditor&newsId=eccb39e8-ae4d-44bc-8792-da679b2d9b65&token=ZWNjYjM5ZTgtYWU0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eccb39e8-ae4d-44bc-8792-da679b2d9b65</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:21:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Signpost India Ltd. has announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company has appointed Ms. Kinjal Mistry as the Company Secretary and Compliance Officer, and re-appointed M/s. Arun S Goel &amp; Company as an Internal Auditor for the financial year 2026-27. The meeting of the Board of Directors commenced at 5:14 p.m. and concluded at 6:27 p.m.</p><ul><li>Signpost India Ltd. announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>Ms. Kinjal Mistry appointed as the Company Secretary and Compliance Officer.</li><li>M/s. Arun S Goel &amp; Company re-appointed as an Internal Auditor for the financial year 2026-27.</li><li>The Board of Directors meeting was held on February 09, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/663f858b-8b81-4715-ab13-94d8df1699f4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Signpost India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LLOYDSTEEL] Promoter and Promoter Group of Lloyds Engineering Works Ltd Sell Shares to Thriveni Earthmovers Private Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Lloyds+Steels+Industries+Ltd&title=Promoter+and+Promoter+Group+of+Lloyds+Engineering+Works+Ltd+Sell+Shares+to+Thriveni+Earthmovers+Private+Limited&newsId=68bc6e92-8a24-49a9-826d-bc8b28709086&token=NjhiYzZlOTItOGEy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68bc6e92-8a24-49a9-826d-bc8b28709086</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pursuant to Regulation 30 of Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations 2015, Lloyds Engineering Works Ltd announced that the Promoter and Promoter Group of the company have sold their shares to Thriveni Earthmovers Private Limited. The transaction was done through a &apos;Block Deal&apos;. The Promoter, Lloyds Enterprises, sold 60,34,299 equity shares at Rs. 49.65 each, amounting to Rs. 29,96,02,945.35. AEON Trading LLP, on behalf of the Promoter Group, sold 4,98,52,941 equity shares at the same price, amounting to Rs. 2,47,51,98,520.65. This transaction amounts to 3.77% of the company&apos;s equity share capital. Thriveni Earthmovers Private Limited, post this transaction, will hold 9.05% of the company&apos;s equity share capital.</p><ul><li>Promoter and Promoter Group of Lloyds Engineering Works Ltd sell shares to Thriveni Earthmovers Private Limited</li><li>Transaction done through &apos;Block Deal&apos;</li><li>Lloyds Enterprises sold 60,34,299 equity shares</li><li>AEON Trading LLP, on behalf of the Promoter Group, sold 4,98,52,941 equity shares</li><li>Thriveni Earthmovers Private Limited will hold 9.05% of the company&apos;s equity share capital post transaction</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/272b1ac4-1abb-425d-9e78-bbc27b02f91e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Lloyds Steels Industries Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AUTOPRD] Automobile Products of India Ltd. to Raise Funds via Rights Issue of Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AUTOMOBILE+PRODUCTS+OF+INDIA+LTD.&title=Automobile+Products+of+India+Ltd.+to+Raise+Funds+via+Rights+Issue+of+Equity+Shares&newsId=88cd7deb-f6a8-46d9-a149-32db424c59b8&token=ODhjZDdkZWItZjZh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88cd7deb-f6a8-46d9-a149-32db424c59b8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Automobile Products of India Ltd. has announced its decision to raise funds by issuing equity shares at a price to be determined by the Board. The total amount to be raised is up to Rs. 14,00,000/- (Rupees Fourteen Lakhs only) on a rights issue basis to eligible equity shareholders. This decision is subject to regulatory and statutory approvals for the purpose of compliance with Minimum Public Shareholding (MPS) requirements.</p><ul><li>Automobile Products of India Ltd. to raise funds via rights issue of equity shares.</li><li>The total amount to be raised is up to Rs. 14,00,000/- (Rupees Fourteen Lakhs only).</li><li>The decision is subject to regulatory and statutory approvals for MPS compliance.</li><li>The rights issue is for eligible equity shareholders of the company.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/feed4910-3299-4748-aa71-72eeea3feef3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AUTOMOBILE PRODUCTS OF INDIA LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NARMP] Narmada Macplast Drip Irrigation Systems Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on Feb 13, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NARMADA+MACPLAST+DRIP+IRRIGATION+SYSTEMS+LTD.&title=Narmada+Macplast+Drip+Irrigation+Systems+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+Feb+13%2C+2026&newsId=2bf4f0af-c881-481a-bb54-1953d54e02cc&token=MmJmNGYwYWYtYzg4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2bf4f0af-c881-481a-bb54-1953d54e02cc</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Narmada Macplast Drip Irrigation Systems Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 13, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ending December 31, 2025. The meeting will also consider any other business that may be necessary with the permission of the Chair. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company has been closed for all designated persons and their immediate relatives with effect from January 01, 2026, and will open 48 hours after the financial results are declared to the Stock Exchange.</p><ul><li>Narmada Macplast Drip Irrigation Systems Ltd to consider and approve unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ending December 31, 2025</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the securities of the Company closed for all designated persons and their immediate relatives from January 01, 2026</li><li>Trading window to open 48 hours after the financial results are declared to the Stock Exchange</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/46f006c3-0fc2-4409-9261-119667886606.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NARMADA MACPLAST DRIP IRRIGATION SYSTEMS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GULFOILLUB] Gulf Oil Achieves Record Q3 with All-Time High Lubes Volumes, Revenue, and EBITDA; Declares Interim Dividend of Rs 21.00 per Share</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Gulf+Oil+Lubricants+India+Ltd&title=Gulf+Oil+Achieves+Record+Q3+with+All-Time+High+Lubes+Volumes%2C+Revenue%2C+and+EBITDA%3B+Declares+Interim+Dividend+of+Rs+21.00+per+Share&newsId=f12700de-2a76-4e3f-a7fd-bda11cec85b4&token=ZjEyNzAwZGUtMmE3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f12700de-2a76-4e3f-a7fd-bda11cec85b4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:13:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Gulf Oil Lubricants India Limited, a Hinduja Group Company, has reported its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine-month ended December 31, 2025. The company achieved record quarterly revenue from operations, both on a standalone and consolidated basis, with growth rates of 10.28% and 10.56%, respectively. The nine-month revenue also crossed Rs. 3,000 Crores. Gulf Oil declared an interim dividend of Rs 21.00 per equity share i.e., 1,050% on the FV of Rs. 2 per Share.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations at Rs. 997.92 Crores (Standalone) and Rs. 1,017.55 Crores (Consolidated) for Q3</li><li>EBITDA at Rs. 130.27 Crores (Standalone) and Rs. 132.46 Crores (Consolidated) for Q3</li><li>Interim dividend of Rs 21.00 per equity share i.e., 1,050% on the FV of Rs. 2 per Share</li><li>Nine-month revenue crossed Rs. 3,000 Crores</li><li>Profit Before Tax (PBT) and Profit After Tax (PAT) impacted by incremental estimated obligations of new labour codes notified in November 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/57946080-6282-4c6e-b92f-0904325e83eb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Gulf Oil Lubricants India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DANUBE] Danube Industries Ltd Announces Q3 2025 Unaudited Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Danube+Industries+Ltd&title=Danube+Industries+Ltd+Announces+Q3+2025+Unaudited+Financial+Results&newsId=613a1e3e-f590-4302-9c86-bb8c70875ab8&token=NjEzYTFlM2UtZjU5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">613a1e3e-f590-4302-9c86-bb8c70875ab8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:12:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Danube Industries Ltd has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at ₹ 32,60,02,000, while the profit before exceptional and extraordinary items is ₹ 4,75,800. The company&apos;s earnings per share (EPS) for continuing operations is ₹ 4.76. The statutory auditors have carried out a limited review report of these results.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for Q3 2025 is ₹ 32,60,02,000</li><li>Profit before exceptional and extraordinary items is ₹ 4,75,800</li><li>EPS for continuing operations is ₹ 4.76</li><li>Statutory auditors have carried out a limited review report</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4ff45fd2-e6ff-4b2a-9717-3cc854c1f1f3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Danube Industries Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUVIDHAA] Suvidhaa Infoserve Ltd. Approves Q3 FY2025-26 Financial Results in Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Suvidhaa+Infoserve+Ltd&title=Suvidhaa+Infoserve+Ltd.+Approves+Q3+FY2025-26+Financial+Results+in+Board+Meeting&newsId=d586140d-4434-420b-ae57-03fc0609d0e2&token=ZDU4NjE0MGQtNDQz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d586140d-4434-420b-ae57-03fc0609d0e2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Suvidhaa Infoserve Ltd. announced the outcome of their board meeting held on February 09, 2026. The board approved the un-audited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. Mr. Prashant Thakar resigned as CFO and Whole Time Director, and his resignation was noted. He was redesignated as a Non-Executive Director. The board approved the re-appointment of Mr. Shail Shah and Mr. Ritesh Chothani as Independent Directors for a second term of five consecutive years, subject to shareholder approval. The board meeting commenced at 6:20 P.M. and concluded at 8.00 P.M.</p><ul><li>Approval of un-audited financial results for Q3 FY2025-26</li><li>Resignation and redesignation of Mr. Prashant Thakar</li><li>Re-appointment of Mr. Shail Shah and Mr. Ritesh Chothani as Independent Directors</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/91c3e8ac-5397-4f4f-a983-431bc8e47503.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Suvidhaa Infoserve Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>