<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:21:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SHREEJISPG] Shreeji Shipping Global Ltd: Hon&apos;ble High Court of Gujarat Passes Interim Order on Litigation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shreeji+Shipping+Global+Ltd&title=Shreeji+Shipping+Global+Ltd%3A+Hon%27ble+High+Court+of+Gujarat+Passes+Interim+Order+on+Litigation&newsId=77825ebf-eb73-472b-8451-d5680b9b007c&token=Nzc4MjVlYmYtZWI3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77825ebf-eb73-472b-8451-d5680b9b007c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shreeji Shipping Global Ltd has informed that the Hon&apos;ble High Court of Gujarat has passed an interim order dated January 06, 2026, in relation to the ongoing litigation. The company is in compliance with the court&apos;s directions and is actively pursuing further legal proceedings. The order involves the release of two of the company&apos;s vessels upon furnishing of security to the Registrar, High Court of Gujarat. The company is taking action to vacate the arrest and reduce the security requirement.</p><ul><li>Hon&apos;ble High Court of Gujarat passes interim order on ongoing litigation</li><li>Company is in compliance with the court&apos;s directions</li><li>Further legal proceedings are being actively pursued</li><li>Two vessels to be released upon furnishing of security to the Registrar, High Court of Gujarat</li><li>Company is taking action to vacate the arrest and reduce the security requirement</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/969d7584-e74d-4815-9794-1d0bc412f189.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shreeji Shipping Global Ltd | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KVTOYS] K. V. Toys India Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Consider New Investment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=K.+V.+Toys+India+Ltd&title=K.+V.+Toys+India+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Consider+New+Investment&newsId=3322874e-9b84-45bb-8126-c2fc975523dd&token=MzMyMjg3NGUtOWI4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3322874e-9b84-45bb-8126-c2fc975523dd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>K. V. Toys India Ltd has informed the BSE that a meeting of the Board of Directors is scheduled on 10/01/2026. The agenda includes considering and approving a proposal for investment in a new entity. This investment would be made by way of subscription or acquisition of equity shares or other securities, subject to applicable provisions of the Companies Act, 2013 and other approvals, if any.</p><ul><li>K. V. Toys India Ltd scheduled a Board Meeting on 10th January, 2026</li><li>The agenda includes considering a new investment proposal</li><li>The investment would be made by subscribing or acquiring equity shares or other securities</li><li>The decision is subject to applicable provisions of the Companies Act, 2013 and other approvals</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/18bc52b4-65ac-4f50-b883-ae536d18eb50.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: K. V. Toys India Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MEESHO] Meesho&apos;s General Manager - User Growth and Content Commerce, Milan Partani, Assumes New Role as General Manager - Commerce Platform</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Meesho+Ltd&title=Meesho%27s+General+Manager+-+User+Growth+and+Content+Commerce%2C+Milan+Partani%2C+Assumes+New+Role+as+General+Manager+-+Commerce+Platform&newsId=162cd2ab-f030-4b5b-9727-d0679fb4ae57&token=MTYyY2QyYWItZjAz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">162cd2ab-f030-4b5b-9727-d0679fb4ae57</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Meesho Ltd. has announced that Mr. Milan Partani, General Manager - User Growth and Content Commerce and Senior Management Personnel (SMP) of the Company, will now assume the role of General Manager - Commerce Platform. He will continue to be a Senior Management Personnel of the Company. This disclosure is made in accordance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI Listing Regulations, read with Schedule II and other applicable provisions of SEBI Listing Regulations.</p><ul><li>Milan Partani will assume the role of General Manager - Commerce Platform</li><li>He will continue to be a Senior Management Personnel of the Company</li><li>This change is in accordance with Regulation 30 of the SEBI Listing Regulations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9bcd6838-350e-4a14-b53e-ee948235f438.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Meesho Ltd | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KAKA] Kaka Industries Reports 34.7% YoY Growth in Q3 FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kaka+Industries+Ltd&title=Kaka+Industries+Reports+34.7%25+YoY+Growth+in+Q3+FY+2025-26&newsId=8bd3f05f-5445-4ada-be4c-f2919c3f05a0&token=OGJkM2YwNWYtNTQ0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8bd3f05f-5445-4ada-be4c-f2919c3f05a0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:51:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Kaka Industries Ltd. has reported a strong Year-on-Year growth of 34.70% in Q3 FY 2025-26, driven by robust performance across product categories. The company&apos;s total revenue was Rs. 63.32 Cr, up from Rs. 47.01 Cr in Q3 FY 2024-25. The uPVC profile board segment led the growth, with healthy traction in PVC, WPC, and uPVC profile applications used in doors, windows, ceilings, wall paneling, and interior furniture solutions. The new production facility for uPVC windows is progressing as planned. The company&apos;s capacity utilization stood at 66% of the installed capacity.</p><ul><li>34.70% YoY growth in Q3 FY 2025-26</li><li>Total Revenue of Rs. 63.32 Cr in Q3 FY 2025-26</li><li>Healthy traction in PVC, WPC, and uPVC profile applications</li><li>New production facility for uPVC windows progressing as planned</li><li>66% capacity utilization in Q3 FY 2025-26</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bc3f3042-c014-4588-8ee4-0f637d2ba838.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kaka Industries Ltd | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HEG] HEG Ltd Announces Share Transfer Processing Status for Period from 07.12.2025 to 06.01.2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HEG+LTD.&title=HEG+Ltd+Announces+Share+Transfer+Processing+Status+for+Period+from+07.12.2025+to+06.01.2026&newsId=b206b89f-bbca-43eb-a673-be22f8622184&token=YjIwNmI4OWYtYmJj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b206b89f-bbca-43eb-a673-be22f8622184</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:51:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>HEG Ltd, in compliance with the SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97, has released a report from the Registrar and Share Transfer Agent, MCS Share Transfer Agent Limited, on the re-lodgement of transfer requests of physical shares for the period from 07.12.2025 to 06.01.2026. The report indicates that HEG Ltd received 2 transfer requests, which were processed within 10 days. None of the requests were approved or rejected.</p><ul><li>HEG Ltd releases share transfer processing status for the period from 07.12.2025 to 06.01.2026.</li><li>Received 2 transfer requests for physical shares.</li><li>All requests processed within 10 days.</li><li>No requests were approved or rejected during this period.</li><li>Compliance with SEBI Circular No. SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/afd78491-6c04-4b32-84a2-6acda3bd67fe.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HEG LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VIRINCHI] Virinchi Ltd Allots 40 Lakh Convertible Equity Warrants at Rs.28/- Each</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Virinchi+Ltd&title=Virinchi+Ltd+Allots+40+Lakh+Convertible+Equity+Warrants+at+Rs.28%2F-+Each&newsId=402b9520-1507-4f9f-a4e5-335929f139e9&token=NDAyYjk1MjAtMTUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">402b9520-1507-4f9f-a4e5-335929f139e9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:47:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Virinchi Ltd has allotted 40,00,000 (Forty Lakh only) convertible equity warrants at an Issue Price of Rs.28/- (Face Value of Rs.10/- and Premium of Rs.18/-) on preferential basis. The allotment was approved by the Stakeholders Relationship Committee and was made to IT Peer Technologies LLC. Each warrant is convertible into 1 equity share upon receipt of the balance amount i.e., Rs. 21/- per warrant, within the stipulated time. The allotment does not result in any change in the paid-up share capital of the Company.</p><ul><li>Virinchi Ltd allotted 40,00,000 convertible equity warrants</li><li>Issue Price of Rs.28/- per warrant</li><li>Allotment approved by Stakeholders Relationship Committee</li><li>Convertible into 1 equity share upon receipt of balance amount</li><li>No change in the paid-up share capital of the Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/96b72663-6dbd-413d-a7a1-54f6c8a80d57.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Virinchi Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RAJGASES] Rajasthan Securities Ltd Regularizes Appointment of Mr. Jiteshkumar Narsingdas Agrawal as Non-Executive Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RAJASTHAN+GASES+LTD.&title=Rajasthan+Securities+Ltd+Regularizes+Appointment+of+Mr.+Jiteshkumar+Narsingdas+Agrawal+as+Non-Executive+Independent+Director&newsId=cdaa0859-b7c7-44e6-89de-26f8a7337370&token=Y2RhYTA4NTktYjdj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cdaa0859-b7c7-44e6-89de-26f8a7337370</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:41:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rajasthan Securities Ltd, previously known as Rajasthan Gases Limited, has regularized the appointment of Mr. Jiteshkumar Narsingdas Agrawal as a Non-Executive Independent Director. Mr. Agrawal was initially appointed as an Additional Non-Executive Independent Director on 7th October 2025, subject to shareholder approval. The shareholders approved his appointment in the Extra-Ordinary General Meeting held on 6th January 2026. Mr. Agrawal holds a Bachelor’s degree in Law and has cleared the Independent Director examination conducted by the Indian Institute of Corporate Affairs. He is known for his integrity, sound judgment, and professional competence. He is not related to the Directors or Key managers of the company and is not debarred from holding the office of a director by virtue of any SEBI order or any other such authority.</p><ul><li>Rajasthan Securities Ltd regularizes the appointment of Mr. Jiteshkumar Narsingdas Agrawal as Non-Executive Independent Director.</li><li>Mr. Agrawal was initially appointed as an Additional Non-Executive Independent Director on 7th October 2025.</li><li>Mr. Agrawal holds a Bachelor’s degree in Law and has cleared the Independent Director examination conducted by the Indian Institute of Corporate Affairs.</li><li>Mr. Agrawal is known for his integrity, sound judgment, and professional competence.</li><li>Mr. Agrawal is not related to the Directors or Key managers of the company and is not debarred from holding the office of a director.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/abb1439f-4ca8-41bf-9aaa-6d52e95f144b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RAJASTHAN GASES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ANGELONE] Angel One Ltd Announces Stock Split, Interim Dividend, and Closed Trading Window</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Angel+One+Ltd&title=Angel+One+Ltd+Announces+Stock+Split%2C+Interim+Dividend%2C+and+Closed+Trading+Window&newsId=d93cdff1-a6f7-46d9-910c-30be02610853&token=ZDkzY2RmZjEtYTZm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d93cdff1-a6f7-46d9-910c-30be02610853</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Angel One Ltd has announced a proposal for alteration in the share capital of the company by sub-division/split of existing equity shares having a face value of Rs. 10 each. The company will also declare the first interim dividend for the financial year 2025-26. The record date for reckoning the shareholders who shall be entitled to receive the interim dividend is Wednesday, January 21, 2026. The trading window in respect of equity shares of the company will remain closed till January 17, 2026.</p><ul><li>Angel One Ltd proposes a stock split of existing equity shares.</li><li>The company will declare the first interim dividend for the financial year 2025-26.</li><li>The record date for dividend entitlement is Wednesday, January 21, 2026.</li><li>The trading window for equity shares will remain closed till January 17, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3a7ca130-d857-4542-a552-3798e5f4c358.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Angel One Ltd | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[DEVYANI] Devyani International Ltd Releases Inaugural Sustainability Report for FY2024-25</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Devyani+International+Ltd&title=Devyani+International+Ltd+Releases+Inaugural+Sustainability+Report+for+FY2024-25&newsId=1600f142-f647-4ada-a396-67f3ff3f3e35&token=MTYwMGYxNDItZjY0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1600f142-f647-4ada-a396-67f3ff3f3e35</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:34:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Devyani International Limited (DIL), one of India’s largest Quick-Service Restaurant (QSR) companies, has published its inaugural Sustainability Report for FY2024-25. The report, prepared with reference to Global Reporting Initiative (GRI) and Sustainability Accounting Standards Board (SASB) standards, outlines the Company’s approach to sustainability, commitments, key initiatives, and performance during the year. It highlights DIL’s focus on environmental stewardship, social impact efforts, and strong governance frameworks. The report aligns with India’s evolving sustainability and disclosure requirements, including Business Responsibility and Sustainability Reporting (BRSR).</p><ul><li>Publication of inaugural Sustainability Report for FY2024-25</li><li>Alignment with Global Reporting Initiative (GRI) and Sustainability Accounting Standards Board (SASB) standards</li><li>Focus on environmental stewardship, social impact efforts, and strong governance frameworks</li><li>Adherence to India’s evolving sustainability and disclosure requirements, including Business Responsibility and Sustainability Reporting (BRSR)</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/123ec017-eebb-41ff-8b69-fe90956ff10c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Devyani International Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ITHL] International Travel House Ltd. to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on 14th January, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INTERNATIONAL+TRAVEL+HOUSE+LTD.-%24&title=International+Travel+House+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+14th+January%2C+2026&newsId=b0b8397c-60bc-4a04-b216-0e32d648b170&token=YjBiODM5N2MtNjBi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b0b8397c-60bc-4a04-b216-0e32d648b170</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>International Travel House Ltd. has announced a Board Meeting scheduled on 14th January, 2026. The meeting will consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results of the Company for the Quarter and Nine months ended 31st December, 2025.</p><ul><li>International Travel House Ltd. is set to approve its Q3 and nine months financial results on 14th January, 2026.</li><li>The results are for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/68f5413a-8a33-47b5-9604-0c1dcf8339e3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INTERNATIONAL TRAVEL HOUSE LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>