<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:44:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[INDLEASE] India Lease Development Ltd Announces Q3 &amp; Nine Months Results for 2025, Highlights Profit Before Tax</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDIA+LEASE+DEVELOPMENT+LTD.&title=India+Lease+Development+Ltd+Announces+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025%2C+Highlights+Profit+Before+Tax&newsId=4ea0656f-71f3-4878-97fa-3b11ca587f79&token=NGVhMDY1NmYtNzFm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4ea0656f-71f3-4878-97fa-3b11ca587f79</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:43:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>India Lease Development Ltd has announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a profit before tax of (11.72) Lakhs. The revenue from operations stood at 12,200.8 Lakhs for the quarter and 36,583.5 Lakhs for the nine months ended December 31, 2025. The profit before exceptional items and tax was (11.72) Lakhs. The company&apos;s total expenses were 68,150 Lakhs for the quarter and 1,73,766.5 Lakhs for the nine months ended December 31, 2025. The net profit for the period from continuing operations was (5.12) Lakhs. The total comprehensive income for the period was (56.02) Lakhs.</p><ul><li>Profit before tax of (11.72) Lakhs</li><li>Revenue from operations of 12,200.8 Lakhs for the quarter</li><li>Total expenses of 68,150 Lakhs for the quarter</li><li>Net profit for the period from continuing operations of (5.12) Lakhs</li><li>Total comprehensive income for the period of (56.02) Lakhs</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ff2296a0-9ddb-4dba-af16-317a58c36598.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDIA LEASE DEVELOPMENT LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NARBADA] Narbada Gems and Jewellery Ltd Receives NCLT Order Sanctioning Scheme</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NARBADA+GEMS+AND+JEWELLERY+LTD.&title=Narbada+Gems+and+Jewellery+Ltd+Receives+NCLT+Order+Sanctioning+Scheme&newsId=6bd094b8-a454-47a6-a176-ba8f1831d56d&token=NmJkMDk0YjgtYTQ1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6bd094b8-a454-47a6-a176-ba8f1831d56d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:43:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Narbada Gems and Jewellery Ltd has received the certified copy of the Order passed by the National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT) on 10th February 2026, sanctioning the Scheme under section 230 — 232 of the Companies Act, 2013. The board of directors of the Company in its meeting held on the same day took note of the receipt of the Order and proposed filing of the same with the Registrar of Companies (ROC). The board also fixed Friday, 27% February, 2026 as the ‘Record Date’ for determining the Company’s eligible shareholders who shall be issued and allotted equity shares of the Transferee Company in accordance with the Scheme.</p><ul><li>Narbada Gems and Jewellery Ltd has received the certified copy of the NCLT Order sanctioning the Scheme.</li><li>The board of directors of the Company proposed filing of the Order with the ROC for the Scheme to become effective.</li><li>Friday, 27% February, 2026 has been fixed as the ‘Record Date’ for determining the Company’s eligible shareholders.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e510218a-c1a0-4f1f-ba07-202c37de4fce.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NARBADA GEMS AND JEWELLERY LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PREMEXPLQ] Premier Explosives&apos; Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025: Revenue Growth and Profit Decline</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PREMIER+EXPLOSIVES+LTD.&title=Premier+Explosives%27+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025%3A+Revenue+Growth+and+Profit+Decline&newsId=bf5fa880-65be-4514-a0d8-513a256631e3&token=YmY1ZmE4ODAtNjVi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf5fa880-65be-4514-a0d8-513a256631e3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:42:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Premier Explosives Ltd. announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a 20.2% increase in total revenue, reaching INR 32,852.51 lakhs compared to INR 27,171.76 lakhs in the same period last year. However, the profit before exceptional items and tax decreased by 42.5% to INR 3,158.13 lakhs, mainly due to an ex-gratia compensation of INR 120 lakhs for employees affected by an accident at the manufacturing facility. The company operates in the High Energy Materials sector and is subject to new labor codes in India, but the impact is not expected to be material.</p><ul><li>Revenue increased by 20.2% to INR 32,852.51 lakhs compared to INR 27,171.76 lakhs in Q3 and nine months 2024</li><li>Profit before exceptional items and tax decreased by 42.5% to INR 3,158.13 lakhs</li><li>Ex-gratia compensation of INR 120 lakhs recognized as an exceptional item</li><li>New labor codes in India have been assessed and found to have a non-material impact on the company&apos;s financials</li><li>Purchase discount of INR 2,246.39 lakhs recognized as other income in the previous quarter</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ecfdfb5c-0f3c-4131-bdac-0bacfb153908.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PREMIER EXPLOSIVES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MIDWESTLTD] Midwest Ltd. Announces Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025, Shifts Registered Office</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Midwest+Ltd&title=Midwest+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025%2C+Shifts+Registered+Office&newsId=b4fdc4df-ec15-47b5-b6e0-ebd93407b854&token=YjRmZGM0ZGYtZWMx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4fdc4df-ec15-47b5-b6e0-ebd93407b854</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:42:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Midwest Ltd., formerly known as Midwest Private Limited, has announced its un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at 1,030.43 million for the quarter and 1,222.52 million for the nine months ended period. The company has also approved the shifting of its registered office to a new location in Hyderabad. The meeting of the Board of Directors commenced at 12.45 P.M. and concluded at 02.45 P.M. on February 12, 2026.</p><ul><li>Midwest Ltd. announces Q3 and nine months financial results for 2025.</li><li>Revenue from operations stands at 1,030.43 million for the quarter and 1,222.52 million for the nine months ended period.</li><li>The company has shifted its registered office to a new location in Hyderabad.</li><li>The meeting of the Board of Directors was held on February 12, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7b5f962a-f669-4afb-ba50-03140965cb30.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Midwest Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PRIMAGR] Prima Agro Ltd Announces Q3 2025 Financial Results with Net Loss of INR 1246 Million</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PRIMA+AGRO+LTD.&title=Prima+Agro+Ltd+Announces+Q3+2025+Financial+Results+with+Net+Loss+of+INR+1246+Million&newsId=3ab61507-2d35-4aa5-989c-54ed592e5cc4&token=M2FiNjE1MDctMmQz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ab61507-2d35-4aa5-989c-54ed592e5cc4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Prima Agro Ltd has announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s standalone revenue from operations was INR 24.28 million, while the consolidated revenue from operations stood at INR 25.01 million. The total expenses for the quarter were INR 30.73 million (standalone) and INR 23.10 million (consolidated). The company reported a net loss of INR 1246 million for the quarter. The Board of Directors has reviewed and approved these results.</p><ul><li>Prima Agro Ltd announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 2025.</li><li>The standalone revenue from operations was INR 24.28 million, and the consolidated revenue from operations stood at INR 25.01 million.</li><li>The total expenses for the quarter were INR 30.73 million (standalone) and INR 23.10 million (consolidated).</li><li>The company reported a net loss of INR 1246 million for the quarter.</li><li>The Board of Directors has reviewed and approved these results.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5520ce77-09ce-49e9-91af-e6a1eeec0754.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PRIMA AGRO LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BAROEXT] Baroda Extrusion Ltd. Approves Q3 Results with Profit After Tax at ₹ 87.61 Lakhs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BARODA+EXTRUSION+LTD.&title=Baroda+Extrusion+Ltd.+Approves+Q3+Results+with+Profit+After+Tax+at+%E2%82%B9+87.61+Lakhs&newsId=a5476ccf-0068-480b-b626-5295a160e647&token=YTU0NzZjY2YtMDA2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5476ccf-0068-480b-b626-5295a160e647</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:42:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Baroda Extrusion Ltd. has announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December 2025. The total income stands at ₹ 4,447.97 Lakhs. The company has approved a loan from its director, Mr. Alpesh Kanugo. The board meeting commenced at 14:00 A.M/P.M and concluded at 14:30 AAM/P.M. The company is engaged in the business of Copper Tubes and Bars etc. The previous quarters/periods figures have been regrouped/rearranged wherever necessary to make it comparable with the current quarter/period. The company has made a preliminary assessment and accounted for the incremental impact under Employee benefits expenses in the Statement of Profit and Loss during the quarter and nine months ended 31 December 2025, in accordance with the new Labour Codes.</p><ul><li>Un-audited financial results for the Quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025 approved.</li><li>Loan approved for Mr. Alpesh Kanugo, Director of the company.</li><li>Company engaged in the business of Copper Tubes and Bars only.</li><li>Preliminary assessment made for the new Labour Codes impact.</li><li>Profit after tax for the period stands at ₹ 87.61 Lakhs.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4f3876bd-271c-4dd0-8599-7c7bf4ce19da.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BARODA EXTRUSION LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PIGL] Power and Instrumentation (Gujarat) Ltd. Allots 6,12,000 Equity Shares to Promoter Group</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Power+and+Instrumentation+%28Gujarat%29+Ltd&title=Power+and+Instrumentation+%28Gujarat%29+Ltd.+Allots+6%2C12%2C000+Equity+Shares+to+Promoter+Group&newsId=c73c64a7-be4c-4ca2-9f9e-50d290f8c585&token=YzczYzY0YTctYmU0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c73c64a7-be4c-4ca2-9f9e-50d290f8c585</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:42:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Power and Instrumentation (Gujarat) Ltd. has informed that the Board of Directors, at their meeting held on February 12, 2026, approved the allotment of 6,12,000 Equity Shares of Rs. 10/- each at a premium of Rs. 73.75/- per equity share. This allotment is pursuant to the conversion of 6,12,000 Convertible Warrants from the total 50,96,000 Convertible Warrants, issued and allotted on September 21, 2024, to the Promoter group under the terms of SEBI (Issue of Capital &amp; Disclosures Requirement) Regulation, 2018. This allotment has increased the company&apos;s paid-up equity capital from Rs. 18,70,09,000/- consisting of 1,87,00,900 Equity Shares of Rs. 10/- each to Rs. 19,31,29,000/- consisting of 1,93,12,900 Equity Shares of Rs. 10/- each.</p><ul><li>Power and Instrumentation (Gujarat) Ltd. allots 6,12,000 Equity Shares to Promoter Group</li><li>Allotment is pursuant to the conversion of 6,12,000 Convertible Warrants from the total 50,96,000 Convertible Warrants</li><li>Allotment approved at the Board of Directors meeting held on February 12, 2026</li><li>Paid-up equity capital increases from Rs. 18,70,09,000/- to Rs. 19,31,29,000/-</li><li>Allotment made under the terms of SEBI (Issue of Capital &amp; Disclosures Requirement) Regulation, 2018</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/08119465-a3d9-40f1-9ebf-f41642a5d095.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Power and Instrumentation (Gujarat) Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FFPL] Foundry Fuel Products Ltd: Appoints Mrs. Sneha Sharma as Additional Director, Records Q3 &amp; Nine Months Financial Results, and Accepts Mrs. Sudha Ramesh&apos;s Resignation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=FOUNDRY+FUEL+PRODUCTS+LTD.&title=Foundry+Fuel+Products+Ltd%3A+Appoints+Mrs.+Sneha+Sharma+as+Additional+Director%2C+Records+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Financial+Results%2C+and+Accepts+Mrs.+Sudha+Ramesh%27s+Resignation&newsId=8d5ebbf6-2d9d-47b6-8a87-8592b401f63e&token=OGQ1ZWJiZjYtMmQ5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d5ebbf6-2d9d-47b6-8a87-8592b401f63e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In a recent meeting on February 12, 2026, the Board of Directors of Foundry Fuel Products Ltd approved and took on record the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The company also announced the resignation of Mrs. Sudha Ramesh from her position as Non-Executive Independent Woman Director due to personal reasons. The board expressed gratitude for her contributions. Furthermore, the board appointed Mrs. Sneha Sharma as an Additional Director in the category of Non-Executive Independent Woman Director for a first term of five consecutive years, subject to approval by members in the ensuing General Meeting.</p><ul><li>Foundry Fuel Products Ltd announced the unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December 2025.</li><li>Mrs. Sudha Ramesh resigned from her position as Non-Executive Independent Woman Director due to personal reasons.</li><li>The board expressed gratitude for Mrs. Sudha Ramesh&apos;s contributions during her long association with the company.</li><li>Mrs. Sneha Sharma appointed as an Additional Director in the category of Non-Executive Independent Woman Director.</li><li>Mrs. Sneha Sharma&apos;s appointment is subject to approval by members in the ensuing General Meeting.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9e57f368-ea53-4ff9-ab92-86e8a6029c69.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: FOUNDRY FUEL PRODUCTS LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BINANIIND] Bil Vyapar Ltd Issues Revised Form G for CIRP with Invitation for EOI</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BINANI+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Bil+Vyapar+Ltd+Issues+Revised+Form+G+for+CIRP+with+Invitation+for+EOI&newsId=d8357bcd-da80-4ce2-856e-72bfb92f7270&token=ZDgzNTdiY2QtZGE4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d8357bcd-da80-4ce2-856e-72bfb92f7270</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:41:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Invitation for EOI</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bil Vyapar Ltd, formerly known as Binani Industries Limited, has issued a revised Form G under Regulation 30 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The company is inviting expressions of interest for the Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP). Bil Vyapar Ltd was primarily engaged in management consultancy services, with total revenue of Rs. 0 and other income of Rs. 2,51,000 in the last financial year. The company&apos;s assets are located in Mumbai, Maharashtra, and Ahmedabad, Gujarat. The last available financial statements of two years and lists of creditors can be obtained by mailing ibc.binani@gmail.com or by visiting the IBBI website. The eligibility criteria for resolution applicants are available at the aforementioned email address. The last date for receipt of expressions of interest is 07.04.2026, and the submission process email ID is ibc.binani@gmail.com.</p><ul><li>Bil Vyapar Ltd issues revised Form G for CIRP</li><li>Invitation for Expression of Interest</li><li>Company was primarily engaged in management consultancy services</li><li>Total revenue of Rs. 0 and other income of Rs. 2,51,000 in the last financial year</li><li>Assets are located in Mumbai, Maharashtra, and Ahmedabad, Gujarat</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2e65da0b-426e-492d-a2bc-8c458512a110.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BINANI INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Invitation for EOI</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EMAINDIA] EMA India Ltd Independent Director, Ms. Honey Bhatia, Resigns Due to Personal Reasons</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=EMA+INDIA+LTD.&title=EMA+India+Ltd+Independent+Director%2C+Ms.+Honey+Bhatia%2C+Resigns+Due+to+Personal+Reasons&newsId=d0837912-f7e2-4bd7-829f-122249e61825&token=ZDA4Mzc5MTItZjdl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d0837912-f7e2-4bd7-829f-122249e61825</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 09:41:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>EMA India Ltd announced the resignation of its Independent Director, Ms. Honey Bhatia, due to personal reasons and other interests she wishes to pursue in the future. Ms. Bhatia&apos;s resignation was accepted by the company with effect from the close of business hours on 11th February 2026. The company expressed its gratitude for her services and contributions during her tenure. Ms. Bhatia confirmed that there are no material reasons for her resignation other than those mentioned in her resignation letter.</p><ul><li>Ms. Honey Bhatia tendered her resignation as Independent Director of EMA India Ltd.</li><li>The resignation was due to personal reasons and other interests Ms. Bhatia wishes to pursue.</li><li>Ms. Bhatia was relieved from the services of the company with effect from 11th February 2026.</li><li>The company acknowledged Ms. Bhatia&apos;s contributions and expressed its appreciation for her services.</li><li>Ms. Bhatia confirmed that there are no other material reasons for her resignation.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6576b971-a7be-40a0-b5c9-99dbf5ee03c0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: EMA INDIA LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>