<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 12:38:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[INDGN] Indegene Ltd Subsidiary Acquires DT Associates and Trilogy Writing and Consulting UK for £2,001,000 and £702,348 Respectively</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Indegene+Ltd&title=Indegene+Ltd+Subsidiary+Acquires+DT+Associates+and+Trilogy+Writing+and+Consulting+UK+for+%C2%A32%2C001%2C000+and+%C2%A3702%2C348+Respectively&newsId=721f3163-4fcd-4bf3-97d8-a1c1545c1a15&token=NzIxZjMxNjMtNGZj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">721f3163-4fcd-4bf3-97d8-a1c1545c1a15</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 12:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Indegene Ltd&apos;s subsidiary, Indegene Healthcare UK Limited, has signed a Share Purchase Agreement (SPA) to acquire 100% equity shares in DT Associates Research and Consulting Services Limited, UK and Trilogy Writing and Consulting Limited, UK. DT Associates is a London-based company providing analytics, technology, and commercial, medical, regulatory and safety services to life science and healthcare organizations, while Trilogy UK provides writing and training services for the pharmaceutical industry. The acquisition is a related party transaction, with the total consideration being £2,703,348. The acquisition is part of Indegene&apos;s internal restructuring and is expected to be completed by 31st March 2026. Both DT Associates and Trilogy UK are based in London, with DT Associates reporting a revenue of £6,400,711 and Trilogy UK reporting a revenue of £2,340,488 in their last financial years.</p><ul><li>Indegene Healthcare UK Limited acquires DT Associates Research and Consulting Services Limited, UK and Trilogy Writing and Consulting Limited, UK.</li><li>The total consideration for the acquisition is £2,703,348.</li><li>The acquisition is a part of Indegene&apos;s internal restructuring.</li><li>DT Associates reported a revenue of £6,400,711 in its last financial year.</li><li>Trilogy UK reported a revenue of £2,340,488 in its last financial year.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d5383f44-c155-488a-9266-d769c0e50daa.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Indegene Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MUFIN] Mufin Green Finance Empanelled with Assam Government for Instant Loans</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Mufin+Green+Finance+Ltd&title=Mufin+Green+Finance+Empanelled+with+Assam+Government+for+Instant+Loans&newsId=f81ea809-462e-4c41-abe1-f54510e36568&token=ZjgxZWE4MDktNDYy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f81ea809-462e-4c41-abe1-f54510e36568</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 11:01:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Mufin Green Finance Limited has been empanelled with the Government of Assam to provide instant loans to more than 5 lakh Assam Government employees directly through the state’s Human Resource Management System (HRMS). This integration enables seamless, real-time access to financing for over five lakh government employees across Assam. Through the HRMS platform, employees can apply for loans and receive approvals instantly — ensuring 24/7 access to funds without delays or paperwork hurdles. Thousands of public sector employees are expected to benefit from the streamlined and transparent loan process. The initiative aligns with broader national objectives of promoting financial inclusion and enhancing access to responsible credit for government staff.</p><ul><li>Mufin Green Finance empanelled with Assam Government for instant loans</li><li>Loans offered directly through the state’s Human Resource Management System (HRMS)</li><li>Seamless, real-time access to financing for over five lakh government employees</li><li>Streamlined and transparent loan process</li><li>Alignment with national objectives of promoting financial inclusion and responsible credit access</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fbf8ad63-90b3-42b2-b958-32b5d302f30b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Mufin Green Finance Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HEROMOTOCO] Hero MotoCorp Delivers Strong 44% Dispatch Growth with 5.58 Lakh Units Sold in February 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HERO+MOTOCORP+LTD.&title=Hero+MotoCorp+Delivers+Strong+44%25+Dispatch+Growth+with+5.58+Lakh+Units+Sold+in+February+2026&newsId=737a4600-9efc-48f0-8759-9ca24dc535e6&token=NzM3YTQ2MDAtOWVm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">737a4600-9efc-48f0-8759-9ca24dc535e6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 11:01:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Hero MotoCorp, the world’s largest manufacturer of motorcycles and scooters, reported its strongest year-on-year (Y-o-Y) dispatch performance for February 2026. The Company dispatched 558,216 units during the month, registering a robust ~44% growth compared to 388,068 units, during the same period last year. The Company also recorded 18% Y-o-Y growth with 458,346 VAHAN registrations in February 2026. The strong performance was driven by continued momentum in the Scooter segment and the 100cc - 125cc segment, which recorded an impressive growth. VIDA, Hero MotoCorp’s emerging mobility business, continued its growth trajectory, recording a three-fold increase in its market share over the same period last year. The Company’s Global Business maintained its growth momentum, recording dispatch growth of ~34% with 41,248 units in February 2026 compared to 30,772 units during the same period last year.</p><ul><li>Hero MotoCorp dispatched 558,216 units in February 2026, a 44% Y-o-Y growth</li><li>The Company recorded 18% Y-o-Y growth with 458,346 VAHAN registrations in February 2026</li><li>Scooter segment and 100cc - 125cc segment recorded impressive growth</li><li>VIDA recorded a three-fold increase in its market share</li><li>Global Business recorded a 34% Y-o-Y dispatch growth in February 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1b5a8bef-8f91-4a2c-8946-be50c33280ce.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HERO MOTOCORP LTD. | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GRINDWELL] Grindwell Norton Ltd. Receives Demand Drop Order from Office of Assistant Commissioner of Commercial Taxes, Bengaluru</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GRINDWELL+NORTON+LTD.-%24&title=Grindwell+Norton+Ltd.+Receives+Demand+Drop+Order+from+Office+of+Assistant+Commissioner+of+Commercial+Taxes%2C+Bengaluru&newsId=4f4da1e4-a73f-452c-a2b8-66c9841e8ac1&token=NGY0ZGExZTQtYTcz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4f4da1e4-a73f-452c-a2b8-66c9841e8ac1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 11:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Legal</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Grindwell Norton Ltd. has received a demand drop order from the Office of the Assistant Commissioner of Commercial Taxes, Bengaluru. The Company was served with a Show Cause Notice amounting to 322,59,706, but after filing a reply, the demand has been reduced to &apos;Nil&apos;. The order was received on February 28, 2026, in response to the Show Cause Notice. There is no material impact on the financial, operational, or other activities of the Company.</p><ul><li>Grindwell Norton Ltd. received a demand drop order from the Office of the Assistant Commissioner of Commercial Taxes, Bengaluru.</li><li>The Company initially received a Show Cause Notice amounting to 322,59,706.</li><li>After filing a reply, the demand was reduced to &apos;Nil&apos;.</li><li>The order was received on February 28, 2026.</li><li>No material impact on the Company&apos;s financial, operational, or other activities.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/75fec25e-7b4f-4375-90fc-c21340ff22bc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GRINDWELL NORTON LTD.-$ | Category: Legal</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BHARATCOAL] Bharat Coking Coal Ltd Reports Provisional Production Performance for Feb&apos;26 and Apr&apos;25-Feb&apos;26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Bharat+Coking+Coal+Ltd&title=Bharat+Coking+Coal+Ltd+Reports+Provisional+Production+Performance+for+Feb%2726+and+Apr%2725-Feb%2726&newsId=e0de55c7-f616-4813-9a3a-a603babad7fc&token=ZTBkZTU1YzctZjYx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0de55c7-f616-4813-9a3a-a603babad7fc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 11:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bharat Coking Coal Limited has released its provisional monthly production performance for February 2026 and the period from April 2025 to February 2026. The report includes production details of raw coal according to the type of coal and mine. The raw coal production and offtake are key metrics provided in the report.</p><ul><li>Bharat Coking Coal Ltd reports provisional production performance for Feb&apos;26</li><li>Performance data for the period Apr&apos;25-Feb&apos;26 also provided</li><li>Raw coal production details according to coal and mine types included</li><li>Key metrics include raw coal production and offtake</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/69725400-d62a-4b49-bca9-f6fb1cc014cc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Bharat Coking Coal Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[OLAELEC] Ola Electric launches ‘Ola Insiders’ with benefits up to ¥50,000 for Gen 1 and Gen 2 customers</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ola+Electric+Mobility+Ltd&title=Ola+Electric+launches+%E2%80%98Ola+Insiders%E2%80%99+with+benefits+up+to+%C2%A550%2C000+for+Gen+1+and+Gen+2+customers&newsId=f4599ded-f79d-4337-ada7-cfcd3703fdd7&token=ZjQ1OTlkZWQtZjc5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4599ded-f79d-4337-ada7-cfcd3703fdd7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 10:37:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ola Electric, India&apos;s leading electric vehicle manufacturer, has announced the launch of an exclusive community program called Ola Insiders. The program offers benefits up to ¥50,000 for Gen 1 and Gen 2 customers who upgrade to Gen 3 scooters and Roadster motorcycles. Existing customers can also unlock benefits of up to ¥20,000 when adding another Ola vehicle under the same registered name, and earn up to ¥5,000 in Ola credits through referrals. The program aims to support seamless vehicle upgrades, enable multi-Ola households, and make it easier for the community to adopt electric mobility.</p><ul><li>Ola Electric launches ‘Ola Insiders’ community program for existing customers</li><li>Gen 1 and Gen 2 customers can upgrade to Gen 3 S1 portfolio and Roadster motorcycles with benefits up to ¥50,000</li><li>Existing customers can unlock benefits of up to ¥20,000 when adding another Ola vehicle</li><li>Customers can earn up to ¥5,000 in Ola credits through referrals</li><li>Program supports seamless vehicle upgrades, enables multi-Ola households, and promotes electric mobility adoption</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ad3420d1-5745-4550-9182-63994f379164.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ola Electric Mobility Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BHARTIARTL] Airtel and Google Collaborate to Advance Spam Protection in India With Secure RCS Messaging</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BHARTI+AIRTEL+LTD.&title=Airtel+and+Google+Collaborate+to+Advance+Spam+Protection+in+India+With+Secure+RCS+Messaging&newsId=670a9270-1cc8-43a5-acdc-cb1a0accd197&token=NjcwYTkyNzAtMWNj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">670a9270-1cc8-43a5-acdc-cb1a0accd197</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 10:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>MoU</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Bharti Airtel and Google have announced a collaboration to offer a secure and engaging messaging experience for millions of users in India. By combining Airtel’s network intelligence with Google’s Rich Communications Services (RCS) platform and spam filtering, users get to experience RCS messaging with high-quality photo/video and interactive elements like message reactions. Airtel has, to date, blocked a staggering 71 billion spam calls and 2.9 billion spam SMSes, leading to a 68.7% decrease in financial losses. However, a protection gap exists within the digital ecosystem, with many non-telco communication platforms and standalone apps lacking safety standards. This partnership between Airtel and Google aims to bridge that gap, extending telecom-grade safeguards to the modern messaging experience. The solution will enable brands to build deeper engagement with their customers who will feel safer and in more control.</p><ul><li>Airtel and Google collaborate to offer secure RCS messaging in India</li><li>Combination of Airtel’s network intelligence with Google’s RCS platform and spam filtering</li><li>Airtel has blocked 71 billion spam calls and 2.9 billion spam SMSes</li><li>Partnership aims to bridge the protection gap in the digital ecosystem</li><li>Solution to enable brands to build deeper engagement with customers</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/467cce5a-42a0-45c7-b7cc-13c78c86bced.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BHARTI AIRTEL LTD. | Category: MoU</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADANIENT] Adani Enterprises Subsidiary to Acquire Defence Unit from Punj Lloyd Ltd.</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADANI+ENTERPRISES+LTD.&title=Adani+Enterprises+Subsidiary+to+Acquire+Defence+Unit+from+Punj+Lloyd+Ltd.&newsId=2aba31c5-afab-4e47-a587-2123a01df65a&token=MmFiYTMxYzUtYWZh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2aba31c5-afab-4e47-a587-2123a01df65a</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Adani Defence Systems and Technologies Ltd (ADSTL), a wholly owned subsidiary of Adani Enterprises Ltd, has executed a Business Transfer Agreement (BTA) with Punj Lloyd Ltd (PLL) for the transfer of a Defence Unit of PLL situated at Malanpur, Madhya Pradesh. The transaction is a slump sale and ADSTL is a wholly owned subsidiary of the Company. No related party transactions are involved in this acquisition.</p><ul><li>Adani Defence Systems and Technologies Ltd (ADSTL) to acquire a Defence Unit of Punj Lloyd Ltd (PLL) situated at Malanpur.</li><li>The transaction is a slump sale.</li><li>ADSTL is a wholly owned subsidiary of Adani Enterprises Ltd.</li><li>No related party transactions are involved in this acquisition.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/23c6e2a6-1a08-4d77-bf34-429ad92aeede.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADANI ENTERPRISES LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADANIENT] Adani Enterprises Subsidiary to Acquire 14.2% Stake in Air Works</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADANI+ENTERPRISES+LTD.&title=Adani+Enterprises+Subsidiary+to+Acquire+14.2%25+Stake+in+Air+Works&newsId=c22b5859-4c1a-494b-8c73-4706ded77e48&token=YzIyYjU4NTktNGMx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c22b5859-4c1a-494b-8c73-4706ded77e48</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Adani Defence Systems &amp; Technologies Ltd (ADSTL), a wholly owned subsidiary of Adani Enterprises Ltd, has signed a Share Purchase Agreement (SPA) with Punj Lloyd Aviation Ltd (PLAL) to acquire a 14.2% stake in Air Works India (Engineering) Private Ltd. Post completion of the acquisition, ADSTL&apos;s stake in Air Works will increase to 99.98%. The acquisition is expected to give ADSTL special rights such as the right to appoint directors, first right to share subscription in case of issuance of shares, and the right to restrict any change in capital structure.</p><ul><li>Adani Defence Systems &amp; Technologies Ltd (ADSTL) to acquire 14.2% stake in Air Works</li><li>ADSTL already holds 85.76% in Air Works, post acquisition stake will increase to 99.98%</li><li>Acquisition expected to give ADSTL special rights like right to appoint directors, first right to share subscription, right to restrict any change in capital structure</li><li>ADSTL is a wholly owned subsidiary of Adani Enterprises Ltd and Air Works is a subsidiary of ADSTL</li><li>Transaction does not fall within related party transactions</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f53b9415-6595-4bc3-96b8-2bd02bb0ef93.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADANI ENTERPRISES LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ABCAPITAL] Aditya Birla Capital Ltd: Chief Technology Officer, Ramesh Narayanaswamy, Resigns</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Aditya+Birla+Capital+Ltd&title=Aditya+Birla+Capital+Ltd%3A+Chief+Technology+Officer%2C+Ramesh+Narayanaswamy%2C+Resigns&newsId=f77d83cf-6f10-4e42-893a-84859e06b718&token=Zjc3ZDgzY2YtNmYx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f77d83cf-6f10-4e42-893a-84859e06b718</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 09:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Aditya Birla Capital Limited has announced the resignation of its Chief Technology Officer, Mr. Ramesh Narayanaswamy. According to the company&apos;s disclosure, Mr. Narayanaswamy has tendered his resignation to pursue opportunities outside the company, with his last day being 28 February 2026. The company has provided all the necessary details as per the SEBI Master Circular No. HO/49/14/14(7)2025-CFD-POD2/1/3762/2026 dated January 30, 2026. The resignation letter from Mr. Narayanaswamy is also enclosed in the disclosure.</p><ul><li>Aditya Birla Capital Limited announces the resignation of its Chief Technology Officer, Mr. Ramesh Narayanaswamy.</li><li>Mr. Narayanaswamy has resigned to pursue opportunities outside the company.</li><li>His last working day will be 28 February 2026.</li><li>The company has disclosed all necessary details as per SEBI regulations.</li><li>The resignation letter from Mr. Narayanaswamy is also provided in the disclosure.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/04ad2547-9dd2-45d2-95e4-ce7709216519.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Aditya Birla Capital Ltd | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>