<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:58:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ENBETRD] Enbee Trade &amp; Finance Ltd Sets Record Date for Rights Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ENBEE+TRADE+%26+FINANCE+LTD.&title=Enbee+Trade+%26+Finance+Ltd+Sets+Record+Date+for+Rights+Issue&newsId=5bb72bfe-9d23-42f8-a65f-4aec6bebd3ae&token=NWJiNzJiZmUtOWQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5bb72bfe-9d23-42f8-a65f-4aec6bebd3ae</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Right Issue</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Enbee Trade &amp; Finance Ltd announced that the Board of Directors has fixed Wednesday, March 04, 2026 as the record date for the purpose of determining equity shareholders who are entitled to receive right entitlement in the Rights Issue. This decision is in accordance with Regulations 42 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligation and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015, as amended and Regulation 68 of the SEBI (ICDR) Regulations, 2018. This announcement comes after the Board&apos;s meeting held on February 25, 2026 for approving the terms of the Rights Issue of the Company.</p><ul><li>Enbee Trade &amp; Finance Ltd sets record date for Rights Issue</li><li>The record date is fixed as Wednesday, March 04, 2026</li><li>The decision is in accordance with SEBI regulations</li><li>The announcement follows the Board&apos;s meeting held on February 25, 2026</li><li>The meeting was for approving the terms of the Rights Issue of the Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/94744d24-f0b6-4b80-8fb5-0e9cd367bb4b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ENBEE TRADE & FINANCE LTD. | Category: Right Issue</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[OFSS] Oracle Financial Services Software Ltd Appoints Simon de Montfort Walker as Additional Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ORACLE+FINANCIAL+SERVICES+SOFTWARE+LTD.&title=Oracle+Financial+Services+Software+Ltd+Appoints+Simon+de+Montfort+Walker+as+Additional+Director&newsId=affc7be5-d3f0-456f-97c1-d23d41fc70a6&token=YWZmYzdiZTUtZDNm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">affc7be5-d3f0-456f-97c1-d23d41fc70a6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:51:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Oracle Financial Services Software Ltd announced the appointment of Mr. Simon de Montfort Walker as an Additional Director in the capacity of Non-Executive, Non-Independent Director. The appointment is subject to the approval of the Shareholders of the Company through a postal ballot. Mr. Walker is currently the Oracle Executive Vice President, Industry Applications, and has extensive experience in financial services technology. He joined Oracle in 2019 and has been responsible for strategy execution, operational performance, and the delivery of AI-driven and cloud-enabled solutions for consumer-focused industries.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Simon de Montfort Walker as an Additional Director</li><li>Mr. Walker&apos;s appointment is subject to the approval of the Shareholders through a postal ballot</li><li>Mr. Walker is currently the Oracle Executive Vice President, Industry Applications</li><li>Mr. Walker has extensive experience in financial services technology</li><li>The appointment is in compliance with the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/03e9ada5-6837-483a-bfab-87d2680b25c9.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ORACLE FINANCIAL SERVICES SOFTWARE LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SANOFICONR] Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd Designates New Senior Management Personnel</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sanofi+Consumer+Healthcare+India+Ltd&title=Sanofi+Consumer+Healthcare+India+Ltd+Designates+New+Senior+Management+Personnel&newsId=0cdd8107-256c-4b96-bd02-9ac3fa0c54ce&token=MGNkZDgxMDctMjU2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0cdd8107-256c-4b96-bd02-9ac3fa0c54ce</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:47:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd has designated Ms. Nupur Gurbaxani, Director, Brand &amp; Innovation and Mr. Viral Shah, Director, External Manufacturing as Senior Management Personnel (SMP) of the Company with effect from 25th February, 2026. Ms. Gurbaxani, who joined in July 2024, has driven the brand turnaround with sharp consumer insights, innovative campaigns and a digital-first approach. Mr. Shah, who joined in May 2024, has driven key initiatives on developing the right infrastructure and partnerships for &apos;Make In India&apos; products. The Board of Directors commenced the meeting at 2:00 p.m. and concluded at 5:20 p.m.</p><ul><li>Ms. Nupur Gurbaxani and Mr. Viral Shah designated as Senior Management Personnel of Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd</li><li>Ms. Gurbaxani has driven brand turnaround since joining in July 2024</li><li>Mr. Shah has driven key initiatives on developing infrastructure and partnerships for &apos;Make In India&apos; products since joining in May 2024</li><li>Meeting of Board of Directors commenced at 2:00 p.m. and concluded at 5:20 p.m.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8c797442-aad7-456e-8000-09c7dbfc89cf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ENBETRD] Enbee Trade &amp; Finance Ltd Approves Rights Issue of Equity Shares worth Rs 12,005.00 Lakhs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ENBEE+TRADE+%26+FINANCE+LTD.&title=Enbee+Trade+%26+Finance+Ltd+Approves+Rights+Issue+of+Equity+Shares+worth+Rs+12%2C005.00+Lakhs&newsId=1f67a11a-5f20-46ef-a2dc-76cfc9868f77&token=MWY2N2ExMWEtNWYy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f67a11a-5f20-46ef-a2dc-76cfc9868f77</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Right Issue</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Enbee Trade &amp; Finance Ltd announced that the Board of Directors in their meeting held on February 25, 2026, had approved the issuance of Equity Shares on rights basis for an amount not exceeding Rs 12,005.00 lakhs. The Rights Issue is for an aggregate amount of Rs 12005.00 Lakhs, assuming full subscription. The Rights Issue Price is Re. 1/- per fully paid-up equity share, and the entire Issue Price will be payable at the time of making the application. The Rights Entitlement Ratio is 21 fully paid-up rights equity share for every 10 fully paid-up equity share held by the eligible equity shareholders as on the Record date. The Rights Issue Schedule starts from March 12, 2026, and closes on March 20, 2026.</p><ul><li>Enbee Trade &amp; Finance Ltd approved the issuance of Equity Shares on rights basis for an amount not exceeding Rs 12,005.00 lakhs.</li><li>The Rights Issue is for an aggregate amount of Rs 12005.00 Lakhs, assuming full subscription.</li><li>The Rights Issue Price is Re. 1/- per fully paid-up equity share.</li><li>The Rights Entitlement Ratio is 21 fully paid-up rights equity share for every 10 fully paid-up equity share held by the eligible equity shareholders as on the Record date.</li><li>The Rights Issue Schedule starts from March 12, 2026, and closes on March 20, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/53611bad-9c5f-4b73-bb2c-a48c59e8a294.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ENBEE TRADE & FINANCE LTD. | Category: Right Issue</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SANOFICONR] Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd Designates New Senior Management Personnel</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sanofi+Consumer+Healthcare+India+Ltd&title=Sanofi+Consumer+Healthcare+India+Ltd+Designates+New+Senior+Management+Personnel&newsId=69c05127-7e1b-420b-aa4b-3719c8c94ea2&token=NjljMDUxMjctN2Ux</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69c05127-7e1b-420b-aa4b-3719c8c94ea2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:32:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd has designated Ms. Nupur Gurbaxani, Director, Brand &amp; Innovation and Mr. Viral Shah, Director, External Manufacturing as Senior Management Personnel (SMP) of the Company with effect from 25th February, 2026. Nupur Gurbaxani, with her rich experience of over 18 years in the consumer industry, has been instrumental in driving the brand turnaround since she joined in July 2024. Mr. Viral Shah, with over 20 years of extensive experience in the pharmaceutical industry, has been leading key initiatives on developing the right infrastructure and partnerships for &apos;Make In India&apos; products.</p><ul><li>Ms. Nupur Gurbaxani designated as Senior Management Personnel</li><li>Mr. Viral Shah designated as Senior Management Personnel</li><li>Nupur Gurbaxani has driven brand turnaround since July 2024</li><li>Viral Shah has led key initiatives on &apos;Make In India&apos; products</li><li>Designation effective from 25th February, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f1e140d6-d4de-4002-9a33-1fbefbc85022.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sanofi Consumer Healthcare India Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FOSECOIND] Foseco India Ltd Appoints Joshi Apte &amp; Associates as Cost Auditor for 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=FOSECO+INDIA+LTD.&title=Foseco+India+Ltd+Appoints+Joshi+Apte+%26+Associates+as+Cost+Auditor+for+2026&newsId=0a191d14-e71b-47eb-898b-76ac4fd72f1b&token=MGExOTFkMTQtZTcx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a191d14-e71b-47eb-898b-76ac4fd72f1b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Expansion</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Foseco India Ltd, a brand of the Vesuvius Group, has appointed Joshi Apte &amp; Associates, Cost Accountants, as the Cost Auditor of the Company for a period of one year effective from January 1, 2026 till December 31, 2026. The firm has over 16 years of experience and a large client base across India, catering to clients across 26 industry segments. The Board of Directors approved this appointment at their meeting held on February 25, 2026.</p><ul><li>Foseco India Ltd appoints Joshi Apte &amp; Associates as Cost Auditor for 2026</li><li>The Cost Auditor appointment is effective from January 1, 2026 till December 31, 2026</li><li>Joshi Apte &amp; Associates is a firm of practicing cost accountants with over 16 years of experience</li><li>The firm has a large client base across India and caters to clients across 26 industry segments</li><li>The appointment was approved at the Board of Directors meeting held on February 25, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bf183b49-2059-4597-abb3-c63273c5a061.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: FOSECO INDIA LTD. | Category: Expansion</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INDSOYA] Indsoya Ltd. Deviates Funds Utilization Towards Lease Payments</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDSOYA+LTD.&title=Indsoya+Ltd.+Deviates+Funds+Utilization+Towards+Lease+Payments&newsId=bf744a2c-0cc4-4302-8eec-54adc7d29a02&token=YmY3NDRhMmMtMGNj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf744a2c-0cc4-4302-8eec-54adc7d29a02</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Indsoya Ltd., formerly known as Apollo Ingredients Limited, has reported a deviation in the utilization of funds raised through a Rights Issue. An amount of Rs. 3 crore, which was initially intended for working capital requirements, raw material procurement, and reducing trade payables, was utilized towards lease payments for a factory owned by a related party. This deviation was approved by the shareholders at the 45th AGM held on September 27, 2025.</p><ul><li>Indsoya Ltd. reports deviation in funds utilization</li><li>Rs. 3 crore originally intended for working capital and raw material procurement used for lease payments</li><li>Lease payments made to a related party</li><li>Deviation approved by shareholders at the 45th AGM held on September 27, 2025</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7c8a61c8-7f91-4bd8-bb35-4ba77371cee1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDSOYA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ANZEN] Anzen India Energy Yield Plus Trust Increases Units to 25,57,18,900 Post Capital Restructuring</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Anzen+India+Energy+Yield+Plus+Trust&title=Anzen+India+Energy+Yield+Plus+Trust+Increases+Units+to+25%2C57%2C18%2C900+Post+Capital+Restructuring&newsId=196bc52f-6fec-413f-ace6-8a85616cfee4&token=MTk2YmM1MmYtNmZl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">196bc52f-6fec-413f-ace6-8a85616cfee4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:21:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Anzen India Energy Yield Plus Trust has informed the Exchange about the Unitholding pattern post capital restructuring. The total number of units issued and outstanding has increased from 19,61,93,900 units to 25,57,18,900 units. The updated unitholding pattern includes changes in the holdings of the Sponsor(s)/Investment Manager, Alternate Investment Fund, Trust, Public Holding, and others. The total public unit holding is 15.82% (1,42,60,100 units) and the total units outstanding are 100.00% (25,57,18,900 units).</p><ul><li>Anzen India Energy Yield Plus Trust increases total units to 25,57,18,900 post capital restructuring.</li><li>Sponsor(s)/Investment Manager, Alternate Investment Fund, Trust, and Public Holding see changes in unitholding.</li><li>Total public unit holding is 15.82% (1,42,60,100 units).</li><li>Total units outstanding are 100.00% (25,57,18,900 units).</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8e20e44c-3413-456e-a67a-1b679816c7c5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Anzen India Energy Yield Plus Trust | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RBLBANK] RBI Grants Approval to SBI Mutual Fund to Acquire 9.99% Stake in RBL Bank</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RBL+Bank+Ltd&title=RBI+Grants+Approval+to+SBI+Mutual+Fund+to+Acquire+9.99%25+Stake+in+RBL+Bank&newsId=f0588fb9-c679-4f06-afff-4cfc042a2a5d&token=ZjA1ODhmYjktYzY3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0588fb9-c679-4f06-afff-4cfc042a2a5d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>RBL Bank Limited has informed the exchange about an intimation under Regulation 30 of SEBI Listing Regulations. The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has granted its approval to SBI Mutual Fund to acquire an &apos;aggregate holding&apos; of up to 9.99% of the paid-up share capital or voting rights in RBL Bank Limited. This approval is subject to certain conditions, including compliance with the relevant provisions of the Banking Regulation Act, 1949, Reserve Bank of India (Commercial Banks — Acquisition and Holding of Shares or Voting Rights) Directions, 2025, provisions of the Foreign Exchange Management Act, 1999, regulations issued by Securities and Exchange Board of India, and any other statutes, regulations and guidelines, as applicable. SBI Mutual Fund is required to acquire the shares within a period of one year from the date of the RBI Letter and ensure that the aggregate holding in the Bank does not exceed 9.99% at all times. If the aggregate holding falls below 5%, prior approval of RBI will be required to increase it to 5% or more.</p><ul><li>RBI grants approval to SBI Mutual Fund to acquire up to 9.99% stake in RBL Bank</li><li>Approval subject to compliance with various regulations and statutes</li><li>SBI Mutual Fund required to acquire shares within one year</li><li>Aggregate holding in the Bank not to exceed 9.99% at all times</li><li>Prior RBI approval required if aggregate holding falls below 5% and needs to be increased to 5% or more</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/51f3d451-aded-4046-9990-e3b6accbb260.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RBL Bank Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GRAVITA] Gravita India Ltd Expands Lead Recycling Capacity by 25% at Mundra Plant</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GRAVITA+INDIA+LTD.&title=Gravita+India+Ltd+Expands+Lead+Recycling+Capacity+by+25%25+at+Mundra+Plant&newsId=4f466753-c206-4382-8dd0-d18f122ac4f7&token=NGY0NjY3NTMtYzIw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4f466753-c206-4382-8dd0-d18f122ac4f7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:21:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Expansion</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Gravita India Ltd, a leading player in the recycling sector, has increased the capacity of its existing recycling unit situated at Mundra, Gujarat. The existing capacity of the unit for Lead recycling has been increased by 80,300 MTPA, bringing the total capacity to 1,45,100 MTPA. The company has invested approximately Rs. 49.00 Crores for this expansion from its internal accruals. This capacity enhancement aligns with the company’s long-term strategy to strengthen its recycling capabilities and meet growing domestic and international demand for sustainable lead products.</p><ul><li>Gravita India Ltd has expanded its lead recycling capacity by 25% at its Mundra plant.</li><li>The existing capacity of the Mundra plant for Lead recycling has been increased by 80,300 MTPA.</li><li>The total capacity of the Mundra plant for Lead recycling now stands at 1,45,100 MTPA.</li><li>The company has invested approximately Rs. 49.00 Crores for this expansion from its internal accruals.</li><li>This capacity enhancement aligns with the company’s long-term strategy to strengthen its recycling capabilities and meet growing domestic and international demand for sustainable lead products.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/16cdd736-91da-4997-a8b7-abe8cd84bc19.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GRAVITA INDIA LTD. | Category: Expansion</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>