<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:50:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[IBINFO] Promoter Group of IB Infotech Enterprises Ltd Acquires Shares from Rajkumar Singh</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IB+INFOTECH+ENTERPRISES+LTD.&title=Promoter+Group+of+IB+Infotech+Enterprises+Ltd+Acquires+Shares+from+Rajkumar+Singh&newsId=deec52ec-0cef-4dff-b579-fa8f33ca3a60&token=ZGVlYzUyZWMtMGNl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">deec52ec-0cef-4dff-b579-fa8f33ca3a60</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:49:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>IB Infotech Enterprises Ltd has received a disclosure under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011 from Bavel Singh and others. The acquirers, who are part of the Promoter/Promoter Group, have acquired 190800 equity shares of the Target Company from Mr. Rajkumar Singh through an on-market transaction. This acquisition increases the holding of Bavel Singh, Rita Singh, Shivani Singh, and Shivangi Singh in the company.</p><ul><li>Bavel Singh and others from the Promoter/Promoter Group of IB Infotech Enterprises Ltd have acquired shares from Rajkumar Singh.</li><li>The acquisition was done through an on-market transaction.</li><li>The total shares acquired by the acquirers are 190800.</li><li>The acquisition increases the holding of Bavel Singh, Rita Singh, Shivani Singh, and Shivangi Singh in the company.</li><li>The total holding of the Promoter and Promoter Group remains the same at 65.85%.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5467D7C9_A01C_428E_9DEB_52EA5E6C38ED_101757.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IB INFOTECH ENTERPRISES LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IBINFO] IB Infotech Enterprises Ltd: Rajkumar Singh &amp; Others Disclose Sale of Shares to Promoter Group Members</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=IB+INFOTECH+ENTERPRISES+LTD.&title=IB+Infotech+Enterprises+Ltd%3A+Rajkumar+Singh+%26+Others+Disclose+Sale+of+Shares+to+Promoter+Group+Members&newsId=3dbb795e-b9a3-4b64-91d6-f938d456c212&token=M2RiYjc5NWUtYjlh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3dbb795e-b9a3-4b64-91d6-f938d456c212</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:47:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>IB Infotech Enterprises Ltd&apos;s Rajkumar Singh and other members of the promoter/promoter group have sold a combined 190,800 equity shares to Bavel Singh, Rita Singh, Shivani Singh, and Shivangi Singh through an on-market transaction. This disclosure has been made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</p><ul><li>Rajkumar Singh and other promoter/promoter group members sell 190,800 equity shares to Bavel Singh, Rita Singh, Shivani Singh, and Shivangi Singh.</li><li>Transaction is an on-market transaction through inter-se transfer of equity shares between immediate relatives of the promoter/promoter group.</li><li>Sale results in a change in shareholding and voting rights percentages for the involved parties.</li><li>Disclosure submitted to stock exchanges under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</li><li>No change in aggregate shareholding of promoter and promoter group pursuant to the transaction.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/76EBAF0F_F672_4D23_8DDD_0FB9542A86DA_101552.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: IB INFOTECH ENTERPRISES LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ESCORTS] Kubota Corporation Announces Mid-Term Business Plan 2030</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Escorts+Kubota+Ltd&title=Kubota+Corporation+Announces+Mid-Term+Business+Plan+2030&newsId=817ea3db-368c-4ae8-b8ed-a79f31fb1fff&token=ODE3ZWEzZGItMzY4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">817ea3db-368c-4ae8-b8ed-a79f31fb1fff</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:44:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Kubota Corporation, the holding company of Escorts Kubota Ltd, has issued its Mid-Term Business Plan 2030. The plan, which covers the period from the FY2026 to FY2030, can be accessed at a specified link. This announcement was made today in Japan.</p><ul><li>Kubota Corporation has released its Mid-Term Business Plan 2030.</li><li>The plan covers the period from the FY2026 to FY2030.</li><li>The announcement was made today in Japan.</li><li>The business plan can be accessed via a provided link.</li><li>Escorts Kubota Ltd is a subsidiary of Kubota Corporation.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/87647824-dbb2-4e37-aff4-a2219f7ad7ba.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Escorts Kubota Ltd | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZFSTEERING] ZF Steering Gear India&apos;s Subsidiary Identified as Material Subsidiary from 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Z.F.STEERING+GEAR+%28INDIA%29+LTD.-%24&title=ZF+Steering+Gear+India%27s+Subsidiary+Identified+as+Material+Subsidiary+from+2026&newsId=e62335e0-0d01-4082-af64-180e4d091738&token=ZTYyMzM1ZTAtMGQw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e62335e0-0d01-4082-af64-180e4d091738</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:43:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Pursuant to Regulation 16(1)(c) of the Listing Regulations, Metacast Auto Private Limited, a subsidiary of ZF Steering Gear (India) Limited, has been identified as a Material Subsidiary of the Company with effect from February 12, 2026. This identification is based on the criterion that the turnover of Metacast has exceeded 10% of the consolidated turnover of ZF India. Both companies will ensure that the necessary disclosures, governance norms, and compliance requirements for Material Subsidiary are adhered to.</p><ul><li>Metacast Auto Private Limited identified as Material Subsidiary of ZF Steering Gear (India) Limited</li><li>Identification effective from February 12, 2026</li><li>Identification based on Metacast&apos;s turnover exceeding 10% of ZF India&apos;s consolidated turnover</li><li>Both companies to adhere to disclosure, governance norms, and compliance requirements for Material Subsidiary</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f76102d2-b3be-4999-8dfa-e507c74ecc04.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Z.F.STEERING GEAR (INDIA) LTD.-$ | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VRLLOG] Bandhan Mutual Fund Disposes Over 2% Shares of VRL Logistics Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VRL+Logistics+Ltd&title=Bandhan+Mutual+Fund+Disposes+Over+2%25+Shares+of+VRL+Logistics+Limited&newsId=55d63d70-a6f8-45ea-bcdb-7350e97f2971&token=NTVkNjNkNzAtYTZm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55d63d70-a6f8-45ea-bcdb-7350e97f2971</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:43:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Sale</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Bandhan Mutual Fund has disposed 2,43,667 equity shares of VRL Logistics Limited on February 10, 2026, leading to a decrease in their holding from 5.0032% to 2.9635%. This disposal has been made through Bandhan Mutual Fund&apos;s schemes and has been reported under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeover) Regulations, 2011.</p><ul><li>Bandhan Mutual Fund disposes 2,43,667 equity shares of VRL Logistics Limited.</li><li>This disposal results in a decrease of Bandhan Mutual Fund&apos;s holding from 5.0032% to 2.9635%.</li><li>The disposal has been made through Bandhan Mutual Fund&apos;s schemes.</li><li>The disclosure has been made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeover) Regulations, 2011.</li><li>VRL Logistics Limited is listed on BSE Limited and National Stock Exchange of India Limited.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3933CE8E_2804_4268_81D7_B126111C83B2_100244.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VRL Logistics Ltd | Category: Sale</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NETWEB] Promoters of Netweb Technologies India Ltd, Sanjay Lodha &amp; Others, Sell Equity Shares</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Netweb+Technologies+India+Ltd&title=Promoters+of+Netweb+Technologies+India+Ltd%2C+Sanjay+Lodha+%26+Others%2C+Sell+Equity+Shares&newsId=d8a0182c-932d-416e-a7ce-b9a13a247a6d&token=ZDhhMDE4MmMtOTMy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d8a0182c-932d-416e-a7ce-b9a13a247a6d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Sale</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sanjay Lodha, Navin Lodha, Niraj Lodha, and Vivek Lodha, promoters of Netweb Technologies India Ltd, have sold equity shares of the company on February 12, 2026. The total shares sold by the promoters are 20,79,935, which is 1.58% of the total paid-up capital of the company. This disclosure was made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</p><ul><li>Sanjay Lodha, Navin Lodha, Niraj Lodha, and Vivek Lodha sold equity shares of Netweb Technologies India Ltd.</li><li>The total shares sold by the promoters are 20,79,935, which is 1.58% of the total paid-up capital of the company.</li><li>This disclosure was made under Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares &amp; Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7AF59042_0555_4DCD_8ED9_76165465EE7C_100450.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Netweb Technologies India Ltd | Category: Sale</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EVANS] Counter Cyclical Investment Pvt Ltd Acquires 22,000 Shares in Evans Electric Ltd via Open Market</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Evans+Electric+Ltd&title=Counter+Cyclical+Investment+Pvt+Ltd+Acquires+22%2C000+Shares+in+Evans+Electric+Ltd+via+Open+Market&newsId=41f941b4-c9b8-4f22-9ab0-394c4c95c349&token=NDFmOTQxYjQtYzli</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41f941b4-c9b8-4f22-9ab0-394c4c95c349</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:38:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Counter Cyclical Investments Private Limited (Portfolio Manager - Acquirer), through its clients, has acquired 22,000 shares in Evans Electric Limited (Target Company) on 11th February 2026. This acquisition is in accordance with Regulation 29(2) of the SEBI SAST Regulations, 2011. Before the acquisition, Counter Cyclical Investments Private Limited held 5.34% shares of Evans Electric Ltd, which increased to 5.74% post-acquisition.</p><ul><li>Counter Cyclical Investments Private Limited acquired 22,000 shares in Evans Electric Ltd on 11th February 2026.</li><li>The acquisition was carried out via the open market.</li><li>Before the acquisition, Counter Cyclical Investments Private Limited held 5.34% shares of Evans Electric Ltd.</li><li>Post-acquisition, Counter Cyclical Investments Private Limited holds 5.74% shares of Evans Electric Ltd.</li><li>The acquisition is in accordance with Regulation 29(2) of the SEBI SAST Regulations, 2011.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/678CEF66_4507_4212_9578_38AE7B79428F_100610.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Evans Electric Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HAPPYFORGE] India Business Excellence Fund III Disposes of 39,10,097 Equity Shares of Happy Forgings Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Happy+Forgings+Ltd&title=India+Business+Excellence+Fund+III+Disposes+of+39%2C10%2C097+Equity+Shares+of+Happy+Forgings+Ltd&newsId=8fe09415-5367-4090-a5d9-bf82d40380d9&token=OGZlMDk0MTUtNTM2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8fe09415-5367-4090-a5d9-bf82d40380d9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:35:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Sale</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>India Business Excellence Fund III, scheme of Business Excellence Trust III, has disclosed the sale of an aggregate 39,10,097 equity shares of Happy Forgings Limited. The disposals were undertaken between June 17, 2025 and February 12, 2026, with the disposal on February 12, 2026 breaching the 2% threshold specified in Regulation 29(2) of the SEBI Takeover Regulations. The total diluted share/voting capital of the company remains unaffected.</p><ul><li>India Business Excellence Fund III disposes of 39,10,097 equity shares of Happy Forgings Limited</li><li>Disposals undertaken between June 17, 2025 and February 12, 2026</li><li>Disposal on February 12, 2026 breached the 2% threshold</li><li>Total diluted share/voting capital of the company remains unaffected</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/E734C4B1_12C4_4547_A98F_8F1E3AE9F33B_100059.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Happy Forgings Ltd | Category: Sale</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EASEMYTRIP] Easy Trip Planners Ltd. to Acquire AB Finance Private Ltd., Issuing Over 5% of Post-Issue Share Capital</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Easy+Trip+Planners+Ltd&title=Easy+Trip+Planners+Ltd.+to+Acquire+AB+Finance+Private+Ltd.%2C+Issuing+Over+5%25+of+Post-Issue+Share+Capital&newsId=f4682dd8-7336-403d-8b84-755bbdd812b7&token=ZjQ2ODJkZDgtNzMz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4682dd8-7336-403d-8b84-755bbdd812b7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Easy Trip Planners Ltd. is making a public announcement regarding the acquisition of AB Finance Private Ltd. The acquisition will result in the company issuing and allotting more than 5% of its post-issue share capital, requiring compliance with Regulation 166A of the SEBI (Issue of Capital and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations 2018. The company obtained a valuation report dated October 24, 2025, from an independent registered valuer, Samarth Valuation Advisory LLP, and determined the issue price of INR 9.19 for each equity share, including a premium of INR 8.19. This announcement should be read in addition to the Corrigendum dated November 21, 2025, and the Postal Ballot Notice dated November 4, 2025.</p><ul><li>Easy Trip Planners Ltd. to acquire AB Finance Private Ltd.</li><li>The acquisition will result in the issuance and allotment of over 5% of the company&apos;s post-issue share capital.</li><li>Compliance with Regulation 166A of the SEBI (Issue of Capital and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations 2018.</li><li>Valuation report obtained from an independent registered valuer, Samarth Valuation Advisory LLP.</li><li>Issue price of INR 9.19 for each equity share, including a premium of INR 8.19.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/03303536-9b22-482a-a6d5-c0e19911269c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Easy Trip Planners Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CHEMKART] Promoter Shailesh Vinodrai Mehta Acquires 52,200 Shares of Chemkart India Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Chemkart+India+Ltd&title=Promoter+Shailesh+Vinodrai+Mehta+Acquires+52%2C200+Shares+of+Chemkart+India+Ltd&newsId=0da8b8d3-17b6-458e-b6ae-fcfcb52ac45d&token=MGRhOGI4ZDMtMTdi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0da8b8d3-17b6-458e-b6ae-fcfcb52ac45d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 04:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shailesh Vinodrai Mehta, a promoter of Chemkart India Ltd, has acquired 52,200 equity shares of the company. The acquisition was made through open market on BSE Limited dated 11 February, 2026. The total equity share capital of the company is INR 12,09,90,000 comprising of 1,20,99,000 Equity Shares of Rs. 10/- Each.</p><ul><li>Shailesh Vinodrai Mehta, a promoter of Chemkart India Ltd, has acquired 52,200 equity shares of the company.</li><li>The acquisition was made through open market on BSE Limited dated 11 February, 2026.</li><li>The total equity share capital of the company is INR 12,09,90,000 comprising of 1,20,99,000 Equity Shares of Rs. 10/- Each.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8A670B7D_82FD_4E03_930D_3F31529EDA7D_095830.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Chemkart India Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>