<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:48:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SIMBHALS] Simbhaoli Sugars Ltd. Reports Q3 2025 Financial Results Under Insolvency Proceedings</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Simbhaoli+Sugars+Ltd&title=Simbhaoli+Sugars+Ltd.+Reports+Q3+2025+Financial+Results+Under+Insolvency+Proceedings&newsId=24774615-45d9-4d88-b7a2-8e155912b616&token=MjQ3NzQ2MTUtNDVk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24774615-45d9-4d88-b7a2-8e155912b616</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:48:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Simbhaoli Sugars Limited has released its unaudited financial statements for the quarter ended 31st December, 2025, under the supervision of the Interim Resolution Professional (IRP). The NCLT admitted an insolvency petition against the company in July 2024, and the IRP, Mr. Anurag Goel, took control of the management and operations. The IRP has taken on record the reviewed standalone financial results, which include interest expenses on borrowings from banks, interest payable on unsecured loans from related parties, and interest payable on delayed payment of sugarcane price to farmers, among other items. The IRP has also discharged the majority of outstanding cane dues, except for those of the Chilwaria unit. The company has not recognized claims in respect of penalties and disputed charges made by its subsidiary, Simbhaoli Power Private Limited.</p><ul><li>Q3 2025 financial results reported under insolvency proceedings</li><li>Interim Resolution Professional (IRP) took control of management and operations in July 2024</li><li>Reviewed standalone financial results include interest expenses on borrowings from banks, interest payable on unsecured loans from related parties, and interest payable on delayed payment of sugarcane price to farmers</li><li>IRP discharged the majority of outstanding cane dues, except for those of the Chilwaria unit</li><li>Company has not recognized claims in respect of penalties and disputed charges made by its subsidiary, Simbhaoli Power Private Limited</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1463dc29-bd40-42ad-a84f-6accdf32cb8d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Simbhaoli Sugars Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MISHTANN] Mishtann Foods Ltd Announces Q3 and Year-to-Date Unaudited Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Mishtann+Foods+Ltd&title=Mishtann+Foods+Ltd+Announces+Q3+and+Year-to-Date+Unaudited+Results+for+2025&newsId=2918f43e-a91e-4682-9381-fc1a393c0684&token=MjkxOGY0M2UtYTkx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2918f43e-a91e-4682-9381-fc1a393c0684</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Mishtann Foods Ltd has announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s Board of Directors approved these results in a meeting held on February 13, 2026. The results will be available on the company&apos;s website. The company&apos;s auditor, H Thakkar &amp; Co. LLP, has issued a limited review report with a qualified opinion due to certain unresolved matters.</p><ul><li>Unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 and year-to-date 2025 approved by the Board of Directors.</li><li>Results to be uploaded on the company&apos;s website.</li><li>Limited review report issued by the auditor with a qualified opinion.</li><li>Company is dealing with certain unresolved matters as per the auditor&apos;s report.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ea00689d-cbec-4a05-b78e-a09be3a185c1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Mishtann Foods Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KENVI] Kenvi Jewels Ltd Declares Unaudited Q3 Results for FY2025-26 with 8.75% YoY Profit Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kenvi+Jewels+Ltd&title=Kenvi+Jewels+Ltd+Declares+Unaudited+Q3+Results+for+FY2025-26+with+8.75%25+YoY+Profit+Growth&newsId=5ed09f26-6c96-4361-bcb5-fa7a28798e4d&token=NWVkMDlmMjYtNmM5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ed09f26-6c96-4361-bcb5-fa7a28798e4d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:46:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Kenvi Jewels Ltd, a leading player in the jewelry industry, announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stood at 5285.36 lakhs, marking a 15.18% QoQ growth and 15.59% YoY growth. The total income for the quarter was 5285.30 lakhs, with a profit before exceptional items and tax of 61.46 lakhs, reflecting an 8.75% YoY growth. The company&apos;s expenses for the quarter amounted to 5223.84 lakhs, with cost of materials consumed being the major contributor. The board has also approved the unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025.</p><ul><li>Unaudited financial results for Q3 FY2025-26 approved by the board</li><li>Revenue from operations stood at 5285.36 lakhs, marking a 15.18% QoQ growth and 15.59% YoY growth</li><li>Profit before exceptional items and tax stood at 61.46 lakhs, reflecting an 8.75% YoY growth</li><li>Total expenses for the quarter amounted to 5223.84 lakhs</li><li>Unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025 also approved</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2e51708a-41ca-42b0-9af7-9a418bb7f3b5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kenvi Jewels Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GARODCH] Garodia Chemicals Ltd. Announces Q3 Results for FY2025-26, Profit Before Tax Down by 8.51 Lakhs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GARODIA+CHEMICALS+LTD.&title=Garodia+Chemicals+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+Results+for+FY2025-26%2C+Profit+Before+Tax+Down+by+8.51+Lakhs&newsId=17344bfe-c6c0-4114-8743-07052b420929&token=MTczNDRiZmUtYzZj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17344bfe-c6c0-4114-8743-07052b420929</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:46:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Garodia Chemicals Ltd. has announced its un-audited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s profit before tax has decreased by 8.51 lakhs compared to the previous quarter. The financial results have been reviewed by the audit committee and approved by the Board of Directors. The company&apos;s books are not prepared as per the Going Concern assumption due to ceasing of business. The other income recognized during the period pertains to the settlement of loans provided by the company&apos;s promoters and associates.</p><ul><li>Profit before tax down by 8.51 lakhs compared to the previous quarter</li><li>Books not prepared as per Going Concern assumption due to ceasing of business</li><li>Other income recognized during the period pertains to the settlement of loans provided by the company&apos;s promoters and associates</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5b1ea3bd-44ad-45db-b80b-1c6474f16b3c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GARODIA CHEMICALS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JAUSPOL] Jauss Polymers Ltd Announces Q3 Results for FY 2025-26, Reports Profit Before Tax of ₹ 457.20 Lakhs</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JAUSS+POLYMERS+LTD.&title=Jauss+Polymers+Ltd+Announces+Q3+Results+for+FY+2025-26%2C+Reports+Profit+Before+Tax+of+%E2%82%B9+457.20+Lakhs&newsId=59f31b12-b4c6-4b5c-bedd-6b57fa33d2ba&token=NTlmMzFiMTItYjRj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59f31b12-b4c6-4b5c-bedd-6b57fa33d2ba</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jauss Polymers Ltd, a company mainly engaged in the manufacturing of plastic bottles, jars, and caps, has announced its unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter ended on 31st December 2025. The company reported a profit before tax of ₹ 457.20 lakhs, a decrease from the previous quarter&apos;s profit before tax of ₹ 423.02 lakhs. The total revenue for the quarter was ₹ 39.44 lakhs. The company&apos;s earnings per share (EPS) for continuing operations were ₹ 1.03 for the quarter. The company&apos;s financial statements have been prepared on a going concern basis, but there are significant events or conditions that cast material uncertainty on the company&apos;s ability to continue as a going concern. The company has not performed an assessment of its ability to continue as a going concern, and it has sold its investment in Innovative Containers Pvt Ltd, indicating its inability to continue as a going concern.</p><ul><li>Profit before tax of ₹ 457.20 lakhs for Q3 FY 2025-26</li><li>Total revenue of ₹ 39.44 lakhs for Q3 FY 2025-26</li><li>EPS for continuing operations of ₹ 1.03 for Q3 FY 2025-26</li><li>Significant events or conditions casting material uncertainty on the company&apos;s ability to continue as a going concern</li><li>Sale of investment in Innovative Containers Pvt Ltd, indicating the company&apos;s inability to continue as a going concern</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/da3e42bf-080c-4fe8-92af-a513241b6486.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JAUSS POLYMERS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RADAAN] Radaan Mediaworks India Ltd Approves Q3 Results for 2025, Announces Resignation of Company Secretary</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RADAAN+MEDIAWORKS+%28I%29+LTD.&title=Radaan+Mediaworks+India+Ltd+Approves+Q3+Results+for+2025%2C+Announces+Resignation+of+Company+Secretary&newsId=2ee6d3d9-2a9d-4c9c-9d6b-c9b0c4538655&token=MmVlNmQzZDktMmE5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ee6d3d9-2a9d-4c9c-9d6b-c9b0c4538655</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:46:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Radaan Mediaworks India Ltd has approved the Q3 results for the year ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025 have been approved by the Board of Directors. However, the company&apos;s net worth has fully eroded and its current liabilities have exceeded its current assets, indicating a material uncertainty that may cast significant doubt on the company&apos;s ability to continue as a going concern. The Board also took note of the resignation of Mr. Balaji Gandla as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer, due to personal reasons, with effect from 14.02.2026.</p><ul><li>Radaan Mediaworks India Ltd has approved the Q3 results for the year ended 31st December 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s net worth has fully eroded and its current liabilities have exceeded its current assets.</li><li>There is a material uncertainty that may cast significant doubt on the company&apos;s ability to continue as a going concern.</li><li>Mr. Balaji Gandla has resigned as Company Secretary and Compliance Officer, with effect from 14.02.2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bb027539-db92-4cf0-aaa7-420c5af41fb6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RADAAN MEDIAWORKS (I) LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PPAP] PPAP Automotive Sells 50% Stake in PPAP Tokai India Rubber to Tokai Kogyo for INR 100 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PPAP+Automotive+Limited&title=PPAP+Automotive+Sells+50%25+Stake+in+PPAP+Tokai+India+Rubber+to+Tokai+Kogyo+for+INR+100+Crores&newsId=f4b773d5-861f-4455-a83d-abe4af780d8e&token=ZjRiNzczZDUtODYx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4b773d5-861f-4455-a83d-abe4af780d8e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:45:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>PPAP Automotive Ltd, a leading manufacturer of Automotive Sealing Systems, Interior &amp; Exterior Automotive parts, has sold its entire 50% stake in PPAP Tokai India Rubber Private Limited to Tokai Kogyo Co. Ltd. for a cash consideration of INR 100 crores. The sale was concluded on 13th February 2026, pursuant to a Settlement Agreement effective from 1st January 2026. The proceeds from the divestment will be used to reduce net debt and fund planned strategic capital expenditure. The joint venture, established in 2012, was not fruitful and the divestment is expected to benefit the company by enabling it to reduce debt and make new investments for higher and sustainable growth.</p><ul><li>PPAP Automotive sold its 50% stake in PPAP Tokai India Rubber to Tokai Kogyo for INR 100 Crores</li><li>The sale was concluded on 13th February 2026</li><li>The proceeds from the divestment will be used to reduce net debt and fund planned strategic capital expenditure</li><li>The joint venture was established in 2012 and did not prove to be fruitful</li><li>The divestment is expected to benefit the company by enabling it to reduce debt and make new investments for higher and sustainable growth</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/94e3ab20-c448-4470-a443-2a1caf31c86d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PPAP Automotive Limited | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ENTERO] Entero Healthcare Solutions Ltd Reports Q3 and YTD Unaudited Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Entero+Healthcare+Solutions+Ltd&title=Entero+Healthcare+Solutions+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+YTD+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=a39980ac-7d3d-4834-86f7-bcc127b340fa&token=YTM5OTgwYWMtN2Qz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a39980ac-7d3d-4834-86f7-bcc127b340fa</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:45:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Entero Healthcare Solutions Ltd, formerly known as Entoro Healthcare Solutions Private Limited, released its unaudited standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The Statutory Auditors have generated the UDIN for the Consolidated Financial Results. Key figures include a revenue from operations of INR 2,285.36 million and a profit before tax of INR (4). The company&apos;s earnings per share (face value of Rs. 10 each) stands at INR 4.40 (*not annualised for the quarters and nine months).</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations: INR 2,285.36 million</li><li>Profit before tax: INR (4) million</li><li>Earnings per share: INR 4.40</li><li>UDIN generated for Consolidated Financial Results</li><li>Statutory Auditors have audited the results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4285eca3-a388-431f-843d-c58c467e6776.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Entero Healthcare Solutions Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GOYALASS] Goyal Associates Ltd: Appointment of New Independent Director and Resignation of Woman Independent Director</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GOYAL+ASSOCIATES+LTD.&title=Goyal+Associates+Ltd%3A+Appointment+of+New+Independent+Director+and+Resignation+of+Woman+Independent+Director&newsId=f0c53f87-bfa5-4ac4-85da-d3ac6a91490e&token=ZjBjNTNmODctYmZh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0c53f87-bfa5-4ac4-85da-d3ac6a91490e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:45:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Goyal Associates Ltd announced the appointment of Mr. Gajjala Kranthikumar Reddy as an Additional Independent Director and the resignation of Mrs. Pragna Makwana from her position as Woman Independent Director. The appointment of Mr. Reddy is subject to approval in the ensuing general meeting, and he is not related to any Director of the Company. Mrs. Makwana tendered her resignation due to medical reasons, expressing gratitude for the support received during her tenure.</p><ul><li>Appointment of Mr. Gajjala Kranthikumar Reddy as Additional Independent Director</li><li>Resignation of Mrs. Pragna Makwana due to medical reasons</li><li>Mr. Reddy&apos;s appointment is subject to approval in the ensuing general meeting</li><li>Mr. Reddy is not related to any Director of the Company</li><li>Mrs. Makwana expressed gratitude for the support received during her tenure</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/021811ef-d0a7-408c-985f-bd16369da3fa.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GOYAL ASSOCIATES LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CRISIL] Crisil Limited Announces Record Date for Final Dividend Payment in 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CRISIL+LTD.&title=Crisil+Limited+Announces+Record+Date+for+Final+Dividend+Payment+in+2026&newsId=1af629fc-ffc0-4511-9c4e-bd9f102a8290&token=MWFmNjI5ZmMtZmZj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1af629fc-ffc0-4511-9c4e-bd9f102a8290</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 12:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Crisil Limited has disclosed the record date for the payment of final dividend for the financial year 2025. The record date is April 3, 2026, and the dividend, if approved by shareholders at the Annual General Meeting scheduled for April 17, 2026, will be paid on April 23, 2026. This information should be noted by all members.</p><ul><li>Crisil Limited has announced the record date for final dividend payment for financial year 2025.</li><li>The record date is set for April 3, 2026.</li><li>The dividend payment, if approved, will be made on April 23, 2026.</li><li>The announcement was made in anticipation of the Annual General Meeting scheduled for April 17, 2026.</li><li>Members are advised to take note of this communication.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4105c276-e51f-431f-ab7c-fa30b59bb05f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CRISIL LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>