<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:50:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[TAKE] Take Solutions Ltd Appoints M/s. Venkat and Rangaa LLP as New Statutory Auditors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TAKE+SOLUTIONS+LTD.&title=Take+Solutions+Ltd+Appoints+M%2Fs.+Venkat+and+Rangaa+LLP+as+New+Statutory+Auditors&newsId=08eb9b88-8da6-4a02-9f07-511ab5900542&token=MDhlYjliODgtOGRh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08eb9b88-8da6-4a02-9f07-511ab5900542</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:50:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Take Solutions Ltd has appointed M/s. Venkat and Rangaa LLP, Chartered Accountants, as the new Statutory Auditors of the company. This appointment is to fill the casual vacancy caused by the resignation of M/s. Sundar Srini &amp; Sridhar, Chartered Accountants. The appointment is subject to the approval of the shareholders. M/s. Venkat and Rangaa LLP, established in 1984, is a multi-faceted professional services firm providing audit, assurance, taxation, and advisory services. The firm has extensive experience in serving public sector undertakings, banks, and public and private companies across diverse sectors.</p><ul><li>Take Solutions Ltd appoints M/s. Venkat and Rangaa LLP as new Statutory Auditors</li><li>Appointment is to fill the casual vacancy caused by the resignation of M/s. Sundar Srini &amp; Sridhar, Chartered Accountants</li><li>M/s. Venkat and Rangaa LLP established in 1984</li><li>The firm has extensive experience in serving diverse sectors</li><li>Appointment is subject to shareholders&apos; approval</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/576792a1-bc71-42e2-89c2-499cd5aba2e7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TAKE SOLUTIONS LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VRAJ] Vraj Iron And Steel Ltd Announces Trading Window Closure Until February 14, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vraj+Iron+And+Steel+Ltd&title=Vraj+Iron+And+Steel+Ltd+Announces+Trading+Window+Closure+Until+February+14%2C+2026&newsId=f5673fee-ab8e-40ce-96b0-9ae2fb1f49d8&token=ZjU2NzNmZWUtYWI4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f5673fee-ab8e-40ce-96b0-9ae2fb1f49d8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:47:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Vraj Iron And Steel Ltd has announced the closure of its trading window for dealing in the securities of the company. The closure will be in effect from January 01, 2026 to 48 hours after the declaration of Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The decision is applicable to Directors/KMP and other designated employees covered under the Code. The closure is due to the scheduled meeting of the Board of Directors on February 12, 2026, to consider the Un-Audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results of the Company for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The trading window will reopen 48 hours after the declaration of the Financial Results, which is expected to be on February 14, 2026.</p><ul><li>Trading window closure from January 01, 2026 to February 14, 2026</li><li>Closure due to consideration of Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q4 2025</li><li>Applicable to Directors/KMP and other designated employees covered under the Code</li><li>Board meeting scheduled on February 12, 2026</li><li>Trading window to reopen 48 hours after the declaration of Financial Results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/dedc2955-ae90-4826-86ac-57853d22675b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vraj Iron And Steel Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[INLANPR] Inland Printers Ltd to Approve Un-audited Financial Results on 12th February 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INLAND+PRINTERS+LTD.&title=Inland+Printers+Ltd+to+Approve+Un-audited+Financial+Results+on+12th+February+2026&newsId=71946745-12a6-4789-8faf-c2ff1de62e44&token=NzE5NDY3NDUtMTJh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71946745-12a6-4789-8faf-c2ff1de62e44</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:44:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Inland Printers Ltd has announced a Board of Directors meeting on 12th February 2026 to consider and approve the un-audited financial results for the quarter and half year ended on 31st December 2025. The trading window for dealing in securities of the Company is closed for the Directors and other employees covered under the code from 1st January 2026 until 48 hours from the announcement of financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025.</p><ul><li>Inland Printers Ltd scheduled a Board of Directors meeting on 12th February 2026</li><li>The meeting aims to consider and approve un-audited financial results for the quarter and half year ended on 31st December 2025</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities of the Company is closed for the Directors and other employees covered under the code from 1st January 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/733a0abf-50e9-4bb6-8f7d-810c846d046e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INLAND PRINTERS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VIKRAN] Vikran Engineering Ltd Executes Loan Agreement of INR 49.15 Crores with Onix Renewable Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Vikran+Engineering+Ltd&title=Vikran+Engineering+Ltd+Executes+Loan+Agreement+of+INR+49.15+Crores+with+Onix+Renewable+Limited&newsId=48ab620d-b925-46c3-9fc7-51aa85aa878f&token=NDhhYjYyMGQtYjky</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48ab620d-b925-46c3-9fc7-51aa85aa878f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Loan Agreement</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Vikran Engineering Limited has executed a Loan Agreement with Onix Renewable Limited for an amount of INR 49.15 Crores. The loan is a demand loan with an interest rate of 15% per annum. The loan agreement was executed on 31st January 2026, but the disclosure to the Stock Exchanges was delayed due to an administrative lapse. The Company has taken steps to strengthen internal processes to ensure timely compliance with Regulation 30 going forward.</p><ul><li>Vikran Engineering Limited enters into a Loan Agreement with Onix Renewable Limited</li><li>Loan amount is INR 49.15 Crores</li><li>Interest Rate is 15% per annum</li><li>Loan is a demand loan</li><li>Company has strengthened internal processes for timely compliance</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9dd81417-f371-4d31-a425-00df722acc55.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Vikran Engineering Ltd | Category: Loan Agreement</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SITAENT] Sita Enterprises Ltd. Announces Q3 FY2025-26 Financial Results with Net Profit of ₹ 217.74 Crores</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SITA+ENTERPRISES+LTD.&title=Sita+Enterprises+Ltd.+Announces+Q3+FY2025-26+Financial+Results+with+Net+Profit+of+%E2%82%B9+217.74+Crores&newsId=ec40039a-f79e-4fed-8cd6-60753d6a6ccd&token=ZWM0MDAzOWEtZjc5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ec40039a-f79e-4fed-8cd6-60753d6a6ccd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:44:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sita Enterprises Ltd. has announced its standalone unaudited financial results for the quarter and period ended 31st December, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at ₹ 263.13 Crores, with a net profit of ₹ 217.74 Crores. The Statutory Auditors, M/s. Patel Shah &amp; Joshi, have issued a Limited Review Report with an unmodified opinion on the financial results. The company is primarily engaged in investment and financing activities.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter ended 31st December, 2025 is ₹ 263.13 Crores.</li><li>Net profit for the quarter is ₹ 217.74 Crores.</li><li>The Statutory Auditors, M/s. Patel Shah &amp; Joshi, have issued a Limited Review Report with an unmodified opinion on the financial results.</li><li>Sita Enterprises Ltd. is primarily engaged in investment and financing activities.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/9430397f-4eb1-4378-b48b-94d010d40aa0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SITA ENTERPRISES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HKG] UR Sugar Industries Ltd to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q4 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HKG+Ltd&title=UR+Sugar+Industries+Ltd+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q4+2025&newsId=00c8b06a-d2c1-4500-bc11-68e7741d82e6&token=MDBjOGIwNmEtZDJj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00c8b06a-d2c1-4500-bc11-68e7741d82e6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:44:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>UR Sugar Industries Ltd has announced a Board of Directors meeting on February 11, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited quarterly results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The meeting will take place at the company&apos;s registered office in Belgaum, Karnataka, India.</p><ul><li>UR Sugar Industries Ltd has scheduled a Board of Directors meeting on February 11, 2026.</li><li>The meeting will be held at the company&apos;s registered office in Belgaum, Karnataka, India.</li><li>The Board will consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025.</li><li>The decision is in accordance with Regulation 29 of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f49f08f5-53b3-4986-906c-098e3f553d3c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HKG Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RBA] Restaurant Brands Asia Ltd Amends Articles of Association, Approves Revisions to Special Rights for Shareholders</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Restaurant+Brands+Asia+Ltd&title=Restaurant+Brands+Asia+Ltd+Amends+Articles+of+Association%2C+Approves+Revisions+to+Special+Rights+for+Shareholders&newsId=4e60a714-f099-4037-8415-865324938d50&token=NGU2MGE3MTQtZjA5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4e60a714-f099-4037-8415-865324938d50</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:43:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Restaurant Brands Asia Ltd, formerly known as Burger King India Limited, amended its Articles of Association and approved revisions to special rights for identified shareholders. The amendments and revisions will be effective upon closing in accordance with the share purchase agreement dated January 20, 2026. The company also reported its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</p><ul><li>Amendment to Articles of Association of the Company</li><li>Revisions to special rights for identified shareholders</li><li>Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Share purchase agreement dated January 20, 2026</li><li>Classification of acquirers as &apos;promoters&apos; of the Company</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/31b0d7d5-6bba-4a12-8bd1-6615f19089a2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Restaurant Brands Asia Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NARBADA] Narbada Gems &amp; Jewellery Limited Reports Q3 FY2025-26 Financial Results with 25% Increase in Revenue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NARBADA+GEMS+AND+JEWELLERY+LTD.&title=Narbada+Gems+%26+Jewellery+Limited+Reports+Q3+FY2025-26+Financial+Results+with+25%25+Increase+in+Revenue&newsId=13cf5fd5-f81f-4079-891f-2015b602991f&token=MTNjZjVmZDUtZjgx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13cf5fd5-f81f-4079-891f-2015b602991f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:42:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Narbada Gems &amp; Jewellery Limited announced its Standalone Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at ₹ 32,237.02 lakhs, a 25% increase compared to the previous quarter. Total income stands at ₹ 2,255.34 lakhs, a slight decrease from ₹ 2,633.61 lakhs in the previous quarter. Profit Before Tax (PBT) is ₹ 3,250.02 lakhs, and Net Profit After Tax (PAT) is ₹ 183.17 lakhs. Earnings Per Share (EPS) for this quarter is ₹ 0.87. The company has also announced a merger update, having received an order from the NCLT for the Scheme of Merger with Uday Jewellery Industries Limited.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations increased by 25% compared to the previous quarter</li><li>Total income decreased slightly compared to the previous quarter</li><li>Profit Before Tax (PBT) is ₹ 3,250.02 lakhs</li><li>Net Profit After Tax (PAT) is ₹ 183.17 lakhs</li><li>The company has announced a merger update</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fd796d9f-a907-4f0f-864a-c6f3ef3d32e8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NARBADA GEMS AND JEWELLERY LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SRAMSET] Shriram Asset Management Company Ltd Grants 7500 Stock Options Under Employees Stock Option Plan, 2022</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHRIRAM+ASSET+MANAGEMENT+CO.LTD.&title=Shriram+Asset+Management+Company+Ltd+Grants+7500+Stock+Options+Under+Employees+Stock+Option+Plan%2C+2022&newsId=f5dc6c62-7729-4243-b971-17900971872b&token=ZjVkYzZjNjItNzcy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f5dc6c62-7729-4243-b971-17900971872b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>ESOP</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shriram Asset Management Company Ltd has approved the grant of 7500 stock options under the Shriram Asset Management Company Limited Employees Stock Option Plan, 2022. The options, each of which is convertible into 1 Equity Share of face value of Rs. 10/- each, will be vested across 3 years from the Date of Grant in 30:30:40 ratio. The exercise price is Rs. 108.95/- per share per option. The options have a validity of 10 years from the date of vesting.</p><ul><li>7500 stock options granted to eligible employees</li><li>Each option upon exercise would be entitled for allotment of one equity share of Rs. 10/- each of the Company</li><li>Options vested across 3 years from the Date of Grant in 30:30:40 ratio</li><li>Exercise Price - Rs. 108.95/- per share per option upon exercise of stock option</li><li>Options have a validity of 10 years from the date of vesting</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a3b500d5-1a66-46b1-9ce5-4502029410f1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHRIRAM ASSET MANAGEMENT CO.LTD. | Category: ESOP</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SRECR] Sreechem Resins Ltd. Clarifies Error in Board Meeting Date for Q3 and Nine Months Results Ended December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SREECHEM+RESINS+LTD.&title=Sreechem+Resins+Ltd.+Clarifies+Error+in+Board+Meeting+Date+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+Ended+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=d6582083-da8f-4cbb-9f6d-6bc5c046fbb1&token=ZDY1ODIwODMtZGE4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6582083-da8f-4cbb-9f6d-6bc5c046fbb1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sreechem Resins Ltd. has clarified an inadvertent human error in the date of the Board Meeting for considering and approving the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The correct date of the Board Meeting is February 05, 2026, not February 04, 2026 as previously mentioned in certain places. The company regrets the error and requests stakeholders to take note of the clarification. Additionally, the trading window for dealing in shares of the company will remain closed till 48 hours after the declaration of the unaudited financial results.</p><ul><li>Sreechem Resins Ltd. clarifies error in Board Meeting date for Q3 and nine months results ended December 31, 2025</li><li>The correct date of the Board Meeting is February 05, 2026</li><li>Trading window for dealing in shares of the company to remain closed till 48 hours after the declaration of the unaudited financial results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/75e0734c-2f71-4f54-a7a5-8b22d55c6d51.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SREECHEM RESINS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>