<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:43:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[PVVINFRA] PVV Infra Ltd. to Approve Q4 Results, Split of Face Value, and Other Business Matters in February 2026 Board Meeting</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PVV+Infra+Ltd&title=PVV+Infra+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q4+Results%2C+Split+of+Face+Value%2C+and+Other+Business+Matters+in+February+2026+Board+Meeting&newsId=6d8cf759-28b7-4b71-ad06-106990a31914&token=NmQ4Y2Y3NTktMjhi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d8cf759-28b7-4b71-ad06-106990a31914</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:42:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>PVV Infra Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will convene on February 10, 2026, to discuss several key matters. The agenda includes the review and approval of unaudited financial results for the quarter ending December 31, 2025, along with the limited review report for the same period. The Board will also consider and approve a sub-division (split) of the face value of the existing equity shares of the company from INR 5 each to INR 1 each, in accordance with the Companies Act, 2013. Additionally, the Board will decide the date for issuing a postal ballot notice and transact other incidental and ancillary matters. The company will close the trading window for transactions in its securities from February 2, 2026, until 48 hours after the declaration of the aforesaid results. The information is available on the company&apos;s website, www.pvvinfra.com.</p><ul><li>PVV Infra Ltd. Board Meeting on February 10, 2026</li><li>Review and approval of Q4 2025 financial results</li><li>Consideration and approval of share face value split</li><li>Decision on postal ballot notice issuance date</li><li>Closure of trading window for securities transactions</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/bd360b6e-e318-45ef-aa01-93ffcedc8168.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PVV Infra Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CAMPUS] Campus Activewear Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Unaudited Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Campus+Activewear+Ltd&title=Campus+Activewear+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=9aa08fa5-4f62-4c30-8130-f0c8030f99dc&token=OWFhMDhmYTUtNGY2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9aa08fa5-4f62-4c30-8130-f0c8030f99dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:42:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Campus Activewear Ltd has announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The total income for the quarter is INR 594.11 crores, with a profit for the period of INR 16.79 crores. The company&apos;s revenue from operations for the nine months ended December 31, 2025, is INR 1,335.28 crores. The company does not have any subsidiary, associate, or joint venture company(ies) as of December 31, 2025.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for the quarter is INR 588.61 crores.</li><li>Profit for the period is INR 16.79 crores.</li><li>Total income for the quarter is INR 594.11 crores.</li><li>Revenue from operations for the nine months ended December 31, 2025, is INR 1,335.28 crores.</li><li>The company does not have any subsidiary, associate, or joint venture company(ies) as of December 31, 2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b90b4283-0f24-49a3-bf69-224ee0e01554.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Campus Activewear Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NPL] National Peroxide Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results on Feb 05, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=National+Peroxide+Ltd&title=National+Peroxide+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+on+Feb+05%2C+2026&newsId=0641e7bc-eb83-446d-bdf6-3d0cebe98638&token=MDY0MWU3YmMtZWI4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0641e7bc-eb83-446d-bdf6-3d0cebe98638</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:42:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>National Peroxide Ltd, formerly known as NPL Chemicals Limited, has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 05, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. This is in accordance with Regulation 29 of the Listing Regulations.</p><ul><li>National Peroxide Ltd to consider and approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>Meeting scheduled on February 05, 2026.</li><li>In accordance with Regulation 29 of the Listing Regulations.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ef4d4c49-5f7b-45e4-ba8b-caf6be31bacc.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: National Peroxide Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[PRIMAGR] Prima Agro Ltd. to Approve Q4 2025 Un-audited Financial Results on Feb 12, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=PRIMA+AGRO+LTD.&title=Prima+Agro+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q4+2025+Un-audited+Financial+Results+on+Feb+12%2C+2026&newsId=b71bf372-1931-4a32-b914-b06db7067131&token=YjcxYmYzNzItMTkz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b71bf372-1931-4a32-b914-b06db7067131</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:41:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Prima Agro Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 12, 2026, to consider and approve the Un-audited Financial Results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will take place at the company&apos;s registered office in Cochin. In addition to the financial results, the board will also discuss the allotment and activation of ISIN for Non-Convertible Preference Shares. The company&apos;s trading window for dealing in securities will be closed from January 1, 2026, to February 14, 2026, following the declaration of the Un-audited Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Prima Agro Ltd. to approve Q4 2025 Un-audited Financial Results on Feb 12, 2026</li><li>Board meeting scheduled on Feb 12, 2026, at the company&apos;s registered office in Cochin</li><li>Consideration and approval of Un-audited Financial Results for the quarter ended Dec 31, 2025</li><li>Discussion on allotment and activation of ISIN for Non-Convertible Preference Shares</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities to remain closed from Jan 1, 2026, to Feb 14, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b4bce374-71bb-42ca-9b17-550a71e991ba.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: PRIMA AGRO LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ZARDIINV] Ardi Investments &amp; Trading Company Ltd to Approve Q4 2025 Unaudited Financial Results on Feb 5, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ARDI+INVESTMENT+%26+TRADING+LTD.&title=Ardi+Investments+%26+Trading+Company+Ltd+to+Approve+Q4+2025+Unaudited+Financial+Results+on+Feb+5%2C+2026&newsId=2a12c607-69ec-4800-a9fc-c3923b7a09dc&token=MmExMmM2MDctNjll</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a12c607-69ec-4800-a9fc-c3923b7a09dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:40:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ardi Investments &amp; Trading Company Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 5, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in securities of the company will be closed for designated employees and their immediate relatives until 48 hours after the declaration of the unaudited financial results.</p><ul><li>Ardi Investments &amp; Trading Company Ltd to approve Q4 2025 unaudited financial results on Feb 5, 2026</li><li>Trading window to be closed for designated employees and their immediate relatives until 48 hours after the financial results declaration</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/83becaea-4715-4bb7-9398-dc6490294f44.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ARDI INVESTMENT & TRADING LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NIHARINF] Nihar Info Global Ltd to Approve Q3 Results and Elect Chairman in February 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NIHAR+INFO+GLOBAL+LTD.&title=Nihar+Info+Global+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+Results+and+Elect+Chairman+in+February+2026&newsId=3a10e0f9-7feb-408f-9424-af8f9d098cee&token=M2ExMGUwZjktN2Zl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a10e0f9-7feb-408f-9424-af8f9d098cee</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:39:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Nihar Info Global Ltd has announced a Board of Directors meeting on 13th February 2026. The agenda includes electing the Chairman, granting leave of absence, noting the minutes of the previous meeting, and approving the Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for the third quarter ended on 31st December 2025.</p><ul><li>Nihar Info Global Ltd has scheduled a Board of Directors meeting for 13th February 2026</li><li>The agenda includes electing the Chairman of the meeting</li><li>The Board will grant leave of absence, if any</li><li>The Minutes of the previous Board meeting held on 13th November 2025 will be taken note of</li><li>The Unaudited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 2025 will be approved</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/802e5aed-d776-43ad-b179-572062f562b1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NIHAR INFO GLOBAL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UPL] UPL Ltd Receives Monitoring Agency Report for Quarter and Nine Months Period Ended December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=UPL+Limited&title=UPL+Ltd+Receives+Monitoring+Agency+Report+for+Quarter+and+Nine+Months+Period+Ended+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=080c57e0-b2b6-4ad3-aeff-a50464c799b9&token=MDgwYzU3ZTAtYjJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">080c57e0-b2b6-4ad3-aeff-a50464c799b9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>UPL Ltd, a leading Agribusiness company, has received a Monitoring Agency Report from CARE Ratings Limited for the quarter and nine months period ended December 31, 2025. The report confirms the utilization of proceeds from the Rights Issue of the Company with no variations or deviations. The information is also available on the Company&apos;s website. The Monitoring Agency Report was prepared in line with the format prescribed by SEBI, capturing comments where applicable. The report does not create any legally binding obligations on the Monitoring Agency, and the MA takes no responsibility for comments of the issuer&apos;s Management/Board.</p><ul><li>UPL Ltd has received a Monitoring Agency Report from CARE Ratings Limited for the quarter and nine months period ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The report confirms the utilization of proceeds from the Rights Issue of the Company with no variations or deviations.</li><li>The information is available on the Company&apos;s website.</li><li>The Monitoring Agency Report was prepared in line with the format prescribed by SEBI.</li><li>The MA takes no responsibility for comments of the issuer&apos;s Management/Board.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/85416ed3-debb-4d57-84f4-c2f143e229b7.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: UPL Limited | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AVONMERC] Avon Mercantile Ltd. Announces 1st EGM for FY 2025-26, Appointment of New Manager</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Avon+Mercantile+Ltd&title=Avon+Mercantile+Ltd.+Announces+1st+EGM+for+FY+2025-26%2C+Appointment+of+New+Manager&newsId=8f922aa3-7ad8-4a52-91d6-44ac0b948e90&token=OGY5MjJhYTMtN2Fk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f922aa3-7ad8-4a52-91d6-44ac0b948e90</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:38:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Avon Mercantile Limited has announced the 1st Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) for the financial year 2025-26, which will be held on Tuesday, 24th February, 2026 at 2:00 P.M. The EGM will be conducted through Video Conference (VC) or Other Audio-Visual Means (OAVM). The company has proposed the appointment of Ms. Nikita Sehrawat as Manager for a period of 5 years. The EGM will also discuss other business matters. The cut-off date for remote e-voting is Tuesday, 17th February, 2026. The remote e-voting will commence on Saturday, 21st February, 2026 at 9.00 a.m. (IST) and will end on Tuesday, 23rd February, 2026 at 5.00 p.m. (IST).</p><ul><li>1st Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) for the financial year 2025-26</li><li>Appointment of Ms. Nikita Sehrawat as Manager for a period of 5 years</li><li>EGM to be conducted through Video Conference (VC) or Other Audio-Visual Means (OAVM)</li><li>Cut-off date for remote e-voting is Tuesday, 17th February, 2026</li><li>Remote e-voting will commence on Saturday, 21st February, 2026 and end on Tuesday, 23rd February, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c7c9d0b5-da7a-4084-89fe-f4db0bb20d5e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Avon Mercantile Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TITANIN] Titan Intech Ltd to Approve Q3 FY26 Financial Results on Feb 11, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Titan+Intech+Ltd&title=Titan+Intech+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+FY26+Financial+Results+on+Feb+11%2C+2026&newsId=a2dd7a65-800b-4761-97e3-8eb38ff1efa4&token=YTJkZDdhNjUtODAw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2dd7a65-800b-4761-97e3-8eb38ff1efa4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:38:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Titan Intech Ltd has scheduled a Board of Directors meeting on February 11, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will also approve the limited review report on unaudited financial results for the same quarter. Any other matter with the permission of the chair will also be discussed.</p><ul><li>Titan Intech Ltd to approve Q3 FY26 financial results on Feb 11, 2026</li><li>Unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, to be considered</li><li>Limited review report on unaudited financial results for Q4 FY25 to be approved</li><li>Meeting to be held at Titan Intech Ltd headquarters</li><li>Available on the company&apos;s website: www.titanintech.in</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a19573c6-ffb0-4303-bb95-fb254c98e31c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Titan Intech Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHARP] Sharp India Ltd to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended 31st December 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SHARP+INDIA+LTD.&title=Sharp+India+Ltd+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+31st+December+2025&newsId=886bbf44-3810-4547-b0c8-e40e0981432b&token=ODg2YmJmNDQtMzgx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">886bbf44-3810-4547-b0c8-e40e0981432b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 09:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sharp India Ltd has informed BSE that the Board of Directors will meet on 10th February 2026 to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December 2025. The meeting will be conducted through Video Conference in accordance with Regulation 29 (1) of the SEBI (Listing Obligations &amp; Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Sharp India Ltd to consider and approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December 2025</li><li>Board Meeting scheduled on 10th February 2026</li><li>Meeting to be conducted through Video Conference</li><li>In compliance with Regulation 29 (1) of the SEBI (Listing Obligations &amp; Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c8ba5511-2f4c-459d-84ee-9a25d0590f51.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SHARP INDIA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>