<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:40:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[ICIL] Indo Count Industries Ltd: No Unpublished Price Sensitive Information Despite Volume Surge</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=INDO+COUNT+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Indo+Count+Industries+Ltd%3A+No+Unpublished+Price+Sensitive+Information+Despite+Volume+Surge&newsId=11cb8bdc-0e30-4a8c-96bc-0a8a1550422f&token=MTFjYjhiZGMtMGUz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11cb8bdc-0e30-4a8c-96bc-0a8a1550422f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Indo Count Industries Ltd has clarified that there is no unpublished price sensitive information or impending information that has become due for disclosure, in response to a query about significant increase in the volume of the company&apos;s security across exchanges. The company has always been prompt in making requisite disclosures as per the materiality policy and guidelines laid down by the Board of Directors. Any significant movement in the volume of shares is market driven.</p><ul><li>Indo Count Industries Ltd has clarified that there is no unpublished price sensitive information despite a significant increase in the volume of the company&apos;s security across exchanges.</li><li>The company has always been prompt in making requisite disclosures as per the materiality policy and guidelines laid down by the Board of Directors.</li><li>Any significant movement in the volume of shares is market driven.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/28faa828-0d33-41a8-a047-028f7cd5b377.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: INDO COUNT INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[RRFIN] RR Financial Consultants Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=RR+FINANCIAL+CONSULTANTS+LTD.&title=RR+Financial+Consultants+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+for+2025&newsId=1103926b-e5f6-4588-8c63-453bfc7e2b87&token=MTEwMzkyNmItZTVm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1103926b-e5f6-4588-8c63-453bfc7e2b87</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>RR Financial Consultants Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on 14th February, 2026 to consider and approve the Unaudited Standalone Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended 31st December, 2025. The meeting will also approve the Limited Review Report as required under Regulation 33(3) of the listing Regulations. The trading window for all Designated persons and their immediate relatives has been closed from 1st January, 2026 till 48 hours after the declaration of the Financial Results i.e. till February 16, 2026.</p><ul><li>RR Financial Consultants Ltd to consider and approve Unaudited Standalone Financial Results for Q3 and nine months ended 31st December, 2025</li><li>The meeting is scheduled on 14th February, 2026</li><li>Limited Review Report to be approved as per Regulation 33(3) of the listing Regulations</li><li>Trading window closed for all Designated persons and their immediate relatives from 1st January, 2026 till 48 hours after the declaration of the Financial Results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/baf158c3-a9b7-467b-a698-7455984aa45d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: RR FINANCIAL CONSULTANTS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HINDCOPPER] Hindustan Copper Ltd Declares Interim Dividend of 20% for FY 2025-26, Fixes Record Date</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HINDUSTAN+COPPER+LTD.&title=Hindustan+Copper+Ltd+Declares+Interim+Dividend+of+20%25+for+FY+2025-26%2C+Fixes+Record+Date&newsId=5cbb2194-c280-4d43-83b9-caaa952efeea&token=NWNiYjIxOTQtYzI4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5cbb2194-c280-4d43-83b9-caaa952efeea</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:39:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Dividend</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Hindustan Copper Ltd (HCL) has declared an interim dividend of 20% (Re.1/- per equity share) for the financial year 2025-26. The record date for determining the eligibility of shareholders to receive the dividend is set as 13th February 2026. The dividend will be paid through electronic mode on or before 6th March 2026. The company has also urged members to update their residential status, PAN, and category with their Depository Participants or the Company. HCL has approved the Unaudited Financial Results (Standalone &amp; Consolidated) for the quarter ended on 31st December 2025. The company will make dividend payments only through electronic modes, and shareholders are requested to ensure their bank account details are updated and validated in their demat account or with the Registrar and Transfer Agent for physical holdings.</p><ul><li>Hindustan Copper Ltd declares an interim dividend of 20% (Re.1/- per equity share) for FY 2025-26.</li><li>The record date for determining the eligibility of shareholders to receive the dividend is set as 13th February 2026.</li><li>Dividend payment will be made only through electronic modes.</li><li>Shareholders are requested to update their residential status, PAN, and category with their Depository Participants or the Company.</li><li>HCL has approved the Unaudited Financial Results (Standalone &amp; Consolidated) for the quarter ended on 31st December 2025.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f53b9f48-eb92-49e7-8792-29ad4a30ae4f.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HINDUSTAN COPPER LTD. | Category: Dividend</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JKIL] J. Kumar Infraprojects Reports Q3 &amp; 9M FY26 Results: Revenue at ₹ 4,138 Cr, PAT at ₹ 277 Cr</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=J.KUMAR+INFRAPROJECTS+LTD.&title=J.+Kumar+Infraprojects+Reports+Q3+%26+9M+FY26+Results%3A+Revenue+at+%E2%82%B9+4%2C138+Cr%2C+PAT+at+%E2%82%B9+277+Cr&newsId=fb90c357-6e61-42f3-8680-1921f4643303&token=ZmI5MGMzNTctNmU2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fb90c357-6e61-42f3-8680-1921f4643303</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:39:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>J. Kumar Infraprojects Limited (JKIL) announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months period ended December 31, 2025. The company reported a moderation in its operating and financial performance due to an extended monsoon season. However, the company maintained a stable balance sheet position with adequate liquidity. The total order book stood at ₹ 19,212 crores. The Managing Director, Kamal J. Gupta, expressed confidence in the company&apos;s growth journey ahead.</p><ul><li>Revenue from Operations for 9M FY26 grew by 2% to ₹ 4,138 crores</li><li>EBITDA for 9M FY26 grew by 1% to ₹ 599 crores</li><li>PAT for 9M FY26 stood at ₹ 277 crores</li><li>Net Debt as on December 31, 2025 stood at negative ₹ 250 crores</li><li>Total Order book as on December 31, 2025 stood at ₹ 19,212 crores</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f52e6dcf-ebb0-48cb-b496-2125178e6142.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: J.KUMAR INFRAPROJECTS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GROWINGTON] Growington Ventures India Ltd: Un-audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Growington+Ventures+India+Ltd&title=Growington+Ventures+India+Ltd%3A+Un-audited+Standalone+and+Consolidated+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=c4480a24-322c-49b6-8a9e-863646d8e20b&token=YzQ0ODBhMjQtMzIy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4480a24-322c-49b6-8a9e-863646d8e20b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:39:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Growington Ventures India Ltd met on 05th February, 2026, and discussed, considered, and approved the un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company has reported revenue from operations of INR 6,512.80 Lakhs and INR 6,108.58 Lakhs for the respective periods. The net profit for the quarter is INR 406.67 Lakhs and INR 375.36 Lakhs for the nine-month period. The company has also reviewed the independent auditor&apos;s report for both standalone and consolidated financial results.</p><ul><li>Un-audited Standalone and Consolidated Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended December 31, 2025</li><li>Revenue from operations of INR 6,512.80 Lakhs and INR 6,108.58 Lakhs for the respective periods</li><li>Net profit of INR 406.67 Lakhs and INR 375.36 Lakhs for the quarter and nine-month period</li><li>Review of the independent auditor&apos;s report for both standalone and consolidated financial results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e3662ae5-0c2f-4355-95ea-4603bda19acb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Growington Ventures India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[REVATHI] Semac Construction Ltd. Approves and Adopts Financial Results for FY 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=REVATHI+EQUIPMENT+LTD.-%24&title=Semac+Construction+Ltd.+Approves+and+Adopts+Financial+Results+for+FY+2025&newsId=7a71aeb3-642e-4b25-9a4b-0cbefe8cff4a&token=N2E3MWFlYjMtNjQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7a71aeb3-642e-4b25-9a4b-0cbefe8cff4a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:39:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Semac Construction Ltd. has approved the unaudited financial statements for the quarter and period ended 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at Rs. 4,604.78 lakhs with a net profit of Rs. 156.98 lakhs. The board has also approved the merger of Semac Construction Technologies India Private Limited with Semac Construction Limited. The company has been notified of the new Labour Codes in India which introduces changes to employee benefits during and after employment.</p><ul><li>Approval and adoption of unaudited financial statements for the quarter and period ended 31st December 2025</li><li>Revenue from operations at Rs. 4,604.78 lakhs</li><li>Net profit of Rs. 156.98 lakhs</li><li>Approval of merger of Semac Construction Technologies India Private Limited with Semac Construction Limited</li><li>Notification of new Labour Codes in India</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e70cb8cd-7409-4eb3-ab38-b22540607055.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: REVATHI EQUIPMENT LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ABCOTS] A B Cotspin India Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on Feb 11, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=A+B+Cotspin+India+Ltd&title=A+B+Cotspin+India+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+Feb+11%2C+2026&newsId=4af99d08-d108-4e8d-9a00-03117ea90a1a&token=NGFmOTlkMDgtZDEw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4af99d08-d108-4e8d-9a00-03117ea90a1a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:38:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>A B Cotspin India Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 11, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the company will be closed for designated persons and their immediate relatives from January 01, 2026, till the expiry of 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results.</p><ul><li>A B Cotspin India Ltd to consider and approve Q3 and nine months financial results on Feb 11, 2026</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities to be closed for designated persons and their immediate relatives from Jan 1, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/95d00daf-93f8-45a2-aba6-e1ed0b68a811.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: A B Cotspin India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VRLLOG] VRL Logistics Ltd Declares Interim Dividend of Rs.5/- per Equity Share and Reports Q3 2025 Financial Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VRL+Logistics+Ltd&title=VRL+Logistics+Ltd+Declares+Interim+Dividend+of+Rs.5%2F-+per+Equity+Share+and+Reports+Q3+2025+Financial+Results&newsId=faea75f7-37e3-4929-8129-1a491d2c29a9&token=ZmFlYTc1ZjctMzdl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">faea75f7-37e3-4929-8129-1a491d2c29a9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:38:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>VRL Logistics Ltd, a company in the goods transport business, has declared an interim dividend of Rs.5/- per equity share. The dividend record date is yet to be announced. The company&apos;s Q3 2025 financial results show a profit for the period of Rs. 16,468.47 lakhs, with revenue from operations at Rs. 82,696.23 lakhs. The company&apos;s total expenses for the quarter were Rs. 74,694.20 lakhs. The financial results are unaudited and have been prepared in accordance with Indian Accounting Standard 34 and other accounting principles generally accepted in India.</p><ul><li>VRL Logistics Ltd declares an interim dividend of Rs.5/- per equity share</li><li>The company&apos;s Q3 2025 financial results show a profit for the period of Rs. 16,468.47 lakhs</li><li>Revenue from operations for Q3 2025 stands at Rs. 82,696.23 lakhs</li><li>The company&apos;s total expenses for Q3 2025 are Rs. 74,694.20 lakhs</li><li>The financial results are unaudited and have been prepared in accordance with Indian Accounting Standard 34 and other accounting principles generally accepted in India</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/10ad6979-e4ec-49b1-96af-ddb0f422b144.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VRL Logistics Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[UPROTECH] Unipro Technologies Ltd to Approve Q3 Financial Statements on Feb 11, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Unipro+Technologies+Ltd&title=Unipro+Technologies+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+Financial+Statements+on+Feb+11%2C+2026&newsId=57777eb7-1e01-48bc-b2ce-c5ab3e655db8&token=NTc3NzdlYjctMWUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57777eb7-1e01-48bc-b2ce-c5ab3e655db8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Unipro Technologies Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 11, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial statements for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will take place at the company&apos;s registered office in Hyderabad, Telangana.</p><ul><li>Unipro Technologies Ltd&apos;s Board of Directors to meet on February 11, 2026</li><li>The meeting will approve the unaudited financial statements for the quarter ended December 31, 2025</li><li>The meeting will be held at the company&apos;s registered office in Hyderabad, Telangana</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2ce709af-a8c9-48db-9222-c280cdebaba0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Unipro Technologies Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GINISILK] Gini Silk Mills Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GINI+SILK+MILLS+LTD.-%24&title=Gini+Silk+Mills+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=46396b37-1990-4f1c-aaf8-dbb62797d5ab&token=NDYzOTZiMzctMTk5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">46396b37-1990-4f1c-aaf8-dbb62797d5ab</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 09:38:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gini Silk Mills Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 11, 2026, at its registered office in Mumbai. The agenda includes the consideration and approval of the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025, along with the limited review report of the statutory auditor. This meeting is in compliance with Regulation 29 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015.</p><ul><li>Gini Silk Mills Ltd scheduled a Board Meeting for February 11, 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025</li><li>The meeting is in compliance with Regulation 29 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/56e1ee44-6bc6-4864-a959-3416117628bd.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GINI SILK MILLS LTD.-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>