<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:23:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[COSMICCRF] Prilika Enterprises Pvt Ltd Acquires 0.12% Stake in Cosmic CRF Ltd</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Cosmic+CRF+Ltd&title=Prilika+Enterprises+Pvt+Ltd+Acquires+0.12%25+Stake+in+Cosmic+CRF+Ltd&newsId=cabcd818-5267-4e2c-8b8e-a93768186d73&token=Y2FiY2Q4MTgtNTI2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cabcd818-5267-4e2c-8b8e-a93768186d73</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:22:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Prilika Enterprises Pvt Ltd, a part of the promoter group, has acquired 10900 equity shares of Cosmic CRF Ltd, which amounts to 0.12% of the total voting rights. This acquisition is in accordance with Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011.</p><ul><li>Prilika Enterprises Pvt Ltd acquires 10900 shares of Cosmic CRF Ltd</li><li>The acquisition amounts to 0.12% of the total voting rights</li><li>Prilika Enterprises Pvt Ltd is a part of the promoter group</li><li>The acquisition is in accordance with Regulation 29(2) of SEBI (Substantial Acquisition of Shares and Takeovers) Regulations, 2011</li><li>Cosmic CRF Ltd has a total equity share capital of Rs. 9,18,76,430 comprising of 91,87,643 equity shares of Rs. 10/- each</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/A31EAB38_22EC_4C38_96AC_7C6DE2F73FFD_145024.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Cosmic CRF Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KPEL] K.P. Energy Ltd Schedules Board Meeting to Approve Q3 Results and Consider Dividend for FY 2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=K.P.+Energy+Ltd&title=K.P.+Energy+Ltd+Schedules+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+Results+and+Consider+Dividend+for+FY+2025-26&newsId=73333b7f-b024-4085-9635-560e0aa6246f&token=NzMzMzNiN2YtYjAy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73333b7f-b024-4085-9635-560e0aa6246f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>K.P. Energy Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on January 21, 2026, to consider and approve the standalone and consolidated unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting will also consider declaring the third interim dividend for the financial year 2025-26. The company&apos;s trading window for insiders will close 48 hours after the results are made public.</p><ul><li>K.P. Energy Ltd to consider and approve Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025 financial results</li><li>The company may declare the third interim dividend for the financial year 2025-26</li><li>Trading window for insiders to close 48 hours after results are made public on January 21, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/39483548-297a-4ab4-9d9d-22b4aa2531cb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: K.P. Energy Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TIPSINDLTD] Tips Music Ltd&apos;s Statutory Auditors Convert Partnership Firm into Limited Liability Partnership</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TIPS+INDUSTRIES+LTD.&title=Tips+Music+Ltd%27s+Statutory+Auditors+Convert+Partnership+Firm+into+Limited+Liability+Partnership&newsId=59d6cb03-9cb5-4f97-8e4b-7cd14719caa0&token=NTlkNmNiMDMtOWNi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59d6cb03-9cb5-4f97-8e4b-7cd14719caa0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:21:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Auditor Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tips Music Ltd has announced that its Statutory Auditors, M S K A &amp; Associates, Chartered Accountants, have been converted into a Limited Liability Partnership (LLP) under the Limited Liability Partnership Act, 2008, with effect from January 13, 2026. The new LLP is named MSKA &amp; Associates LLP, Chartered Accountants, with ICAI firm registration number 105047W/W101187. The conversion does not affect the existing audit engagement, as MSKA &amp; Associates LLP will continue to act as the Statutory Auditors for the remaining tenure of appointment.</p><ul><li>Tips Music Ltd&apos;s Statutory Auditors have been converted into a Limited Liability Partnership (LLP)</li><li>The new LLP is named MSKA &amp; Associates LLP, Chartered Accountants</li><li>The conversion does not affect the existing audit engagement</li><li>MSKA &amp; Associates LLP will continue to act as the Statutory Auditors for the remaining tenure</li><li>The conversion took effect on January 13, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0eb3ffc7-337e-418b-a29d-7313c2aefae1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TIPS INDUSTRIES LTD. | Category: Auditor Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SILVERTUC] Silver Touch Technologies Ltd. Announces Bonus Issue, Stock Split, and Capital Reclassification</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Silver+Touch+Technologies+Ltd&title=Silver+Touch+Technologies+Ltd.+Announces+Bonus+Issue%2C+Stock+Split%2C+and+Capital+Reclassification&newsId=605e3d0b-48a7-46b0-b3d9-d2ab209864c1&token=NjA1ZTNkMGItNDhh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">605e3d0b-48a7-46b0-b3d9-d2ab209864c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Bonus</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Silver Touch Technologies Ltd. has announced a bonus issue, stock split, and reclassification of its authorized share capital. The Board of Directors recommended a bonus issue of 1:1, meaning one bonus equity share for every one fully paid-up equity share. The company will also sub-divide its existing equity shares of face value of Rs. 10/- each into five equity shares of face value of Rs. 2/- each. Furthermore, the company will alter the capital clause of its Memorandum of Association, reclassifying the authorized share capital of the company. The proposed changes are subject to approval from the shareholders and the applicable statutory authorities.</p><ul><li>Bonus issue of 1:1</li><li>Stock split from Rs. 10/- face value to Rs. 2/- face value</li><li>Reclassification of authorized share capital</li><li>Subject to approval of shareholders and statutory authorities</li><li>Expected completion by 15th March, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2084138b-5ee5-45c5-95d2-d321b60d3a70.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Silver Touch Technologies Ltd | Category: Bonus</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CYBERMEDIA] Cyber Media India Ltd Announces First and Final Call Notice for Rights Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CYBER+MEDIA+%28INDIA%29+LTD.&title=Cyber+Media+India+Ltd+Announces+First+and+Final+Call+Notice+for+Rights+Issue&newsId=7d743473-1624-4dd7-8ffb-6c1558aa0332&token=N2Q3NDM0NzMtMTYy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7d743473-1624-4dd7-8ffb-6c1558aa0332</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:19:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Rights Issue</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cyber Media India Ltd has sent the First and Final Call Notice along with detailed instructions, ASBA Application Form and Payment Slip to the holders of the partly paid-up equity shares. The documents were sent to the shareholders whose names appear in the Register of Members as on the Record Date fixed for this purpose. The aforesaid documents are available on the Company’s website and the Company’s Registrar &amp; Transfer Agents’ website.</p><ul><li>Cyber Media India Ltd has announced the First and Final Call Notice for the Rights Issue.</li><li>The notice along with detailed instructions, ASBA Application Form and Payment Slip have been sent to the holders of the partly paid-up equity shares.</li><li>The documents were sent to the shareholders as per the Register of Members on the specified Record Date.</li><li>The documents are available on the Company’s website and the Company’s Registrar &amp; Transfer Agents’ website.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d28c05b6-addd-40f1-9c83-a8147bdf076b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CYBER MEDIA (INDIA) LTD. | Category: Rights Issue</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MARUTI] Maruti Suzuki Starts Exports of VICTORIS, Badged as &apos;Across&apos;</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=MARUTI+SUZUKI+INDIA+LTD.&title=Maruti+Suzuki+Starts+Exports+of+VICTORIS%2C+Badged+as+%27Across%27&newsId=1952b0f1-6bcd-4e97-82f8-a40760a30a69&token=MTk1MmIwZjEtNmJj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1952b0f1-6bcd-4e97-82f8-a40760a30a69</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:17:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Maruti Suzuki India Limited has commenced exports of its premium SUV, VICTORIS, which will be globally sold as ‘Across’. Over 450 vehicles have been shipped from Mundra and Pipavav ports to over 100 countries and regions, including Latin America, Middle East and Africa. VICTORIS, engineered as a modern SUV, has demonstrated global safety credentials, earning a 5-star safety rating in both Global NCAP and Bharat NCAP. Maruti Suzuki, which emerged as India’s number one passenger vehicle exporter for the fifth year in a row in CY2025, is hopeful that VICTORIS will be well received in international markets.</p><ul><li>Maruti Suzuki commences exports of VICTORIS, badged as ‘Across’</li><li>VICTORIS is planned to be exported to over 100 countries and regions</li><li>VICTORIS has demonstrated global safety credentials, earning a 5-star safety rating in both Global NCAP and Bharat NCAP</li><li>Maruti Suzuki emerged as India’s number one passenger vehicle exporter for the fifth year in a row in CY2025</li><li>VICTORIS is expected to support Maruti Suzuki’s export ambitions</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a314d6ab-06fc-4863-86e6-47ff70deab0c.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: MARUTI SUZUKI INDIA LTD. | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AUSOMENT] AuSom Enterprise Ltd: No Price Sensitive Information or Impactful Events Affecting Company Operations</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AuSom+Enterprise+Limited&title=AuSom+Enterprise+Ltd%3A+No+Price+Sensitive+Information+or+Impactful+Events+Affecting+Company+Operations&newsId=444618d8-64b6-4cb6-956d-5e05bdfd43d8&token=NDQ0NjE4ZDgtNjRi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">444618d8-64b6-4cb6-956d-5e05bdfd43d8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>AuSom Enterprise Ltd has clarified that there are no events or information that have a bearing on the operation or performance of the company. This includes all price sensitive information and any potential announcements that may influence the price or volume behavior of the scrip.</p><ul><li>AuSom Enterprise Ltd has no price sensitive information to disclose</li><li>No events or information are affecting the company&apos;s operations</li><li>There are no impending announcements that may influence the scrip&apos;s price or volume behavior</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5f1c9497-040d-43ed-bdf2-f08d2eda3156.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AuSom Enterprise Limited | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[FLUOROCHEM] Gujarat Fluorochemicals Ltd Submits Monthly Report on Share Transfers Under SEBI Special Window</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Gujarat+Fluorochemicals+Ltd&title=Gujarat+Fluorochemicals+Ltd+Submits+Monthly+Report+on+Share+Transfers+Under+SEBI+Special+Window&newsId=ad5c1a5a-fb4b-400d-8fa0-ae6808b6c2f0&token=YWQ1YzFhNWEtZmI0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad5c1a5a-fb4b-400d-8fa0-ae6808b6c2f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Gujarat Fluorochemicals Ltd has submitted a report on shares re-lodged for transfer and demat. The report, prepared in accordance with SEBI Circular no. SEBI/HO/MIRSD/MIRSD-PoD/P/CIR/2025/97, provides details of requests received, processed, approved, and rejected during the month ended 31st December, 2025. The average time taken for processing these requests is also included in the report. The Registrar and Transfer Agent of the company has provided this report, which is now being taken on record by the company.</p><ul><li>Gujarat Fluorochemicals Ltd submits monthly report on share transfers under SEBI Special Window.</li><li>Report includes details of requests received, processed, approved, and rejected during the month ended 31st December, 2025.</li><li>Average time taken for processing requests is also part of the report.</li><li>Registrar and Transfer Agent of the company has provided the report.</li><li>Company is taking the report on record.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f2c1546b-23da-487e-b804-2a3223d28c45.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Gujarat Fluorochemicals Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CAPFIN] Capfin India Ltd Postpones Board Meeting to Approve Q3 Results</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Capfin+India+Ltd&title=Capfin+India+Ltd+Postpones+Board+Meeting+to+Approve+Q3+Results&newsId=a56d131c-d4c0-434f-a303-f0b91a71b9f4&token=YTU2ZDEzMWMtZDRj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a56d131c-d4c0-434f-a303-f0b91a71b9f4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Capfin India Ltd has informed the BSE that the meeting of the Board of Directors, originally scheduled for January 16, 2026, to consider and approve the Un-audited Financial Results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, has been postponed due to unforeseen circumstances. The meeting has been rescheduled to January 23, 2026. In accordance with the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, the Trading Window in respect of dealings in the securities of the Company will remain closed until 48 hours from the declaration of financial results.</p><ul><li>Capfin India Ltd postpones Board meeting to approve Q3 results</li><li>Meeting rescheduled to January 23, 2026</li><li>Trading Window to remain closed until 48 hours after results declaration</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8fb127ec-624e-43cb-a288-5814d0dcbf15.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Capfin India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SILVERTUC] Silver Touch Technologies Ltd Announces Stock Split, Capital Reclassification, and Bonus Shares Issue</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Silver+Touch+Technologies+Ltd&title=Silver+Touch+Technologies+Ltd+Announces+Stock+Split%2C+Capital+Reclassification%2C+and+Bonus+Shares+Issue&newsId=48d24d5a-8fe9-407c-8ac2-2f50d8bc3188&token=NDhkMjRkNWEtOGZl</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48d24d5a-8fe9-407c-8ac2-2f50d8bc3188</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Stock Split, Capital Reclassification, Bonus Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Silver Touch Technologies Ltd has announced several corporate actions in a recent board meeting. The company plans to sub-divide its existing equity shares with a face value of INR 10 each into five equity shares with a face value of INR 2 each. This move aims to enhance liquidity and enable higher participation from public shareholders. Additionally, the company will reclassify its authorized share capital from INR 16,00,00,000 divided into 8,00,00,000 equity shares of INR 2 each to INR 16,00,00,000 divided into 1,60,00,000 equity shares of INR 10 each. Furthermore, Silver Touch Technologies Ltd will increase its authorized share capital by creating additional equity shares aggregating to INR 30,00,00,000 comprising 15,00,00,000 equity shares of INR 2 each. Lastly, the company will issue bonus shares in the ratio of 1:1, i.e., one bonus equity share for every one equity share held by the shareholders.</p><ul><li>The company will sub-divide its existing equity shares with a face value of INR 10 each into five equity shares with a face value of INR 2 each.</li><li>Silver Touch Technologies Ltd will reclassify its authorized share capital from INR 16,00,00,000 divided into 8,00,00,000 equity shares of INR 2 each to INR 16,00,00,000 divided into 1,60,00,000 equity shares of INR 10 each.</li><li>The company will increase its authorized share capital by creating additional equity shares aggregating to INR 30,00,00,000 comprising 15,00,00,000 equity shares of INR 2 each.</li><li>Silver Touch Technologies Ltd will issue bonus shares in the ratio of 1:1, i.e., one bonus equity share for every one equity share held by the shareholders.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f72cf2f4-67d4-4ae6-ac84-73da92bd83e1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Silver Touch Technologies Ltd | Category: Stock Split, Capital Reclassification, Bonus Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>