<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 18:29:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[AMBER] Amber Enterprises India Ltd Subsidiary, IL JIN, Acquires Control Over Stelltek Through Majority Board Representation</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Amber+Enterprises+India+Ltd&title=Amber+Enterprises+India+Ltd+Subsidiary%2C+IL+JIN%2C+Acquires+Control+Over+Stelltek+Through+Majority+Board+Representation&newsId=8e347c9b-5a67-4b17-b5a5-795260556aed&token=OGUzNDdjOWItNWE2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8e347c9b-5a67-4b17-b5a5-795260556aed</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 16:47:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>IL JIN Electronics (India) Private Limited, a material subsidiary of Amber Enterprises India Ltd, has acquired control over Stelltek Technologies Private Limited through a majority Board representation, following an Amendment Agreement to the Joint Venture Agreement dated 18 September 2023 with Stelltek and Nexxbase Marketing Private Limited. This move has resulted in Stelltek becoming a step-down subsidiary of Amber.</p><ul><li>IL JIN has been granted the right to nominate and appoint the majority of Directors on the Board of Stelltek.</li><li>IL JIN has acquired control over Stelltek through a majority Board representation, gaining authority over its management and decisions.</li><li>Stelltek has ceased to be a joint venture of ILJIN and has become a subsidiary of IL JIN, thereby becoming a step-down subsidiary of Amber.</li><li>IL JIN has initiated the appointment of Mr. Sudhir Goyal as a Non-Executive Additional Director on the Board of Stelltek.</li><li>Stelltek is engaged in the business of Manufacturing, assembling and designing of wearables and other smart electronics products.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/d16dbdad-74f5-46e3-897f-7befb26db0cf.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Amber Enterprises India Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADITYA] Aditya Ispat Ltd. Board Meeting on 18/02/2026 to Discuss Loss Mitigation and Valuation Reports</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADITYA+ISPAT+LTD.&title=Aditya+Ispat+Ltd.+Board+Meeting+on+18%2F02%2F2026+to+Discuss+Loss+Mitigation+and+Valuation+Reports&newsId=23ee45ca-b8bd-4b1e-9770-69c7d2f2dbf6&token=MjNlZTQ1Y2EtYjhi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23ee45ca-b8bd-4b1e-9770-69c7d2f2dbf6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 16:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Aditya Ispat Ltd. has informed the BSE about a scheduled Board Meeting on the 18th of February, 2026. The agenda includes taking note of the valuation reports, considering the action report submitted by the management for loss mitigation, and discussing and finalizing the approach for mitigation of losses. The company will also discuss any other business, given the permission of the Chairman.</p><ul><li>Aditya Ispat Ltd. to hold a Board Meeting on 18/02/2026</li><li>Meeting agenda includes discussing valuation reports</li><li>Action report for loss mitigation to be considered</li><li>Approach for loss mitigation to be finalized</li><li>Permission of Chairman sought for discussing other business</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/062587a4-fe3c-4137-b23f-c45ecc0ddb08.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADITYA ISPAT LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AMBER] Amber Enterprises India Ltd Subsidiary Acquires Control Over Joint Venture Partner Stelltek</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Amber+Enterprises+India+Ltd&title=Amber+Enterprises+India+Ltd+Subsidiary+Acquires+Control+Over+Joint+Venture+Partner+Stelltek&newsId=a9bd896b-5d8f-4f42-a9e9-d05d6a809679&token=YTliZDg5NmItNWQ4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a9bd896b-5d8f-4f42-a9e9-d05d6a809679</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 16:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Amber Enterprises India Ltd&apos;s subsidiary, IL JIN Electronics (India) Private Limited, has executed an Amendment Agreement to the Joint Venture Agreement dated 18 September 2023 with Stelltek Technologies Private Limited and Nexxbase Marketing Private Limited. This amendment grants IL JIN the right to nominate and appoint the majority of Directors on the Board of Stelltek, thereby exercising control over the management and policy decisions of Stelltek. As a result, Stelltek ceases to be a joint venture and becomes a step-down subsidiary of Amber Enterprises India Ltd.</p><ul><li>IL JIN Electronics (India) Private Limited, a subsidiary of Amber Enterprises India Ltd, has acquired control over Stelltek Technologies Private Limited.</li><li>The acquisition was made through an Amendment Agreement to the Joint Venture Agreement dated 18 September 2023.</li><li>IL JIN has been granted the right to nominate and appoint the majority of Directors on the Board of Stelltek.</li><li>Stelltek has ceased to be a joint venture and has become a step-down subsidiary of Amber Enterprises India Ltd.</li><li>The acquisition does not involve any change in shareholding or capital structure.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/724dbaef-19e0-4adf-a5df-3b0e23d96513.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Amber Enterprises India Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CARTRADE] CarTrade Tech Unveils Multi-Agent AI Ecosystem to Enhance Customer Experience and Accelerate Margin Expansion</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CarTrade+Tech+Ltd&title=CarTrade+Tech+Unveils+Multi-Agent+AI+Ecosystem+to+Enhance+Customer+Experience+and+Accelerate+Margin+Expansion&newsId=f516e2dd-c129-4320-bfec-ac59ea5e7900&token=ZjUxNmUyZGQtYzEy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f516e2dd-c129-4320-bfec-ac59ea5e7900</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 16:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>CarTrade Tech Limited has announced its Multi-Agent AI Ecosystem, a transformative technology initiative aimed at improving customer experience and accelerating margin expansion. The company reported its strongest quarterly performance to date with record quarterly revenue of X228 crore and a 37% EBITDA margin in Q3 FY26. The Multi-Agent AI Strategy involves deploying specialized AI agents across core platforms to enhance transaction efficiency, improve customer outcomes, and deepen engagement across customer segments.</p><ul><li>CarTrade Tech reported its strongest quarterly performance with record revenue and EBITDA margin</li><li>The company is deploying a Multi-Agent AI Ecosystem across core platforms</li><li>The AI agents are designed to enhance transaction efficiency, improve customer outcomes, and deepen engagement</li><li>CarTrade Tech&apos;s platforms attract over 150 million annual users with strong organic traffic and monthly growth</li><li>The company maintains a highly liquid balance sheet with over 1,145 crore in cash</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/6e9de16c-a6a7-436b-aec7-f98236b78493.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CarTrade Tech Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EXHICON] Monitoring Agency Report for Exhicon Events Media Solutions Ltd&apos;s Preferential Issue of Warrants for Q4 2025 Released</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Exhicon+Events+Media+Solutions+Ltd&title=Monitoring+Agency+Report+for+Exhicon+Events+Media+Solutions+Ltd%27s+Preferential+Issue+of+Warrants+for+Q4+2025+Released&newsId=043ede86-5927-4b82-b7d3-cc78a8ebeeae&token=MDQzZWRlODYtNTky</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">043ede86-5927-4b82-b7d3-cc78a8ebeeae</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 16:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Monitoring Agency Report for Exhicon Events Media Solutions Ltd&apos;s Preferential Issue of Warrants for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, has been released by Infomerics Valuation and Rating Ltd. The report indicates no deviation from the objects and provides an objective view of the utilization of the issue proceeds in relation to the objects of the issue. The report is based on the information provided by the Issuer and information obtained from sources believed by the Monitoring Agency to be accurate and reliable.</p><ul><li>Monitoring Agency Report for Q4 2025 released for Exhicon Events Media Solutions Ltd&apos;s Preferential Issue of Warrants</li><li>No deviation from the objects indicated in the report</li><li>Infomerics Valuation and Rating Ltd is the Monitoring Agency</li><li>The report is based on the information provided by the Issuer and sources believed to be accurate and reliable by the Monitoring Agency</li><li>The Monitoring Agency does not perform an audit and undertakes no independent verification of any information</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8f816173-6949-4651-9f94-280ce0354dca.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Exhicon Events Media Solutions Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BBOX] Black Box Ltd Denies Rumors of Promoters Selling Shareholding</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Black+Box+Ltd&title=Black+Box+Ltd+Denies+Rumors+of+Promoters+Selling+Shareholding&newsId=0b56d601-0a07-4459-8775-fb4f1c086ffd&token=MGI1NmQ2MDEtMGEw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b56d601-0a07-4459-8775-fb4f1c086ffd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 15:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Clarification</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Black Box Ltd has issued a clarification regarding a market rumor that the company&apos;s promoters intend to sell a large part of their shareholding. The company has categorically stated that this &apos;news item&apos; is absolutely untrue and there is no truth whatsoever in the claim of any change in the promoter holding. The company also mentioned a preferential issue of compulsorily convertible warrants in 2024, in which the promoters participated, subscribing 51.76% of the issue. The company is committed to adhering to the highest standards of corporate governance and will continue to inform the exchanges of any material events in a timely manner.</p><ul><li>Black Box Ltd denies rumors of promoters selling shareholding</li><li>The news item regarding promoters selling shareholding is absolutely untrue</li><li>Company participated in a preferential issue of compulsorily convertible warrants in 2024</li><li>Company is committed to adhering to the highest standards of corporate governance</li><li>Company will continue to inform the exchanges of any material events in a timely manner</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b11287af-386f-4d93-9fb6-ce22345bdd4b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Black Box Ltd | Category: Clarification</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[BEL] Bharat Electronics Ltd. to Form Joint Venture with Safran Electronics and Defense, France</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=BHARAT+ELECTRONICS+LTD.&title=Bharat+Electronics+Ltd.+to+Form+Joint+Venture+with+Safran+Electronics+and+Defense%2C+France&newsId=f8c16523-742c-4c40-87d0-470166e7d061&token=ZjhjMTY1MjMtNzQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f8c16523-742c-4c40-87d0-470166e7d061</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Bharat Electronics Limited (BEL) has announced that its Board of Directors has approved the signing of a Joint Venture Agreement (JVA) with M/s. Safran Electronics and Defence (SED), France for Project HAMMER. The JV will incorporate a Private Limited Company under the Companies Act, 2013, with the primary purpose of operating a &apos;Center of Excellence&apos; for the manufacturing, supply, maintenance, and repair of the Guidance Kit (GK) of HAMMER Weapon System. The registered office and principal place of business will be in Pune or any other mutually agreed location. The primary &apos;End Users&apos; are the Indian Air Force and Indian Navy. The equity will be split 50:50 between BEL and SED. The Board will consist of 4 Directors; 2 nominated by BEL and 2 by SED. The Chairman is appointed by the nominees but does not have a casting vote. The operationalisation of the provisions of JV agreement is subject to regulatory and administrative approvals from both the Countries.</p><ul><li>BEL and SED to form a Joint Venture for Project HAMMER</li><li>JV to incorporate a Private Limited Company under the Companies Act, 2013</li><li>Center of Excellence to be set up in Pune or mutually agreed location</li><li>Primary End Users are Indian Air Force and Indian Navy</li><li>Equity to be split 50:50 between BEL and SED</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5c8357ca-dec6-49e6-a96e-2af60b8108f8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: BHARAT ELECTRONICS LTD. | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ARROWGREEN] Arrow Greentech Reports Q3 FY26 Revenue of Rs. 561 Millions with 1.7% YoY Growth</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Arrow+Greentech+Ltd&title=Arrow+Greentech+Reports+Q3+FY26+Revenue+of+Rs.+561+Millions+with+1.7%25+YoY+Growth&newsId=c13726ff-00de-4855-9882-3aedf529c5ce&token=YzEzNzI2ZmYtMDBk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c13726ff-00de-4855-9882-3aedf529c5ce</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Updates</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Arrow Greentech Ltd, a leader in green packaging technology, announced its un-audited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st Dec 2025. The company reported a revenue from operations of Rs. 561 Millions in Q3 FY26, with a marginal growth of 1.7% YoY. The EBITDA stood at Rs. 192 Millions, with an EBITDA margin of 34.3%, increased by 175 bps YoY. The Profit After Tax (PAT) came at Rs. 133 Millions, with a PAT margin of 22.8%, witnessing a margin expansion of 19 bps YoY.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations for Q3 FY26 stood at Rs. 561 Millions, as compared to Rs. 551 Millions in Q3 FY25</li><li>EBITDA for Q3 FY26 is Rs. 192 Millions, as compared to Rs. 179 Millions in Q3 FY25</li><li>PBT for Q3 FY26 is Rs. 193 Millions, as compared to Rs. 175 Millions in Q3 FY25</li><li>PAT for Q3 FY26 is at Rs. 133 Millions as compared to Rs. 128 Millions in Q3 FY25, with PAT margins of 23.1% in Q3 FY26</li><li>Green Products segment delivered revenue of Rs. 103 million as compared to 53 million, growth of 94% YoY</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/42220f68-9210-4374-bdb1-80d5931af8b6.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Arrow Greentech Ltd | Category: Quarterly Updates</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ARROWGREEN] Arrow Greentech Ltd. Addresses Noncompliance, Assures Future Compliance</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Arrow+Greentech+Ltd&title=Arrow+Greentech+Ltd.+Addresses+Noncompliance%2C+Assures+Future+Compliance&newsId=ebadc8f9-8584-4716-b058-dca6f862ab92&token=ZWJhZGM4ZjktODU4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ebadc8f9-8584-4716-b058-dca6f862ab92</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 14:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In response to the NSE Letter and BSE Email dated December 16, 2025, Arrow Greentech Ltd. addressed the matter of noncompliance/delayed compliance of Regulation 23(9) of SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The Board of Directors, in its meeting held on February 13, 2026, took note of the matter, acknowledging that the delay was not intentional and advised to ensure future compliance. The Company has paid the fine levied by the Stock Exchanges and is committed to strengthening its processes to avoid such delays in the future.</p><ul><li>Arrow Greentech Ltd. addresses noncompliance with SEBI regulations</li><li>The delay in compliance was not intentional, as per the Board</li><li>The Company has paid the fine imposed by the Stock Exchanges</li><li>The Board advised to ensure future compliance with regulations</li><li>Company to strengthen processes to avoid such delays in the future</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1cc1c416-df2c-4e5f-884a-2bdd2b97a9e3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Arrow Greentech Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GNFC] Gujarat Narmada Valley Fertilizers &amp; Chemicals Ltd: No Loss of Life or Property Damage in Chlorine Gas Leak Incident</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GUJARAT+NARMADA+VALLEY+FERTILIZERS+%26+CHEMICALS+LTD.&title=Gujarat+Narmada+Valley+Fertilizers+%26+Chemicals+Ltd%3A+No+Loss+of+Life+or+Property+Damage+in+Chlorine+Gas+Leak+Incident&newsId=b239a4e7-4b21-4ba2-80eb-611992533ce1&token=YjIzOWE0ZTctNGIy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b239a4e7-4b21-4ba2-80eb-611992533ce1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 13:04:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Business Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>On February 14, 2026, a sudden leakage of Chlorine gas occurred at the TDI-I Plant of GNFC Ltd. at Bharuch. The incident led to an automatic shutdown of the plant as per the in-built safety system, and remained confined within the plant premises with no adverse impact on the surrounding area. No loss of life or damage to property was reported, and normal plant operations were safely restored by 02:12 hours.</p><ul><li>Sudden Chlorine gas leak at GNFC Ltd.&apos;s TDI-I Plant in Bharuch</li><li>Automatic shutdown of the plant due to in-built safety system</li><li>No loss of life or damage to property reported</li><li>Normal plant operations safely restored by 02:12 hours</li><li>Incident remained confined within the plant premises with no adverse impact on the surrounding area</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7590bab0-4b81-4dde-a765-75228cfaf731.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GUJARAT NARMADA VALLEY FERTILIZERS & CHEMICALS LTD. | Category: Business Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>