<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 21:31:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[TENNIND] Tenneco Clean Air India Delivers Strong Q3 Growth; Launches DaVinci DCx Advanced Suspension Technology, Wins Clean Air Business with European Truck OEM</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Tenneco+Clean+Air+India+Ltd&title=Tenneco+Clean+Air+India+Delivers+Strong+Q3+Growth%3B+Launches+DaVinci+DCx+Advanced+Suspension+Technology%2C+Wins+Clean+Air+Business+with+European+Truck+OEM&newsId=932e112a-e63d-402e-9eaa-f2d420942f41&token=OTMyZTExMmEtZTYz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">932e112a-e63d-402e-9eaa-f2d420942f41</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:58:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Tenneco Clean Air India Limited (Tenneco India) announced its financial results for Q3 &amp; 9M’ FY2026. The quarter demonstrated sustained operational performance across revenue and profitability parameters. Quarterly Financial Highlights (INR Millions): Q3 FY2026 Q3 FY2025 i Remarks Change Revenue from Operations 12,853 10,412 14.7% Value-added Revenue (VAR)* 11,941 10,412 14.7% EBITDA 2,92258/ 7.8% 24.8% PAT/Margin 1,188 / 1,254 / -5.39 (VAR) 9.9% 12.0% Adjusted PAT excludes a one-time impact of 203 mn (1.7%) Margin (VAR) 11.7% 12.0% ROCE &gt;80% &gt;40% *VAR (Value Added Revenue) is used as the primary performance metric as it excludes pass-through substrate costs from revenue from operations and better reflects the underlying operating performance, margins, and comparability across periods. Business Highlights: Q3 FY2026 was marked by a strategic technology leadership milestone: the selection of the DaVinci DCx advanced suspension system by a leading Indian OEM for a new-generation flagship SUV platform. Tenneco also secured a high-value strategic Clean Air program with a leading global commercial vehicle OEM. Driven by sustained business growth, Tenneco Clean Air India plans to establish a new greenfield Clean Air plant in North India (Kharkhoda, Haryana).</p><ul><li>Tenneco India delivered strong Q3 growth with value-added revenue up 14.7% and EBITDA growing 24.8% YoY.</li><li>Launched DaVinci DCx advanced suspension technology, selected by a leading Indian OEM for a new-generation flagship SUV platform.</li><li>Secured a high-value strategic Clean Air program with a leading global commercial vehicle OEM.</li><li>Plans to establish a new greenfield Clean Air plant in North India (Kharkhoda, Haryana).</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ab815f5a-bd45-437d-a8cb-46923ca9468e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Tenneco Clean Air India Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TENNIND] Tenneco Clean Air India Ltd. to Expand Capacity with INR 710 Million Investment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Tenneco+Clean+Air+India+Ltd&title=Tenneco+Clean+Air+India+Ltd.+to+Expand+Capacity+with+INR+710+Million+Investment&newsId=f8b191a1-4a2b-40e9-9669-6b5bca8cae11&token=ZjhiMTkxYTEtNGEy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f8b191a1-4a2b-40e9-9669-6b5bca8cae11</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:54:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Expansion</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Tenneco Clean Air India Ltd., formerly known as Tenneco Clean Air India Private Limited, has announced a proposal for capacity expansion. The company&apos;s Board of Directors, in a meeting held on Friday, 13th February 2026, approved the setting up of a new factory at Kharkhoda, Haryana. The expansion will add ~130K &apos;cold end&apos; products and ~256K &apos;hot end&apos; products annually, with the investment of approximately INR 710 million. The company plans to finance this expansion through internal accruals. The rationale behind this expansion is the growth in demand and improving manufacturing footprint in Northern India.</p><ul><li>Tenneco Clean Air India Ltd. to expand capacity with a new factory in Kharkhoda, Haryana</li><li>Approximately INR 710 million investment for the expansion</li><li>Expansion to add ~130K &apos;cold end&apos; products and ~256K &apos;hot end&apos; products annually</li><li>Financing for the expansion to be through internal accruals</li><li>Expansion driven by growth in demand and improving manufacturing footprint in Northern India</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/0876f6ba-dcc1-4b07-8125-08fab257b8d4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Tenneco Clean Air India Ltd | Category: Expansion</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TASTYBIT] Tasty Bite Eatables Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025, Announces Changes in Board of Directors</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TASTY+BITE+EATABLES+LTD.&title=Tasty+Bite+Eatables+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025%2C+Announces+Changes+in+Board+of+Directors&newsId=a5c29d85-be05-4a9c-869e-b6d1bbefb1db&token=YTVjMjlkODUtYmUw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5c29d85-be05-4a9c-869e-b6d1bbefb1db</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:52:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tasty Bite Eatables Limited has reported its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at INR 430.29 million for the quarter and INR 553.13 million for the nine months period. The company has recognized an incremental provision towards Gratuity amounting to INR 4.53 million as an exceptional item. The Board of Directors approved the un-audited financial results and took note of the resignation of Mr. Pradeep Poddar as Chairman, Independent Director. Mr. Rahul Bhatnagar has been appointed as the new Chairman, Independent Director of the company.</p><ul><li>Tasty Bite Eatables Ltd reported a revenue from operations of INR 430.29 million for Q3 and INR 553.13 million for the nine months period ended on 31st December 2025.</li><li>The company recognized an incremental provision towards Gratuity amounting to INR 4.53 million as an exceptional item.</li><li>Mr. Pradeep Poddar resigned as Chairman, Independent Director of the company.</li><li>Mr. Rahul Bhatnagar has been appointed as the new Chairman, Independent Director of the company.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/43637723-dbd1-4e72-ae9d-5adc1e147f34.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TASTY BITE EATABLES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NATCAPSUQ] Natural Capsules Q3 &amp; 9MFY26 Results: Revenue Up, EBITDA Margins Down</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NATURAL+CAPSULES+LTD.&title=Natural+Capsules+Q3+%26+9MFY26+Results%3A+Revenue+Up%2C+EBITDA+Margins+Down&newsId=2191cc57-013e-44cc-868d-78ffb1b1339a&token=MjE5MWNjNTctMDEz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2191cc57-013e-44cc-868d-78ffb1b1339a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Natural Capsules Limited, a leading manufacturer of hard capsules shell, has announced its financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue for the quarter stood at 37.75 Cr, an increase of 2.33 Cr compared to the same period last year. However, EBITDA margins saw a decline of 6.16% due to various factors including a temporary shutdown of the Puducherry unit following regulatory action. The unit is now operational and the delayed shipments have been executed in the current quarter. The company also announced that US trade tariffs impacting their HPMC capsules have been eased, restoring visibility on growth in the US market. For the nine months ended December 31, 2025, the revenue stood at 128.75 Cr, an increase of 2.89 Cr compared to the same period last year. The company&apos;s PAT for the nine months stood at 19.69 Cr.</p><ul><li>Revenue for Q3 FY26 stood at 37.75 Cr, an increase of 2.33 Cr Y-o-Y</li><li>EBITDA margins for Q3 FY26 declined by 6.16%</li><li>US trade tariffs impacting HPMC capsules have been eased</li><li>Puducherry unit is now operational</li><li>Company&apos;s PAT for 9MFY26 stood at 19.69 Cr</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1afc0646-6d28-4491-b014-3a91272900cb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NATURAL CAPSULES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TENNIND] Tenneco Clean Air India Ltd Approves Q3 &amp; Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Tenneco+Clean+Air+India+Ltd&title=Tenneco+Clean+Air+India+Ltd+Approves+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=14f8d8f1-badf-428b-ad98-a18de11afccc&token=MTRmOGQ4ZjEtYmFk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">14f8d8f1-badf-428b-ad98-a18de11afccc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:43:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tenneco Clean Air India Ltd, formerly known as Tenneco Clean Air India Private Limited, announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The results have been reviewed by the statutory auditors, M/s. Deloitte Haskins &amp; Sells. The meeting was held on February 13, 2026, and the results were approved by the Board of Directors. The Company&apos;s revenue from operations, total income, and profit before tax are key figures of interest.</p><ul><li>Tenneco Clean Air India Ltd announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025.</li><li>The results have been reviewed by the statutory auditors, M/s. Deloitte Haskins &amp; Sells.</li><li>The meeting was held on February 13, 2026, and the results were approved by the Board of Directors.</li><li>Key figures include revenue from operations, total income, and profit before tax.</li><li>The financial results are available on the Company&apos;s website.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3774b043-8d3f-4a4c-a7ec-1ff2b98bc66d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Tenneco Clean Air India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TENNIND] Tenneco Clean Air India Ltd Reports Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results for 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Tenneco+Clean+Air+India+Ltd&title=Tenneco+Clean+Air+India+Ltd+Reports+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+for+2025&newsId=8d2b9f7d-9b6b-4846-91e7-8ed1cf1a2544&token=OGQyYjlmN2QtOWI2</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d2b9f7d-9b6b-4846-91e7-8ed1cf1a2544</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:42:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tenneco Clean Air India Ltd, formerly known as Tenneco Clean Air India Private Limited, announced its unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The results have been reviewed by the statutory auditors, M/s. Deloitte Haskins &amp; Sells. The board of directors approved the financial results during a meeting held on February 13, 2026. The company&apos;s revenue, expenses, and profit before exceptional items and tax are detailed in the statement of unaudited consolidated financial results.</p><ul><li>Unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for Q3 and nine months ended on December 31, 2025</li><li>Reviewed by statutory auditors, M/s. Deloitte Haskins &amp; Sells</li><li>Approved by the board of directors during a meeting on February 13, 2026</li><li>Includes revenue, expenses, and profit before exceptional items and tax</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/a55d0898-1df8-4caa-b439-73a1ed59006d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Tenneco Clean Air India Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TASTYBIT] Tasty Bite Eatables Ltd. Approves Q3 Results, Announces Change in Chairmanship</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TASTY+BITE+EATABLES+LTD.&title=Tasty+Bite+Eatables+Ltd.+Approves+Q3+Results%2C+Announces+Change+in+Chairmanship&newsId=56a4be52-b633-4a6c-ae30-6eec4ed71796&token=NTZhNGJlNTItYjYz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56a4be52-b633-4a6c-ae30-6eec4ed71796</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:42:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Tasty Bite Eatables Ltd. has approved the financial results for the quarter ended on 31 December 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at INR 430.29 million and INR 553.13 million for the quarter and nine months ended 31 December 2025 respectively. The company noted the resignation of Mr. Pradeep Poddar as Chairman and Independent Director, effective 31 March 2026, and appointed Mr. Rahul Bhatnagar as the new Chairman and Independent Director, effective 01 April 2026. The company also recognized an incremental provision towards Gratuity amounting to INR 4.53 million in the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, as an exceptional item.</p><ul><li>Tasty Bite Eatables Ltd. approved the financial results for Q3 and nine months ended 31 December 2025.</li><li>The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at INR 430.29 million for the quarter and INR 553.13 million for the nine months ended 31 December 2025.</li><li>Mr. Pradeep Poddar resigned as Chairman and Independent Director, effective 31 March 2026.</li><li>Mr. Rahul Bhatnagar appointed as the new Chairman and Independent Director, effective 01 April 2026.</li><li>The company recognized an exceptional item of INR 4.53 million towards Gratuity provision.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/805a4175-6dcd-4d96-ba71-df8f02d0e9bb.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TASTY BITE EATABLES LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[EKANSH] Ekansh Concepts Ltd Board Meeting: Brijmohan Agarwal Appointed as Additional Director, Heeralal Agarwal and Ekta Gupta Resign</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Ekansh+Concepts+Ltd&title=Ekansh+Concepts+Ltd+Board+Meeting%3A+Brijmohan+Agarwal+Appointed+as+Additional+Director%2C+Heeralal+Agarwal+and+Ekta+Gupta+Resign&newsId=51e18d23-c439-475f-9197-36e98454b42e&token=NTFlMThkMjMtYzQz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">51e18d23-c439-475f-9197-36e98454b42e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>In a recent board meeting, Ekansh Concepts Ltd appointed Mr. Brijmohan Agarwal as an Additional Director (Non-Executive Independent) for a term of 5 consecutive years, effective from February 13, 2026. The meeting also saw the resignation of Mr. Heeralal Agarwal as Whole Time Director and Ms. Ekta Gupta as Independent Director, both with effect from closing business hours of February 13, 2026. The board also approved the reconstitution of Audit Committee, Nomination and Remuneration Committee and Stakeholders’ Relationship Committee.</p><ul><li>Brijmohan Agarwal appointed as Additional Director</li><li>Heeralal Agarwal and Ekta Gupta resign from their respective positions</li><li>Reconstitution of Audit Committee, Nomination and Remuneration Committee and Stakeholders’ Relationship Committee</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/b021bc8f-d147-47ec-a430-726673deb95d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Ekansh Concepts Ltd | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[IXIGO] IXIGO PTE. LTD., wholly owned subsidiary of Le Travenues Technology Limited, Approves Acquisitions in Spain</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Le+Travenues+Technology+Ltd&title=IXIGO+PTE.+LTD.%2C+wholly+owned+subsidiary+of+Le+Travenues+Technology+Limited%2C+Approves+Acquisitions+in+Spain&newsId=32610a57-69e1-4792-a008-d7b42e3cf20a&token=MzI2MTBhNTctNjll</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32610a57-69e1-4792-a008-d7b42e3cf20a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>IXIGO PTE. LTD., wholly owned subsidiary of Le Travenues Technology Limited, has approved the acquisition of 60% stake in Online Travel Solutions, S.L. (Trenes) for a total consideration of €11.70 million and 45.02% stake in Squad As Service, S.L. (Sqaas) for a total consideration of €0.45 million. Trenes is the second largest train OTA in Spain and Sqaas is an early stage technology and AI company. The acquisitions are expected to be completed by March 31, 2026, subject to regulatory approvals.</p><ul><li>Acquisition of 60% stake in Online Travel Solutions, S.L. (Trenes) for a total consideration of €11.70 million</li><li>Acquisition of 45.02% stake in Squad As Service, S.L. (Sqaas) for a total consideration of €0.45 million</li><li>Trenes is the second largest train OTA in Spain</li><li>Sqaas is an early stage technology and AI company</li><li>Expected completion date of the acquisitions is March 31, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7feba64e-382d-4cac-9a41-3c4314031eea.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Le Travenues Technology Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JUBLPHARMA] Jubilant Pharmova&apos;s Montreal Facility Receives USFDA&apos;s &apos;Official Action Indicated&apos; Classification</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jubilant+Pharmova+Ltd&title=Jubilant+Pharmova%27s+Montreal+Facility+Receives+USFDA%27s+%27Official+Action+Indicated%27+Classification&newsId=9afbc240-00c5-47b9-a18d-55a22612fb9f&token=OWFmYmMyNDAtMDBj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9afbc240-00c5-47b9-a18d-55a22612fb9f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 17:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>USFDA</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Jubilant Pharmova Limited announced that Jubilant HollisterStier General Partnership (JHSGP) has received an &apos;Official Action Indicated&apos; (OAI) classification from the United States Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) for its Contract manufacturing facility at Montreal, Canada. This classification is pursuant to the audit conducted in October and November 2025. JHSGP has been working closely with USFDA and has resumed production operations at the facility in Q4’FY26 after implementing robust remediation measures.</p><ul><li>Jubilant HollisterStier General Partnership (JHSGP) received an &apos;Official Action Indicated&apos; (OAI) classification from the USFDA for its Montreal facility.</li><li>The OAI classification is pursuant to the audit conducted in October and November 2025.</li><li>JHSGP has been working closely with USFDA and has resumed production operations at the facility in Q4’FY26.</li><li>JHSGP is a Canada based strategic alliance, jointly owned by subsidiaries of Jubilant Pharmova Limited.</li><li>The Montreal facility is a key contributor to the company’s global CDMO capabilities, offering contract manufacturing services for sterile products.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/c6ea51c9-a06c-426b-92fd-a1a06a8bc3a5.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jubilant Pharmova Ltd | Category: USFDA</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>