<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:55:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[SWOEF] Swojas Foods Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results on Feb 10, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SWOJAS+ENERGY+FOODS+LTD.&title=Swojas+Foods+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+on+Feb+10%2C+2026&newsId=5945eb7a-ac1d-42fd-97c4-aabd29889b03&token=NTk0NWViN2EtYWMx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5945eb7a-ac1d-42fd-97c4-aabd29889b03</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:51:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Swojas Foods Ltd has announced a board meeting on February 10, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited standalone financial results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in the securities of the company will open after 48 hours of the declaration of the financial results for all designated persons, their immediate relatives, and all connected persons covered under the company&apos;s code of conduct.</p><ul><li>Swojas Foods Ltd board meeting scheduled on February 10, 2026</li><li>Consideration and approval of un-audited standalone financial results for Q3 and nine months ended on December 31, 2025</li><li>Trading window to open after 48 hours of financial results declaration for designated persons, their immediate relatives, and connected persons</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e193a06f-2da7-4314-8eb2-e2edb1b5814b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SWOJAS ENERGY FOODS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LUPIN] Lupin and TB Alliance Collaborate to Advance Telacebec for Tuberculosis and Other Mycobacterial Diseases Treatment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LUPIN+LTD.&title=Lupin+and+TB+Alliance+Collaborate+to+Advance+Telacebec+for+Tuberculosis+and+Other+Mycobacterial+Diseases+Treatment&newsId=949467fe-acdc-438e-a604-b41599c1c805&token=OTQ5NDY3ZmUtYWNk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">949467fe-acdc-438e-a604-b41599c1c805</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Global pharma major Lupin Limited has joined forces with TB Alliance, a nonprofit drug developer, to advance the clinical development and commercialization of the investigational drug Telacebec (formerly known as Q203). The collaboration aims to provide advanced treatment options for patients affected by tuberculosis (TB), leprosy, and buruli ulcer. Lupin will contribute its manufacturing scale, global distribution capabilities, regulatory affairs expertise, and supply chain management to ensure global access to Telacebec. TB Alliance will continue to lead the development process.</p><ul><li>Lupin and TB Alliance collaborate to advance Telacebec for the treatment of tuberculosis, leprosy, and buruli ulcer.</li><li>Lupin to provide manufacturing, regulatory affairs, and supply chain expertise to ensure global access to Telacebec.</li><li>TB Alliance to continue leading the development process of Telacebec.</li><li>Telacebec represents scientific innovation with the potential to transform treatment for neglected diseases.</li><li>Collaboration combines deep scientific expertise with global Chemistry, Manufacturing and Controls and access capabilities.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/99059640-8707-44f7-9fd2-e5f5a81d7176.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LUPIN LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CIPLA] Cipla Ltd Appoints Mr Arun Kakatkar as Global Chief People Officer and Senior Management Personnel</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CIPLA+LTD.&title=Cipla+Ltd+Appoints+Mr+Arun+Kakatkar+as+Global+Chief+People+Officer+and+Senior+Management+Personnel&newsId=61e9979f-2425-453c-b718-d9e592e67f0b&token=NjFlOTk3OWYtMjQy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61e9979f-2425-453c-b718-d9e592e67f0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:42:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Management Change</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Cipla Ltd, a well-known pharmaceutical company, has announced the appointment of Mr Arun Kakatkar as the Global Chief People Officer and Senior Management Personnel. Mr Kakatkar, a seasoned business leader with extensive experience across multiple business functions, industries, and geographies, will take up his new role from 17th March, 2026. He has held senior leadership roles with various global organizations including Microsoft Corporation, Kalyani Group, and TE Connectivity India. Mr Kakatkar is passionate about building organizational and leadership capability, fostering strong culture, and enabling sustainable business outcomes.</p><ul><li>Cipla Ltd appoints Mr Arun Kakatkar as Global Chief People Officer and Senior Management Personnel</li><li>Mr Kakatkar has extensive experience across multiple business functions, industries, and geographies</li><li>He has held senior leadership roles with various global organizations</li><li>Mr Kakatkar is passionate about building organizational and leadership capability</li><li>He will take up his new role from 17th March, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/eaeeb83d-4c33-4cfd-bd06-d65886da1fd3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CIPLA LTD. | Category: Management Change</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HONDAPOWER] Honda India Power Products Ltd to Consider and Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 &amp; Nine Months of FY 2025-26 and Declare Interim Dividend</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Honda+India+Power+Products+Ltd&title=Honda+India+Power+Products+Ltd+to+Consider+and+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+%26+Nine+Months+of+FY+2025-26+and+Declare+Interim+Dividend&newsId=c871d552-1457-47f4-af4f-c4e1fc552d84&token=Yzg3MWQ1NTItMTQ1</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c871d552-1457-47f4-af4f-c4e1fc552d84</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:39:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Honda India Power Products Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 13, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The company may also declare an interim dividend on the equity shares. The record date for determining the members eligible to receive the interim dividend has been fixed as Thursday, February 19, 2026. Additionally, in compliance with the SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, the trading window will be closed from January 01, 2026, to February 15, 2026 (both days inclusive).</p><ul><li>Honda India Power Products Ltd to consider and approve unaudited financial results for Q3 &amp; Nine Months of FY 2025-26</li><li>The company may declare an interim dividend on the equity shares</li><li>The record date for determining the members eligible for interim dividend is February 19, 2026</li><li>Trading window to remain closed from January 01, 2026, to February 15, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/eb0c62e6-6a78-4cb0-9bf4-625e6f1204f3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Honda India Power Products Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SHALBY] Shalby Ltd to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Financial Results on Feb 11, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Shalby+Ltd&title=Shalby+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Financial+Results+on+Feb+11%2C+2026&newsId=0b63fd51-fb29-4a32-9798-87f73c072e2e&token=MGI2M2ZkNTEtZmIy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b63fd51-fb29-4a32-9798-87f73c072e2e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:38:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Shalby Ltd, a company listed on the BSE, has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 11, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited standalone and consolidated financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. In accordance with the Company&apos;s Code of Conduct for Prevention of Insider Trading and Fair Disclosure of Unpublished Price Sensitive Information, the trading window for dealing in securities of the Company for all designated persons and insiders has been closed from January 01, 2026, and will remain closed till 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results.</p><ul><li>Shalby Ltd to consider and approve unaudited financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>Trading window for dealing in securities of the Company for all designated persons and insiders is closed from January 01, 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/1ae5e44d-cb01-4f07-ad40-647959c7f2c3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Shalby Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KINGFA] Kingfa Science &amp; Technology (India) Ltd. to Approve Q3 and 9M Financial Results on Feb 7, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kingfa+Science+%26+Technology+%28India%29+Ltd-%24&title=Kingfa+Science+%26+Technology+%28India%29+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q3+and+9M+Financial+Results+on+Feb+7%2C+2026&newsId=ad5d5912-be2d-4f06-8a93-95c4a39497e5&token=YWQ1ZDU5MTItYmUy</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad5d5912-be2d-4f06-8a93-95c4a39497e5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:38:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Kingfa Science &amp; Technology (India) Ltd. has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 7, 2026, to consider and approve the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The meeting is in accordance with Regulation 29(1) of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations 2015. The trading window for all directors, key managerial personnel, designated employees, and other connected persons has been closed from January 1, 2026, and will reopen 48 hours after the announcement of the results.</p><ul><li>Kingfa Science &amp; Technology (India) Ltd. to approve Q3 and 9M financial results on Feb 7, 2026</li><li>Meeting scheduled in accordance with Regulation 29(1) of the SEBI (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations 2015</li><li>Trading window for all directors, key managerial personnel, designated employees, and other connected persons closed from Jan 1, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/22bf2526-eb15-4bad-8daf-c6081cd28873.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kingfa Science & Technology (India) Ltd-$ | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AUROPHARMA] Aurobindo Pharma: Trading Volume Surge Due to Market Forces, No Specific Company News</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=AUROBINDO+PHARMA+LTD.&title=Aurobindo+Pharma%3A+Trading+Volume+Surge+Due+to+Market+Forces%2C+No+Specific+Company+News&newsId=21794fce-104e-48e7-a00a-135baed9a9ba&token=MjE3OTRmY2UtMTA0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21794fce-104e-48e7-a00a-135baed9a9ba</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:38:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Aurobindo Pharma Ltd. has clarified a significant volume movement in its shares, stating that it&apos;s due to market forces and not any specific company-related news. The Government of India has imposed a Minimum Import Price (MIP) on Penicillin-G, 6-Aminopenicillanic Acid (6-APA), and Amoxicillin Trinydrate, impacting imports for domestic consumption. Aurobindo Pharma&apos;s subsidiary, Lyfius Pharma Private Limited, is engaged in the manufacturing of Penicillin-G and downstream derivatives. However, the company confirmed no other information or announcement that could affect its security&apos;s price or volume movement.</p><ul><li>Aurobindo Pharma clarifies volume movement of its shares</li><li>Market forces responsible for the surge in trading volume</li><li>Government of India imposes Minimum Import Price (MIP) on certain pharmaceutical products</li><li>Aurobindo Pharma&apos;s subsidiary involved in the manufacturing of affected products</li><li>No specific company-related information affecting security&apos;s price or volume</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/8edd237c-78a6-4aac-9e1f-23fd24bad405.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: AUROBINDO PHARMA LTD. | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GODREJPROP] Godrej Properties Sells Homes Worth INR 2,000 Crore at Godrej Trilogy Launch in Worli, Mumbai</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Godrej+Properties+Ltd&title=Godrej+Properties+Sells+Homes+Worth+INR+2%2C000+Crore+at+Godrej+Trilogy+Launch+in+Worli%2C+Mumbai&newsId=4ce7c0bc-097c-4ebc-a7aa-fb267fecf607&token=NGNlN2MwYmMtMDk3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4ce7c0bc-097c-4ebc-a7aa-fb267fecf607</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Godrej Properties Ltd. (GPL) announced that it has sold homes worth over INR 2,000 crore in Phase 1 of its project Godrej Trilogy, in Worli, South Mumbai. The project comprises of three towers, offering 3-bedroom and 4-bedroom residences with just three apartments per floor. Godrej Trilogy presents a distinctive trilogy of views, offering uninterrupted panoramas of the Arabian Sea, the Mumbai Skyline, and the historic Mahalaxmi Racecourse. The project is strategically located on Dr. Annie Besant Road, providing two-minute access to the Mumbai Coastal Road, as well as immediate proximity to the Bandra—Worli Sea Link and Metro Line 3.</p><ul><li>Godrej Properties sells homes worth over INR 2,000 crore at Godrej Trilogy in Worli, Mumbai</li><li>Project comprises of three towers with 3-bedroom and 4-bedroom residences</li><li>Offers uninterrupted panoramas of the Arabian Sea, the Mumbai Skyline, and the historic Mahalaxmi Racecourse</li><li>Strategically located on Dr. Annie Besant Road with easy access to Mumbai Coastal Road, Bandra—Worli Sea Link and Metro Line 3</li><li>Designed as an IGBC Platinum pre-certified project, reflecting a deep commitment to sustainable design and environmental stewardship</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/128811fb-0f8c-42f3-b941-ed4bc218ddec.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Godrej Properties Ltd | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NSL] Northern Spirits Ltd. to Approve Q3 and Nine Months Results on Feb 9, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Northern+Spirits+Ltd&title=Northern+Spirits+Ltd.+to+Approve+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Results+on+Feb+9%2C+2026&newsId=ac4cf925-15c8-4e4c-ac60-9c3b03673c13&token=YWM0Y2Y5MjUtMTVj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac4cf925-15c8-4e4c-ac60-9c3b03673c13</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Northern Spirits Ltd. has scheduled a Board of Directors meeting on February 9, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results for the Quarter and Nine Months ended 31° December, 2025. The meeting is pursuant to Regulation 29 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015. The company&apos;s trading window for dealing in the securities will remain closed for Designated Persons and their immediate relatives till February 11, 2026.</p><ul><li>Northern Spirits Ltd. to approve Q3 and nine months results on Feb 9, 2026</li><li>The results are for the quarter and nine months ended 31° December, 2025</li><li>Meeting is pursuant to Regulation 29 of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (Listing Obligations and Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015</li><li>Trading window for dealing in the securities will remain closed for Designated Persons and their immediate relatives till February 11, 2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/35c12196-f3a6-43d0-95f6-d19779577da1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Northern Spirits Ltd | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TORNTPHARM] Torrent Pharmaceuticals to Approve Audited Financial Results and Consider Interim Dividend Payment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TORRENT+PHARMACEUTICALS+LTD.&title=Torrent+Pharmaceuticals+to+Approve+Audited+Financial+Results+and+Consider+Interim+Dividend+Payment&newsId=7be09891-5bad-40d6-bc70-85faccd82936&token=N2JlMDk4OTEtNWJh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7be09891-5bad-40d6-bc70-85faccd82936</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Torrent Pharmaceuticals Ltd has announced a Board Meeting scheduled on 13th February 2026. The meeting will consider and approve the Audited Financial Results on a standalone basis and Unaudited Financial Results on a consolidated basis for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December 2025. The Board will also consider the payment of an Interim Dividend for the year 2025-2026.</p><ul><li>Torrent Pharmaceuticals Ltd has scheduled a Board Meeting on 13th February 2026</li><li>The meeting will consider and approve the Audited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended on 31st December 2025</li><li>The company will also consider the Unaudited Financial Results on a consolidated basis</li><li>The Board will discuss the payment of an Interim Dividend for the year 2025-2026</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/79379a8d-586a-4d64-954a-9bc2985041b2.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TORRENT PHARMACEUTICALS LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>