<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:53:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[STCORP] S &amp; T Corporation Ltd Announces Q3 FY 2025-26 Unaudited Financial Results with New Business Segment</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=S%26T+CORPORATION+LTD.&title=S+%26+T+Corporation+Ltd+Announces+Q3+FY+2025-26+Unaudited+Financial+Results+with+New+Business+Segment&newsId=b6e2cb7f-3934-4148-ac2c-1ab10e5e20f9&token=YjZlMmNiN2YtMzkz</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6e2cb7f-3934-4148-ac2c-1ab10e5e20f9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:53:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>S &amp; T Corporation Ltd has announced its unaudited financial results for the third quarter of FY 2025-26. The company has commenced operations in a new business segment relating to Trading of Textiles. The new segment is in the initial stage of operations. The segment information has been disclosed in accordance with the requirements of Ind AS 108 - Operating Segments. The financial results include the performance of this new segment from the date of commencement. The company&apos;s Board of Directors approved the unaudited financial results on Standalone operations and Consolidated Financial Statements along with its Subsidiary Ssavai Abodes LLP (95% stake). The review report was issued by the Statutory Auditor, M L R AND ASSOCIATES LLP.</p><ul><li>S &amp; T Corporation Ltd announced unaudited financial results for Q3 FY 2025-26</li><li>The company has commenced a new business segment relating to Trading of Textiles</li><li>New segment is in the initial stage of operations</li><li>Segment information disclosed as per Ind AS 108 - Operating Segments</li><li>Financial results include the performance of the new segment from the date of commencement</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2fd4ac22-956a-4fb1-b0ad-8722d0acec7b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: S&T CORPORATION LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CONFIPET] Confidence Petroleum India Ltd. Announces Extra-Ordinary General Meeting on February 27, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CONFIDENCE+PETROLEUM+INDIA+LTD.&title=Confidence+Petroleum+India+Ltd.+Announces+Extra-Ordinary+General+Meeting+on+February+27%2C+2026&newsId=090a2e46-69e5-4884-baeb-ecfc819e8281&token=MDkwYTJlNDYtNjll</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">090a2e46-69e5-4884-baeb-ecfc819e8281</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:53:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Board Meeting</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Confidence Petroleum India Ltd. has announced an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) to be held on February 27, 2026. The meeting will be conducted through Video Conferencing (VC) or Other Audio Visual Means (OAVM) due to the ongoing pandemic situation. The EGM will discuss and decide on several special businesses, including the appointment of Mrs. Nimisha Rohit Agrawal as a Non-Executive Independent Director, Mr. Prasad Manjarkhede as an Executive Director, and Mrs. Ketki Mahandra Save as a Non-Executive Non-Independent Additional Independent Director. The EGM will also provide an opportunity for members to cast their votes electronically on these matters.</p><ul><li>Extra-Ordinary General Meeting on February 27, 2026</li><li>Appointment of Mrs. Nimisha Rohit Agrawal as a Non-Executive Independent Director</li><li>Appointment of Mr. Prasad Manjarkhede as an Executive Director</li><li>Appointment of Mrs. Ketki Mahandra Save as a Non-Executive Non-Independent Additional Independent Director</li><li>Electronic voting facility for members</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4f160f98-46ad-41d7-8a8f-7f7fdba84c28.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CONFIDENCE PETROLEUM INDIA LTD. | Category: Board Meeting</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SANDESH] Sandesh Ltd: Board Approves Q3 &amp; 9M Financial Results for FY2025-26, Announces Changes in Senior Management</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=SANDESH+LTD.&title=Sandesh+Ltd%3A+Board+Approves+Q3+%26+9M+Financial+Results+for+FY2025-26%2C+Announces+Changes+in+Senior+Management&newsId=e0e9291c-8a04-4d92-a2ea-3e4dd72fc08d&token=ZTBlOTI5MWMtOGEw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0e9291c-8a04-4d92-a2ea-3e4dd72fc08d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:53:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Board of Directors of Sandesh Ltd, at its meeting held on February 05, 2026, approved and took on record the Standalone and Consolidated Unaudited Financial Results for the quarter and nine months ended on December 31, 2025. The company has also announced a change in Senior Management Personnel, with Mr. Prashant Kumar Nema ceasing to be the Senior Management Personnel and Mr. Giriraj Sharma being appointed as the new Senior Management Personnel.</p><ul><li>Board approved Standalone and Consolidated Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and 9M FY2025-26</li><li>Change in Senior Management Personnel: Mr. Prashant Kumar Nema ceased to be the Senior Management Personnel, Mr. Giriraj Sharma appointed as new Senior Management Personnel</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/04d9ee5e-3804-4e26-85ce-d1ac2937b25b.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: SANDESH LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JPTRLES] Jupiter Industries &amp; Leasing Ltd. Approves Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months Ended December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=JUPITER+INDUSTRIES+%26+LEASING+LTD.&title=Jupiter+Industries+%26+Leasing+Ltd.+Approves+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+Ended+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=81b7c585-7cfe-4e00-8983-dce2b5e91126&token=ODFiN2M1ODUtN2Nm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">81b7c585-7cfe-4e00-8983-dce2b5e91126</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:53:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jupiter Industries &amp; Leasing Ltd. announced its unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025, at its board meeting on February 5, 2026. The company reported a loss from operations before exceptional items of INR 8.15 crores. The financial results are subject to a limited review by the statutory auditors and have been prepared on a going concern basis, considering the infusion of funds for its operations.</p><ul><li>The Board of Directors considered and approved the unaudited financial results for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025.</li><li>The company reported a loss from operations before exceptional items of INR 8.15 crores.</li><li>The financial results are subject to a limited review by the statutory auditors and have been prepared on a going concern basis.</li><li>The company&apos;s ability to continue as a going concern is dependent upon the infusion of funds for its operations.</li><li>There is no business activity in the Company during the current financial year or in the preceding financial year.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/7a3bcf90-0696-4509-a72f-797b1d3d0bad.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: JUPITER INDUSTRIES & LEASING LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[GANGAPA] Ganga Papers India Ltd Reports Unaudited Financial Results for Quarter Ended December 31, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=GANGA+PAPERS+INDIA+LTD.&title=Ganga+Papers+India+Ltd+Reports+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Quarter+Ended+December+31%2C+2025&newsId=9210c521-76d0-40f0-bb79-862be0a21dcd&token=OTIxMGM1MjEtNzZk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9210c521-76d0-40f0-bb79-862be0a21dcd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ganga Papers India Ltd has reported its unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company&apos;s revenue from operations stands at Rs. 19,352.10 Lacs, with a profit before tax of Rs. 209.30 Lacs. The earnings per share (EPS) for the quarter is Rs. 5.02. The company&apos;s business activity falls within the primary business segment of Paper Manufacturing.</p><ul><li>Revenue from operations: Rs. 19,352.10 Lacs</li><li>Profit before tax: Rs. 209.30 Lacs</li><li>EPS for the quarter: Rs. 5.02</li><li>Business segment: Paper Manufacturing</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/49aac002-38f1-40ea-8ee8-240afa1a1859.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: GANGA PAPERS INDIA LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MINDACORP] Minda Corporation Ltd: No Deviation Observed in Monitoring Agency Report for Q3 FY2025-26</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Minda+Corporation+Ltd&title=Minda+Corporation+Ltd%3A+No+Deviation+Observed+in+Monitoring+Agency+Report+for+Q3+FY2025-26&newsId=0ac9b48d-92b1-47ac-8041-ccc121b88eb6&token=MGFjOWI0OGQtOTJi</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ac9b48d-92b1-47ac-8041-ccc121b88eb6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:52:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Monthly Update</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Acuité Ratings and Research Limited, the Monitoring Agency, has issued a report for Minda Corporation Limited for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The report states that there is no deviation observed in the utilization of issue proceeds. The company has not appointed any other Monitoring Agency and no Government/Statutory approval is required for the objects. The issuer has not observed any favorable or unfavorable events that may affect the viability of the objects.</p><ul><li>No deviation observed in the utilization of issue proceeds</li><li>No Government/Statutory approval required for the objects</li><li>No favorable or unfavorable events observed affecting the viability of the objects</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fc03c571-374c-427b-a346-22bfb486778d.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Minda Corporation Ltd | Category: Monthly Update</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[TRANSCOR] Transcorp Reports Strong Profit Growth of 49% in Q3 FY26, Receives RBI&apos;s In-Principle Approval for Centralised Payments Systems</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=TRANSCORP+INTERNATIONAL+LTD.&title=Transcorp+Reports+Strong+Profit+Growth+of+49%25+in+Q3+FY26%2C+Receives+RBI%27s+In-Principle+Approval+for+Centralised+Payments+Systems&newsId=a48c1f0b-2ef2-430e-8a30-e2ec9855e216&token=YTQ4YzFmMGItMmVm</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a48c1f0b-2ef2-430e-8a30-e2ec9855e216</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:52:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Transcorp International Limited announced its financial results for the quarter and nine months ended 31 December 2025, demonstrating strong profitability growth and lowest average debt utilisation. The Company has received RBI&apos;s in principle approval for Centralised Payments Systems, enabling it to initiate and settle RTGS and NEFT transactions. Financial performance highlights include a 49.4% increase in Profit Before Tax (Standalone) in Q3 FY26 over the immediately preceding quarter and a 299% year-on-year growth compared to the corresponding quarter of the previous year. The lowest finance costs in the Company’s history were incurred in Q3 FY26, contributing to higher profitability. Profit Before Tax (PBT) increased significantly to ¥386.54 Lakhs for the nine months ended 31 December 2025, registering a robust 67.3% growth. Transcorp has also fully repaid all public Fixed Deposits, further enhancing its liquidity position and balance sheet strength.</p><ul><li>Profit Before Tax (Standalone) in Q3 FY26 increased by 49.4% over the immediately preceding quarter and 299% year-on-year.</li><li>Q3 FY26 incurred the lowest interest/finance cost in the Company’s history.</li><li>Profit Before Tax (PBT) for the nine months ended 31 December 2025 increased by 67.3%.</li><li>Highest transaction volumes in digital payments were recorded for any given nine-month period.</li><li>Transcorp received in-principle approval from the RBI for participation in Centralized Payment Systems.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/50d95ee5-7594-4e3b-9780-d8ea9dd53159.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: TRANSCORP INTERNATIONAL LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[HIMATSEIDE] Himatsingka Seide Ltd to Approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and Nine Months of FY2026 on Feb 11</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=HIMATSINGKA+SEIDE+LTD.&title=Himatsingka+Seide+Ltd+to+Approve+Unaudited+Financial+Results+for+Q3+and+Nine+Months+of+FY2026+on+Feb+11&newsId=65ed7acb-2fcb-4b08-a0a4-a5627cdbf56d&token=NjVlZDdhY2ItMmZj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65ed7acb-2fcb-4b08-a0a4-a5627cdbf56d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:52:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Himatsingka Seide Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 11, 2026, to consider and approve the Unaudited Financial Results (Standalone and Consolidated) for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. The trading window for dealing in securities of the Company will remain closed until 48 hours after the declaration of the Unaudited Financial Results.</p><ul><li>Himatsingka Seide Ltd to approve Unaudited Financial Results for Q3 and nine months of FY2026 on Feb 11</li><li>The trading window for dealing in securities of the Company will remain closed until 48 hours after the declaration of the Unaudited Financial Results</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/cee84ae7-ecc8-41cf-9d49-757f5adb10d8.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: HIMATSINGKA SEIDE LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[VAGHANI] Emrock Corporation Ltd to Approve Q3 Results on Feb 12, 2026; Trading Window Closed</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=VAGHANI+TECHNO-BUILD+LTD.&title=Emrock+Corporation+Ltd+to+Approve+Q3+Results+on+Feb+12%2C+2026%3B+Trading+Window+Closed&newsId=d6e5bb5a-7a9f-46be-96cc-86eabcb8c46f&token=ZDZlNWJiNWEtN2E5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6e5bb5a-7a9f-46be-96cc-86eabcb8c46f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:52:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Quarterly Result</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Emrock Corporation Ltd has announced that its Board of Directors will meet on February 12, 2026, to consider and approve the un-audited standalone financial results for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025. The meeting will be held at the company&apos;s registered office in Ahmedabad, Gujarat. In compliance with the company&apos;s code of conduct on insider trading, the trading window has been closed from January 1, 2026, and will remain closed until 48 hours after the declaration of the financial results for the quarter ended on December 31, 2025.</p><ul><li>Emrock Corporation Ltd to approve Q3 results on Feb 12, 2026</li><li>Trading window closed from Jan 1, 2026, until 48 hours after Q3 result declaration</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/f32c1c60-59c1-491a-b3d6-c97fc3e0ca10.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: VAGHANI TECHNO-BUILD LTD. | Category: Quarterly Result</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LTIM] LTIMindtree Recognized as a Leader in Everest Group Payments IT Services PEAK Matrix® Assessment 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LTIMindtree+Ltd&title=LTIMindtree+Recognized+as+a+Leader+in+Everest+Group+Payments+IT+Services+PEAK+Matrix%C2%AE+Assessment+2025&newsId=69fba481-31d0-4f93-af73-37eb974e0057&token=NjlmYmE0ODEtMzFk</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69fba481-31d0-4f93-af73-37eb974e0057</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:52:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>LTIMindtree, a leading global technology consulting and digital solutions provider, has been positioned as a Leader in the Everest Group Payments IT Services PEAK Matrix® Assessment 2025. This recognition is for being a strategic transformation partner that combines modernization scale, platform alliances, and innovation across real-time, digital assets, and ensures secure, regulator-ready payment environments. The assessment comes at a time when enterprises are rapidly modernizing legacy payments platforms to support real-time, cross-border, and ISO 20022 compliant payment environments, while enhancing resiliency, interoperability, and regulatory compliance. LTIMindtree stands out for its product engineering expertise across major payment platforms like Finastra GPP/P2G, alongside leading credit card platforms and money transfer systems, backed by Centers of Excellence and global transformation programs. Everest Group also highlighted LTIMindtree’s strength in payment hub modernization, ISO 20022 migrations, scheme compliance, and Request-to-Pay implementations.</p><ul><li>LTIMindtree recognized as a Leader in Everest Group Payments IT Services PEAK Matrix® Assessment 2025</li><li>Strategic transformation partner combining modernization scale, platform alliances, and innovation</li><li>Expertise in product engineering across major payment platforms</li><li>Strength in payment hub modernization, ISO 20022 migrations, scheme compliance, and Request-to-Pay implementations</li><li>Focus on AI-powered modernization and early adoption of agentic AI across fraud prevention, rulebook automation, and payment operations</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/edf1ae59-8df6-4b51-b1e0-43b2679b23d1.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LTIMindtree Ltd | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>