<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stockwatch - Key Events</title>
    <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/</link>
    <description>Real-time corporate announcements, deals, and financial results.</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:49:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <atom:link href="https://api.stockwatch.live/api/keyEvents" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[NTPC] NTPC Ltd Completes Acquisition of 1350MW Coal-based Thermal Power Plant</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NTPC+LTD.&title=NTPC+Ltd+Completes+Acquisition+of+1350MW+Coal-based+Thermal+Power+Plant&newsId=d76fae91-1fa1-4681-8d95-59d70c19a7a0&token=ZDc2ZmFlOTEtMWZh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d76fae91-1fa1-4681-8d95-59d70c19a7a0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:37:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>NTPC Ltd, in collaboration with Maharashtra State Power Generation Company Limited (MAHAGENCO), has successfully completed the acquisition of Sinnar Thermal Power Limited (STPL). The acquisition was carried out in accordance with the Resolution Plan approved by the National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT) under the Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code 2016 (IBC). STPL owns a 1350MW coal-based thermal power plant located in Sinnar, Nashik, Maharashtra. This acquisition increases NTPC group&apos;s total installed capacity to 88,132 MW and commercial capacity to 87,052 MW.</p><ul><li>NTPC Ltd and MAHAGENCO complete acquisition of Sinnar Thermal Power Limited</li><li>Acquisition involves a 1350MW coal-based thermal power plant in Sinnar, Nashik, Maharashtra</li><li>Transaction completed in accordance with NCLT approved Resolution Plan under IBC 2016</li><li>NTPC group&apos;s total installed capacity now stands at 88,132 MW</li><li>Commercial capacity of NTPC group increased to 87,052 MW</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/e44e5ec4-3f59-4368-b1db-4f644c5815e0.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NTPC LTD. | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[CEATLTD] Ceat Ltd Achieves ESG Score of 69 in 2025 S&amp;P Global CSA</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=CEAT+LTD.&title=Ceat+Ltd+Achieves+ESG+Score+of+69+in+2025+S%26P+Global+CSA&newsId=d585a373-f70f-412a-818a-4ddd024d30fe&token=ZDU4NWEzNzMtZjcw</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d585a373-f70f-412a-818a-4ddd024d30fe</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:37:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Transmission of Shares</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Ceat Ltd has been assigned an ESG (Environmental, Social, and Governance) score of 69 in the 2025 S&amp;P Global Corporate Sustainability Assessment (CSA). This score is in accordance with the ESG Score requirements under Regulation 30 and 51 of SEBI (Listing Obligations &amp; Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015 and related rules, regulations, and SEBI Circulars.</p><ul><li>Ceat Ltd has been assigned an ESG score of 69 in the 2025 S&amp;P Global Corporate Sustainability Assessment (CSA)</li><li>The ESG score is part of the ESG Score requirements under Regulation 30 and 51 of SEBI (Listing Obligations &amp; Disclosure Requirements) Regulations, 2015 and related rules, regulations, and SEBI Circulars</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/ee4939c9-6c26-4b22-8532-22029e601af4.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: CEAT LTD. | Category: Transmission of Shares</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[NATCOPHARM] Natco Pharma to Launch Semaglutide in India in March 2026 with Eris Lifesciences</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=NATCO+PHARMA+LTD.&title=Natco+Pharma+to+Launch+Semaglutide+in+India+in+March+2026+with+Eris+Lifesciences&newsId=8e98bc53-91c9-480b-904c-8cfdf94be405&token=OGU5OGJjNTMtOTFj</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8e98bc53-91c9-480b-904c-8cfdf94be405</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:37:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Natco Pharma Ltd has received approval from the Central Drugs Standard Control Organisation (CDSCO) for Semaglutide in India. The company is working with different marketing partners to launch the product in the month of March 2026 in India. Natco Pharma has formed a partnership with Eris Lifesciences Ltd for the said product, which is in the ordinary course of business and has no material impact on the operations of the company. The company has been consistently making disclosures to the Stock Exchanges as required under Regulation 30 of the SEBI (LODR) Regulations, 2015 and continues to adhere to the said regulations.</p><ul><li>Natco Pharma has received approval from the CDSCO for Semaglutide in India</li><li>The company plans to launch Semaglutide in India in March 2026</li><li>Natco Pharma has partnered with Eris Lifesciences Ltd for the launch</li><li>The partnership is in the ordinary course of business and has no material impact on the company&apos;s operations</li><li>Natco Pharma has a history of making required disclosures to the Stock Exchanges</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/3c1ef757-0547-4dc7-af6b-164823c4135e.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: NATCO PHARMA LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[LT] L&amp;T Secures Major Orders for Power Transmission Infrastructure in India and Abroad</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=LARSEN+%26+TOUBRO+LTD.&title=L%26T+Secures+Major+Orders+for+Power+Transmission+Infrastructure+in+India+and+Abroad&newsId=ff4c352e-e94b-4698-86db-44d69a8c23b1&token=ZmY0YzM1MmUtZTk0</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff4c352e-e94b-4698-86db-44d69a8c23b1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Larsen &amp; Toubro Limited&apos;s Power Transmission &amp; Distribution (PT&amp;D) vertical has won a series of EPC orders for the establishment of electricity grid system elements in India and the Middle East. The Indian project involves the design, supply, and construction of two 220 kV Gas Insulated Substations in West Bengal, along with associated transmission line segments. The Middle Eastern projects include the turnkey construction of five substations and over 250 KM transmission lines, up to 500 kV level, in three different countries. These orders reflect the strong customer trust in L&amp;T for safe, flawless, sustainable, and timely creation of grid backbone.</p><ul><li>L&amp;T&apos;s PT&amp;D vertical secures EPC orders for electricity grid system elements in India and the Middle East.</li><li>Two 220 kV Gas Insulated Substations to be built in West Bengal&apos;s Durgapur-Raniganj-Asansol industrial belt.</li><li>Associated transmission line segments with advanced conductors and multi-circuit towers also included in the Indian project.</li><li>Five substations and over 250 KM transmission lines to be constructed in the Middle East, up to 500 kV level.</li><li>Orders reflect customer trust in L&amp;T for safe, flawless, sustainable, and timely creation of grid backbone.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/4ca2f330-a7a6-43ed-a48d-46b671ea3127.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: LARSEN & TOUBRO LTD. | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[KACL] Kaiser Corporation Ltd: Promoter Amav Enterprises Private Sells Shares Worth INR 96,99,182.04</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Kaiser+Corporation+Limited&title=Kaiser+Corporation+Ltd%3A+Promoter+Amav+Enterprises+Private+Sells+Shares+Worth+INR+96%2C99%2C182.04&newsId=0dff1a64-3b7b-4678-9e27-f84909fa56c4&token=MGRmZjFhNjQtM2I3</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0dff1a64-3b7b-4678-9e27-f84909fa56c4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 04:03:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Deals</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Pursuant to Regulation 7(2) of SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations, 2015, Kaiser Corporation Ltd. has received a disclosure from promoter Amav Enterprises Private regarding the sale of shares. The sale includes 22,84,772 shares worth INR 96,99,182.04 as of 24th February 2026.</p><ul><li>Promoter Amav Enterprises Private sold 22,84,772 shares of Kaiser Corporation Ltd.</li><li>The total value of the shares sold is INR 96,99,182.04.</li><li>The sale was disclosed on 24th February 2026.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2f53e588-f4db-4005-bbe4-f28c0bbe2cfe.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Kaiser Corporation Limited | Category: Deals</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[MINDSPACE] Mindspace REIT Pre-Leases c.5.3 Lakh Sq Ft in Hyderabad Campus to Chalet Hotels Ltd. for Luxury Hotel</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Mindspace+Business+Parks+REIT&title=Mindspace+REIT+Pre-Leases+c.5.3+Lakh+Sq+Ft+in+Hyderabad+Campus+to+Chalet+Hotels+Ltd.+for+Luxury+Hotel&newsId=af06d626-619a-4aaa-a8ed-87052f393659&token=YWYwNmQ2MjYtNjE5</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">af06d626-619a-4aaa-a8ed-87052f393659</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:22:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>New Launch</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Mindspace Business Parks REIT has pre-leased a building comprising ¢.5.3 lakh sq.ft. of leasable area at its Mindspace Madhapur campus in Hyderabad to Chalet Hotels Limited for a luxury hotel. The project involves an outlay of c.INR 350 Cr and is expected to be completed by Q4FY28. This will strengthen the Park’s integrated ecosystem and augment its premium positioning, attractiveness, and long-term competitiveness. The mixed-use development will comprise a ~ 330 key luxury hotel along with an ancillary commercial space. Mindspace Madhapur is Hyderabad’s largest Grade A integrated business campus, spanning over 13 million square feet of premium IT/ITeS office space, complemented by two Westin-branded hotels and the Inorbit Mall. The upcoming development will be the third on-campus hotel, aimed at deepening the integrated ‘work-stay-meet’ ecosystem and supporting business travel, client engagements and corporate events within the campus.</p><ul><li>Mindspace REIT pre-leases c.5.3 lakh sq.ft. of leasable area in Hyderabad campus to Chalet Hotels Limited for a luxury hotel.</li><li>The project involves an outlay of c.INR 350 Cr and is expected to be completed by Q4FY28.</li><li>The mixed-use development will comprise a ~ 330 key luxury hotel along with an ancillary commercial space.</li><li>Mindspace Madhapur is Hyderabad’s largest Grade A integrated business campus.</li><li>The upcoming development will be the third on-campus hotel, aimed at deepening the integrated ‘work-stay-meet’ ecosystem.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/5b910085-2d07-493b-a5ee-b27ca1b458f3.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Mindspace Business Parks REIT | Category: New Launch</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[ADANIPORTS] Adani Ports Announces Early Results of Cash Tender Offer for its Senior Notes</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=ADANI+PORTS+AND+SPECIAL+ECONOMIC+ZONE+LTD.&title=Adani+Ports+Announces+Early+Results+of+Cash+Tender+Offer+for+its+Senior+Notes&newsId=1613e6df-dda2-4487-8b37-073b1478eb04&token=MTYxM2U2ZGYtZGRh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1613e6df-dda2-4487-8b37-073b1478eb04</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:02:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Investment</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone Ltd has announced the early results of its tender offers to purchase for cash its outstanding 4.00% Senior Notes due 2027 and outstanding 3.10% Senior Notes due 2031. The early results indicate that US$101,584,000 worth of 4.0% Notes and US$95,360,000 worth of 3.10% Notes have been tendered. The early settlement date is expected to be on or about February 27, 2026.</p><ul><li>Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone Ltd has announced the early results of its tender offers for its Senior Notes.</li><li>The tender offers are for US$345,137,000 in aggregate principal amount of the outstanding 4.0% Senior Notes due 2027 and US$150,000,000 in aggregate principal amount of the outstanding 3.10% Senior Notes due 2031.</li><li>As of the early tender date, US$101,584,000 worth of 4.0% Notes and US$95,360,000 worth of 3.10% Notes have been tendered.</li><li>The early settlement date is expected to be on or about February 27, 2026.</li><li>The tender offers are subject to certain conditions and the satisfaction or waiver of such conditions.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/166449cc-feea-4d0f-8dd2-43d7d0d85122.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: ADANI PORTS AND SPECIAL ECONOMIC ZONE LTD. | Category: Investment</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[JONJUA] Jonjua Air Limited, Promoter Group, Sells Portion of Holding in Jonjua Overseas Limited</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Jonjua+Overseas+Ltd&title=Jonjua+Air+Limited%2C+Promoter+Group%2C+Sells+Portion+of+Holding+in+Jonjua+Overseas+Limited&newsId=3c938612-1a19-4d6a-81ac-d921ae518963&token=M2M5Mzg2MTItMWEx</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3c938612-1a19-4d6a-81ac-d921ae518963</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Acquisitions</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Jonjua Air Limited, a Promoter Group, has sold a portion of its holding in Jonjua Overseas Limited on 24/02/2026. The disclosure of this transaction is attached and is in compliance with Regulation 29 (2) of SEBI (SAST) Regulations, 2011, and other applicable rules and regulations. The sale details are as follows: Before the sale, Jonjua Air Limited held 12.16% of the total diluted share/voting capital of Jonjua Overseas Limited. Post-sale, their holding has reduced to 1.61%. The sale was conducted off-market. The equity share capital and total voting capital of Jonjua Overseas Limited remain unchanged at Rs. 10 each, with a total of 2,72,77,597 equity shares.</p><ul><li>Jonjua Air Limited, a Promoter Group, sold a portion of its holding in Jonjua Overseas Limited.</li><li>The sale was conducted on 24/02/2026.</li><li>The sale was conducted off-market.</li><li>Before the sale, Jonjua Air Limited held 12.16% of the total diluted share/voting capital of Jonjua Overseas Limited.</li><li>Post-sale, Jonjua Air Limited&apos;s holding has reduced to 1.61%.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/2209d768-189e-4502-b1fb-b7cfc8b18d12.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Jonjua Overseas Ltd | Category: Acquisitions</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[AXISCADES] AXISCADES Technologies Limited Signs Agreement with French Government for Space Situational Awareness Capability Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Axiscades+Technologies+Ltd&title=AXISCADES+Technologies+Limited+Signs+Agreement+with+French+Government+for+Space+Situational+Awareness+Capability+Enhancement&newsId=1b9c9241-84a8-444e-a8e9-7b67faf345db&token=MWI5YzkyNDEtODRh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b9c9241-84a8-444e-a8e9-7b67faf345db</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 02:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Joint Ventures</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>AXISCADES Technologies Limited, a leading end-to-end technology, product and solutions provider in the Aerospace, Defence and ESAI domains, has signed an agreement at the Embassy of France, New Delhi, in the presence of Ms. Eléonore Caroit, Minister Delegate to the Minister for Europe and Foreign Affairs, as a part of the delegation of HE Mr. Emmanuel Macron, President of the French Republic, to India. The agreement aims to enhance India’s capability in Space Situational Awareness. AXISCADES is headquartered in Bangalore with subsidiaries and offices worldwide, in France, Germany, Denmark, USA, and Canada, and has a diverse team of over 3000+ professionals. The company has deep domain experience in Weapon Systems, Avionics, Radar, Electronic Warfare, C4l2, Drones, Anti-Drone Systems, Test Solutions, GSE and GHE, and has executed several innovative in-house projects and partnered solutions for Land, Naval, Aerospace and Homeland Security. The comprehensive portfolio of solutions covers the complete product development lifecycle from concept evaluation to manufacturing support and certification. Certain statements in this communication may be ‘forward-looking statements’ and AXISCADES Technologies Ltd. will not be responsible for any action taken based on such statements.</p><ul><li>AXISCADES Technologies Limited signs agreement with French Government for Space Situational Awareness Capability Enhancement.</li><li>Agreement signed in the presence of Ms. Eléonore Caroit, Minister Delegate to the Minister for Europe and Foreign Affairs, as a part of the delegation of HE Mr. Emmanuel Macron, President of the French Republic, to India.</li><li>AXISCADES is a leading end-to-end technology, product and solutions provider in the Aerospace, Defence and ESAI domains.</li><li>Company has deep domain experience in Weapon Systems, Avionics, Radar, Electronic Warfare, C4l2, Drones, Anti-Drone Systems, Test Solutions, GSE and GHE.</li><li>AXISCADES has a diverse team of over 3000+ professionals and comprehensive portfolio of solutions covering the complete product development lifecycle.</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/fd81bcd9-f3a5-4e24-9383-1d243de81570.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Axiscades Technologies Ltd | Category: Joint Ventures</small>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[SUMUKAAG] Sumuka Agro Industries Fixes Record Date for Gujjubhai Foods Merger</title>
      <link>https://www.stockwatch.live/news?showModal=true&name=Sumuka+Agro+Industries+Ltd&title=Sumuka+Agro+Industries+Fixes+Record+Date+for+Gujjubhai+Foods+Merger&newsId=181d45db-1cac-4a62-8445-ab8b84299a11&token=MTgxZDQ1ZGItMWNh</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">181d45db-1cac-4a62-8445-ab8b84299a11</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 17:51:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Merger</category>
      <description><![CDATA[<strong>🔥 Trending</strong><br/><p>Sumuka Agro Industries Ltd. has fixed Monday, March 9, 2026, as the record date for determining the shareholders of Gujjubhai Foods Private Limited who shall be entitled to receive fully paid-up equity shares of Sumuka Agro Industries as per the share exchange ratio set out in the Scheme of Merger. This follows the sanction of the merger by the National Company Law Tribunal, Mumbai Bench. The share exchange ratio is 7 (Seven) fully paid up equity shares of Sumuka Agro Industries for every 4 (Four) fully paid equity shares held by the shareholders of Gujjubhai Foods.</p><ul><li>Sumuka Agro Industries has fixed March 9, 2026, as the record date for the merger with Gujjubhai Foods</li><li>The merger is based on a share exchange ratio of 7:4</li><li>The merger has been sanctioned by the National Company Law Tribunal, Mumbai Bench</li><li>The record date is set for determining the shareholders of Gujjubhai Foods who shall be entitled to receive Sumuka Agro Industries shares</li></ul><p>📄 <a href="https://www.bseindia.com/xml-data/corpfiling/AttachLive/83e1f9ee-d168-48b4-b98c-747d2c76caec.pdf">Read Official Filing (PDF)</a></p><br/><small>Company: Sumuka Agro Industries Ltd | Category: Merger</small>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>