<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:38:20 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Lenexis Foodworks launches ₹1456 Cr open offer for Restaurant Brands Asia</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Lenexis-Foodworks-launches-1456-Cr-open-offer-for-Restaurant-Brands-Asia/69836589f5a3f0ebac9b3dc2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Lenexis-Foodworks-launches-1456-Cr-open-offer-for-Restaurant-Brands-Asia/69836589f5a3f0ebac9b3dc2</guid><description>Lenexis Foodworks Private Limited and associates launched a ₹1456.43 crore open offer for up to 26% of Restaurant Brands Asia Limited at ₹70 per share. This move, part of underlying acquisition deals, aims to strengthen management and operations. The offer is subject to crucial CCI and SEBI approvals. Retail investors will have an exit window between March 17 and April 2, 2026. Specific financial guidance for Restaurant Brands Asia was not disclosed as part of this announcement.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:28:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IndiGo Cuts Wide-Body Flights Amidst Operational Strain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Cuts-Wide-Body-Flights-Amidst-Operational-Strain/69835617f5a3f0ebac9afd00</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Cuts-Wide-Body-Flights-Amidst-Operational-Strain/69835617f5a3f0ebac9afd00</guid><description>IndiGo has announced significant reductions in its long-haul network, including the suspension of Copenhagen flights and reduced frequencies to Manchester and London Heathrow. The airline attributes these immediate measures to escalating geopolitical airspace constraints and airport congestion, which have extended flight times and strained its wet-leased Boeing 787-9 operations. This strategic recalibration comes as IndiGo seeks to restore operational reliability for its wide-body services, initiated in March 2025.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:26:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69835617f5a3f0ebac9afcff_1770218795212.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CCL Products' Q3 PAT Surges 286% on Dividend, Declares ₹2.75 Interim Payout</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/CCL-Products-Q3-PAT-Surges-286percent-on-Dividend-Declares-275-Interim-Payout/69836511f5a3f0ebac9b3c5b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/CCL-Products-Q3-PAT-Surges-286percent-on-Dividend-Declares-275-Interim-Payout/69836511f5a3f0ebac9b3c5b</guid><description>CCL Products India Ltd. announced a significant Q3 FY26 surge in standalone net profit, up 286.5% YoY to ₹3,624.90 Lakhs, largely propelled by substantial dividend income from its Vietnamese subsidiary. Consolidated net profit rose 59.0% to ₹10,026.78 Lakhs. The company declared an interim dividend of ₹2.75 per share. Revenue grew robustly by 40.5% standalone and 38.5% consolidated.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:26:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Coal India Bets Big on Minerals, Chemicals Amid Energy Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Coal-India-Bets-Big-on-Minerals-Chemicals-Amid-Energy-Shift/698364bef5a3f0ebac9b3aef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Coal-India-Bets-Big-on-Minerals-Chemicals-Amid-Energy-Shift/698364bef5a3f0ebac9b3aef</guid><description>Coal India Limited (CIL) is embarking on a significant diversification strategy. The company will establish an intermediate holding company in Chile to explore critical minerals like lithium and copper, while also investing ₹3,189.54 crore in its subsidiary BCGCL for a coal-to-ammonium nitrate project in Odisha. These moves aim to secure future revenue streams and reduce reliance on its traditional coal operations in anticipation of evolving global energy demands.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:24:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>SEBI Eases Options OTR, Market Makers Get Relief</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Eases-Options-OTR-Market-Makers-Get-Relief/6983649ef5a3f0ebac9b3a26</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Eases-Options-OTR-Market-Makers-Get-Relief/6983649ef5a3f0ebac9b3a26</guid><description>SEBI is adjusting its order-to-trade ratio (OTR) framework effective April 6, 2026, excluding specific options premium bands and market maker orders from penalty calculations to foster liquidity. This move aims to reduce friction in derivatives trading, though broader market participants face increased transaction costs due to recent STT hikes in the Budget. The Indian derivatives market sees high retail participation, with over 90% experiencing losses, making the net impact of these regulatory shifts crucial.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:24:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Force Motors Profit Skyrockets 266% Driven by Government Incentives</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Force-Motors-Profit-Skyrockets-266percent-Driven-by-Government-Incentives/69836425f5a3f0ebac9b389d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Force-Motors-Profit-Skyrockets-266percent-Driven-by-Government-Incentives/69836425f5a3f0ebac9b389d</guid><description>Force Motors reported a stellar Q3 FY26, with standalone net profit surging 266.07% year-on-year to ₹40,286 Lakhs, primarily driven by ₹28,863 Lakhs in government incentives. Revenue climbed 12.65% to ₹2,12,843 Lakhs. Consolidated net profit also saw a significant leap of 252.23% to ₹40,615 Lakhs. However, the financial impact of new End-of-Life Vehicles Rules, effective April 1, 2025, remains undetermined.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:22:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Equities: Selective Recovery Ahead?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Equities-Selective-Recovery-Ahead/698363bff5a3f0ebac9b374c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Equities-Selective-Recovery-Ahead/698363bff5a3f0ebac9b374c</guid><description>Motilal Oswal Private Wealth advises a balanced approach for Indian equities in 2026, tilting towards large caps and hybrids. The firm anticipates earnings growth of 12-14%, driven by domestic policy support and normalizing macro concerns like elevated valuations and rupee depreciation. A recent India-US trade deal and stable interest rates are expected to catalyze a selective market recovery, potentially attracting foreign portfolio investors, though mid- and small-cap segments may present only tactical opportunities.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Rane (Madras) Q3 Profit Soars, But Valuation Concerns Linger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rane-Madras-Q3-Profit-Soars-But-Valuation-Concerns-Linger/698363adf5a3f0ebac9b36a3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rane-Madras-Q3-Profit-Soars-But-Valuation-Concerns-Linger/698363adf5a3f0ebac9b36a3</guid><description>Rane (Madras) Limited announced a significant surge in its third-quarter fiscal year 2026 net profit, reaching ₹31 crore, a dramatic increase from ₹0.4 crore in the prior year's period. Total revenue grew 21% to ₹1,019 crore, driven by strong domestic and international demand. Despite these robust operational results, the company's stock trades at a premium valuation, facing increased scrutiny amid underperformance relative to industry peers and a challenging auto component sector outlook.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:20:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Carborundum Universal: Standalone Surge Amidst Global Woes; FY26 Guidance Cut</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Carborundum-Universal-Standalone-Surge-Amidst-Global-Woes-FY26-Guidance-Cut/69836368f5a3f0ebac9b34cf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Carborundum-Universal-Standalone-Surge-Amidst-Global-Woes-FY26-Guidance-Cut/69836368f5a3f0ebac9b34cf</guid><description>Carborundum Universal reported a mixed Q3 FY'26. Standalone operations posted robust growth in revenue, PBIT, and PAT. However, consolidated performance faced significant headwinds from international subsidiaries including VAW (impacted by sanctions), Foskor, Rhodius, and Awuko, leading to a 23% YoY decline in consolidated PBIT. Consequently, the company revised down its FY'26 guidance for consolidated Ceramics sales growth and Abrasives PBIT margins, signaling near-term challenges despite strong domestic execution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:19:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Carborundum Cuts Guidance Amidst Overseas Woes, Standalone Shines</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Carborundum-Cuts-Guidance-Amidst-Overseas-Woes-Standalone-Shines/69836352f5a3f0ebac9b3442</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Carborundum-Cuts-Guidance-Amidst-Overseas-Woes-Standalone-Shines/69836352f5a3f0ebac9b3442</guid><description>Carborundum Universal reported a mixed Q3 FY'26, with robust standalone performance offset by challenges in overseas entities like VAW due to sanctions. Consolidated PBIT dropped 23% YoY. The company revised FY'26 guidance downwards for consolidated Ceramics sales growth and Abrasives PBIT margins, signaling headwinds despite a strong domestic order book and positive impacts from the EU FTA.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TCI Declares ₹9 Dividend, Boosts Consolidated PAT Despite Standalone Revenue Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/TCI-Declares-9-Dividend-Boosts-Consolidated-PAT-Despite-Standalone-Revenue-Dip/69836334f5a3f0ebac9b3358</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/TCI-Declares-9-Dividend-Boosts-Consolidated-PAT-Despite-Standalone-Revenue-Dip/69836334f5a3f0ebac9b3358</guid><description>Transport Corporation of India (TCI) declared a ₹9 interim dividend alongside its Q3 FY26 results. Consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) grew 12.0% YoY to ₹2,103 Cr, while standalone revenue declined 3.5% to ₹11,132 Cr. Standalone 9M PAT increased 12.0%, but EPS dipped 2.3% due to ESOP dilution. Mr. Rajendra Sharma was appointed CEO Designate – TCI Freight. The board also seeks shareholder approval for a ₹500 Cr related party transaction. Balance sheet and cash flow data were not disclosed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:18:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Apollo Tyres Q3 Profit Surges 39.5%, Declares ₹3.5 Dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Apollo-Tyres-Q3-Profit-Surges-395percent-Declares-35-Dividend/698362d2f5a3f0ebac9b3229</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Apollo-Tyres-Q3-Profit-Surges-395percent-Declares-35-Dividend/698362d2f5a3f0ebac9b3229</guid><description>Apollo Tyres posted a strong third quarter, with profit surging 39.5% to ₹471 crore and revenue growing 11.8% to ₹6,928 crore. The company also declared an interim dividend of ₹3.50 per share, setting February 10 as the record date. Operating income jumped 25.2% quarter-on-quarter.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:16:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Force Motors Q3 Profit Skyrockets 266% Driven by Incentives</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Force-Motors-Q3-Profit-Skyrockets-266percent-Driven-by-Incentives/698362b9f5a3f0ebac9b3165</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Force-Motors-Q3-Profit-Skyrockets-266percent-Driven-by-Incentives/698362b9f5a3f0ebac9b3165</guid><description>Force Motors reported a dramatic 266.1% YoY surge in standalone net profit for Q3 FY2026, reaching ₹40,286 Lakhs. This was primarily fueled by an exceptional income of ₹28,863 Lakhs from government incentives. While revenue grew 12.7% YoY, the company provided no future guidance and faces potential impacts from new environmental regulations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:16:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>SMIORE Q3 EBITDA Plunges 55% Despite Arjas Steel Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SMIORE-Q3-EBITDA-Plunges-55percent-Despite-Arjas-Steel-Boost/6983626ef5a3f0ebac9b3086</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SMIORE-Q3-EBITDA-Plunges-55percent-Despite-Arjas-Steel-Boost/6983626ef5a3f0ebac9b3086</guid><description>Sandur Manganese &amp; Iron Ores Limited (SMIORE) reported a sharp 55% year-on-year decline in consolidated EBITDA for Q3FY26, falling to ₹279 crore from ₹615 crore, with EBITDA margins contracting by 21.7 percentage points to 22.6%. Despite this, consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) saw a marginal 7.4% rise to ₹116 crore, partly due to an exceptional item. The nine-month period (9MFY26), however, shows robust 93% revenue growth to ₹3,632 crore, driven by the strategic acquisition of Arjas Steel Private Limited, though EBITDA margins contracted by 4.4 percentage points.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:14:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Asian Granito India Surges: Profit Turns Positive, Margins Expand Sharply in Q3 FY26</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Asian-Granito-India-Surges-Profit-Turns-Positive-Margins-Expand-Sharply-in-Q3-FY26/69836246f5a3f0ebac9b2f66</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Asian-Granito-India-Surges-Profit-Turns-Positive-Margins-Expand-Sharply-in-Q3-FY26/69836246f5a3f0ebac9b2f66</guid><description>Asian Granito India (AGL) reported a robust Q3 FY26, turning profitable with PAT at ₹18.49 crore versus a loss last year. Consolidated revenue climbed 15.8% YoY to ₹423.93 crore, while EBITDA surged 210% to ₹40.80 crore, with margins expanding dramatically by 603 bps to 9.62%. The company also expanded into Dubai, UK, and Senegal, with exports contributing 13% to quarterly revenue.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:14:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Avalon Technologies Surges 48.7% Revenue Amidst Margin Pressure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Avalon-Technologies-Surges-487percent-Revenue-Amidst-Margin-Pressure/698361b7f5a3f0ebac9b2da8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Avalon-Technologies-Surges-487percent-Revenue-Amidst-Margin-Pressure/698361b7f5a3f0ebac9b2da8</guid><description>Avalon Technologies reported a strong Q3 FY26 with revenue soaring 48.7% YoY to INR 418 Cr. However, margins faced pressure, with EBITDA down 84 bps and PAT down 58 bps YoY. The company maintains a robust INR 2,016 Cr order book and is poised to benefit from Electronic Manufacturing Services (EMS) sector tailwinds.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:11:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal to Spur Investment, Remove Uncertainty: Sebi Chief</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-to-Spur-Investment-Remove-Uncertainty-Sebi-Chief/6983618bf5a3f0ebac9b2cb0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-to-Spur-Investment-Remove-Uncertainty-Sebi-Chief/6983618bf5a3f0ebac9b2cb0</guid><description>Securities and Exchange Board of India Chairman Tuhin Kanta Pandey stated that the India-US trade deal will eliminate trade uncertainties and enhance investment prospects for India. He noted a positive turn in foreign portfolio investor (FPI) activity following the agreement, providing a counterpoint to recent outflows. Pandey also confirmed no immediate plans for further derivative market tightening and outlined Sebi's initiatives to develop the corporate bond market.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:11:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Avalon Technologies Posts Robust Q3 YoY Growth, PAT Jumps 44.7%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Avalon-Technologies-Posts-Robust-Q3-YoY-Growth-PAT-Jumps-447percent/6983616cf5a3f0ebac9b2c21</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Avalon-Technologies-Posts-Robust-Q3-YoY-Growth-PAT-Jumps-447percent/6983616cf5a3f0ebac9b2c21</guid><description>Avalon Technologies Limited reported strong year-on-year financial results for Q3 FY26. Standalone revenue grew 41.7% to ₹2,145.17 Mn, with Profit After Tax (PAT) soaring 44.7% to ₹238.33 Mn. The nine-month standalone PAT more than doubled YoY. Consolidated revenue also showed significant growth of 48.7% YoY. However, the company provided no forward-looking guidance, and detailed balance sheet or cash flow data was absent.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Transport Corp declares ₹9 dividend; Q3 standalone dips but consolidated shines</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Transport-Corp-declares-9-dividend-Q3-standalone-dips-but-consolidated-shines/698360d8f5a3f0ebac9b2a76</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Transport-Corp-declares-9-dividend-Q3-standalone-dips-but-consolidated-shines/698360d8f5a3f0ebac9b2a76</guid><description>Transport Corporation of India (TCI) announced its Q3 FY26 results, declaring a ₹9 interim dividend. While standalone revenue declined 3.53% YoY to ₹11,132 Cr and net profit fell 15.83% to ₹654 Cr, the consolidated picture was robust. Consolidated revenue rose 8.45% to ₹35,930 Cr and net profit surged 65.68% to ₹4,137 Cr. The company also approved material related-party transactions up to ₹500 Cr with Container Corporation of India (CONCOR).</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:08:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Quality Power Electrical Q3 Revenue Soars 292% on Acquisition, Expands Global Vision</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Quality-Power-Electrical-Q3-Revenue-Soars-292percent-on-Acquisition-Expands-Global-Vision/698352e3f5a3f0ebac9af0e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Quality-Power-Electrical-Q3-Revenue-Soars-292percent-on-Acquisition-Expands-Global-Vision/698352e3f5a3f0ebac9af0e1</guid><description>Quality Power Electrical Equipments Limited reported a stellar Q3 FY26, with consolidated revenue skyrocketing 292.4% year-on-year to ₹2,839.91 million, largely driven by the consolidation of Mehru Electrical &amp; Mechanical Engineers Private Limited. Standalone revenue also posted robust growth, increasing 60.9% YoY to ₹577.06 million. The company advanced its Sangli plant timeline, approved significant CAPEX for a global engineering centre, and is evaluating a new manufacturing facility in Turkey, signalling a strong push into European markets. An acquisition of a 50% stake in Sukrut Electric Company Private Limited was also executed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:08:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698352e3f5a3f0ebac9af0e0_1770217573044.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian IPOs Launch with Reduced Sizes Amidst Trade Deal Optimism</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Indian-IPOs-Launch-with-Reduced-Sizes-Amidst-Trade-Deal-Optimism/69836097f5a3f0ebac9b2936</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Indian-IPOs-Launch-with-Reduced-Sizes-Amidst-Trade-Deal-Optimism/69836097f5a3f0ebac9b2936</guid><description>Micro-loan provider Aye Finance and AI firm Fractal Analytics will launch their IPOs on February 9, albeit with significantly reduced issue sizes. Aye Finance's offering is now Rs 1,010 crore (down from Rs 1,450 crore), and Fractal Analytics' is Rs 2,834 crore (down from prior estimates). This recalibration reflects persistent valuation pressures and cautious investor sentiment, primarily from domestic institutions, even as a recent India-US trade deal bolsters overall market optimism and opens a brief IPO window.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:07:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Berger Paints Commissions New Automated Resin Plant in Hindupur</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Berger-Paints-Commissions-New-Automated-Resin-Plant-in-Hindupur/69836080f5a3f0ebac9b2883</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Berger-Paints-Commissions-New-Automated-Resin-Plant-in-Hindupur/69836080f5a3f0ebac9b2883</guid><description>Berger Paints India announced the start of commercial production at its new, fully automated resin manufacturing facility in Hindupur, Andhra Pradesh, effective February 4, 2026. The ₹78 crore plant boasts an annual capacity of 12,000 MT and is expected to significantly reduce production costs and enhance profit margins.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:06:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Apollo Tyres' ₹5810 Cr Capex Fuels Growth Ambition Post-Q3 Beat</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Apollo-Tyres-5810-Cr-Capex-Fuels-Growth-Ambition-Post-Q3-Beat/69835ffaf5a3f0ebac9b26d8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Apollo-Tyres-5810-Cr-Capex-Fuels-Growth-Ambition-Post-Q3-Beat/69835ffaf5a3f0ebac9b26d8</guid><description>Apollo Tyres reported a robust 39.6% year-on-year net profit increase to ₹470.5 crore in Q3 FY26, fueled by an 11.8% revenue growth to ₹7,743 crore. The company declared an interim dividend of ₹3.50 per share and unveiled a significant ₹5,810 crore capacity expansion for its Andhra Pradesh plant, aiming to substantially boost Passenger Car Radial (PCR) and Truck Bus Radial (TBR) tyre production by FY2029.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:04:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Reliance Bets Big on AI Infrastructure to Lead India's Digital Future</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Reliance-Bets-Big-on-AI-Infrastructure-to-Lead-Indias-Digital-Future/698352d2f5a3f0ebac9af092</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Reliance-Bets-Big-on-AI-Infrastructure-to-Lead-Indias-Digital-Future/698352d2f5a3f0ebac9af092</guid><description>Reliance Industries is aggressively building foundational AI infrastructure, partnering with global tech giants like NVIDIA to develop proprietary AI models and data centers. This strategic shift aims to capitalize on India's booming digital economy and establish a dominant position in the rapidly growing AI market. The company is leveraging extensive partnerships and a stable policy environment to attract significant capital, mirroring its successful strategy from 2020's digital asset funding, while BlackRock's CEO Larry Fink sees India entering its next growth era.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:04:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698352d2f5a3f0ebac9af091_1770217388530.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Novo Nordisk Faces Profit Paradox on Oral Wegovy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Novo-Nordisk-Faces-Profit-Paradox-on-Oral-Wegovy/69835f9bf5a3f0ebac9b2550</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Novo-Nordisk-Faces-Profit-Paradox-on-Oral-Wegovy/69835f9bf5a3f0ebac9b2550</guid><description>Novo Nordisk's stock crashed nearly 20%, wiping billions off its market cap after issuing a stark 2026 earnings downgrade. The company is grappling with the economic reality of its popular oral Wegovy drug. Despite patient appeal, the pill's vastly increased manufacturing costs and lower price point, combined with significant cannibalization of its high-margin injectable version, have compressed gross margins from an estimated 90% to around 35%. This creates a strategic dilemma where growth in oral drug sales actively erodes overall profitability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:02:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Marico Buys 60% of Cosmix Wellness for ₹375 Cr to Bolster Digital Health</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Marico-Buys-60percent-of-Cosmix-Wellness-for-375-Cr-to-Bolster-Digital-Health/69835f77f5a3f0ebac9b2494</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Marico-Buys-60percent-of-Cosmix-Wellness-for-375-Cr-to-Bolster-Digital-Health/69835f77f5a3f0ebac9b2494</guid><description>Marico Ltd. is acquiring a 60% stake in Cosmix Wellness Private Ltd. for approximately ₹375 crore, valuing the digital-first functional wellness brand at ₹375 crore. Cosmix, boasting an annual revenue run rate of ₹100 crore and high-teen EBITDA margins, specializes in plant-based nutrition. This move significantly enhances Marico's digital-first portfolio, aligning with the strong consumer demand for wellness and plant-based products in India.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:02:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ambani, Fink Ignite 'Era of India' Investment Drive: Shift from Savers to Shareholders</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Ambani-Fink-Ignite-Era-of-India-Investment-Drive-Shift-from-Savers-to-Shareholders/69835f0ff5a3f0ebac9b2337</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Ambani-Fink-Ignite-Era-of-India-Investment-Drive-Shift-from-Savers-to-Shareholders/69835f0ff5a3f0ebac9b2337</guid><description>Reliance Industries Chairman Mukesh Ambani and BlackRock Chairman Larry Fink have declared India's entry into a new investment era. They urged Indian households to transition from passive savers to active investors, leveraging the nation's robust economic growth and technological advancements. This shift aims to unlock personal wealth and reduce foreign capital dependency, capitalizing on a 'once in tens of centuries opportunity'.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:00:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ashika Credit Capital PAT Soars on Fair Value Gains; Q3 Turns Loss</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Ashika-Credit-Capital-PAT-Soars-on-Fair-Value-Gains-Q3-Turns-Loss/69835ef7f5a3f0ebac9b22ca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Ashika-Credit-Capital-PAT-Soars-on-Fair-Value-Gains-Q3-Turns-Loss/69835ef7f5a3f0ebac9b22ca</guid><description>Ashika Credit Capital Limited has reported a significant turnaround in its nine-month performance ending December 31, 2025, with consolidated PAT surging to ₹6,440.74 Lakhs from a loss last year. This was primarily fueled by a ₹7,899.76 Lakhs net gain on fair value changes. However, the latest quarter (Q3 FY26) saw a sharp sequential decline, with consolidated PAT falling to a loss of ₹30.91 Lakhs from a profit of ₹1,249.20 Lakhs in Q2 FY26. Financial figures were restated due to amalgamation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Spright Agro Posts Massive Q3 Loss Amidst 91.7% Revenue Plunge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Spright-Agro-Posts-Massive-Q3-Loss-Amidst-917percent-Revenue-Plunge/69835eb5f5a3f0ebac9b2160</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Spright-Agro-Posts-Massive-Q3-Loss-Amidst-917percent-Revenue-Plunge/69835eb5f5a3f0ebac9b2160</guid><description>Spright Agro Limited (formerly Tine Agro Limited) has reported a grim Q3 FY26 performance, with revenue from operations plummeting 91.7% year-on-year to ₹455.73 lacs. The company swung to a net loss of ₹1,034.90 lacs from a profit of ₹708.88 lacs in the prior year's quarter. Basic EPS fell to ₹(0.10) from ₹0.07. For the nine months, revenue declined 34.1% and the company posted a net loss. A critical observation by the statutory auditors noted pending verification of trade receivables, payables, and advances.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 14:59:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Avalon Technologies Posts Robust Q3 Growth, Revenue Soars 48% YoY</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Avalon-Technologies-Posts-Robust-Q3-Growth-Revenue-Soars-48percent-YoY/69835e6ff5a3f0ebac9b2078</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Avalon-Technologies-Posts-Robust-Q3-Growth-Revenue-Soars-48percent-YoY/69835e6ff5a3f0ebac9b2078</guid><description>Avalon Technologies Limited announced its Q3 FY26 results, showcasing impressive year-on-year growth across standalone and consolidated financials. Standalone revenue surged 41.7% YoY to ₹2,145.17M, while consolidated revenue jumped 48.6% YoY to ₹4,175.42M. Consolidated PAT rose 35.9% YoY to ₹326.02M. However, standalone PAT saw a marginal 3.8% dip QoQ. The company provided no future guidance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 14:57:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Midwest's Green Pivot Faces Valuation Scrutiny Amidst Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Midwests-Green-Pivot-Faces-Valuation-Scrutiny-Amidst-Expansion/69835e31f5a3f0ebac9b1f90</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Midwests-Green-Pivot-Faces-Valuation-Scrutiny-Amidst-Expansion/69835e31f5a3f0ebac9b1f90</guid><description>Midwest Ltd, a dominant granite producer, is aggressively pivoting into high-growth sectors like quartz and rare earth elements (REEs) to fuel India's electric vehicle (EV) and solar ambitions. The company aims for 2.5x revenue growth and 3x profitability increase within four years, targeting a 35% ROCE. However, its current market valuation, trading at a P/E multiple of approximately 40-56x, appears ambitious given recent ROCE figures hovering around 20-21% and increasing capital expenditure for diversification. While macro tailwinds support critical mineral demand, execution risk and reliance on niche deposits present significant investor considerations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 14:56:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>LeafyBus, Eicher Ink Deal for 100 Electric Sleeper Buses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/LeafyBus-Eicher-Ink-Deal-for-100-Electric-Sleeper-Buses/6983517cf5a3f0ebac9aebb2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/LeafyBus-Eicher-Ink-Deal-for-100-Electric-Sleeper-Buses/6983517cf5a3f0ebac9aebb2</guid><description>LeafyBus, India's first long-distance electric bus operator, has partnered with Eicher Trucks &amp; Buses to deploy 100 electric intercity sleeper buses. The initial phase will see 35 buses operational by March 31, 2026, marking a significant move into the EV segment for intercity travel. The collaboration aims to accelerate cleaner mobility by making EV travel commercially viable and accessible.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 14:56:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983517cf5a3f0ebac9aebb1_1770216988542.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lloyds Engineering Q3 PAT Soars 193% on Acquisitions, Order Book Robust</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Lloyds-Engineering-Q3-PAT-Soars-193percent-on-Acquisitions-Order-Book-Robust/69835e0af5a3f0ebac9b1eac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Lloyds-Engineering-Q3-PAT-Soars-193percent-on-Acquisitions-Order-Book-Robust/69835e0af5a3f0ebac9b1eac</guid><description>Lloyds Engineering Works has reported a significant surge in its consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) for the third quarter of FY26, growing by an impressive 193% year-on-year to ₹61.03 Crore. Consolidated revenue rose 31% to ₹316.66 Crore. The company's order book stands strong at ₹2,011.22 Crore (consolidated), bolstered by approved acquisitions and a proposed merger scheme. These strategic moves, including acquiring stakes in Metalfab Hightech and Techno Industries, are set to enhance its capabilities and market presence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 14:56:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lloyds Engineering Works Charts Aggressive Growth Post-Merger, Secures Mega Steel Order</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Lloyds-Engineering-Works-Charts-Aggressive-Growth-Post-Merger-Secures-Mega-Steel-Order/69835d5bf5a3f0ebac9b1d15</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Lloyds-Engineering-Works-Charts-Aggressive-Growth-Post-Merger-Secures-Mega-Steel-Order/69835d5bf5a3f0ebac9b1d15</guid><description>Lloyds Engineering Works (LEWL) announced robust consolidated results for Q3 and 9MFY26, with revenue up 2.34% and EBITDA soaring 44.39% QoQ. The company is set to merge with associate LICL, creating a vertically integrated platform, and secured a significant ₹613 Cr order from SAIL. Management targets over ₹3,000 Cr revenue for FY26, a fourfold increase, driven by organic expansion, acquisitions, and consolidation, despite a dip in standalone Q3 performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 14:53:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>ABDL's Q3 Profit Surges 11%, Eyes 18% EBITDA Margin Goal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ABDLs-Q3-Profit-Surges-11percent-Eyes-18percent-EBITDA-Margin-Goal/69835d46f5a3f0ebac9b1c48</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ABDLs-Q3-Profit-Surges-11percent-Eyes-18percent-EBITDA-Margin-Goal/69835d46f5a3f0ebac9b1c48</guid><description>Allied Blenders and Distillers (ABDL) reported a solid Q3 FY26, with revenue up 2.8% YoY to ₹1,004 crore and PAT surging 10.9% to ₹64 crore. EBITDA grew 14.1% YoY to ₹137 crore, reflecting improved margins. The company raised its FY28 EBITDA margin guidance to 18% driven by premiumization and backward integration, while net debt reduced QoQ.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 14:52:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lloyds Engineering Surges on Consolidated Growth, Eyes 4x Revenue Jump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Lloyds-Engineering-Surges-on-Consolidated-Growth-Eyes-4x-Revenue-Jump/69835d1cf5a3f0ebac9b1b7a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Lloyds-Engineering-Surges-on-Consolidated-Growth-Eyes-4x-Revenue-Jump/69835d1cf5a3f0ebac9b1b7a</guid><description>Lloyds Engineering Works Limited (LEWL) reported a stark divergence in Q3FY26 results, with consolidated PAT soaring 83.65% YoY to ₹66.70 Cr on a 2.34% revenue increase, driven by margin expansion and subsidiaries. However, standalone PAT declined 15.29% YoY to ₹28.53 Cr. The company boasts a consolidated order book of ₹6,630 Cr and aims for 4x revenue growth in FY26, bolstered by technology tie-ups, acquisitions, and a major ₹613 Cr SAIL order.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 14:52:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sambhv Steel Tubes Hits Record Revenue, Eyes Expansion Amidst Market Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sambhv-Steel-Tubes-Hits-Record-Revenue-Eyes-Expansion-Amidst-Market-Gains/69835082f5a3f0ebac9ae89d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sambhv-Steel-Tubes-Hits-Record-Revenue-Eyes-Expansion-Amidst-Market-Gains/69835082f5a3f0ebac9ae89d</guid><description>Sambhv Steel Tubes Limited posted its best-ever 9-month performance for FY'26, with revenue surging 70% YoY to INR 1,728 crore and EBITDA up 73% to INR 184 crore. Q3 FY'26 saw revenue climb 60% YoY to INR 589 crore. The company announced aggressive capacity expansions, including a new greenfield project and doubling stainless steel CR capacity, alongside exploring entry into seamless pipes. PLI scheme 2.0 approval further bolsters its strategic growth plans.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 14:52:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69835082f5a3f0ebac9ae89c_1770216701074.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Quality Power Electrical Surges 291% on Consolidation, Eyes Global Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Quality-Power-Electrical-Surges-291percent-on-Consolidation-Eyes-Global-Expansion/69835cbaf5a3f0ebac9b19fe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Quality-Power-Electrical-Surges-291percent-on-Consolidation-Eyes-Global-Expansion/69835cbaf5a3f0ebac9b19fe</guid><description>Quality Power Electrical Equipments Limited announced stellar Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated revenue soaring 291% YoY to ₹2,840 million, driven by subsidiary integration. Standalone revenue also climbed 61% YoY. The company advanced expansion projects, approved CAPEX for a new tech centre, and appointed a new CEO, signalling a strong growth trajectory and global market ambitions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 14:50:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TruAlt Bioenergy Revenue Surges 70%, But Margins Dip Amidst Ethanol Ramp-Up</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/TruAlt-Bioenergy-Revenue-Surges-70percent-But-Margins-Dip-Amidst-Ethanol-Ramp-Up/69835ca6f5a3f0ebac9b1982</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/TruAlt-Bioenergy-Revenue-Surges-70percent-But-Margins-Dip-Amidst-Ethanol-Ramp-Up/69835ca6f5a3f0ebac9b1982</guid><description>TruAlt Bioenergy posted a robust Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue soaring 70.20% YoY to ₹720.72 crore, driven by ethanol segment consolidation and plant commissioning. However, EBITDA margins compressed significantly to 18.36% from 29.23% YoY, leading to an 8.79% decline in consolidated PAT to ₹66.02 crore. Management cites transitional operating factors for the PAT dip. The company is advancing its CBG and SAF segments, eyeing expansion through joint ventures.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 14:50:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Medanta Q3 PAT Dives 33% Amid Noida Launch, Expansion Spree</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Medanta-Q3-PAT-Dives-33percent-Amid-Noida-Launch-Expansion-Spree/6983506ff5a3f0ebac9ae7e2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Medanta-Q3-PAT-Dives-33percent-Amid-Noida-Launch-Expansion-Spree/6983506ff5a3f0ebac9ae7e2</guid><description>Global Health (Medanta) reported a 19.1% YoY revenue jump to INR 11,428 million in Q3 FY26. However, reported PAT plunged 33.5% to INR 950 million, hit by the Noida facility's initial costs and a INR 366 million exceptional charge. Excluding Noida, EBITDA rose 10.9%. The company unveiled ambitious expansion plans, including new hospitals in Delhi, Mumbai, and Guwahati, backed by over INR 39,013 million in future Capex.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 14:50:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983506ff5a3f0ebac9ae7e1_1770216540777.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>