<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:48:13 +0000</pubDate><item><title>MatX Secures $500M to Challenge Nvidia with Ambitious AI Chip Claims</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MatX-Secures-500M-to-Challenge-Nvidia-with-Ambitious-AI-Chip-Claims/699e4f4804a25a58c8537946</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MatX-Secures-500M-to-Challenge-Nvidia-with-Ambitious-AI-Chip-Claims/699e4f4804a25a58c8537946</guid><description>MatX, a startup featuring former Google TPU engineers, has secured $500 million in Series B funding, co-led by Jane Street and Leopold Aschenbrenner's Situational Awareness fund. The company aims to deliver AI processors ten times more effective than Nvidia's GPUs for LLM training and inference by 2027. This infusion of capital underscores significant investor confidence in specialized AI hardware, though MatX faces a formidable challenge against incumbents and a crowded startup ecosystem. The funding follows a $100 million Series A, which valued the company at over $300 million.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:24:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e4f4804a25a58c8537945_1771982956609.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Biocon Q3 FY26 Profit Surges 475% on Integration Push; Revenue Up 11%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Biocon-Q3-FY26-Profit-Surges-475percent-on-Integration-Push-Revenue-Up-11percent/699e4d1c04a25a58c85377b9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Biocon-Q3-FY26-Profit-Surges-475percent-on-Integration-Push-Revenue-Up-11percent/699e4d1c04a25a58c85377b9</guid><description>Biocon reported a robust Q3 FY26, with reported net profit soaring 475% year-on-year to ₹144 crore on an 11% rise in total revenue to ₹4,290 crore. The company is actively integrating Biocon Biologics as a wholly-owned subsidiary, a move aimed at simplifying its structure and unlocking synergies. Growth was led by strong performances in its Generics and Biosimilars segments, though the CRDMO segment saw a revenue dip.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:15:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e4d1c04a25a58c85377b8_1771983193597.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Oil Prices Surge on Geopolitics, Fundamentals Lag</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Oil-Prices-Surge-on-Geopolitics-Fundamentals-Lag/699e4c6904a25a58c85376ef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Oil-Prices-Surge-on-Geopolitics-Fundamentals-Lag/699e4c6904a25a58c85376ef</guid><description>Geopolitical tensions surrounding US-Iran nuclear talks and significant military deployments have propelled oil prices to six-month peaks. Brent crude hovers near $71 and WTI around $66 per barrel. However, this rally appears increasingly disconnected from underlying fundamentals, with analysts forecasting a substantial supply surplus for 2026. The market's focus on the Strait of Hormuz chokepoint risk may be overpricing potential disruptions, masking growing inventory levels and bearish EIA price targets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:12:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e4c6904a25a58c85376ee_1771983677165.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Capex Rally Faces Reality: Execution Woes Plague Smaller EPC Players</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Capex-Rally-Faces-Reality-Execution-Woes-Plague-Smaller-EPC-Players/699e4a3304a25a58c8537419</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Capex-Rally-Faces-Reality-Execution-Woes-Plague-Smaller-EPC-Players/699e4a3304a25a58c8537419</guid><description>India's capital expenditure sector, energized by a 9% budget allocation hike to ₹12.2 lakh crore for FY27, is seeing investors look beyond large players like L&amp;T and ABB India towards smaller EPC firms. However, these smaller companies face significant headwinds. The December 2025 quarter highlighted project implementation delays and land acquisition issues, compounded by rising input costs for cement and steel, which are compressing operating margins. While order books remain robust, the ability to execute these projects efficiently amidst these challenges is a critical concern for investors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:02:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e4a3304a25a58c8537418_1771983443450.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dhawan's Contrarian Bets: Bluspring &amp; AGI - Value Trap or Rebound?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dhawans-Contrarian-Bets-Bluspring-and-AGI-Value-Trap-or-Rebound/699e49e204a25a58c85373ae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dhawans-Contrarian-Bets-Bluspring-and-AGI-Value-Trap-or-Rebound/699e49e204a25a58c85373ae</guid><description>Veteran investor Ashish Dhawan is doubling down on infrastructure services firm Bluspring Enterprises and packaging solutions provider AGI Greenpac, significantly increasing his stake in both. While Bluspring grapples with consistent net losses despite revenue growth, AGI Greenpac faces regulatory hurdles after a Supreme Court ruling, despite strong operational metrics. This aggressive accumulation signals a high-conviction play against prevailing market skepticism, raising questions about whether these are deep-value opportunities or potential value traps.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:01:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e49e204a25a58c85373ad_1771981849070.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>WTO Faces Geopolitical Reckoning on Industrial Policy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/WTO-Faces-Geopolitical-Reckoning-on-Industrial-Policy/699e49d104a25a58c853738a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/WTO-Faces-Geopolitical-Reckoning-on-Industrial-Policy/699e49d104a25a58c853738a</guid><description>The upcoming 14th WTO Ministerial Conference (MC-14) will confront escalating global industrial policy interventions, export controls, and subsidy disputes, highlighted by China's challenges to India's manufacturing incentives. This battleground reflects a broader geopolitical shift where national security and supply chain resilience supersede traditional trade liberalization, challenging the WTO's foundational principles and capacity to mediate.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 01:01:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e49d104a25a58c8537389_1771981413747.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Ambition: Incentive Maze Risks Stifling True Innovation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-Incentive-Maze-Risks-Stifling-True-Innovation/699e496804a25a58c85372a1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-Incentive-Maze-Risks-Stifling-True-Innovation/699e496804a25a58c85372a1</guid><description>Recent revelations from the India AI Impact Summit 2026 highlight a critical disconnect: a surge in patent filings, particularly from private universities, is driven by reimbursement and ranking incentives rather than demonstrable innovation or commercial success. This 'innovation theater' risks undermining India's ambition to be an AI powerhouse, as low patent grant rates and limited market translation contrast sharply with global benchmarks and the nation's growing talent pool and investment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 00:59:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e496804a25a58c85372a0_1771982719299.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Banks' NIM Squeeze Deepens as Deposit Flight Fuels Costly Funding</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banks-NIM-Squeeze-Deepens-as-Deposit-Flight-Fuels-Costly-Funding/699e495b04a25a58c8537282</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banks-NIM-Squeeze-Deepens-as-Deposit-Flight-Fuels-Costly-Funding/699e495b04a25a58c8537282</guid><description>Indian banks are grappling with a significant squeeze on Net Interest Margins (NIMs) as a structural shift sees low-cost retail deposits migrate to alternative investments. This outflow compels banks to seek expensive wholesale funding, widening the gap between asset yields and liability costs. Compounding this are permanent liquidity leaks from tax payments, physical cash withdrawals, and RBI currency mop-ups. Banks must urgently recalibrate business models beyond reactive rate hikes to manage heightened funding costs and structural liquidity mismatches.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 00:59:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e495b04a25a58c8537281_1771981612877.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jonjua Overseas: Promoter entity sells 2.98% stake via off-market trade</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jonjua-Overseas-Promoter-entity-sells-298percent-stake-via-off-market-trade/699e434104a25a58c8536e2b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jonjua-Overseas-Promoter-entity-sells-298percent-stake-via-off-market-trade/699e434104a25a58c8536e2b</guid><description>Jonjua Air Limited, a promoter group entity of Jonjua Overseas Limited, has divested 4.43 lakh shares, representing 2.98% of the total equity. The off-market transaction on February 24, 2026, reduces Jonjua Air's stake to 9.18%. This follows a previous stake sale by the same entity in early January.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 00:33:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e434104a25a58c8536e2a_1771983721706.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coal India Prioritizes Stability in Coal Exchange Reform</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Coal-India-Prioritizes-Stability-in-Coal-Exchange-Reform/699e3da604a25a58c85369fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Coal-India-Prioritizes-Stability-in-Coal-Exchange-Reform/699e3da604a25a58c85369fb</guid><description>Coal India Limited is advocating for a phased introduction of the proposed coal exchange mechanism, prioritizing stability in electricity tariffs and national energy security. The company, while aligning with reformist agendas, stresses the need for calibrated implementation to protect long-term power assets from excessive market volatility. Executive Director V.S. Maharaj articulated this position at the Indian Coal Markets Conference, noting that modernization must be carefully managed. Mjunction Services Limited, a joint venture between Tata Steel and SAIL, has expressed strong interest in developing India's coal exchange, leveraging two decades of experience in coal auctions. The coal ministry has initiated public consultation on draft rules for the coal exchange, following amendments to the Mines and Minerals (Development and Regulation) Act.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 00:09:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e3da604a25a58c85369fa_1771979362379.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TANFAC EGM Approves ₹500Cr Fundraise, Share Sub-division</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/TANFAC-EGM-Approves-500Cr-Fundraise-Share-Sub-division/699e3cb504a25a58c85368cd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/TANFAC-EGM-Approves-500Cr-Fundraise-Share-Sub-division/699e3cb504a25a58c85368cd</guid><description>TANFAC Industries' Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) on February 23, 2026, saw shareholders approve a significant ₹500 crore equity fundraising plan and the sub-division of equity shares. The meeting also sanctioned leadership changes, appointing Mr. Afzal Harunbhai Malkani as Managing Director and Mrs. Sandhya Venugopal Sharma as a Director. These moves signal potential strategic shifts and enhanced shareholder accessibility.</description><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 00:05:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699e3cb504a25a58c85368cc_1771979119517.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>