<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:45:00 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India's Regulators Tighten Grip: Mining &amp; Industry Face Rising ESG Costs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Indias-Regulators-Tighten-Grip-Mining-and-Industry-Face-Rising-ESG-Costs/69856f44e769d12df1d50bff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Indias-Regulators-Tighten-Grip-Mining-and-Industry-Face-Rising-ESG-Costs/69856f44e769d12df1d50bff</guid><description>India's National Green Tribunal (NGT) is escalating enforcement, with recent orders targeting illegal river mining in Chhattisgarh and environmental norm violations by Jindal Steel &amp; Power Limited (JSPL) at its Utkal C-Block coal mine. These actions highlight a broader trend of increased regulatory oversight and rising ESG compliance costs for resource-intensive industries. JSPL, a large-cap entity with a market capitalization around ₹118,000-120,000 crore and a TTM P/E ratio fluctuating between approximately 24x and 59x, faces specific scrutiny. The broader mining sector's average P/E sits near 18.94x, while the infrastructure sector's P/E is around 21.6x, indicating potential valuation sensitivities. Companies must navigate heightened environmental, social, and governance (ESG) demands, impacting operational expenditures and investor confidence.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:34:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69856f44e769d12df1d50bfe_1770352515583.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty, Sensex Dip Ahead of RBI Policy; Global Cues Weigh</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-Sensex-Dip-Ahead-of-RBI-Policy-Global-Cues-Weigh/69856d61e769d12df1d50512</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-Sensex-Dip-Ahead-of-RBI-Policy-Global-Cues-Weigh/69856d61e769d12df1d50512</guid><description>Indian equity benchmarks Nifty50 and BSE Sensex opened lower on Thursday, caught in a cautious mood ahead of the Reserve Bank of India's monetary policy announcement. Global markets also signaled weakness, with major Asian indices and US futures trading in the red. Analysts highlight concerns over foreign institutional investor (FII) selling and a risk-off sentiment globally. Investors are anticipating the RBI's stance on interest rates and its outlook on economic growth.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:26:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69856d61e769d12df1d50511_1770352507150.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trent's Margin Surge: A Tactical Value Play Amidst Retail Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Trents-Margin-Surge-A-Tactical-Value-Play-Amidst-Retail-Shifts/69856b85e769d12df1d502f5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Trents-Margin-Surge-A-Tactical-Value-Play-Amidst-Retail-Shifts/69856b85e769d12df1d502f5</guid><description>Trent Limited posted strong Q3 FY26 results, notably improving EBITDA margins by approximately 200 basis points year-over-year to 20.2%, driven by cost efficiencies and operational leverage. This performance occurred despite a moderated revenue growth of 15% YoY, influenced by consumer spending shifts post-GST adjustments. The company's aggressive network expansion continues, with a ~30% rise in store count and a 40% increase in business area. Despite a ~28% stock price correction over the past year, Trent's current P/E of around 80-90x is at the lower end of its historical trading range, presenting a compelling valuation thesis.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:18:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69856b85e769d12df1d502f4_1770351725084.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HEIL Earnings Surge Amidst LVA Rally &amp; ETP Bounce</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HEIL-Earnings-Surge-Amidst-LVA-Rally-and-ETP-Bounce/69856a1be769d12df1d50102</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HEIL-Earnings-Surge-Amidst-LVA-Rally-and-ETP-Bounce/69856a1be769d12df1d50102</guid><description>Hitachi Energy India Ltd (HEIL) posted a 90.3% year-on-year surge in net profit for Q3 FY2026, driven by robust execution and a record order backlog of ₹29,872.2 crore. Latent View Analytics Ltd (LVA) rallied to near its 52-week high, supported by consistent revenue growth and positive analyst sentiment. Easy Trip Planners Ltd (ETP) experienced a notable price increase, contrasting with recent financial losses and sales contraction, suggesting market forces or speculative activity.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:12:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69856a1be769d12df1d50101_1770351236813.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Godrej Properties Profit Jumps, Revenue Falls; Stock Cautiously Higher</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Godrej-Properties-Profit-Jumps-Revenue-Falls-Stock-Cautiously-Higher/6985692de769d12df1d4ff48</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Godrej-Properties-Profit-Jumps-Revenue-Falls-Stock-Cautiously-Higher/6985692de769d12df1d4ff48</guid><description>Godrej Properties Ltd. posted a 23% year-on-year increase in net profit for Q3 FY26, reaching ₹193.87 crore. However, this was achieved on a significant 17% decline in total income to ₹1,033.84 crore. The stock initially surged but pared gains, reflecting underlying operational concerns amidst strong bookings. Analysts maintain a 'Buy' rating but have lowered price targets, citing valuation adjustments and execution risks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:08:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985692de769d12df1d4ff47_1770351251847.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nykaa Q3 Beat Sparks Broker Rally Amidst Analyst Caution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Nykaa-Q3-Beat-Sparks-Broker-Rally-Amidst-Analyst-Caution/698568cee769d12df1d4fd95</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Nykaa-Q3-Beat-Sparks-Broker-Rally-Amidst-Analyst-Caution/698568cee769d12df1d4fd95</guid><description>FSN e-Commerce Ventures (Nykaa) reported a strong December quarter, exceeding profit expectations with a 141.55% year-on-year net profit surge to ₹63.31 crore and a 26.73% revenue jump to ₹2,873.26 crore. This performance propelled brokerage firms Nomura and Jefferies to reiterate or upgrade their 'buy' ratings with price targets of ₹305 and ₹315 respectively. However, a significant divergence exists between these bullish outlooks and the broader analyst consensus, which implies a mere 3% upside and includes a notable number of 'sell' recommendations, raising questions about the sustainability of Nykaa's recent operational improvements against its valuation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:06:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698568cee769d12df1d4fd94_1770351427498.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bandhan Small Cap Fund: Scale Tests Stellar Growth Amidst Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Bandhan-Small-Cap-Fund-Scale-Tests-Stellar-Growth-Amidst-Volatility/698568b1e769d12df1d4fcea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Bandhan-Small-Cap-Fund-Scale-Tests-Stellar-Growth-Amidst-Volatility/698568b1e769d12df1d4fcea</guid><description>Bandhan Small Cap Fund has witnessed a dramatic surge, with assets under management (AUM) doubling to ₹20,000 crore by February 2026. An initial investment of ₹10,000 has reportedly grown to ₹46,374 as of December 2025. Despite this rapid expansion and strong historical returns, the fund navigates the turbulent small-cap segment, characterized by a sharp correction in 2025 and a cautious approach by its managers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:06:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698568b1e769d12df1d4fce9_1770351551639.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-EU FTA: 'Mother of All Deals' Masks Gender Blind Spots</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-EU-FTA-Mother-of-All-Deals-Masks-Gender-Blind-Spots/69856841e769d12df1d4fb79</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-EU-FTA-Mother-of-All-Deals-Masks-Gender-Blind-Spots/69856841e769d12df1d4fb79</guid><description>The recently concluded India-EU Free Trade Agreement (FTA), dubbed the 'Mother of all Deals,' has sparked optimism for economic integration. However, a critical analysis reveals a persistent neglect of gender considerations, potentially disadvantaging women. Despite provisions in the FTA referencing UN and ILO conventions, concerns remain about effective implementation and the risk of gender clauses becoming trade barriers. Historical data suggests prior trade liberalizations have, at times, negatively impacted female employment shares due to constraints on working hours and skill-upgrading. The agreement's focus on key sectors like textiles and agriculture, vital for women's employment, necessitates a gender-responsive approach to ensure equitable benefits, rather than allowing pre-existing disadvantages to be amplified.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:04:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69856841e769d12df1d4fb78_1770351845080.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vatika Ltd Faces Insolvency Amidst Debt Dispute Over NCDs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Vatika-Ltd-Faces-Insolvency-Amidst-Debt-Dispute-Over-NCDs/69856760e769d12df1d4f94d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Vatika-Ltd-Faces-Insolvency-Amidst-Debt-Dispute-Over-NCDs/69856760e769d12df1d4f94d</guid><description>Gurgaon's Vatika Ltd has been admitted into the Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP) by the National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT) upon an application by IDBI Trusteeship Services. The applicant claims a default of approximately ₹274 crore on Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs). Vatika contests the admission, arguing the petition is premature as the NCD redemption date had not yet passed due to mutually agreed extensions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:00:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69856760e769d12df1d4f94c_1770350540271.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rishabh Instruments Q3 Profit Surges 161% on Margin Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rishabh-Instruments-Q3-Profit-Surges-161percent-on-Margin-Expansion/6985674ae769d12df1d4f88c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rishabh-Instruments-Q3-Profit-Surges-161percent-on-Margin-Expansion/6985674ae769d12df1d4f88c</guid><description>Rishabh Instruments reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated PAT soaring 161.5% YoY to ₹205.1 Mn. The surge was powered by a significant 920 bps EBITDA margin expansion to 17.1%, attributed to sourcing and operational efficiencies. Standalone revenue grew 3.1% YoY, driven by strong export performance. The company highlighted traction in new geographies and strategic business unit improvements, offsetting planned declines in loss-making contracts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 04:00:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985674ae769d12df1d4f88b_1770350703485.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ACME Solar Secures 301 MW FDRE Project, Boosts Capacity to 8,071 MW</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/ACME-Solar-Secures-301-MW-FDRE-Project-Boosts-Capacity-to-8071-MW/69856659e769d12df1d4f6b9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/ACME-Solar-Secures-301-MW-FDRE-Project-Boosts-Capacity-to-8071-MW/69856659e769d12df1d4f6b9</guid><description>ACME Solar Holdings has won a 301 MW/1,204 MWh FDRE project via e-reverse auction. This substantial win escalates the company's diversified contracted capacity to 8,071 MW, integrating Solar and BESS for non-solar hour supply. With 2,962 MW operational and 5,109 MW under construction, ACME reinforces its position in renewable energy solutions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 03:56:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69856659e769d12df1d4f6b8_1770350465199.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CME Boosts Gold/Silver Margins Amid Volatility, Tightening Trader Access</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/CME-Boosts-GoldSilver-Margins-Amid-Volatility-Tightening-Trader-Access/698561a8e769d12df1d4f383</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/CME-Boosts-GoldSilver-Margins-Amid-Volatility-Tightening-Trader-Access/698561a8e769d12df1d4f383</guid><description>CME Group has increased initial and maintenance margin requirements for COMEX 100 gold and COMEX 5000 silver futures. These adjustments, ranging up to 18% for non-high-risk silver accounts, follow sharp price declines after a period of parabolic gains. While intended to manage risk during heightened volatility, the move increases capital demands, potentially restricting smaller market participants and affecting short-term liquidity.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 03:36:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698561a8e769d12df1d4f382_1770349922164.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Yes Bank Recovers ₹282 Cr from NPA Settlement, Boosts Asset Quality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Yes-Bank-Recovers-282-Cr-from-NPA-Settlement-Boosts-Asset-Quality/69855f4fe769d12df1d4e855</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Yes-Bank-Recovers-282-Cr-from-NPA-Settlement-Boosts-Asset-Quality/69855f4fe769d12df1d4e855</guid><description>Yes Bank has successfully recovered INR 282 crore from a Non-Performing Advance (NPA) through a One Time Settlement (OTS). The settlement, valued at INR 288 crore, was agreed upon on November 27, 2025, with the remaining INR 6 crore expected shortly. This material recovery positively impacts the bank's cash flow and significantly strengthens its overall asset quality metrics and balance sheet.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 03:26:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69855f4fe769d12df1d4e854_1770348612420.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Talbros Automotive Bags Rs. 1000 Cr Orders, Boosts EV and Export Business</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Talbros-Automotive-Bags-Rs-1000-Cr-Orders-Boosts-EV-and-Export-Business/69855e64e769d12df1d4e6d6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Talbros-Automotive-Bags-Rs-1000-Cr-Orders-Boosts-EV-and-Export-Business/69855e64e769d12df1d4e6d6</guid><description>Talbros Automotive Components Limited (TACL) and its JVs have secured over Rs. 1,000 Crores in multi-year orders from leading OEMs for delivery over the next five years, commencing FY27. Key wins include significant export orders for forgings and chassis components for the EV segment, alongside domestic orders for gaskets and rubber parts. This strengthens TACL's revenue visibility and global market position.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 03:22:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69855e64e769d12df1d4e6d5_1770348723545.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Talbros Automotive Bags Rs 1,000 Cr Multi-Year Orders, Fuels Future Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Talbros-Automotive-Bags-Rs-1000-Cr-Multi-Year-Orders-Fuels-Future-Growth/69855c82e769d12df1d4e4de</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Talbros-Automotive-Bags-Rs-1000-Cr-Multi-Year-Orders-Fuels-Future-Growth/69855c82e769d12df1d4e4de</guid><description>Talbros Automotive Components Limited (TACL) and its Joint Ventures (JVs) have clinched multi-year orders valued at over ₹1,000 Crores from major Original Equipment Manufacturers (OEMs) in domestic and international markets. These substantial orders are slated for execution over the next five years, commencing in Fiscal Year 2027, and are expected to significantly enhance TACL's revenue visibility and profitability. The wins span across gaskets, heat shields, forgings, hoses, anti-vibration parts, and EV BIW components, with exports contributing ₹700 Crores and the EV segment ₹100 Crores.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 03:14:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69855c82e769d12df1d4e4dd_1770347742532.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NCC's Order Surge vs. Profit Dip: Guidance Void Sparks Concern</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCCs-Order-Surge-vs-Profit-Dip-Guidance-Void-Sparks-Concern/69855aa2e769d12df1d4e2e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCCs-Order-Surge-vs-Profit-Dip-Guidance-Void-Sparks-Concern/69855aa2e769d12df1d4e2e1</guid><description>NCC Ltd. reported a 36.6% profit drop in Q3 FY26 on 9% lower revenue, withdrawing future guidance due to execution headwinds. Despite this, the company secured ₹22,311 crore in orders year-to-date, maintaining a ₹79,571 crore order book. While EBITDA margins improved, rising interest costs and a sharp standalone profit fall underscore execution risks, even as analysts maintain a 'Buy' rating with substantial price targets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 03:06:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69855aa2e769d12df1d4e2e0_1770347527082.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Viyash Scientific Surges Post-Merger: Q3 Profits Soar, Debt Plummets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Viyash-Scientific-Surges-Post-Merger-Q3-Profits-Soar-Debt-Plummets/69855a30e769d12df1d4e18d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Viyash-Scientific-Surges-Post-Merger-Q3-Profits-Soar-Debt-Plummets/69855a30e769d12df1d4e18d</guid><description>Viyash Scientific Limited posted robust Q3 FY26 results, its first as a merged entity. Revenue climbed 11% YoY to ₹8,584 Million, while Adjusted EBITDA surged 64% to ₹1,854 Million, expanding margins by 690 basis points to 21.6%. Net Debt to LTM EBITDA fell sharply to 0.4x from 1.2x, showcasing strengthened financials. Management anticipates significant synergy realization and growth in animal health and API/CDMO sectors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 03:04:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69855a30e769d12df1d4e18c_1770347296782.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PGIM India Reopens Overseas Funds Amidst SEBI's 'Headroom' Allowance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/PGIM-India-Reopens-Overseas-Funds-Amidst-SEBIs-Headroom-Allowance/698559b7e769d12df1d4e036</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/PGIM-India-Reopens-Overseas-Funds-Amidst-SEBIs-Headroom-Allowance/698559b7e769d12df1d4e036</guid><description>PGIM India Mutual Fund is resuming subscriptions for three overseas fund-of-fund schemes on February 6, following a near two-month halt. This reopening is permitted by a SEBI directive allowing AMCs to utilize 'headroom' within global investment limits as of February 1, 2022, capped at ₹5 lakh per investor daily. This controlled re-entry into international markets reflects ongoing regulatory caution despite positive macro sentiment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 03:02:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698559b7e769d12df1d4e035_1770347890551.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>FedBank Surges on Fitch Upgrade; NSDL Glitch, Commodity Slump Emerge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/FedBank-Surges-on-Fitch-Upgrade-NSDL-Glitch-Commodity-Slump-Emerge/69855853e769d12df1d4de4a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/FedBank-Surges-on-Fitch-Upgrade-NSDL-Glitch-Commodity-Slump-Emerge/69855853e769d12df1d4de4a</guid><description>Federal Bank's Long-Term Issuer Default Rating outlook was revised to Positive from Stable by Fitch Ratings, coinciding with RBI approval for Blackstone to acquire up to 9.99% stake. Meanwhile, NSDL experienced a significant technical network disruption impacting settlement flows. Precious metal ETFs saw sharp declines as silver spot slumped 9% and gold dipped over 1%. SJVN commenced operations at its Assam solar plant, and KRBL launched a low glycemic index rice variant. Stallion India plans a ₹364 crore rights issue at ₹99 per share.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 02:56:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69855853e769d12df1d4de49_1770346645249.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Software Stocks: AI Fear Overblown, Says Analyst</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Software-Stocks-AI-Fear-Overblown-Says-Analyst/69855273e769d12df1d4c72c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Software-Stocks-AI-Fear-Overblown-Says-Analyst/69855273e769d12df1d4c72c</guid><description>Amidst a broad market sell-off driven by fears of artificial intelligence disruption, Wedbush analyst Dan Ives is advising investors to target leading software companies. Ives characterizes the current pessimism as an "exaggerated doomsday scenario," suggesting that many enterprises will not rapidly abandon established, mission-critical software infrastructure for nascent AI solutions. His favored companies—Microsoft, Palantir, CrowdStrike, Snowflake, and Salesforce—are identified as strong players capable of navigating and capitalizing on technological shifts, rather than succumbing to them. The market's broad-stroke reaction to AI risks has created valuation opportunities for these sector leaders.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 02:31:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69855273e769d12df1d4c72b_1770345463299.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold, Silver Dip Amid Dollar Surge; Rate Cut Hopes Anchor</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Dip-Amid-Dollar-Surge-Rate-Cut-Hopes-Anchor/6985524be769d12df1d4beaf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Dip-Amid-Dollar-Surge-Rate-Cut-Hopes-Anchor/6985524be769d12df1d4beaf</guid><description>Precious metals gold and silver extended losses, pressured by a strengthening US dollar and global equity weakness. Spot gold traded near $4,741.79 per ounce, while silver saw sharper declines to approximately $68.74. Despite softer US labor data reinforcing expectations for Federal Reserve rate cuts, immediate macro headwinds dominated market sentiment. Analysts observe near-term fragility but maintain a solid long-term bull case driven by sustained central bank demand and persistent geopolitical concerns.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 02:30:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985524be769d12df1d4beae_1770345241068.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rio Tinto, Glencore Deal Collapse: Valuation Chasm Blocks Mining Giant</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Rio-Tinto-Glencore-Deal-Collapse-Valuation-Chasm-Blocks-Mining-Giant/69855234e769d12df1d4bccc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Rio-Tinto-Glencore-Deal-Collapse-Valuation-Chasm-Blocks-Mining-Giant/69855234e769d12df1d4bccc</guid><description>Rio Tinto and Glencore have terminated merger discussions, ending months of negotiation over a potential $200 billion industry behemoth. The primary impasse stemmed from significant valuation disagreements, with Glencore seeking a higher premium and a larger ownership stake, which Rio Tinto deemed insufficient for its shareholders. This failure underscores the complex challenges in achieving large-scale consolidation within the global mining sector, despite the prevailing demand for critical minerals.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 02:30:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69855234e769d12df1d4bccb_1770345109210.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global Markets Sink: Tech Rout Deepens, Silver Plunges ~9%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Markets-Sink-Tech-Rout-Deepens-Silver-Plunges-9percent/69855057e769d12df1d4b333</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Markets-Sink-Tech-Rout-Deepens-Silver-Plunges-9percent/69855057e769d12df1d4b333</guid><description>Global markets are trading lower as a steep rout in technology stocks continues across the US and Asia. Silver prices have plunged by approximately 9% in India and 8.86% on COMEX. Indian benchmarks are set for a negative open, with GIFT Nifty indicating a drop, despite domestic institutional investors being net buyers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 02:22:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69855057e769d12df1d4b332_1770344631145.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global Tech Rout, AI Race Overshadow Indian Earnings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Tech-Rout-AI-Race-Overshadow-Indian-Earnings/69854a42e769d12df1d4af0b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Tech-Rout-AI-Race-Overshadow-Indian-Earnings/69854a42e769d12df1d4af0b</guid><description>Indian equities are poised for a subdued start on February 6, 2026, mirroring a sharp tech-led decline on Wall Street and subsequent Asian market losses. Investors await the Reserve Bank of India's policy decision. Corporate results presented a mixed picture, with strong revenue growth at Bharti Airtel offset by a profit drop, while Hero MotoCorp and LIC posted robust profit increases. Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles reported a significant net loss, underscoring varied corporate fortunes amidst global economic uncertainty and intense AI investment competition. GIFT Nifty futures indicated weakness.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 01:56:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69854a42e769d12df1d4af0a_1770343156109.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Policy Pause Expected: Growth Strong, Inflation Low</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Policy-Pause-Expected-Growth-Strong-Inflation-Low/698549c3e769d12df1d4adbc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Policy-Pause-Expected-Growth-Strong-Inflation-Low/698549c3e769d12df1d4adbc</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's Monetary Policy Committee is widely anticipated to maintain its repo rate at 5.25% on February 6, 2026. With inflation projected at a low 2.0% for FY26 and GDP growth forecasts revised upward to around 7.4%, the central bank has room to pause its easing cycle. The focus is expected to shift to liquidity management, with the recent India-US trade deal providing a positive backdrop for exports and investment. Market participants await forward guidance on the central bank's outlook.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 01:54:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698549c3e769d12df1d4adbb_1770342987597.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Torrent Power Bullish Options Play: What Investors Need to Know</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Torrent-Power-Bullish-Options-Play-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/69854514e769d12df1d4aa39</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Torrent-Power-Bullish-Options-Play-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/69854514e769d12df1d4aa39</guid><description>HDFC Securities analyst Nandish Shah has structured a Bull Spread strategy on Torrent Power, buying the 1420 Call and selling the 1450 Call for a ₹11 net cost per share ahead of the February 24 expiry. This move anticipates gains if the stock closes above ₹1431, with maximum profit achievable at or above ₹1450. The strategy is underpinned by observed long build-up in futures and bullish technical indicators on Torrent Power's stock charts, signaling potential upside.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 01:34:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69854514e769d12df1d4aa38_1770341778978.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global Markets Tumble: AI Fears, Layoffs Spark Sell-Off</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Markets-Tumble-AI-Fears-Layoffs-Spark-Sell-Off/6985449ee769d12df1d4a8d6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Markets-Tumble-AI-Fears-Layoffs-Spark-Sell-Off/6985449ee769d12df1d4a8d6</guid><description>Global equities extended significant losses as investors grappled with fears of AI impacting software profits and a surge in US layoffs to a 17-year high. Asian markets, including South Korea's Kospi and Japan's Nikkei, saw sharp declines. Precious metals and cryptocurrencies experienced severe volatility and price drops, reflecting a broad risk-off sentiment. Futures indicate continued weakness in US markets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 01:32:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985449ee769d12df1d4a8d5_1770341653889.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Telcos Demand 10x Call Rate Hike Amid Fraud Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/India-Telcos-Demand-10x-Call-Rate-Hike-Amid-Fraud-Surge/69854336e769d12df1d4a6e8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/India-Telcos-Demand-10x-Call-Rate-Hike-Amid-Fraud-Surge/69854336e769d12df1d4a6e8</guid><description>Indian telecom operators are demanding a tenfold increase in international incoming call termination charges (ITC), proposing to raise the rate from ₹0.65 to ₹4-5 per minute. This aggressive push is driven by the perceived misuse of current low rates for widespread international telecom fraud and spam, alongside a significant imbalance in call traffic volumes. Operators argue the existing structure leads to revenue leakage and financial strain, particularly with currency depreciation. The proposed hike aims to act as a deterrent to fraudulent traffic and realign India's charges with global benchmarks, with minimal expected impact on domestic consumers.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 01:26:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69854336e769d12df1d4a6e7_1770341268000.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Tumbles 16% From Record Highs as Dollar Rebounds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Tumbles-16percent-From-Record-Highs-as-Dollar-Rebounds/698542b6e769d12df1d4a551</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Tumbles-16percent-From-Record-Highs-as-Dollar-Rebounds/698542b6e769d12df1d4a551</guid><description>Silver prices have sharply reversed, shedding 16% from recent record highs to hover near $65 per ounce. A resurgent US Dollar, fueled by hawkish Fed expectations and eased geopolitical tensions, is weighing on the white metal. Increased margin requirements by CME Group and potential crypto-related liquidations also contributed to the steep decline. Analysts suggest a technical correction, with UBS forecasting volatility but maintaining a $105/oz target for March 2026.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 01:24:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698542b6e769d12df1d4a550_1770341148614.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Demographic Dividend at Risk: Higher Ed Underfunded</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Demographic-Dividend-at-Risk-Higher-Ed-Underfunded/6985423fe769d12df1d4a3ef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Demographic-Dividend-at-Risk-Higher-Ed-Underfunded/6985423fe769d12df1d4a3ef</guid><description>A Reserve Bank of India report highlights a critical misallocation of educational funds across Indian states, potentially squandering the nation's demographic dividend. Despite a growing youth population poised to drive economic growth, spending increasingly favors foundational school education over higher education and vocational training. This imbalance, observed across youthful, intermediate, and ageing states alike, risks future unemployment and productivity gaps, undermining the very economic potential the demographic dividend represents. The data suggests a national strategic misstep, prioritizing short-term enrollment over long-term skill development and innovation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 01:22:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985423fe769d12df1d4a3ee_1770341052578.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 16th FC Prioritizes GDP Over Demographics</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-16th-FC-Prioritizes-GDP-Over-Demographics/698541d1e769d12df1d4a281</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-16th-FC-Prioritizes-GDP-Over-Demographics/698541d1e769d12df1d4a281</guid><description>The 16th Finance Commission has recalibrated India's fiscal devolution formula, placing significant emphasis on a state's contribution to national GDP, a departure from previous models. This shift prioritizes economic efficiency, potentially redistributing funds towards high-growth states while adjusting allocations for population, area, and income disparities. Concerns persist regarding fiscally unsustainable subsidies, though a push for an independent Fiscal Council is notably absent.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 01:20:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698541d1e769d12df1d4a280_1770340955942.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Economic Tightrope: Growth Forecasts, Sectoral Shifts &amp; Geopolitical Capital</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economic-Tightrope-Growth-Forecasts-Sectoral-Shifts-and-Geopolitical-Capital/6985415ce769d12df1d4a103</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economic-Tightrope-Growth-Forecasts-Sectoral-Shifts-and-Geopolitical-Capital/6985415ce769d12df1d4a103</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman projects realistic growth, citing strong capital expenditure (capex) implementation. However, private sector investment is visibly shifting from core manufacturing to "frontier sectors." Capital inflows remain sensitive to geopolitical signaling, with recent US-India dialogue influencing market sentiment. The IT sector faces AI-driven disruption risks, while regulatory bodies intensify scrutiny on market dominance. Subsidy reforms and state debt management present ongoing data integration and fiscal challenges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 01:18:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985415ce769d12df1d4a102_1770340844765.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>10 Stocks Eye: Hero MotoCorp, LIC, Airtel Q3 Results Spark Market Moves</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/10-Stocks-Eye-Hero-MotoCorp-LIC-Airtel-Q3-Results-Spark-Market-Moves/69853d97e769d12df1d49dde</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/10-Stocks-Eye-Hero-MotoCorp-LIC-Airtel-Q3-Results-Spark-Market-Moves/69853d97e769d12df1d49dde</guid><description>Indian markets are poised for a cautious opening, with GIFT Nifty signaling lower trade. A host of blue-chip companies, including Hero MotoCorp, Federal Bank, Bharti Airtel, and LIC, have reported their third-quarter FY26 financial results. The outcomes present a mixed picture, with strong revenue growth for many, yet some also falling short of analyst profit expectations. Investors are closely assessing these developments ahead of the budget.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 01:02:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69853d97e769d12df1d49ddd_1770339875768.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget STT Hike Fuels Hybrid Funds Amidst Gold's Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Budget-STT-Hike-Fuels-Hybrid-Funds-Amidst-Golds-Volatility/69853d1be769d12df1d49c6a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Budget-STT-Hike-Fuels-Hybrid-Funds-Amidst-Golds-Volatility/69853d1be769d12df1d49c6a</guid><description>Early 2026 markets grapple with budget-induced volatility and a Securities Transaction Tax (STT) hike on F&amp;O trades, channeling investor interest towards multi-asset funds, buoyed by gold's performance. However, aggressive hybrid funds present a case for long-term risk-adjusted returns, as rising derivative costs penalize high-churn strategies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 01:00:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69853d1be769d12df1d49c69_1770339691207.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zota Health: Investor Bets on Growth Amidst Widening Losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zota-Health-Investor-Bets-on-Growth-Amidst-Widening-Losses/6985387ae769d12df1d498ae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Zota-Health-Investor-Bets-on-Growth-Amidst-Widening-Losses/6985387ae769d12df1d498ae</guid><description>Zota Health Care successfully raised ₹350 crore through a Qualified Institutional Placement (QIP), boosting FII holdings to 8.1% and DII holdings to 7.2%. The company's DAVAINDIA generic pharmacy network, now contributing 74% of revenue, is expanding rapidly. Despite a 98% YoY sales surge to ₹143 crore in Q3FY26, the company reported a widened net loss of ₹30 crore, raising concerns about the profitability of its low-margin, high-volume strategy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 00:40:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985387ae769d12df1d498ad_1770339062851.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Cold Chain: Urban Surge Tests Legacy Logistics</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Cold-Chain-Urban-Surge-Tests-Legacy-Logistics/6985386ce769d12df1d497fd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Cold-Chain-Urban-Surge-Tests-Legacy-Logistics/6985386ce769d12df1d497fd</guid><description>India's cold chain market, projected for robust growth, faces a critical inflection point. Rapid demand from quick commerce and pharmaceuticals necessitates a shift towards urban micro-fulfillment centers, challenging traditional large-scale, commodity-focused cold storage. Companies like Snowman Logistics and Mahindra Logistics are adapting their strategies, investing in capacity and operational efficiency, but future success hinges on mastering integrated, multi-temperature logistics for fragmented, high-speed delivery networks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 00:40:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985386ce769d12df1d497fc_1770338484373.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Textiles Rally on US Tariff Cut, Valuations Pose Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/India-Textiles-Rally-on-US-Tariff-Cut-Valuations-Pose-Risk/698537f5e769d12df1d4968b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/India-Textiles-Rally-on-US-Tariff-Cut-Valuations-Pose-Risk/698537f5e769d12df1d4968b</guid><description>A recent US-India trade deal slashed textile tariffs to 18% from 50%, poised to boost Indian exporters like Indo Count, Welspun Living, and Gokaldas Exports by restoring volumes and margins. However, these companies currently trade at premium valuations, outstripping historical averages and industry peers, suggesting potential headwinds despite the positive trade outlook. The EU-India FTA further brightens the long-term export prospects.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 00:38:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698537f5e769d12df1d4968a_1770338373663.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Growth Engine Shifts Gears Amidst Fiscal Prudence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Growth-Engine-Shifts-Gears-Amidst-Fiscal-Prudence/69853688e769d12df1d494a0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Growth-Engine-Shifts-Gears-Amidst-Fiscal-Prudence/69853688e769d12df1d494a0</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026-27 doubles down on capital expenditure (capex) with a record Rs 12.22 lakh crore allocation, aiming to sustain economic growth. Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman highlighted nascent signs of private sector investment picking up, particularly in frontier sectors. The budget also includes policy clarifications on Sovereign Gold Bonds (SGBs) and an increase in Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on derivatives to curb speculation. Global investor sentiment appears to be cautiously optimistic, with interest from Nordic funds noted, and the rupee showing recovery post diplomatic engagements. The nominal GDP growth target of 10% is deemed realistic by the Finance Minister.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 00:32:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69853688e769d12df1d4949f_1770338075863.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bengal Fiscal Deficit Dips Below 3% Amidst Grant Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Bengal-Fiscal-Deficit-Dips-Below-3percent-Amidst-Grant-Surge/69853434e769d12df1d491e3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Bengal-Fiscal-Deficit-Dips-Below-3percent-Amidst-Grant-Surge/69853434e769d12df1d491e3</guid><description>West Bengal has projected a fiscal deficit of 2.91% of its Gross State Domestic Product (GSDP) for FY27, a milestone not achieved since FY18. This reduction below the 3% threshold is attributed to restrained revenue expenditure growth and a substantial 115.75% surge in grants-in-aid from the Centre. The state's GSDP is forecast to expand by 8%, with capital expenditure planned to increase by over 42%. While fiscal prudence is emphasized, the significant reliance on central transfers raises questions about the long-term sustainability of these fiscal improvements.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 00:22:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69853434e769d12df1d491e2_1770337440122.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>