<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 04:44:41 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Hyundai India Profit Misses Target Amid Margin Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-India-Profit-Misses-Target-Amid-Margin-Squeeze/698179d669d815649b7283cd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-India-Profit-Misses-Target-Amid-Margin-Squeeze/698179d669d815649b7283cd</guid><description>Hyundai Motor India reported a Q3 FY26 profit of Rs 1,234 crore, missing Motilal Oswal's Rs 1,380 crore forecast, primarily due to a 130 basis point quarter-on-quarter contraction in gross margins. Escalating input costs and an adverse product mix pressured profitability. Despite this, the company's growth trajectory is projected to remain intact, supported by a robust product pipeline, strong SUV demand, and anticipated export volume growth. Motilal Oswal maintains a 'Buy' rating with a target of Rs 2,567.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 04:34:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698179d669d815649b7283cc_1770093258798.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Chola Finance Posts Steady Q3 Growth, Asset Quality Improves</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Chola-Finance-Posts-Steady-Q3-Growth-Asset-Quality-Improves/6981796169d815649b728278</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Chola-Finance-Posts-Steady-Q3-Growth-Asset-Quality-Improves/6981796169d815649b728278</guid><description>Cholamandalam Investment and Finance Company (Chola) reported steady net profit growth in Q3 FY26, driven by its vehicle finance and mortgage segments. Despite recent market underperformance, the company's long-term fundamentals remain robust. Asset quality is stabilizing with improving collections, and net interest margins are expected to expand due to cost benefits and a better product mix. The company maintains a strong capital position, positioning it for sustained growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 04:32:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981796169d815649b728277_1770093156857.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal Sparks Bernstein 'Trading Buy' on Nifty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Sparks-Bernstein-Trading-Buy-on-Nifty/6981787069d815649b727f8e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Sparks-Bernstein-Trading-Buy-on-Nifty/6981787069d815649b727f8e</guid><description>Bernstein analysts have issued a 'trading buy' recommendation for Indian equities, citing the recent India-US trade agreement as a catalyst. The pact, which reduces US tariffs on Indian goods to 18%, is expected to improve market sentiment, even as sluggish earnings persist. Bernstein maintains its Nifty 50 year-end target of 28,100. Financials, IT, and Telecom are highlighted as favored sectors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981787069d815649b727f8d_1770092959644.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Markets Surge on Trade Deal Hopes; Top Stocks Hit Upper Circuit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indian-Markets-Surge-on-Trade-Deal-Hopes-Top-Stocks-Hit-Upper-Circuit/6981789a69d815649b7280b4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indian-Markets-Surge-on-Trade-Deal-Hopes-Top-Stocks-Hit-Upper-Circuit/6981789a69d815649b7280b4</guid><description>India's equity market began February 3, 2026, with a substantial rally, as the S&amp;P BSE Sensex climbed 4.47% during pre-opening trade. Key sectors including metals, power, and auto also posted strong gains. Gokaldas Exports Ltd. surged 20%, boosted by positive sentiment from the India-U.S. trade deal, while Garware Hi-Tech Films Ltd. and Pearl Global Industries Ltd. also hit their upper circuit limits, driven by broader market momentum.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 04:27:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981789a69d815649b7280b3_1770092828433.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Bets Big on Pumped Hydro Storage, Eyes 267 GW Potential</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Bets-Big-on-Pumped-Hydro-Storage-Eyes-267-GW-Potential/6981761569d815649b727b66</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Bets-Big-on-Pumped-Hydro-Storage-Eyes-267-GW-Potential/6981761569d815649b727b66</guid><description>India is prioritizing hydro pumped storage projects (PSP) for grid stability over battery energy storage systems (BESS), citing indigenous technology and longer lifespans. The nation boasts a 267 GW PSP potential, crucial for meeting future energy demands. However, a massive ₹5.8 lakh crore investment is projected, requiring government support and policy coordination to accelerate deployment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 04:26:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981761569d815649b727b65_1770092691628.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PB Fintech Plans QIP for Acquisitions Amidst Strong Q3 Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/PB-Fintech-Plans-QIP-for-Acquisitions-Amidst-Strong-Q3-Growth/6981762e69d815649b727c89</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/PB-Fintech-Plans-QIP-for-Acquisitions-Amidst-Strong-Q3-Growth/6981762e69d815649b727c89</guid><description>PB Fintech's board will convene on February 5th to consider a Qualified Institutions Placement (QIP), aimed at funding potential acquisitions. This strategic move follows a robust third quarter for FY26, which saw net profit surge 165% to ₹189 crore and operating revenue climb 37% to ₹1,771 crore. The company aims to leverage its expertise and capital for inorganic growth, capitalizing on a rapidly expanding Indian InsurTech market and favorable regulatory shifts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 04:24:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981762e69d815649b727c88_1770092572420.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trade Accord Sparks ₹20 Lakh Crore Market Rally</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Trade-Accord-Sparks-20-Lakh-Crore-Market-Rally/6981770669d815649b727dc3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Trade-Accord-Sparks-20-Lakh-Crore-Market-Rally/6981770669d815649b727dc3</guid><description>Indian equity markets opened sharply higher on Tuesday, propelled by a landmark India-US trade agreement. The deal, which slashes tariffs on Indian exports to the US from 50% to 18%, injected approximately ₹20 lakh crore into the market capitalization of BSE-listed companies, pushing the total from ₹455 lakh crore to ₹474 lakh crore. The Nifty 50 index recorded its largest ever single-day opening gain of 1,200 points, signaling robust investor optimism. Export-reliant sectors like textiles, shrimp, and automotive experienced significant upward momentum, with many textile stocks hitting their upper circuit limits.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 04:22:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981770669d815649b727dc2_1770092409328.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Chola Investment: Q3 Strength Amid Stock Correction</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Chola-Investment-Q3-Strength-Amid-Stock-Correction/6981759d69d815649b727a15</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Chola-Investment-Q3-Strength-Amid-Stock-Correction/6981759d69d815649b727a15</guid><description>Cholamandalam Investment (Chola) reported strong Q3 FY26 performance, driven by sustained AUM growth and expanding net interest margins. Despite a recent stock correction exceeding 10%, the company's fundamentals remain robust, supported by stable asset quality and a well-diversified product mix. Analysts note the company's strategic initiatives and healthy capital position as key drivers for future upside potential, even as market conditions present short-term headwinds.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 04:12:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Truhome Finance Appoints Ex-SBI Chief Khara as Chairperson</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Truhome-Finance-Appoints-Ex-SBI-Chief-Khara-as-Chairperson/6981754069d815649b72789f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Truhome-Finance-Appoints-Ex-SBI-Chief-Khara-as-Chairperson/6981754069d815649b72789f</guid><description>Truhome Finance has appointed Dinesh Kumar Khara, former Chairman of State Bank of India, as its Chairperson for a five-year term. Khara's extensive experience, including orchestrating a major bank merger at SBI, is expected to drive Truhome's expansion and strategic direction in India's competitive mortgage market. Recent financial reports indicate solid AUM growth and comfortable asset quality, though specific live market trading data remains unavailable or inconsistent.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 04:10:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Budget 2026 Ups Tax Penalties for Updated Returns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Ups-Tax-Penalties-for-Updated-Returns/6981752969d815649b7277b0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Ups-Tax-Penalties-for-Updated-Returns/6981752969d815649b7277b0</guid><description>The Indian government, via the Finance Bill, 2026, has significantly altered rules for filing Updated Income Tax Returns (ITR-U). Taxpayers now have a 48-month window to rectify disclosures, but face escalating additional taxes. New provisions also permit filing post-reassessment notices, albeit with higher penalty rates. These changes signal a drive for enhanced compliance and revenue collection through a more stringent, yet clarified, voluntary disclosure mechanism.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 04:10:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IndusInd Bank Taps Piramal Exec for Consumer Finance Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IndusInd-Bank-Taps-Piramal-Exec-for-Consumer-Finance-Push/698174b169d815649b7275fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IndusInd-Bank-Taps-Piramal-Exec-for-Consumer-Finance-Push/698174b169d815649b7275fb</guid><description>IndusInd Bank has appointed Jagdeep Mallareddy, formerly CEO of retail lending at Piramal Finance, to lead its consumer finance business. This strategic hire, personally selected by CEO Rajiv Anand, is crucial for bolstering the bank's retail pivot and growth ambitions. The move occurs as IndusInd continues to reshape its leadership following significant accounting discrepancies and a period of underperformance.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 04:08:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Medusa Beverages Expands National Footprint, Targets 1.4M Cases</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Medusa-Beverages-Expands-National-Footprint-Targets-14M-Cases/6981743569d815649b7274a5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Medusa-Beverages-Expands-National-Footprint-Targets-14M-Cases/6981743569d815649b7274a5</guid><description>Medusa Beverages is intensifying its market presence with a strategic draught beer launch in Delhi and expansion into Karnataka, Jharkhand, and Kerala. This move aims to capture the on-trade and HORECA segments, targeting 100 outlets in Delhi alone and leveraging new breweries to boost production capacity. The company anticipates closing FY26 with approximately 1.4 million cases sold, a 40-45% year-on-year increase, and is preparing for further funding rounds to fuel its pan-India growth strategy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 04:08:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981743569d815649b7274a4_1770091683169.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Tariffs Slashed to 18% in India Trade Deal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Tariffs-Slashed-to-18percent-in-India-Trade-Deal/6981707c69d815649b726eae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Tariffs-Slashed-to-18percent-in-India-Trade-Deal/6981707c69d815649b726eae</guid><description>A landmark India-US trade agreement dramatically reduces US tariffs on Indian goods to 18%, eliminating a punitive 25% levy previously tied to Russian oil purchases. This move significantly enhances India's export competitiveness, particularly benefiting sectors like textiles, chemicals, auto ancillaries, and aquaculture, which had been heavily impacted by prior 50% duties. The accord is also expected to stabilize the Indian Rupee and potentially attract renewed foreign investment amidst favorable macroeconomic indicators.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 04:02:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981707c69d815649b726ead_1770091244805.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Reliance Jio Studios Acquires Sikhya Entertainment for ₹150 Cr, Eyes Global Content</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Reliance-Jio-Studios-Acquires-Sikhya-Entertainment-for-150-Cr-Eyes-Global-Content/698170eb69d815649b72711d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Reliance-Jio-Studios-Acquires-Sikhya-Entertainment-for-150-Cr-Eyes-Global-Content/698170eb69d815649b72711d</guid><description>Reliance Industries' Jio Studios has acquired a 50.1% majority stake in Sikhya Entertainment for ₹150 crore. This strategic move by RIL's media arm aims to significantly enhance its presence in the entertainment sector and amplify the global reach of Indian narratives by synergizing Jio's scale with Sikhya's award-winning content production capabilities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 03:58:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698170eb69d815649b72711c_1770091115821.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aditya Birla Housing Finance Secures ₹2,750 Cr PE Boost from Advent International</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Aditya-Birla-Housing-Finance-Secures-2750-Cr-PE-Boost-from-Advent-International/6981709669d815649b726f9a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Aditya-Birla-Housing-Finance-Secures-2750-Cr-PE-Boost-from-Advent-International/6981709669d815649b726f9a</guid><description>Aditya Birla Housing Finance (ABHFL) is set to receive ₹2,750 Crores from global PE firm Advent International's entity Indriya Limited. This investment pegs ABHFL's post-money valuation at ₹19,250 Crores, with Advent acquiring a 14.3% stake. The capital infusion aims to fuel ABHFL's impressive 48% CAGR AUM growth and expand market share in the robust Indian housing sector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 03:58:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981709669d815649b726f99_1770090986543.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SpaceX Acquires xAI in $1.25T Mega-Merger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/SpaceX-Acquires-xAI-in-125T-Mega-Merger/69816f0d69d815649b7269e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/SpaceX-Acquires-xAI-in-125T-Mega-Merger/69816f0d69d815649b7269e1</guid><description>SpaceX finalized its acquisition of Elon Musk's AI firm xAI for $1.25 trillion, merging the aerospace giant with the artificial intelligence startup. The combined entity aims to pioneer space-based data centers, leveraging SpaceX's Starship capabilities to harness solar power for AI computation. This strategic consolidation precedes a highly anticipated SpaceX IPO, expected later this year, positioning the merged company as a dominant force in both space exploration and advanced AI.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 03:48:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69816f0d69d815649b7269e0_1770090362793.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Pact Boosts Equities, Eyes Foreign Inflows</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Pact-Boosts-Equities-Eyes-Foreign-Inflows/69816f9069d815649b726c50</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Pact-Boosts-Equities-Eyes-Foreign-Inflows/69816f9069d815649b726c50</guid><description>Indian equities registered a notable advance following the announcement of a US-India trade agreement that substantially reduced reciprocal tariffs. The pact is seen as a critical catalyst to reverse recent foreign investor outflows and improve sentiment. Initial market reactions included a sharp surge in Nifty 50 futures and gains in cash equities, signaling a renewed appetite for Indian assets. This development, coupled with recent budget measures, aims to bolster investor confidence and economic growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 03:46:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>BASF India Gets NSE Nod for Agri Biz Demerger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/BASF-India-Gets-NSE-Nod-for-Agri-Biz-Demerger/69816f8569d815649b726c3d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/BASF-India-Gets-NSE-Nod-for-Agri-Biz-Demerger/69816f8569d815649b726c3d</guid><description>BASF India has received a 'no objection' letter from NSE for its agri business demerger into subsidiary BASIL. This follows BSE's nod. The scheme awaits NCLT approvals, with NSE imposing disclosure conditions and a tight listing timeline for the new entity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 03:46:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal: Tariffs Slashed, Markets Surge on Risk-On</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Tariffs-Slashed-Markets-Surge-on-Risk-On/69816f2369d815649b726a86</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Tariffs-Slashed-Markets-Surge-on-Risk-On/69816f2369d815649b726a86</guid><description>A significant trade pact between India and the United States has slashed punitive tariffs on Indian goods from 50% to 18%, effectively ending a year of trade friction. Market analysts hail this as a crucial "risk-on" trigger, expected to lure foreign institutional investors back to Indian equities and stabilize the rupee. The agreement is projected to enhance export competitiveness for sectors like textiles, pharmaceuticals, and auto ancillaries, while strengthening India's macroeconomic fundamentals.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 03:44:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Silver Faces Volatility Amid Fed Policy, Geopolitical Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Faces-Volatility-Amid-Fed-Policy-Geopolitical-Shifts/69816e9969d815649b72689c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Faces-Volatility-Amid-Fed-Policy-Geopolitical-Shifts/69816e9969d815649b72689c</guid><description>Silver experienced a divergence on February 3, 2026, with Comex prices rising to $82.70 per ounce while MCX futures saw steep declines from recent record highs, settling around ₹2.99 lakh per kilogram. This volatility followed a sharp market correction after the US Federal Reserve held interest rates steady and President Trump nominated Kevin Warsh as the next Fed chair. While geopolitical tensions continue to provide underlying support, recent de-escalation signals and robust US manufacturing data are shifting market sentiment. Investors now eye key economic indicators, including RBI policy and US jobs data, for further direction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 03:42:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Gold, Silver Rebound Sharply After Fed Nominee Shock</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Rebound-Sharply-After-Fed-Nominee-Shock/69816da769d815649b72670c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Rebound-Sharply-After-Fed-Nominee-Shock/69816da769d815649b72670c</guid><description>Precious metals gold and silver experienced a significant overnight rebound, with gold surpassing $4,850 per ounce and silver climbing past $85 per ounce on COMEX. This recovery follows a dramatic sell-off, largely attributed to President Trump's nomination of Kevin Warsh for Federal Reserve Chair, perceived as a hawkish signal. Despite volatility, underlying support from central bank purchases and fiscal concerns persists.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 03:38:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Silver Rebounds Sharply After Steep Decline Amidst Market Turbulence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Rebounds-Sharply-After-Steep-Decline-Amidst-Market-Turbulence/69816d2d69d815649b7265c3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Rebounds-Sharply-After-Steep-Decline-Amidst-Market-Turbulence/69816d2d69d815649b7265c3</guid><description>Silver prices showed signs of recovery on February 3, 2026, with spot silver climbing nearly 8% to $82.74 and COMEX futures reaching $85/oz. This rebound follows a dramatic over 35% plunge from ₹4,20,000 per kilogram to ₹2,65,000. The market turbulence was exacerbated by a more than 15% increase in CME silver futures margins in late January 2026, forcing traders to liquidate positions. Analysts point to a fundamental supply deficit and robust industrial demand, particularly in solar energy, EVs, and data centers, as key factors supporting the recovery.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 03:36:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>PSL Evolution Powers Indian Banks: HDFC, Indian Bank Insights</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSL-Evolution-Powers-Indian-Banks-HDFC-Indian-Bank-Insights/6981698969d815649b72586c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSL-Evolution-Powers-Indian-Banks-HDFC-Indian-Bank-Insights/6981698969d815649b72586c</guid><description>Motilal Oswal Financial Services notes a significant transformation in India's Priority Sector Lending (PSL), evolving from a compliance burden into an earnings driver. Private banks are actively expanding on-balance-sheet PSL assets, reducing reliance on certificates and low-yield deposits. Public Sector Banks (PSBs) are also seeing improved performance, though some still rely on PSLCs. This strategic shift, coupled with robust asset quality and efficient management, positions banks for enhanced profitability. HDFC Bank and Indian Bank are highlighted for their strong operational performance and strategic PSL integration.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 03:33:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981698969d815649b72586b_1770089597154.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Markets Stabilize; AMD, SMCI Face Earnings Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Markets-Stabilize-AMD-SMCI-Face-Earnings-Scrutiny/698169ec69d815649b725a0c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Markets-Stabilize-AMD-SMCI-Face-Earnings-Scrutiny/698169ec69d815649b725a0c</guid><description>Tuesday saw a return to calmer trading conditions globally, with Asian stocks and gold posting rebounds following sharp swings. Improved US manufacturing data provided an overnight boost, while investors awaited the Reserve Bank of Australia's policy decision, with a rate hike widely expected. The focus sharpens on key earnings reports from Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) and Super Micro Computer (SMCI) later today, crucial for sentiment in the technology and AI infrastructure sectors. AMD, a major player in AI chips, faces scrutiny following strong recent performance, while Super Micro Computer navigates competitive pressures in the server hardware market.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 03:26:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698169ec69d815649b725a0b_1770089184482.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Tariff Cut Boosts Indian Shrimp Exporters</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/US-Tariff-Cut-Boosts-Indian-Shrimp-Exporters/6981696e69d815649b7257c0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/US-Tariff-Cut-Boosts-Indian-Shrimp-Exporters/6981696e69d815649b7257c0</guid><description>A significant reduction in US import tariffs on Indian shrimp, from 50% to 18%, is expected to restore lost competitiveness and market share for exporters. Companies previously contending with margin pressures and volume losses anticipate improved earnings visibility. While some stocks showed mixed reactions on Monday, the sector is poised for a turnaround following this key trade development.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 03:20:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Gold Rebounds: SAMCO Sees Healthy Consolidation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Rebounds-SAMCO-Sees-Healthy-Consolidation/698168f969d815649b725658</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Rebounds-SAMCO-Sees-Healthy-Consolidation/698168f969d815649b725658</guid><description>Gold saw a rebound on Tuesday, February 3rd, following recent declines, driven by bargain buying and short-covering. Analysts at SAMCO Securities interpret this move not as a decisive trend change, but as part of a broader consolidation phase. Despite short-term volatility, SAMCO maintains that gold's long-term price structure remains intact, supported by structural drivers like central bank demand and geopolitical risks. This consolidation is viewed as healthy, potentially building a stronger base for future upward movements.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 03:18:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>KEC International Secures Rs 1,020 Cr Orders Across Verticals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KEC-International-Secures-Rs-1020-Cr-Orders-Across-Verticals/6981687d69d815649b72551a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KEC-International-Secures-Rs-1020-Cr-Orders-Across-Verticals/6981687d69d815649b72551a</guid><description>KEC International announced new orders worth Rs. 1,020 Crores across its Civil, Transportation, T&amp;D, and Cables verticals. Key wins include a multispeciality hospital and a railway siding project, adding to its Rs. 20,300 Crores year-to-date intake. These orders highlight continued business momentum for the global EPC major.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 03:16:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Power Sector Faces Privatization Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Power-Sector-Faces-Privatization-Push/698164d769d815649b725221</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Power-Sector-Faces-Privatization-Push/698164d769d815649b725221</guid><description>The 16th Finance Commission has proposed privatizing India's power distribution sector to tackle its chronic financial distress, characterized by ₹7.5 lakh crore in outstanding debt and ₹6.77 lakh crore in accumulated losses as of FY2024. The plan involves state-created Special Purpose Vehicles (SPVs) to isolate bad debt, thereby making utilities more attractive for private investment and paving the way for sector modernization. Central government assistance will be tied to states' commitment to privatization.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 03:04:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698164d769d815649b725220_1770087793881.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Economic Outlook: Growth, FDI, and Inflation Confidence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/India-Economic-Outlook-Growth-FDI-and-Inflation-Confidence/698164bd69d815649b725126</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/India-Economic-Outlook-Growth-FDI-and-Inflation-Confidence/698164bd69d815649b725126</guid><description>Economic Affairs Secretary Anuradha Thakur projects sustained growth momentum, citing government capex and rising private investment. She anticipates improved foreign direct investment (FDI), particularly in chemicals and biopharma, driven by Budget measures. Thakur also affirmed confidence in the flexible inflation targeting mechanism, emphasizing headline inflation's relevance to public experience, and outlined plans for asset monetization targeting ₹80,000 crore, including CPSE REITs.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 03:02:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698164bd69d815649b725125_1770087701240.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal Slashes Tariffs, Sparks Sector Rally</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Slashes-Tariffs-Sparks-Sector-Rally/69815fad69d815649b72477e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Slashes-Tariffs-Sparks-Sector-Rally/69815fad69d815649b72477e</guid><description>India and the United States have finalized a trade deal dramatically cutting tariffs on Indian exports to the US from an average of 50% to approximately 18%. This pact is projected to enhance the global competitiveness of labor-intensive sectors and potentially reverse recent foreign portfolio investor (FPI) outflows.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 03:02:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69815fad69d815649b72477d_1770087611351.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Customs Reforms to Slash Business Turnaround Time via Technology</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Customs-Reforms-to-Slash-Business-Turnaround-Time-via-Technology/6981644569d815649b724f75</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Customs-Reforms-to-Slash-Business-Turnaround-Time-via-Technology/6981644569d815649b724f75</guid><description>CBIC Chairman Vivek Chaturvedi expressed confidence in meeting Budget targets, highlighting significant customs reforms. The strategy centers on process simplification and technology adoption to reduce cargo dwell times and improve business agility. Initiatives include duty exemptions for critical sectors like nuclear power and electric vehicles, alongside updated baggage rules. An integrated IT system is planned within two years to enable instantaneous risk assessment, promising a faster, more efficient user experience.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 02:58:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Airtel's Q3 Preview: Arpu Gains, Africa Strength in Focus</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Airtels-Q3-Preview-Arpu-Gains-Africa-Strength-in-Focus/69815fd369d815649b72486e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Airtels-Q3-Preview-Arpu-Gains-Africa-Strength-in-Focus/69815fd369d815649b72486e</guid><description>Bharti Airtel is poised for stable third-quarter performance in FY26, with analysts projecting continued growth in India's average revenue per user (ARPU) and robust operations in Africa. Consolidated revenue is expected to see a year-on-year increase between 14% and 19%. Key investor watchpoints include the trajectory of EBITDA margins amidst network investments and potential currency fluctuations impacting African segment earnings.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 02:58:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69815fd369d815649b72486d_1770087377561.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Railways Embraces PPP Amidst Record Infra Spending</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Railways-Embraces-PPP-Amidst-Record-Infra-Spending/698163cc69d815649b724de7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Railways-Embraces-PPP-Amidst-Record-Infra-Spending/698163cc69d815649b724de7</guid><description>Expenditure Secretary V Vualnam has signaled a significant strategic shift towards Public-Private Partnerships (PPPs) for railway projects, moving away from traditional Engineering, Procurement, and Construction (EPC) contracts. This transition is underpinned by the government's substantial capital expenditure increase for infrastructure. Station development is identified as a primary focus for PPP integration, aiming to enhance project financing and construction quality by drawing on lessons learned from the highway sector. The move aligns with the government's overarching strategy of fiscal prudence and maximizing infrastructure's economic multiplier effect.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 02:57:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698163cc69d815649b724de6_1770087472942.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Tariff Cut Sparks India Market Rally; Key Q3 Results Due</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Tariff-Cut-Sparks-India-Market-Rally-Key-Q3-Results-Due/6981601469d815649b7249fc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Tariff-Cut-Sparks-India-Market-Rally-Key-Q3-Results-Due/6981601469d815649b7249fc</guid><description>Indian markets opened with significant gains on Tuesday, driven by the US decision to reduce reciprocal tariffs on Indian goods to 18% from 25%. This move, coupled with India's pledge to cease Russian oil imports, has positively influenced global trade sentiment. Investors are also closely monitoring a slew of Q3 FY26 earnings reports from major Indian corporations throughout the day, which will provide further directional cues.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 02:54:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981601469d815649b7249fb_1770087189391.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>M&amp;M Rides Auto Boom, Delhivery Targets Logistics Profitability</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/MandM-Rides-Auto-Boom-Delhivery-Targets-Logistics-Profitability/6981608969d815649b724b19</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/MandM-Rides-Auto-Boom-Delhivery-Targets-Logistics-Profitability/6981608969d815649b724b19</guid><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra is poised for continued growth driven by strong tractor demand and new automotive product launches, projecting outperformance in FY26. Concurrently, logistics firm Delhivery demonstrated robust Q3 performance, unveiling strategies to double EBITDA margins and achieve substantial Return on Invested Capital amid sector expansion.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 02:52:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6981608969d815649b724b18_1770087094185.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold, Silver Rebound: Shutdown, Fed Policy Shift Spark Recovery</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Rebound-Shutdown-Fed-Policy-Shift-Spark-Recovery/69815f9669d815649b724692</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Rebound-Shutdown-Fed-Policy-Shift-Spark-Recovery/69815f9669d815649b724692</guid><description>Gold and silver prices surged Tuesday, clawing back losses from a steep two-day correction. Traders reassessed positions amid US government shutdown uncertainty and evolving Federal Reserve policy expectations. While the US dollar held firm, its usual dampening effect on gold was counteracted by broader macro worries. Analysts suggest the recent pullback was technical, with long-term uptrends intact for gold, while silver faces a potentially slower recovery due to leverage.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 02:38:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>US Manufacturing Rebound Lifts Asia Amid Commodity Sell-off</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Manufacturing-Rebound-Lifts-Asia-Amid-Commodity-Sell-off/69815f2069d815649b72456d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Manufacturing-Rebound-Lifts-Asia-Amid-Commodity-Sell-off/69815f2069d815649b72456d</guid><description>Asian equities staged a significant recovery, with technology shares spearheading the advance, following a robust expansion in US manufacturing activity that bolstered economic outlook. This rebound occurred against a backdrop of extreme volatility in precious metals, which experienced sharp sell-offs triggered by the Federal Reserve nomination before paring some losses. Regional developments and AI infrastructure demand also shaped market sentiment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 02:36:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Gold Plunges Amid Fed Nomination Turmoil; Futures Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Plunges-Amid-Fed-Nomination-Turmoil-Futures-Dip/69815eae69d815649b723e5a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Plunges-Amid-Fed-Nomination-Turmoil-Futures-Dip/69815eae69d815649b723e5a</guid><description>Gold prices saw a significant drop around February 1-2, 2026, plummeting by as much as 10-11.4% following the nomination of Kevin Warsh as Federal Reserve chair and a rebound in the US dollar. MCX futures also declined, closing at Rs 143,000 per 10 grams. Analysts predict potential further declines, with support levels near $4,300-$4,320, viewing current dips as potential long-term buying opportunities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 02:34:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Budget 2026: Gen Z Economy Boom &amp; Digital India Drive</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Budget-2026-Gen-Z-Economy-Boom-and-Digital-India-Drive/69815d4269d815649b722095</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Budget-2026-Gen-Z-Economy-Boom-and-Digital-India-Drive/69815d4269d815649b722095</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 marks a significant pivot towards Gen Z and the digital economy. Key initiatives include a major boost for the AVGC sector with content creator labs, simplified travel taxes, reduced import duties on personal tech, new incentives for young workers via the ELI Scheme, extended recognition for deep-tech startups, and a streamlined foreign asset disclosure process. These measures aim to foster innovation, create jobs, and enhance global competitiveness.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 02:32:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69815d4269d815649b722094_1770085831315.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Analyst Flags Four Stocks Amidst Market Recovery</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Analyst-Flags-Four-Stocks-Amidst-Market-Recovery/69815b5e69d815649b721c61</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Analyst-Flags-Four-Stocks-Amidst-Market-Recovery/69815b5e69d815649b721c61</guid><description>Somil Mehta, Head - Alternate Research at Mirae Asset Sharekhan, has put forth recommendations for NMDC, DLF, Blue Star, and IOC, citing specific technical chart patterns and indicators for potential upside. These calls emerge as the market digests the India-US trade deal and post-budget sentiment, following a volatile January correction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 02:28:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69815b5e69d815649b721c60_1770085699440.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>