<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 09:19:51 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Adani Group's Massive ₹80,000 Crore Deal Spree: How They Rebuilt Trust After Crisis!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Adani-Groups-Massive-80000-Crore-Deal-Spree-How-They-Rebuilt-Trust-After-Crisis/694d0062e10c98d0788927bc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Adani-Groups-Massive-80000-Crore-Deal-Spree-How-They-Rebuilt-Trust-After-Crisis/694d0062e10c98d0788927bc</guid><description>Adani Group has completed 33 acquisitions totaling approximately ₹80,000 crore ($9.6 billion) since early 2023. This aggressive deal-making across core sectors like ports, cement, and power signals a strong recovery and sustained access to capital following the short-seller allegations that impacted its market standing. The group focused on balance-sheet repair and strategic expansion, gradually restoring investor confidence.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 09:04:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694d0062e10c98d0788927bb_1766654260688.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Overhauls Rural Jobs Act: Govt Claims Pro-Poor, Experts Warn of Setbacks!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Overhauls-Rural-Jobs-Act-Govt-Claims-Pro-Poor-Experts-Warn-of-Setbacks/694cfd72e10c98d07889252e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Overhauls-Rural-Jobs-Act-Govt-Claims-Pro-Poor-Experts-Warn-of-Setbacks/694cfd72e10c98d07889252e</guid><description>India has replaced the MGNREGA with the new VB-G RAM G Act, increasing guaranteed workdays to 125. While Minister Shivraj Singh Chouhan calls it 'pro-poor,' critics like Aruna Sharma fear the shift to a centrally-sponsored model and increased state funding share will compromise employment guarantees. Concerns also exist over centralization of work categories and potential reduction in worker bargaining power due to pauses during agricultural seasons.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 08:54:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cfd72e10c98d07889252d_1766653365337.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pulsar Capital Eyes Nandhana Palace: $50M+ Deal Signals Major Restaurant Sector Shake-up!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Pulsar-Capital-Eyes-Nandhana-Palace-50M-Deal-Signals-Major-Restaurant-Sector-Shake-up/694cf79ee10c98d07889211a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Pulsar-Capital-Eyes-Nandhana-Palace-50M-Deal-Signals-Major-Restaurant-Sector-Shake-up/694cf79ee10c98d07889211a</guid><description>Dubai-based Pulsar Capital is nearing a $50-60 million acquisition of Bengaluru's popular Andhra-cuisine chain, Nandhana Palace. This deal signifies a potential full exit for Nandhana's promoters and is a key step in Pulsar Capital's strategy to build a consolidated food platform. The acquisition highlights growing investor interest and consolidation trends within India's booming food services market.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 08:25:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cf79ee10c98d078892119_1766651954816.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Signature Global Bets Big: ₹4,800 Crore Luxury Housing Project Launched in Gurugram!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Signature-Global-Bets-Big-4800-Crore-Luxury-Housing-Project-Launched-in-Gurugram/694cf5fbe10c98d078891e70</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Signature-Global-Bets-Big-4800-Crore-Luxury-Housing-Project-Launched-in-Gurugram/694cf5fbe10c98d078891e70</guid><description>Signature Global is investing Rs 4,800 crore to develop a new luxury housing project, 'Sarvam at DXP Estate', in Gurugram. Located on Dwarka Expressway, the project will feature 1,798 apartments, with initial sales targeting units priced between Rs 3-4 crore. The company plans to fund this expansion primarily through internal accruals and customer advances, aiming to achieve its annual sales bookings target.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 08:23:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cf5fbe10c98d078891e6f_1766651453949.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Budget 2026 Game Plan: CII Reveals 4 Pillars for HUGE Economic Stability &amp; Growth! Click to See the Strategy!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-2026-Game-Plan-CII-Reveals-4-Pillars-for-HUGE-Economic-Stability-and-Growth-Click-to-See-the-Strategy/694cf5ade10c98d078891db7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-2026-Game-Plan-CII-Reveals-4-Pillars-for-HUGE-Economic-Stability-and-Growth-Click-to-See-the-Strategy/694cf5ade10c98d078891db7</guid><description>Ahead of Budget 2026, the Confederation of Indian Industry (CII) has proposed a four-pillar strategy for India's macroeconomic stability. Key recommendations include debt sustainability, fiscal transparency, revenue mobilization, and expenditure efficiency. CII also urged a clear privatization roadmap for Public Sector Enterprises and reforms in subsidies like PDS and fertilizers to enhance efficiency and curb misuse, aiming to sustain India's strong growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 08:20:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cf5ade10c98d078891db6_1766651453142.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RECORD SMASHED! Shyam Dhani IPO Oversubscribed 900+ Times, Secures ₹25,000 Crore Bids – India's Top SME Debut?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/RECORD-SMASHED-Shyam-Dhani-IPO-Oversubscribed-900-Times-Secures-25000-Crore-Bids-Indias-Top-SME-Debut/694cf555e10c98d078891cfe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/RECORD-SMASHED-Shyam-Dhani-IPO-Oversubscribed-900-Times-Secures-25000-Crore-Bids-Indias-Top-SME-Debut/694cf555e10c98d078891cfe</guid><description>Jaipur-based Shyam Dhani Industries' ₹38.5 crore IPO has seen an unprecedented response, attracting bids worth over ₹25,000 crore. Subscribed more than 900 times, it has become India's most subscribed SME IPO of 2025 and ranks fifth in SME history. The issue witnessed massive demand from retail and non-institutional investors, signalling a strong appetite for small and medium enterprise offerings despite general market concerns.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 08:20:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cf555e10c98d078891cfd_1766651363530.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jharkhand's Secret Weapon: 45,000 Hectares of Old Coal Land Could Power India's Green Future!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Jharkhands-Secret-Weapon-45000-Hectares-of-Old-Coal-Land-Could-Power-Indias-Green-Future/694cf0fce10c98d078891921</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Jharkhands-Secret-Weapon-45000-Hectares-of-Old-Coal-Land-Could-Power-Indias-Green-Future/694cf0fce10c98d078891921</guid><description>A new study by iFOREST reveals Jharkhand can repurpose 45,000 hectares of mining land for green investments like renewable energy and manufacturing, crucial for India's net-zero transition. With over 11,000 hectares available immediately from closed mines, this offers significant opportunities for economic diversification and job creation in coal-dependent regions, supported by ₹16,977 crore in District Mineral Foundation funds.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 07:57:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cf0fce10c98d078891920_1766650465295.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aravallis Under Threat? New Definition Opens 50% Area to Mining, Contradicts Minister's Claims!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Aravallis-Under-Threat-New-Definition-Opens-50percent-Area-to-Mining-Contradicts-Ministers-Claims/694ceed6e10c98d0788916ff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Aravallis-Under-Threat-New-Definition-Opens-50percent-Area-to-Mining-Contradicts-Ministers-Claims/694ceed6e10c98d0788916ff</guid><description>An analysis by Delhi Science Forum reveals that a new definition of Aravalli hills, accepted by the Supreme Court, could make nearly 50% of the region vulnerable to mining. This finding contradicts Environment Minister Bhupender Yadav's statement that 90% of the Aravallis are protected, raising environmental concerns about potential degradation and resource exploitation in the ecologically sensitive region.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 07:52:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ceed6e10c98d0788916fe_1766649635391.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Expressway Woes: NHAI Threatens Contract Cancellation for Underperforming Road Builder!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Expressway-Woes-NHAI-Threatens-Contract-Cancellation-for-Underperforming-Road-Builder/694cee52e10c98d078891614</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Expressway-Woes-NHAI-Threatens-Contract-Cancellation-for-Underperforming-Road-Builder/694cee52e10c98d078891614</guid><description>National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) has issued an intention to terminate Roadways Solutions India Infra Ltd (RSIL) over severe delays and "absolute non-performance" on a crucial 35-km stretch of the Delhi-Mumbai Expressway in Gujarat. With only 4.9% physical progress, the project's completion is now at risk of extending beyond March 2028, raising concerns about contractor selection and national infrastructure timelines.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 07:50:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cee52e10c98d078891613_1766649501754.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026 Shockwave: Top Firms Demand Next-Gen Reforms, AI Boost &amp; Tax Certainty!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Shockwave-Top-Firms-Demand-Next-Gen-Reforms-AI-Boost-and-Tax-Certainty/694ceec7e10c98d0788916c5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Shockwave-Top-Firms-Demand-Next-Gen-Reforms-AI-Boost-and-Tax-Certainty/694ceec7e10c98d0788916c5</guid><description>Industry giants Deloitte and ASSOCHAM are urging the government for sweeping reforms in the upcoming Budget 2026-27. Their demands focus on boosting 'next-gen' manufacturing, digital sovereignty, and crucial tax certainty, alongside raw material security and incentives for strategic sectors like space and nuclear energy. These recommendations aim to fortify India's economic resilience amid global instability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 07:47:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ceec7e10c98d0788916c4_1766649662291.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Defence Giant Set for Explosive Growth? SBI Securities' Top Pick for 2026 Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defence-Giant-Set-for-Explosive-Growth-SBI-Securities-Top-Pick-for-2026-Revealed/694ce7c7e10c98d078890b33</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defence-Giant-Set-for-Explosive-Growth-SBI-Securities-Top-Pick-for-2026-Revealed/694ce7c7e10c98d078890b33</guid><description>Sunny Agrawal from SBI Securities has named Bharat Dynamics Limited as his top defence stock pick for 2026. He cited a robust order book of around ₹23,000 crore and expects supply chain issues to resolve, leading to strong earnings growth. Agrawal forecasts profits could double in two years, with a target price of ₹1800, representing a 21% upside from its current trading levels. The defence sector's long-term outlook remains positive due to continuous new orders.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 07:21:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ce7c7e10c98d078890b32_1766647991009.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Rs 1 Lakh Crore Credit Boom? Digital Lending &amp; Premium Choices Fueling Massive Retail Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Rs-1-Lakh-Crore-Credit-Boom-Digital-Lending-and-Premium-Choices-Fueling-Massive-Retail-Surge/694ce807e10c98d078890bb2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Rs-1-Lakh-Crore-Credit-Boom-Digital-Lending-and-Premium-Choices-Fueling-Massive-Retail-Surge/694ce807e10c98d078890bb2</guid><description>India's retail credit landscape is rapidly transforming, driven by a surge in digital-first lending models and increasing consumer demand for premium products. HDB Financial Services reports nearly 99% of loans are now processed digitally, speeding up decisions and widening access through AI-driven credit scoring. This trend, observed across states like Uttar Pradesh and Maharashtra, reflects a growing aspirational consumption beyond major cities, impacting consumer electronics and durables.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 07:21:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ce807e10c98d078890bb1_1766647945237.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Retail Revolution: Tier II/III Cities Fueling Explosive 2026 Growth! Investors, Don't Miss This!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Retail-Revolution-Tier-IIIII-Cities-Fueling-Explosive-2026-Growth-Investors-Dont-Miss-This/694ce610e10c98d078890933</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Retail-Revolution-Tier-IIIII-Cities-Fueling-Explosive-2026-Growth-Investors-Dont-Miss-This/694ce610e10c98d078890933</guid><description>India's $1.1 trillion retail sector is set for accelerated growth in 2026, driven by a significant shift in demand from metros to Tier II and III cities. With robust fundamentals, digital integration, and policy support like GST reforms, experts predict double-digit expansion. While challenges persist, trends like premiumisation, value retail, and AI-driven omnichannel strategies position the sector for a highly optimistic future, promising significant opportunities for investors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 07:14:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ce610e10c98d078890932_1766647383795.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Truck Market Roars Back: Experts Predict Major Growth Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Truck-Market-Roars-Back-Experts-Predict-Major-Growth-Surge/694ce644e10c98d07889099f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Truck-Market-Roars-Back-Experts-Predict-Major-Growth-Surge/694ce644e10c98d07889099f</guid><description>India's medium and heavy commercial vehicle (M&amp;HCV) industry is poised for a significant upcycle, with Nomura forecasting 8% growth in FY26 and 10% in FY27. Key drivers include rising freight rates, improved GST affordability, and the aging truck fleet demanding replacements. Fleet operator profitability is improving, boosting confidence in new vehicle purchases and signalling a strong recovery ahead.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 07:12:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ce644e10c98d07889099e_1766647574023.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Set to Lead Global Fight Against 'Conflict Diamonds' Starting 2026!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/India-Set-to-Lead-Global-Fight-Against-Conflict-Diamonds-Starting-2026/694ce519e10c98d07889081c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/India-Set-to-Lead-Global-Fight-Against-Conflict-Diamonds-Starting-2026/694ce519e10c98d07889081c</guid><description>India will chair the Kimberley Process, a global initiative aimed at preventing the trade in conflict diamonds, starting January 1, 2026. The nation, a leading diamond manufacturing and trade hub, will focus on strengthening governance, advancing digital certification, and building consumer trust during its tenure. This marks the third time India will lead the process, underscoring its pivotal role in ensuring ethical diamond sourcing.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 07:09:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ce519e10c98d07889081b_1766647127071.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Commercial Vehicle Boom Ahead? Nomura Predicts Major Indian Industry Upswing!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Commercial-Vehicle-Boom-Ahead-Nomura-Predicts-Major-Indian-Industry-Upswing/694ce3a6e10c98d078890695</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Commercial-Vehicle-Boom-Ahead-Nomura-Predicts-Major-Indian-Industry-Upswing/694ce3a6e10c98d078890695</guid><description>A Nomura report forecasts a significant upcycle for India's medium and heavy commercial vehicle (M&amp;HCV) industry, expecting 8% growth in FY26 and 10% in FY27. Key drivers include robust replacement demand fueled by rising freight rates, GST benefits, and an aging truck fleet. Improved fleet operator economics and cash flows are boosting confidence in new vehicle purchases, positioning the sector for sustained recovery despite limited impact from the Dedicated Freight Corridor.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 07:04:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ce3a6e10c98d078890694_1766646774956.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Marginal Farmers Left Behind: Cooperatives Fail to Reach Millions, Report Reveals Shocking Truth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indias-Marginal-Farmers-Left-Behind-Cooperatives-Fail-to-Reach-Millions-Report-Reveals-Shocking-Truth/694cdec9e10c98d078890240</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indias-Marginal-Farmers-Left-Behind-Cooperatives-Fail-to-Reach-Millions-Report-Reveals-Shocking-Truth/694cdec9e10c98d078890240</guid><description>A new report by FEED highlights that less than 25% of India's marginal farmers are members of agricultural cooperatives. These farmers, who form the majority of agricultural households, face structural barriers like complex procedures and social exclusion, hindering their access to credit, inputs, and services. This results in greater dependence on informal markets and increased vulnerability. While cooperatives improve outcomes for members, significant challenges remain, including limited digital adoption and a stark gender gap in leadership roles.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 06:41:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cdec9e10c98d07889023f_1766645525637.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zepto's Secret IPO Plan Revealed! Quick Commerce Giant Eyes Stock Market Listing Next Year</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Zeptos-Secret-IPO-Plan-Revealed-Quick-Commerce-Giant-Eyes-Stock-Market-Listing-Next-Year/694cdf25e10c98d07889030c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Zeptos-Secret-IPO-Plan-Revealed-Quick-Commerce-Giant-Eyes-Stock-Market-Listing-Next-Year/694cdf25e10c98d07889030c</guid><description>Quick commerce startup Zepto is set to confidentially file its draft IPO papers on December 26, aiming for a stock market listing next year. This move positions Zepto, founded in 2020, to become one of the youngest startups to go public in India, joining rivals like Blinkit (Eternal) and Swiggy in the public arena. The company was last valued at around $7 billion.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 06:41:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cdf25e10c98d07889030b_1766645700155.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vedanta Sesa Goa Saves Enough Energy to Power 6,000 Homes Annually Through Tech Upgrades!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Vedanta-Sesa-Goa-Saves-Enough-Energy-to-Power-6000-Homes-Annually-Through-Tech-Upgrades/694cde3ae10c98d07889012c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Vedanta-Sesa-Goa-Saves-Enough-Energy-to-Power-6000-Homes-Annually-Through-Tech-Upgrades/694cde3ae10c98d07889012c</guid><description>Vedanta's Sesa Goa subsidiary has achieved nearly 8 million energy units in savings for FY'25 and the current fiscal. This accomplishment, driven by technology upgrades like smart systems and innovations, is enough to supply electricity to over 6,000 average Indian households annually. The initiative underscores the company's dedication to sustainable mining and clean energy as part of India's national goals.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 06:38:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cde3ae10c98d07889012b_1766645557728.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Gig Workers Strike! Amazon, Zomato, Swiggy Platforms Face Nationwide Shutdown This December!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-Gig-Workers-Strike-Amazon-Zomato-Swiggy-Platforms-Face-Nationwide-Shutdown-This-December/694cdd70e10c98d07888fff7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indias-Gig-Workers-Strike-Amazon-Zomato-Swiggy-Platforms-Face-Nationwide-Shutdown-This-December/694cdd70e10c98d07888fff7</guid><description>Delivery workers from major platforms like Amazon, Zomato, Zepto, Blinkit, Swiggy, and Flipkart are planning a nationwide strike on December 25 and December 31, 2025. Unions cite worsening conditions including falling incomes, unsafe delivery deadlines, and lack of social security. They are demanding fair pay systems, an end to hazardous ultra-fast delivery models, and better job security measures like insurance and pension benefits.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 06:36:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cdd70e10c98d07888fff6_1766645175323.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 2026 Economic Forecast: Reforms, Data Overhaul, and US Trade Deal Take Center Stage!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2026-Economic-Forecast-Reforms-Data-Overhaul-and-US-Trade-Deal-Take-Center-Stage/694cde5be10c98d07889016c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2026-Economic-Forecast-Reforms-Data-Overhaul-and-US-Trade-Deal-Take-Center-Stage/694cde5be10c98d07889016c</guid><description>India's economy is poised for continued macro-economic reforms into 2026, supported by sub-one percent retail inflation and monetary policy easing. Key developments to watch include a significant overhaul of GDP and inflation calculation methods with new base years (2022-23 for GDP/IIP, 2024 for CPI). The Reserve Bank of India has already cut its repo rate to 5.25% to boost growth. Additionally, progress is expected on the US-India trade deal and amendments to the Insolvency Code, shaping the economic landscape.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 06:36:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cde5be10c98d07889016b_1766645459865.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PAN Card Urgency: Final 6 Days to Link Aadhaar! Avoid Deactivation by January 1st</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/PAN-Card-Urgency-Final-6-Days-to-Link-Aadhaar-Avoid-Deactivation-by-January-1st/694cd849e10c98d07888fb30</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/PAN-Card-Urgency-Final-6-Days-to-Link-Aadhaar-Avoid-Deactivation-by-January-1st/694cd849e10c98d07888fb30</guid><description>Indian taxpayers who obtained Aadhaar on or before October 1, 2024, have until December 31, 2025, to link it with their Permanent Account Number (PAN). Failure to do so by this deadline will result in PAN deactivation from January 1, 2026, impacting financial transactions, tax filing, and investments. This specific deadline applies to a group of PAN holders who received their PAN using an Aadhaar Enrolment ID.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 06:12:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cd849e10c98d07888fb2f_1766643864244.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold to Skyrocket to $5200? Expert Reveals Shocking 2026 Forecast!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-to-Skyrocket-to-5200-Expert-Reveals-Shocking-2026-Forecast/694cd7efe10c98d07888fa91</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-to-Skyrocket-to-5200-Expert-Reveals-Shocking-2026-Forecast/694cd7efe10c98d07888fa91</guid><description>Gold is projected to surge significantly in 2026, potentially reaching $5,200 per ounce, according to Anindya Banerjee, Senior VP at Kotak Securities. Central banks are actively diversifying their reserves away from the US dollar, a trend expected to intensify with ongoing de-dollarization efforts. This, combined with potential Federal Reserve rate cuts and broader currency debasement, creates a strongly bullish outlook for the precious metal.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 06:12:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cd7efe10c98d07888fa90_1766643765526.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Real Estate Gold Rush: Why Smart Investors Are Ditching Metros for Tier II &amp; III Cities!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Real-Estate-Gold-Rush-Why-Smart-Investors-Are-Ditching-Metros-for-Tier-II-and-III-Cities/694cd835e10c98d07888fae7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Real-Estate-Gold-Rush-Why-Smart-Investors-Are-Ditching-Metros-for-Tier-II-and-III-Cities/694cd835e10c98d07888fae7</guid><description>Real estate investment is surging in India's Tier II and III cities, driven by rising incomes, robust infrastructure, and evolving buyer preferences. Manoj Dhanotiya of Micro Mitti highlights that these cities are attracting significant urban population growth and organized employment, offering greater affordability and larger homes than metros. While challenges like market oversupply exist, these emerging locations present promising capital appreciation potential, making them attractive for diversified investment portfolios.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 06:12:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cd835e10c98d07888fae6_1766643965518.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Toyota Sales Plummet: China's Subsidy Cut Triggers Major Global Slump! Is Your Investment Safe?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Toyota-Sales-Plummet-Chinas-Subsidy-Cut-Triggers-Major-Global-Slump-Is-Your-Investment-Safe/694cd7a0e10c98d07888fa35</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Toyota-Sales-Plummet-Chinas-Subsidy-Cut-Triggers-Major-Global-Slump-Is-Your-Investment-Safe/694cd7a0e10c98d07888fa35</guid><description>Toyota Motor Corporation reported a significant 1.9% drop in global sales to 965,919 units and a 3.4% decrease in production to 934,001 units in November. The decline is largely attributed to a sharp 12% fall in sales in China, where the government has ended subsidies for electric and fuel-efficient vehicles, impacting sales of Toyota and Lexus brands.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 06:12:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cd7a0e10c98d07888fa34_1766643882299.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Holds Steady on Christmas Day: Unchanged Rates Despite Global Buzz - What Investors Need to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Holds-Steady-on-Christmas-Day-Unchanged-Rates-Despite-Global-Buzz-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/694cd532e10c98d07888f78f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Holds-Steady-on-Christmas-Day-Unchanged-Rates-Despite-Global-Buzz-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/694cd532e10c98d07888f78f</guid><description>On December 25, 2025, gold prices in India remained unchanged. 24K gold held at ₹138,250 per 10 grams, and 22K gold stayed at ₹126,729 per 10 grams. Prices are influenced by global rates, US dollar, and import duties. The market saw consolidation after hitting record highs, with investors assessing upcoming US Federal Reserve actions and geopolitical events.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 06:02:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cd532e10c98d07888f78e_1766643113488.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India IPO Boom Hits Record ₹1.75 Lakh Cr, But Investor Returns Plummet to 3-Year Low!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/India-IPO-Boom-Hits-Record-175-Lakh-Cr-But-Investor-Returns-Plummet-to-3-Year-Low/694cd558e10c98d07888f825</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/India-IPO-Boom-Hits-Record-175-Lakh-Cr-But-Investor-Returns-Plummet-to-3-Year-Low/694cd558e10c98d07888f825</guid><description>India's IPO market achieved a record ₹1.75 lakh crore in fundraising in 2025 from 101 companies. However, average listing gains have dropped to a three-year low of 9.9%, significantly down from previous years. This decline is attributed to richer IPO valuations, subdued demand, higher supply, and increased investor selectivity. The trend of Offer-for-Sale (OFS) also dominated IPO proceeds, indicating promoter stake monetization.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 06:02:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cd558e10c98d07888f824_1766643219768.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Game-Changing Tax Overhaul Arrives April 1st! Discover the New Rules and Lower Rates!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Game-Changing-Tax-Overhaul-Arrives-April-1st-Discover-the-New-Rules-and-Lower-Rates/694cd534e10c98d07888f7ba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Game-Changing-Tax-Overhaul-Arrives-April-1st-Discover-the-New-Rules-and-Lower-Rates/694cd534e10c98d07888f7ba</guid><description>India is set to implement a major tax overhaul starting April 1, 2025, with a new Income Tax Act replacing the old one. The government has already simplified the GST structure, compressing slabs and cutting rates on many goods and services to boost domestic demand amidst global economic challenges. Further reforms are planned for customs duties, aiming for greater transparency and simplification. These changes aim to stimulate consumption, support growth, and enhance ease of doing business.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 06:00:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cd534e10c98d07888f7b9_1766643061603.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's $1 Trillion Export Dream Fades: Why Shipments Are Losing Momentum!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-1-Trillion-Export-Dream-Fades-Why-Shipments-Are-Losing-Momentum/694cd4a4e10c98d07888f6e9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-1-Trillion-Export-Dream-Fades-Why-Shipments-Are-Losing-Momentum/694cd4a4e10c98d07888f6e9</guid><description>India is likely to miss its ambitious $1 trillion export target for FY26 due to a global economic slowdown and rising protectionism, according to the Global Trade Research Initiative (GTRI). Founder Ajay Shrivastava projects total exports to reach only around $850 billion, falling short by $150 billion. While services exports show growth, merchandise shipments are stagnant. Achieving the target hinges on major trade agreements and diversifying India's export basket to include more medium to high-tech products.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 06:00:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cd4a4e10c98d07888f6e8_1766642915726.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Luxury Housing EXPLODES Beyond Metros: $103 Billion Boom on the Horizon!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Luxury-Housing-EXPLODES-Beyond-Metros-103-Billion-Boom-on-the-Horizon/694cd38be10c98d07888f5b3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Luxury-Housing-EXPLODES-Beyond-Metros-103-Billion-Boom-on-the-Horizon/694cd38be10c98d07888f5b3</guid><description>India's premium and luxury housing market is experiencing a significant expansion, shifting demand from major metros to Tier-2 and Tier-3 cities. Projections show this segment growing at a 35% CAGR, from $17 billion in 2024 to over $103 billion by 2030, driven by rising incomes, lifestyle upgrades, and a preference for enhanced living experiences in emerging urban centers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 05:55:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cd38be10c98d07888f5b2_1766642639820.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>New Tax Regime Shake-up: Is ELSS Losing Its Luster While PPF Stays Strong?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/New-Tax-Regime-Shake-up-Is-ELSS-Losing-Its-Luster-While-PPF-Stays-Strong/694cce3fe10c98d07888f175</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/New-Tax-Regime-Shake-up-Is-ELSS-Losing-Its-Luster-While-PPF-Stays-Strong/694cce3fe10c98d07888f175</guid><description>India's new optional tax regime, now the default, offers lower tax rates and fewer deductions. This shift has significantly reduced the appeal of Equity Linked Savings Schemes (ELSS). While investments like PPF remain attractive for debt savings, taxpayers are adapting their strategies. Experts advise focusing on goal-based investing rather than solely tax benefits, warning against potential underinvestment due to the reduced compulsion to save for tax purposes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 05:32:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cce3fe10c98d07888f174_1766641450399.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Symbiotec Pharmalab Launches Massive ₹2,180 Crore IPO: A Game Changer for Pharma Investors?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Symbiotec-Pharmalab-Launches-Massive-2180-Crore-IPO-A-Game-Changer-for-Pharma-Investors/694ccdfee10c98d07888f11d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Symbiotec-Pharmalab-Launches-Massive-2180-Crore-IPO-A-Game-Changer-for-Pharma-Investors/694ccdfee10c98d07888f11d</guid><description>Symbiotec Pharmalab Limited has announced an Initial Public Offering (IPO) worth ₹2,180 crore. The offering includes a ₹150 crore fresh issue to raise capital and a ₹2,030 crore offer for sale by existing shareholders. The company, a global leader in corticosteroid and steroidal-hormone APIs, was advised by Khaitan &amp; Co, while TT&amp;A and Hogan Lovells represented the book running lead managers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 05:32:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ccdfee10c98d07888f11c_1766641255283.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mumbai's New Airport Era Begins: Air India Express Launches Flights, Unlocking Massive Travel Potential!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Mumbais-New-Airport-Era-Begins-Air-India-Express-Launches-Flights-Unlocking-Massive-Travel-Potential/694ccd9fe10c98d07888f063</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Mumbais-New-Airport-Era-Begins-Air-India-Express-Launches-Flights-Unlocking-Massive-Travel-Potential/694ccd9fe10c98d07888f063</guid><description>Air India Express has officially inaugurated commercial operations at the new Navi Mumbai International Airport (NMIA), becoming one of the first airlines to launch services on its opening day. The Tata Group-owned carrier commenced direct flights to Bengaluru and Delhi, marking a significant step for Mumbai's second aviation gateway. This expansion aims to enhance capacity and ease congestion at the existing Mumbai airport, with further service ramp-ups planned.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 05:30:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ccd9fe10c98d07888f062_1766641117144.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Invesco India's Top Funds Surge: Discover Top 3 Equity Schemes Beating Benchmarks!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Invesco-Indias-Top-Funds-Surge-Discover-Top-3-Equity-Schemes-Beating-Benchmarks/694ccd4be10c98d07888f002</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Invesco-Indias-Top-Funds-Surge-Discover-Top-3-Equity-Schemes-Beating-Benchmarks/694ccd4be10c98d07888f002</guid><description>Invesco India Mutual Fund, managing ₹1.5 trillion, focuses on quality businesses with strong fundamentals, ESG integration, and risk management. This analysis highlights its top 3 equity schemes: Invesco India Small Cap Fund (32.7% 5-yr CAGR vs 30.5% benchmark), Invesco India Focused Fund (23.2% 5-yr CAGR vs 21.2% benchmark), and Invesco India Mid Cap Fund (29.6% 5-yr CAGR vs 28.9% benchmark), all outperforming their respective indices and peers with strong risk-reward ratios.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 05:27:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ccd4be10c98d07888f001_1766641131360.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Deepak Fertilisers' Bold Move: Acquisition Set to Ignite Explosives Market Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Deepak-Fertilisers-Bold-Move-Acquisition-Set-to-Ignite-Explosives-Market-Growth/694ccd28e10c98d07888efb3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Deepak-Fertilisers-Bold-Move-Acquisition-Set-to-Ignite-Explosives-Market-Growth/694ccd28e10c98d07888efb3</guid><description>Deepak Fertilisers and Petrochemicals Corporation, via its subsidiary Deepak Mining Solutions, has agreed to acquire 100% equity in an unnamed explosives manufacturer. This strategic move aims to boost exports of value-added products and services, leveraging upcoming Technical Ammonium Nitrate (TAN) capacities. The deal value and acquired company name are confidential until the transaction closes, pending fulfillment of certain conditions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 05:27:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ccd28e10c98d07888efb2_1766641011996.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Talks Heat Up: Ambassador Kwatra Reveals Key Progress &amp; Stellar Space Partnership!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/India-US-Trade-Talks-Heat-Up-Ambassador-Kwatra-Reveals-Key-Progress-and-Stellar-Space-Partnership/694cc7bbe10c98d07888e6f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/India-US-Trade-Talks-Heat-Up-Ambassador-Kwatra-Reveals-Key-Progress-and-Stellar-Space-Partnership/694cc7bbe10c98d07888e6f0</guid><description>India's Ambassador to the US, Vinay Kwatra, confirmed continuous engagement with the United States Trade Representative (USTR) to forge a mutually beneficial and balanced trade arrangement. He highlighted significant progress in bilateral ties, particularly in space cooperation, citing the recent successful launch of an American commercial satellite by ISRO's LVM3 rocket as a major milestone. This event underscores the deepening partnership between India and the US in technology and exploration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 05:04:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cc7bbe10c98d07888e6ef_1766639692874.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2026 Cinema Comeback: India's ₹13,500 Crore Box Office Surge! Big Stars Fade, Content Reigns Supreme. Uncover the Secrets!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/2026-Cinema-Comeback-Indias-13500-Crore-Box-Office-Surge-Big-Stars-Fade-Content-Reigns-Supreme-Uncover-the-Secrets/694cc62ce10c98d07888e544</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/2026-Cinema-Comeback-Indias-13500-Crore-Box-Office-Surge-Big-Stars-Fade-Content-Reigns-Supreme-Uncover-the-Secrets/694cc62ce10c98d07888e544</guid><description>Indian cinemas are set for a strong 2026, following a robust 2025 projected to close with ₹13,000-13,500 crore in collections, a 10-14% year-on-year increase. While major star-led films saw mixed success, surprise hits and the booming performance of regional cinema underscore a shift. Experts highlight that audiences now prioritize strong narratives and unique concepts over just star power or scale. The industry looks towards original stories, well-made mid-budget films, and stricter adherence to anti-piracy measures and theatrical windows for continued growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 04:58:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cc62ce10c98d07888e543_1766639208270.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ola Electric's Shocking Comeback: Can Bhavish Aggarwal Reclaim Lost Ground From TVS &amp; Bajaj?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Ola-Electrics-Shocking-Comeback-Can-Bhavish-Aggarwal-Reclaim-Lost-Ground-From-TVS-and-Bajaj/694cc5bde10c98d07888e4c5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Ola-Electrics-Shocking-Comeback-Can-Bhavish-Aggarwal-Reclaim-Lost-Ground-From-TVS-and-Bajaj/694cc5bde10c98d07888e4c5</guid><description>Once India's EV leader, Ola Electric faces a severe market share decline and valuation drop, now fifth in sales behind TVS Motors and Bajaj Auto. CEO Bhavish Aggarwal sold personal shares to repay loans amid regulatory scrutiny over service and consumer rights. The company is focused on cost-cutting and improving ownership experience while also expanding into battery storage.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 04:54:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cc5bde10c98d07888e4c4_1766639381959.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lenskart Eyes Korea: $23 Million Investment in iiNeer Corp. to Revolutionize Optical Tech!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Lenskart-Eyes-Korea-23-Million-Investment-in-iiNeer-Corp-to-Revolutionize-Optical-Tech/694cc545e10c98d07888e428</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Lenskart-Eyes-Korea-23-Million-Investment-in-iiNeer-Corp-to-Revolutionize-Optical-Tech/694cc545e10c98d07888e428</guid><description>Lenskart Singapore is acquiring a 29.24% stake in South Korean startup iiNeer Corp. for approximately ₹186 million ($23 million). This strategic investment aims to bolster Lenskart's in-house optical hardware capabilities, including lens cutting and testing equipment, promising improved operational efficiencies and cost reductions. The deal is expected to conclude by January 31, 2026.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 04:53:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cc545e10c98d07888e427_1766638980974.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Forces Chase Oil Tanker Away From Venezuela! Is This A New Blockade Tactic?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/US-Forces-Chase-Oil-Tanker-Away-From-Venezuela-Is-This-A-New-Blockade-Tactic/694cc3b4e10c98d07888e281</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/US-Forces-Chase-Oil-Tanker-Away-From-Venezuela-Is-This-A-New-Blockade-Tactic/694cc3b4e10c98d07888e281</guid><description>US forces pursued a sanctioned oil tanker, Bella 1, which turned away from Venezuela towards the Atlantic Ocean. This incident highlights the US strategy under President Trump to pressure Venezuela's government by disrupting its oil exports through an ongoing blockade, a move aiming to squeeze the nation's finances.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 04:44:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694cc3b4e10c98d07888e280_1766638767290.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>