<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:58:39 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Aviation Fuel Costs Drop, Airlines Get Relief</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Aviation-Fuel-Costs-Drop-Airlines-Get-Relief/697eda9246be08bbe62fa72d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Aviation-Fuel-Costs-Drop-Airlines-Get-Relief/697eda9246be08bbe62fa72d</guid><description>Indian airlines received a significant cost reprieve as Aviation Turbine Fuel (ATF) prices were reduced for the second consecutive month, effective February 1, 2026. Domestic ATF costs fell by approximately Rs 929.63 per kilolitre (nearly 1%), with international rates also declining by roughly 1.6%. These reductions are crucial, as fuel constitutes 35-40% of an airline's operating expenses, directly impacting profitability and ticket pricing strategies.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:48:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697eda9246be08bbe62fa72c_1769921251665.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gabion Technologies Secures ₹6.35 Cr Orders, Gains Bullet Train Project Approval</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Gabion-Technologies-Secures-635-Cr-Orders-Gains-Bullet-Train-Project-Approval/697ed9a246be08bbe62fa672</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Gabion-Technologies-Secures-635-Cr-Orders-Gains-Bullet-Train-Project-Approval/697ed9a246be08bbe62fa672</guid><description>Gabion Technologies India has announced receipt of multiple work and supply orders aggregating approximately ₹6.35 Cr during the week of January 25-31, 2026. Key among these is a crucial Notice of No Objection (NONO) from Larsen &amp; Toubro Limited, approving Gabion Technologies as a vendor for slope protection works for the Mumbai-Ahmedabad High Speed Rail (MAHSR) Project, following successful sample testing. The company stated these orders do not alter its business model or risk profile.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:43:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ed9a246be08bbe62fa671_1769921012381.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold, Silver Plunge: Dollar Surge, Profit-Taking Hit Bullion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Plunge-Dollar-Surge-Profit-Taking-Hit-Bullion/697ed6d846be08bbe62fa0ee</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Plunge-Dollar-Surge-Profit-Taking-Hit-Bullion/697ed6d846be08bbe62fa0ee</guid><description>Precious metals experienced a dramatic sell-off on Friday, January 30, 2026, with spot gold falling nearly 10% and silver over 27% from record highs. This global rout led to approximately 9% lower openings on India's MCX on February 1, with gold trading near ₹1.4 lakh/10g and silver near ₹2.74 lakh/kg. Analysts cite a strengthening US dollar, profit-booking, and hawkish Federal Reserve expectations as key triggers. Divergent investor sentiment exists, with caution urged for silver due to its volatility and overbought condition, while gold's long-term fundamentals are seen as more stable.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:33:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ed6d846be08bbe62fa0ed_1769920406952.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Defence Earnings Diverge: BDL Slumps, Zen Tech Soars</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defence-Earnings-Diverge-BDL-Slumps-Zen-Tech-Soars/697ed6d546be08bbe62fa0db</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defence-Earnings-Diverge-BDL-Slumps-Zen-Tech-Soars/697ed6d546be08bbe62fa0db</guid><description>Defense sector stocks Bharat Dynamics Ltd. and Zen Technologies Ltd. saw divergent market reactions following their third-quarter earnings announcements for the period ending December 31, 2025. Bharat Dynamics reported a significant profit decline and revenue miss, leading to a stock drop. In contrast, Zen Technologies posted robust consolidated financial growth, driven by strong order inflows and a healthy order book, propelling its shares upward.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:31:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ed6d546be08bbe62fa0da_1769920291301.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Tumbles 6% Ahead of Budget 2026 on Dollar Surge, Tensions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Tumbles-6percent-Ahead-of-Budget-2026-on-Dollar-Surge-Tensions/697ed66046be08bbe62fa028</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Tumbles-6percent-Ahead-of-Budget-2026-on-Dollar-Surge-Tensions/697ed66046be08bbe62fa028</guid><description>Gold prices plummeted 6% on February 1 to Rs 1,43,205 per 10 grams on the MCX. The sharp decline from Rs 1,52,345 was attributed to a strengthening dollar and ongoing geopolitical tensions. Spot gold on Comex also fell over 8% to approximately $4,879 per ounce, with traders bracing for the Union Budget 2026.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:30:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ed66046be08bbe62fa027_1769920170328.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Plunges Amid Dollar Surge, Budget Watch</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Plunges-Amid-Dollar-Surge-Budget-Watch/697ed5e246be08bbe62f9f36</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Plunges-Amid-Dollar-Surge-Budget-Watch/697ed5e246be08bbe62f9f36</guid><description>Silver prices experienced a significant downturn on February 1, 2026, with MCX contracts falling by 6% to ₹2,74,410 per kilogram. This decline mirrored global trends, exacerbated by a strengthening U.S. dollar and profit-taking following a recent surge past ₹4 lakh. Market participants are keenly observing the upcoming Union Budget 2026 for potential policy announcements that could further influence silver's cost and accessibility in India.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:28:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ed5e246be08bbe62f9f35_1769920039283.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Commodities Crater: Leverage, Margins Spark Gold &amp; Silver Rout</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Commodities-Crater-Leverage-Margins-Spark-Gold-and-Silver-Rout/697ed56f46be08bbe62f9eb3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Commodities-Crater-Leverage-Margins-Spark-Gold-and-Silver-Rout/697ed56f46be08bbe62f9eb3</guid><description>Precious metals gold and silver experienced a violent one-day collapse, with silver futures plunging as much as 38% and gold futures down approximately 16% from record highs. This drastic sell-off, described as the largest single-day drop in decades for both metals, occurred as exchanges, including CME Group, announced significant margin requirement increases. The event highlighted the dangers of excessive leverage in commodity markets, leading to substantial losses for traders and forcing exchanges to step in amidst extreme volatility. The situation unfolded on Sunday, February 1, 2026, coinciding with India's presentation of the Union Budget 2026.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:26:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ed56f46be08bbe62f9eb2_1769919951172.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Braces for Budget Amidst FPI Sell-off; Tax Relief Sought</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Braces-for-Budget-Amidst-FPI-Sell-off-Tax-Relief-Sought/697ed4fa46be08bbe62f9dbe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Braces-for-Budget-Amidst-FPI-Sell-off-Tax-Relief-Sought/697ed4fa46be08bbe62f9dbe</guid><description>Foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) have continued their significant offloading of Indian equities, divesting ₹38,740 crore in January 2026 alone, following a record ₹2.40 lakh crore exodus in 2025. This sustained capital flight has intensified focus on the upcoming Union Budget, with investors and analysts anticipating potential tax reforms to restore FPI sentiment. Key expectations centre on adjustments to long-term capital gains (LTCG) tax, including a possible increase in the exemption limit and a reduction in the tax rate, alongside potential tweaks to Securities Transaction Tax (STT).</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:24:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ed4fa46be08bbe62f9dbd_1769919820065.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget Day Nerves: India Markets Flat Amidst Fiscal Caution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-Day-Nerves-India-Markets-Flat-Amidst-Fiscal-Caution/697ed39346be08bbe62f9b8e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-Day-Nerves-India-Markets-Flat-Amidst-Fiscal-Caution/697ed39346be08bbe62f9b8e</guid><description>Indian equity indices saw muted activity during a special Sunday trading session preceding the Union Budget 2026. Investors maintained a cautious stance, evident in flat movements of the Nifty 50 and Sensex. Expectations center on a growth-oriented, fiscally prudent budget, with potential boosts for manufacturing exports and defense sectors, while historical market reactions to fiscal events vary widely.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:22:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ed39346be08bbe62f9b8d_1769919726379.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hyundai India Smashes Records With Highest-Ever Monthly Sales</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-India-Smashes-Records-With-Highest-Ever-Monthly-Sales/697ed40546be08bbe62f9c9e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-India-Smashes-Records-With-Highest-Ever-Monthly-Sales/697ed40546be08bbe62f9c9e</guid><description>Hyundai Motor India Limited (HMIL) has posted its best-ever January with record domestic sales of 59,107 units, a 9.5% YoY rise. Total monthly sales hit an all-time high of 73,137 units (+11.5% YoY), driven by a strong 20.9% export growth to 14,030 units. Models VENUE and AURA also set personal sales records.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:19:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ed40546be08bbe62f9c9d_1769919563747.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: Railways Poised for Record Capex, Modernization Drive</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Budget-2026-Railways-Poised-for-Record-Capex-Modernization-Drive/697ed39046be08bbe62f9b68</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Budget-2026-Railways-Poised-for-Record-Capex-Modernization-Drive/697ed39046be08bbe62f9b68</guid><description>Union Budget 2026 is set to announce a significant, possibly record-breaking, capital expenditure for Indian Railways. The allocation aims to bolster infrastructure-led economic growth and prioritizes the expansion of Vande Bharat sleeper services, enhanced safety through widespread Kavach system deployment, and modernization of passenger amenities via Amrit Bharat trains. This strategic investment underscores a continued commitment to driving efficiency and connectivity across the network despite prevailing global economic uncertainties.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:18:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ed39046be08bbe62f9b67_1769919473089.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Top Gainers Emerge as Market Opens Positive</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Top-Gainers-Emerge-as-Market-Opens-Positive/697ed0be46be08bbe62f99b6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Top-Gainers-Emerge-as-Market-Opens-Positive/697ed0be46be08bbe62f99b6</guid><description>In a spirited pre-opening session, IFCI Limited, C.E. Info Systems (MapmyIndia), and SPL Petrochemicals Limited registered significant gains on the BSE. IFCI and SPL Petrochemicals saw buying interest following board approvals of their Q3 2025 financial results, while MapmyIndia's advance was attributed to broader market momentum. The S&amp;P BSE Sensex commenced trading higher, contrasting with a notable downturn in the metals sector.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 04:05:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ed0be46be08bbe62f99b5_1769918731665.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Textile Stocks Surge on Budget 2026 Hopes, FTA Tailwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Textile-Stocks-Surge-on-Budget-2026-Hopes-FTA-Tailwinds/697ecf6246be08bbe62f9931</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Textile-Stocks-Surge-on-Budget-2026-Hopes-FTA-Tailwinds/697ecf6246be08bbe62f9931</guid><description>Textile manufacturers and exporters are under investor scrutiny ahead of Union Budget 2026, with companies like Gokaldas Exports, Welspun Living, Vardhman Textiles, Pearl Global, and Trident attracting attention. Buoyed by recent free trade agreements with the EU and UK, the sector anticipates policy support to enhance global competitiveness, scale operations, and protect MSME employment. Building on initiatives from Budget 2025, which focused on cotton productivity and technical textiles, the market looks for continuity and new incentives to sustain growth amidst global economic uncertainties.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 03:59:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ecf6246be08bbe62f9930_1769918390628.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tobacco Tax Hike Squeezes ITC, GPI Shares</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Tobacco-Tax-Hike-Squeezes-ITC-GPI-Shares/697ece6c46be08bbe62f9808</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Tobacco-Tax-Hike-Squeezes-ITC-GPI-Shares/697ece6c46be08bbe62f9808</guid><description>India's enhanced excise duty on cigarettes, effective February 1, 2026, has already triggered substantial share price drops for ITC and Godfrey Phillips India, shedding over 11% in January. Analysts forecast price hikes of 22-50%, directly impacting volumes and profitability, while the government aims to align with WHO tax benchmarks. This regulatory shift forces a sharper focus on diversification strategies for the tobacco majors.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 03:57:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ece6c46be08bbe62f9807_1769918225141.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>APY Pension Hike Pressure Builds Before Budget 2026-27</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/APY-Pension-Hike-Pressure-Builds-Before-Budget-2026-27/697ece6146be08bbe62f97f5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/APY-Pension-Hike-Pressure-Builds-Before-Budget-2026-27/697ece6146be08bbe62f97f5</guid><description>As the Union Budget 2026-27 approaches, subscriber pressure is mounting for increased payouts from the Atal Pension Yojana (APY). Persistent inflation is eroding the real value of the current Rs 1,000-5,000 monthly pension, a key retirement safety net for over 8.66 crore informal sector workers. Despite government assurances of scheme continuation, a formal indication of pension hikes remains absent, setting the stage for keen observation of budget announcements.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 03:55:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ece6146be08bbe62f97f4_1769918124856.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>L&amp;T in Focus: Budget Signals Infrastructure Spending Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/LandT-in-Focus-Budget-Signals-Infrastructure-Spending-Surge/697ecb9946be08bbe62f96b4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/LandT-in-Focus-Budget-Signals-Infrastructure-Spending-Surge/697ecb9946be08bbe62f96b4</guid><description>Larsen &amp; Toubro shares are attracting investor attention ahead of the Union Budget presentation, driven by anticipation of increased capital expenditure. CFO R Shankar Raman forecasts a potential 10% rise in government capex for FY27, seeing ample liquidity to support infrastructure development. As a key indicator for India's industrial and construction sectors, L&amp;T's performance is closely monitored for broader economic trends.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 03:43:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ecb9946be08bbe62f96b3_1769917414820.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PB Fintech: Q3 Results Preview Amid Sector Growth &amp; Cost Pressures</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/PB-Fintech-Q3-Results-Preview-Amid-Sector-Growth-and-Cost-Pressures/697ec8cc46be08bbe62f91b5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/PB-Fintech-Q3-Results-Preview-Amid-Sector-Growth-and-Cost-Pressures/697ec8cc46be08bbe62f91b5</guid><description>PB Fintech, operator of Policybazaar, is anticipated to announce robust third-quarter fiscal 2026 earnings on February 2, 2026. Analyst consensus forecasts a near doubling of net profit to ₹142.26 crore, driven by a 19% revenue increase to ₹1,538.26 crore. Investors will scrutinize management commentary on the impact of GST rate changes on the company's take rate, especially within a market focused on cost efficiencies.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 03:32:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ec8cc46be08bbe62f91b4_1769916710491.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bank Nifty Eyes Budget Cues Amidst Key Resistance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bank-Nifty-Eyes-Budget-Cues-Amidst-Key-Resistance/697ec6ec46be08bbe62f9036</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bank-Nifty-Eyes-Budget-Cues-Amidst-Key-Resistance/697ec6ec46be08bbe62f9036</guid><description>The Bank Nifty index is poised for potential upside as investors await Union Budget announcements, despite a recent pullback. The index closed Friday at 59,610.45, having gained 0.74% in January. Key technical indicators suggest a cautiously optimistic outlook, with critical resistance at 60,000-60,400 and support around 59,000-58,700. Analysts anticipate continued volatility as fiscal policy details emerge.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 03:30:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ec6ec46be08bbe62f9035_1769916484459.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bajaj Auto Q3: Record Revenue, Profit Growth Amid Valuation Debate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bajaj-Auto-Q3-Record-Revenue-Profit-Growth-Amid-Valuation-Debate/697ec6ed46be08bbe62f9042</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bajaj-Auto-Q3-Record-Revenue-Profit-Growth-Amid-Valuation-Debate/697ec6ed46be08bbe62f9042</guid><description>Bajaj Auto reported its highest-ever quarterly revenue of ₹16,204.45 crore and a 25% year-on-year profit increase to ₹2,749.82 crore for Q3 FY26. This performance, driven by strong domestic and export sales, reached new highs in EBITDA at ₹3,161 crore with margins at 20.8%. Despite the robust operational showing, analysts remain divided on the stock's outlook, with concerns over premium valuation multiples tempering optimism.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 03:24:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ec6ed46be08bbe62f9041_1769916222933.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Budget Dilemma: Growth Claims Clash with Inequality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-Dilemma-Growth-Claims-Clash-with-Inequality/697ec14746be08bbe62f8df9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-Dilemma-Growth-Claims-Clash-with-Inequality/697ec14746be08bbe62f8df9</guid><description>India's economy projects robust growth, with GDP expected to expand 7.4% in FY26. However, this optimistic macroeconomic picture masks deep-seated concerns regarding widening income inequality and persistent joblessness, particularly among youth. While the government highlights gains in areas like foreign investment and infrastructure development, the benefits of this growth appear unevenly distributed, challenging the constitutional ideal of shared prosperity.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 03:02:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ec14746be08bbe62f8df8_1769914891623.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Growth 'Oasis': Strengths vs. Domestic Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-Oasis-Strengths-vs-Domestic-Headwinds/697ec0d846be08bbe62f8d46</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-Oasis-Strengths-vs-Domestic-Headwinds/697ec0d846be08bbe62f8d46</guid><description>India's economy is forecast to grow at 7.4% in FY26, presenting a resilient 'oasis' against global turbulence. The Economic Survey 2025-26 confirms strong fiscal health and contained inflation. However, declining household savings, rising debt, stagnant wages, and MSME sector challenges signal significant domestic vulnerabilities that investors must monitor. The rupee's depreciation further complicates the outlook.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 02:59:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ec0d846be08bbe62f8d45_1769914738949.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Reform Agenda Takes Center Stage</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Reform-Agenda-Takes-Center-Stage/697ec0d246be08bbe62f8cf3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Reform-Agenda-Takes-Center-Stage/697ec0d246be08bbe62f8cf3</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026 eschews broad tax relief for a deep reform agenda. Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman's speech pivots to Part B, highlighting 'Reform Express' initiatives aimed at boosting manufacturing, exports, and global competitiveness. This structural focus addresses challenging global trade dynamics and aims to streamline regulations. Despite favorable macroeconomic indicators like projected GDP growth and easing inflation, market sentiment remains cautious due to external pressures. Key initiatives include customs reform and unified export zones, signaling a long-term economic strategy rather than short-term stimulus.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 02:58:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ec0d246be08bbe62f8cf2_1769914656639.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Markets Brace for Budget; Commodities Swing, FIIs Shift Stance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-Brace-for-Budget-Commodities-Swing-FIIs-Shift-Stance/697ebf0946be08bbe62f8acc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-Brace-for-Budget-Commodities-Swing-FIIs-Shift-Stance/697ebf0946be08bbe62f8acc</guid><description>Indian equity markets traded on Sunday for the Union Budget 2026-27, following a cautious Friday close. Gold and silver prices saw sharp declines from recent highs, influenced by a strengthening dollar. Crude oil prices showed mixed signals. Provisional data for Friday indicated a notable shift in institutional flows, with Foreign Institutional Investors (FIIs) turning net buyers and Domestic Institutional Investors (DIIs) net sellers. Sectoral performance varied, with Aquaculture showing strength while Metals – Non-Ferrous faced pressure.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 02:56:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ebf0946be08bbe62f8acb_1769914505201.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Commercial LPG Price Hike Adds to Business Costs Ahead of Budget</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Commercial-LPG-Price-Hike-Adds-to-Business-Costs-Ahead-of-Budget/697ebf6346be08bbe62f8bc8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Commercial-LPG-Price-Hike-Adds-to-Business-Costs-Ahead-of-Budget/697ebf6346be08bbe62f8bc8</guid><description>Effective February 1, 2026, oil marketing companies (OMCs) have raised the price of 19-kg commercial LPG cylinders by ₹49. The revision brings the retail price in Delhi to ₹1,740.50. This increase places immediate pressure on operating costs for businesses, particularly in the food and hospitality sectors. Domestic LPG cylinder prices remain unchanged. This adjustment aligns with OMCs' monthly price reviews influenced by global fuel trends and domestic economic factors.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 02:53:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ebf6346be08bbe62f8bc7_1769914437953.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Eyes MedTech Leap with Research-Linked Incentive Policy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Eyes-MedTech-Leap-with-Research-Linked-Incentive-Policy/697ebef546be08bbe62f8a6f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Eyes-MedTech-Leap-with-Research-Linked-Incentive-Policy/697ebef546be08bbe62f8a6f</guid><description>India's medical device sector, heavily reliant on imports for sophisticated equipment, faces significant barriers in design-led research and development. To bridge this gap, a proposed Research-Linked Incentive (RLI) aims to directly support invention and de-risk the journey from prototype to market. This initiative is designed to complement existing manufacturing policies by cultivating a domestic pipeline of India-origin devices, thereby fulfilling the ambition of 'Innovate in India'.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 02:50:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ebef546be08bbe62f8a6e_1769914185754.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget Day: Markets Brace for Fiscal Outlook Amid Global Jitters</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-Day-Markets-Brace-for-Fiscal-Outlook-Amid-Global-Jitters/697eb9c746be08bbe62f6e14</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-Day-Markets-Brace-for-Fiscal-Outlook-Amid-Global-Jitters/697eb9c746be08bbe62f6e14</guid><description>Indian equity markets are set for a cautious opening as GIFT Nifty futures trade marginally lower, ahead of Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman's Union Budget presentation for FY27. The Economic Survey projects India's GDP growth at 6.8-7.2% for the fiscal year, signaling confidence in policy reforms. However, market sentiment remains influenced by global headwinds, including rising US tariffs and geopolitical tensions, which impacted international markets, leading to a subdued close on Wall Street and in Asia.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 02:30:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697eb9c746be08bbe62f6e13_1769912939992.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NTPC Stock Eyes Dip on Revenue Miss, Renewable Lag</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/NTPC-Stock-Eyes-Dip-on-Revenue-Miss-Renewable-Lag/697eb8d746be08bbe62f6d78</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/NTPC-Stock-Eyes-Dip-on-Revenue-Miss-Renewable-Lag/697eb8d746be08bbe62f6d78</guid><description>NTPC Ltd. reported a standalone revenue miss of ₹40,643 crore for the December quarter, down 1.8% year-on-year, and flat EBITDA of ₹11,991 crore, falling short of analyst expectations. Despite these headwinds, net profit rose 5.8% to ₹4,987 crore and margins improved. However, execution challenges in its renewable energy arm, NTPC Green Energy, which commissioned only 2.1 GW against a 5 GW target, led to a 73% profit decline in that division. Tendering plans for renewables have also been moderated.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 02:27:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697eb8d746be08bbe62f6d77_1769912829897.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Markets Eye Budget 2026; Key Stocks Hover Amidst Cautious Trade</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Eye-Budget-2026-Key-Stocks-Hover-Amidst-Cautious-Trade/697eb24846be08bbe62f6b42</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indian-Markets-Eye-Budget-2026-Key-Stocks-Hover-Amidst-Cautious-Trade/697eb24846be08bbe62f6b42</guid><description>Indian equity markets are poised for a subdued start on Sunday, February 1, 2026, as indicated by GIFT Nifty futures trading near 25,400. This follows a cautious trading session on Friday, January 31, where both the Nifty 50 and BSE Sensex concluded lower, snapping a three-day gaining streak. Investor sentiment remains tempered by anticipation for the Union Budget 2026, while global markets present mixed signals.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 01:55:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697eb24846be08bbe62f6b41_1769910936323.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Markets Await Budget: Tax Reforms, Growth Signals Crucial</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-Await-Budget-Tax-Reforms-Growth-Signals-Crucial/697ead9b46be08bbe62f69aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-Await-Budget-Tax-Reforms-Growth-Signals-Crucial/697ead9b46be08bbe62f69aa</guid><description>Indian markets are treading cautiously ahead of the Union Budget, with a strong consensus among investors and market veterans for significant capital gains tax reforms. Expectations center on standardizing holding periods and potentially reversing recent tax rate adjustments to boost market sentiment. Alongside tax relief, investors anticipate fiscal signals reinforcing GDP growth and corporate earnings recovery. This anticipation occurs against a backdrop of subdued global economic cues, including contraction in China's manufacturing sector, and a recent sharp correction in gold and silver prices.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 01:36:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ead9b46be08bbe62f69a9_1769909724294.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget Day Sparks India Market Focus Amidst Sector Bets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-Day-Sparks-India-Market-Focus-Amidst-Sector-Bets/697ead2346be08bbe62f68f1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-Day-Sparks-India-Market-Focus-Amidst-Sector-Bets/697ead2346be08bbe62f68f1</guid><description>Indian equity markets are engaged in a special Sunday trading session on February 1, 2026, for the Union Budget 2026 presentation. Indices closed Friday lower, extending January's decline due to foreign fund outflows and global uncertainty. Investor attention is fixed on expected Budget allocations favouring defence, infrastructure, railways, and financial sectors, alongside a broader emphasis on capital expenditure.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 01:34:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ead2346be08bbe62f68f0_1769909612319.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Rural Focus, Global Fortitude</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Rural-Focus-Global-Fortitude/697eaac246be08bbe62f67c1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Rural-Focus-Global-Fortitude/697eaac246be08bbe62f67c1</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman presented India's Union Budget 2026, projecting a robust 7.4% GDP growth for the fiscal year ending March 31. The budget prioritizes rural development and agriculture, proposing a significant increase for the 'Viksit Bharat - G Ram G' employment scheme. This fiscal plan unfolds amidst India's demonstrated economic resilience, having navigated prohibitive US tariffs and stimulated domestic consumption through tax adjustments and infrastructure spending.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 01:23:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697eaac246be08bbe62f67c0_1769909008286.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nvidia CEO Confirms Major OpenAI Investment Amidst Funding Buzz</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nvidia-CEO-Confirms-Major-OpenAI-Investment-Amidst-Funding-Buzz/697ea95e46be08bbe62f670c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nvidia-CEO-Confirms-Major-OpenAI-Investment-Amidst-Funding-Buzz/697ea95e46be08bbe62f670c</guid><description>Nvidia CEO Jensen Huang confirmed a substantial, though scaled-back, investment in OpenAI, refuting prior reports of internal doubt. The move comes as OpenAI seeks up to $100 billion, amid increased competition and larger potential investments from rivals like Amazon. Nvidia’s stock saw high trading volume as investors processed the news.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 01:18:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ea95e46be08bbe62f670b_1769908706128.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bajaj Auto Q3 Results: Mixed Analyst Views Amidst Record Revenue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bajaj-Auto-Q3-Results-Mixed-Analyst-Views-Amidst-Record-Revenue/697ea43a46be08bbe62f65ae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bajaj-Auto-Q3-Results-Mixed-Analyst-Views-Amidst-Record-Revenue/697ea43a46be08bbe62f65ae</guid><description>Bajaj Auto posted its highest-ever quarterly revenue and profit in Q3 FY26, driven by strong domestic and export performance. Despite the robust financials, analysts remain divided, with price targets ranging from ₹9,015 to ₹11,500. Key growth drivers include a recovering export market, an expanding EV portfolio contributing 25% to domestic revenue, and plans for new product launches. However, concerns persist around market share erosion in motorcycles and the company's motorcycle-heavy product mix, fueling debate on its current valuation which trades at a premium to its historical average.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:56:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ea43a46be08bbe62f65ad_1769907387179.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's IPO Surge Tempered by Ethics Call</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-IPO-Surge-Tempered-by-Ethics-Call/697ea25646be08bbe62f64af</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-IPO-Surge-Tempered-by-Ethics-Call/697ea25646be08bbe62f64af</guid><description>Amidst record-breaking IPO activity and robust capital market growth, Securities and Exchange Board of India (Sebi) Chairman Tuhin Kanta Pandey has called for a shift from mere technical compliance to professional conscience. Pandey stressed that ethical substance, not just adherence to rules, is crucial for preventing corporate failures. The Insolvency and Bankruptcy Board of India (IBBI) Chairman Ravi Mital also advocated for streamlining compliance requirements. These discussions occurred at the World Forum of Accountants 2.0, organized by the Institute of Chartered Accountants of India (ICAI), where the evolving role of accountants in an increasingly complex financial ecosystem was a key theme. Technology's impact on auditing and the necessity of human judgment were also highlighted.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:49:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ea25646be08bbe62f64ae_1769906940412.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Soars Past $5,500; Supply Side Gears Up Amid Discovery Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Soars-Past-5500-Supply-Side-Gears-Up-Amid-Discovery-Woes/697ea1da46be08bbe62f6348</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Soars-Past-5500-Supply-Side-Gears-Up-Amid-Discovery-Woes/697ea1da46be08bbe62f6348</guid><description>Gold prices have breached $5,500 per ounce, reaching new all-time highs fueled by persistent geopolitical uncertainty, US dollar weakness, and robust central bank demand. This price surge is now prompting a significant increase in gold mining exploration budgets after a period of decline, signaling a potential future supply response. However, the industry faces headwinds from smaller, more costly discoveries and declining ore grades, mirroring parallels with past commodity cycles.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:48:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ea1da46be08bbe62f6347_1769906838869.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Foreign Capital Fuels India Mid-Cap Bank Rally</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Foreign-Capital-Fuels-India-Mid-Cap-Bank-Rally/697ea1eb46be08bbe62f639e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Foreign-Capital-Fuels-India-Mid-Cap-Bank-Rally/697ea1eb46be08bbe62f639e</guid><description>Global financial institutions are increasing stakes in Indian mid-cap banks, attracted by growth potential and valuations significantly below large-cap competitors. This trend, highlighted by Sumitomo Mitsui's investment in YES Bank and Blackstone's planned stake in Federal Bank, signals foreign confidence. Despite pressures on Net Interest Margins (NIMs) for some, mid-sized lenders like IDFC First Bank and Federal Bank are demonstrating operational resilience, driven by robust retail loan expansion.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:46:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ea1eb46be08bbe62f639d_1769906730308.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Price Crash Batters Hindustan Zinc</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Price-Crash-Batters-Hindustan-Zinc/697e9e9246be08bbe62f6225</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Price-Crash-Batters-Hindustan-Zinc/697e9e9246be08bbe62f6225</guid><description>Hindustan Zinc Ltd. shares experienced their steepest single-day fall since 2008, shedding ₹36,000 crore in market capitalization, following a historic global drop in silver prices. The broader Nifty Metal index also suffered, with HZL and Vedanta contributing significantly to the rout. Vedanta's recent stake sale via OFS adds another layer of investor focus.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:34:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e9e9246be08bbe62f6224_1769905919226.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Hotels See $2B Investment Surge, Focus on Cash Flow</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Hotels-See-2B-Investment-Surge-Focus-on-Cash-Flow/697e9cb746be08bbe62f613a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Hotels-See-2B-Investment-Surge-Focus-on-Cash-Flow/697e9cb746be08bbe62f613a</guid><description>The Indian hospitality industry is experiencing a significant influx of approximately $2 billion in investments, with a clear preference for operational hotel properties. This strategic shift away from speculative greenfield developments is driven by high construction costs, elevated interest rates, and a desire for early cash flows. Major players like Indian Hotels Company (IHCL), Chalet Hotels, and Lemon Tree Hotels are actively involved in acquisitions and portfolio expansion. The sector is buoyed by strong domestic demand and a positive macroeconomic outlook for India, projected to grow between 7.5% and 7.8% in fiscal 2025-26.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:24:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697e9cb746be08bbe62f6139_1769905450737.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>