<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:55:47 +0000</pubDate><item><title>RBI Bans Dark Patterns: Indian Banks Face Trust Overhaul</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Bans-Dark-Patterns-Indian-Banks-Face-Trust-Overhaul/699d9bee04a25a58c84f1bc2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Bans-Dark-Patterns-Indian-Banks-Face-Trust-Overhaul/699d9bee04a25a58c84f1bc2</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has mandated a sweeping crackdown on "dark patterns" within banking applications, requiring all commercial banks to eliminate deceptive design tactics by July 2026. This directive, spurred by widespread consumer complaints identified by LocalCircles, aims to foster greater transparency and consumer trust in India's rapidly expanding digital finance ecosystem. Banks face significant operational and revenue model adjustments as they must comply with explicit consent requirements and prohibit manipulative interface designs, aligning with a global trend towards stricter digital consumer protection.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:39:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d9bee04a25a58c84f1bc1_1771936910465.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Meme Coin Pippin Soars Amidst Crypto Slump; Bitcoin Tests $60K</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/AI-Meme-Coin-Pippin-Soars-Amidst-Crypto-Slump-Bitcoin-Tests-60K/699d9b8104a25a58c84f1abc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/AI-Meme-Coin-Pippin-Soars-Amidst-Crypto-Slump-Bitcoin-Tests-60K/699d9b8104a25a58c84f1abc</guid><description>AI-driven memecoin Pippin has surged over 135% in four weeks, defying a broader crypto downturn where Bitcoin recently dipped below $63,000 before stabilizing around $63,200. While Pippin's rally is fueled by speculative interest, concerns of manipulation and money laundering persist. Bitcoin faces critical $60,000 support, with analysts warning of cascading liquidations if breached, as institutional demand wanes and macro pressures intensify.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:37:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d9b8104a25a58c84f1abb_1771936867425.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SGB Tax Shift Nixes Early Exit Appeal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/SGB-Tax-Shift-Nixes-Early-Exit-Appeal/699d9afc04a25a58c84f19a2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/SGB-Tax-Shift-Nixes-Early-Exit-Appeal/699d9afc04a25a58c84f19a2</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India has announced early redemption dates for five Sovereign Gold Bond (SGB) tranches maturing in April 2026. However, a significant shift in tax policy effective April 1, 2026, will subject premature redemptions to capital gains tax, eroding a key advantage for investors previously able to exit tax-free after five years. This change incentivizes holding SGBs until the full eight-year tenure for continued tax exemption.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:35:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d9afc04a25a58c84f19a1_1771936661046.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AMD Seals $60B Meta AI Chip Deal: Strategic Bet or Margin Pressure?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AMD-Seals-60B-Meta-AI-Chip-Deal-Strategic-Bet-or-Margin-Pressure/699d9afb04a25a58c84f198b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AMD-Seals-60B-Meta-AI-Chip-Deal-Strategic-Bet-or-Margin-Pressure/699d9afb04a25a58c84f198b</guid><description>Advanced Micro Devices (AMD) announced a substantial five-year pact to supply Meta Platforms with up to $60 billion in AI chips and custom CPUs. The deal includes a warrant for Meta to acquire up to 10% of AMD, contingent on performance targets. While AMD shares surged over 10%, the agreement highlights Meta's massive AI infrastructure investment ($115-$135 billion projected for 2026) and its strategy to diversify beyond Nvidia, even as it develops its own silicon. Analysts see sustained demand but also note competitive pressures and the conditional nature of Meta's stake.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:35:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Retail Loans Surge: Gold Rally Masks Unsecured Lending Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Retail-Loans-Surge-Gold-Rally-Masks-Unsecured-Lending-Risk/699d9a7f04a25a58c84f18ac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Retail-Loans-Surge-Gold-Rally-Masks-Unsecured-Lending-Risk/699d9a7f04a25a58c84f18ac</guid><description>India's retail lending sector expanded 18.1% to ₹162 lakh crore in Q4 FY26, propelled by a 44.1% surge in gold loans amid soaring prices and festive demand. Home and personal loans also saw significant growth. However, rising write-offs in unsecured portfolios and a moderation in credit supply indicate underlying risks, prompting regulatory caution despite an overall improvement in overdue loans.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:33:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's AI Paradox: Hyper-personalization or Hyper-fragmentation?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-AI-Paradox-Hyper-personalization-or-Hyper-fragmentation/699d99bd04a25a58c84f169f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-AI-Paradox-Hyper-personalization-or-Hyper-fragmentation/699d99bd04a25a58c84f169f</guid><description>India's vast population defies a single market approach. While AI promises efficiency and personalization for consumer, content, and fintech sectors, its true impact lies in amplifying market fragmentation. Success hinges not just on technological adoption but on mastering operational discipline and deep local insights across diverse micro-economies. The 'Scale Paradox' intensifies as AI implementation costs and complexity create new divides. A calibrated strategy focusing on standardized backbones and customized front-ends remains paramount for navigating this layered opportunity.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:29:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d99bd04a25a58c84f169e_1771936400072.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Sons Board Standoff: Debt Worries vs. Private Status</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Sons-Board-Standoff-Debt-Worries-vs-Private-Status/699d99a204a25a58c84f166b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Sons-Board-Standoff-Debt-Worries-vs-Private-Status/699d99a204a25a58c84f166b</guid><description>Tata Sons' board meeting to extend Chairman N Chandrasekaran's tenure was postponed due to emerging differences, primarily voiced by Noel Tata regarding substantial losses in new ventures like Tata Digital and Air India. These financial strains raise concerns about mounting debt and the potential necessity of an IPO, contrasting with the group's aim to remain an unlisted entity. The situation highlights a critical juncture for the conglomerate's governance and financing strategy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:29:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d99a204a25a58c84f166a_1771936379662.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India: Global Supply Chain Pivot &amp; Consumer Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Global-Supply-Chain-Pivot-and-Consumer-Boom/699d999704a25a58c84f1651</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Global-Supply-Chain-Pivot-and-Consumer-Boom/699d999704a25a58c84f1651</guid><description>Global firms are increasingly integrating India into their supply chains due to geopolitical shifts and rising costs elsewhere. India's 'Make in India' and PLI schemes are driving significant Foreign Direct Investment (FDI) into manufacturing, from electronics to automotive. Simultaneously, a rapidly expanding middle class fuels premiumization, creating a robust consumer market. The recent UK-India Free Trade Agreement further solidifies bilateral trade and investment opportunities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:29:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d999704a25a58c84f1650_1771936323735.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Medical Travel Market Surges Past $13 Billion Target</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-Medical-Travel-Market-Surges-Past-13-Billion-Target/699d999204a25a58c84f1632</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-Medical-Travel-Market-Surges-Past-13-Billion-Target/699d999204a25a58c84f1632</guid><description>India's medical value travel (MVT) market is on track to surpass $13 billion by 2026, more than doubling its $6 billion valuation from 2022. This growth is propelled by the nation's reputation for high-quality, affordable healthcare delivered by internationally accredited institutions and respected professionals. Strategic initiatives like the 'Heal in India' campaign and streamlined medical visas are further solidifying its position as a preferred global health destination. However, sustained leadership hinges on systemic maturity and addressing competitive pressures.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:29:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d999204a25a58c84f1631_1771936301250.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zee Monetizes Legacy IP for Vertical Video Era</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Zee-Monetizes-Legacy-IP-for-Vertical-Video-Era/699d999204a25a58c84f161b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Zee-Monetizes-Legacy-IP-for-Vertical-Video-Era/699d999204a25a58c84f161b</guid><description>Zee Entertainment is strategically leveraging its extensive library of legacy television intellectual property by partnering with mobile-first platform Story TV. This collaboration adapts popular Zee titles into short-form, vertical micro-episodes designed for smartphone consumption, aiming to capture value in India's rapidly expanding digital video segment. The move signals Zee's efforts to monetize dormant assets amidst a fragmented media ecosystem, while Story TV seeks to bolster its content offering in a format projected for significant growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:29:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d999204a25a58c84f161a_1771936288901.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Per Capita Income Surges: Demographics Drive Growth Amidst Global Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Per-Capita-Income-Surges-Demographics-Drive-Growth-Amidst-Global-Shifts/699d995704a25a58c84f159c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Per-Capita-Income-Surges-Demographics-Drive-Growth-Amidst-Global-Shifts/699d995704a25a58c84f159c</guid><description>India's per capita income is accelerating at a faster pace than GDP growth, primarily fueled by a significant deceleration in population expansion, according to RBI Deputy Governor Poonam Gupta. This demographic shift, coupled with sustained economic expansion and macroeconomic stability, positions India favorably against global peers, though forward-looking analysis suggests continued reform pace is critical for sustaining momentum.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:28:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d995704a25a58c84f159b_1771936692726.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Swiggy Launches 'Toing' App to Capture Budget Food Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Swiggy-Launches-Toing-App-to-Capture-Budget-Food-Market/699d97c104a25a58c84f13ef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Swiggy-Launches-Toing-App-to-Capture-Budget-Food-Market/699d97c104a25a58c84f13ef</guid><description>Swiggy has launched its new app, Toing, in Delhi NCR, specifically targeting budget-conscious consumers and students with highly affordable food options. The platform guarantees the lowest item prices, matching restaurant table menus, and crucially, eliminates all packaging charges and platform fees. This aggressive pricing strategy aims to capture a significant segment of the market where affordability is paramount.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:21:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d97c104a25a58c84f13ee_1771936131694.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Jewelry Market Fragmentation: Silver Surges Amidst Digital Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/India-Jewelry-Market-Fragmentation-Silver-Surges-Amidst-Digital-Shift/699d94e704a25a58c84f11bf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/India-Jewelry-Market-Fragmentation-Silver-Surges-Amidst-Digital-Shift/699d94e704a25a58c84f11bf</guid><description>India's multi-billion dollar jewelry market is undergoing a profound fragmentation. Consumer preferences are diverging sharply, influenced by design aesthetics, lifestyle shifts, and digital engagement, moving beyond simple gold-to-silver trends. Retailers face a dual challenge: managing pressured gold margins against silver's flexibility, and adapting to a hybrid online-offline buying journey. This necessitates a strategic re-evaluation of metal sourcing and consumer engagement models, as styling evolves into a key differentiator. The market dynamic is now defined by this intricate interplay of fragmented demand and diverging economic realities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:09:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d94e704a25a58c84f11be_1771936907845.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's STT Hike Fuels Derivatives Debate Amid Court Challenge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Indias-STT-Hike-Fuels-Derivatives-Debate-Amid-Court-Challenge/699d941904a25a58c84f107b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Indias-STT-Hike-Fuels-Derivatives-Debate-Amid-Court-Challenge/699d941904a25a58c84f107b</guid><description>Budget 2026-27 significantly increased Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on Indian derivatives, targeting speculative trading. The move triggered immediate market declines and heightened concerns over trading costs and liquidity. This fiscal adjustment occurs as the Supreme Court reviews a constitutional challenge to STT, examining its legality and potential impact on market participants and government revenue. Analysts anticipate a cautious market response to these compounded pressures.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:05:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d941904a25a58c84f107a_1771935032105.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jindal Power's $1B Loan Signals Resilience Amid India's Strained Dollar Debt Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Jindal-Powers-1B-Loan-Signals-Resilience-Amid-Indias-Strained-Dollar-Debt-Market/699d931304a25a58c84f0ecf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Jindal-Powers-1B-Loan-Signals-Resilience-Amid-Indias-Strained-Dollar-Debt-Market/699d931304a25a58c84f0ecf</guid><description>Jindal Power Ltd. has finalized a significant offshore loan package totaling up to $1 billion to fuel international expansion, including a major project in Botswana. This substantial funding injection offers a vital lifeline to India's dollar loan market, which has seen volumes shrink by nearly half year-to-date in 2026 due to trade swings and increased protectionism. The deal's initial $500 million tranche was priced at approximately 300 basis points over SOFR.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:01:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d931304a25a58c84f0ece_1771934787960.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TATA.ev, Shell Accelerate India EV Charging Network</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/TATAev-Shell-Accelerate-India-EV-Charging-Network/699d930604a25a58c84f0eb5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/TATAev-Shell-Accelerate-India-EV-Charging-Network/699d930604a25a58c84f0eb5</guid><description>TATA.ev and Shell India have deployed 21 new high-speed EV charging hubs featuring 120 kW DC fast chargers across key Indian cities and highways. This significant expansion boosts TATA.ev's network to over 130 locations, addressing India's critical need for public EV charging infrastructure. The move supports TATA Motors' market leadership aspirations amidst rapid EV sector growth and intense competition.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 12:01:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d930604a25a58c84f0eb4_1771936642527.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Voltas Eyes Market Share Hike Amidst AI Push &amp; Competition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Voltas-Eyes-Market-Share-Hike-Amidst-AI-Push-and-Competition/699d928a04a25a58c84f0ddf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Voltas-Eyes-Market-Share-Hike-Amidst-AI-Push-and-Competition/699d928a04a25a58c84f0ddf</guid><description>Tata Group firm Voltas is setting ambitious targets: 20% share in the air conditioner market and 15-20% in broader appliances by 2026. The company unveiled its Summer 2026 portfolio, led by AI-enabled Vertis ACs featuring adaptive cooling and geofencing. This strategic push aims to capture growing demand in India's consumer durables sector, projected to expand significantly. Voltas is also investing in domestic manufacturing capacity to bolster its 'Make in India' initiative and leveraging its extensive distribution network. However, these moves occur against a backdrop of increasing competition, moderating consumer spending, and recent profit declines, raising questions about margin sustainability and the true impact of AI differentiation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:59:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d928a04a25a58c84f0dde_1771934479243.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI's Mis-selling Rules Shift Burden to 'Seller Beware'</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-Mis-selling-Rules-Shift-Burden-to-Seller-Beware/699d91a004a25a58c84f0c54</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-Mis-selling-Rules-Shift-Burden-to-Seller-Beware/699d91a004a25a58c84f0c54</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India has proposed 'Responsible Business Conduct Amendment Directions, 2026,' fundamentally altering financial product sales. The draft shifts accountability from customer consent to product suitability, imposing a 'seller beware' doctrine. This mandates rigorous customer profiling and could pressure fee-based revenue for institutions, particularly impacting bancassurance channels by disallowing bundled sales and requiring clearer agent identification. Post-sale verification and enhanced redressal mechanisms, including full refunds for proven mis-selling, are also key components.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:55:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d91a004a25a58c84f0c53_1771934430498.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Anthropic Prioritizes Safety, Leads Enterprise AI Race</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Anthropic-Prioritizes-Safety-Leads-Enterprise-AI-Race/699d912e04a25a58c84f0ba3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Anthropic-Prioritizes-Safety-Leads-Enterprise-AI-Race/699d912e04a25a58c84f0ba3</guid><description>Anthropic, under CEO Dario Amodei, strategically emphasizes AI regulation and safety, distinguishing itself with a public-benefit corporate structure. The company achieved a $380 billion valuation following a $30 billion Series G round in February 2026. Anthropic leads the enterprise AI market, especially in coding, by building trust through its "Constitutional AI" framework, addressing business concerns about AI risks.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:53:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d912e04a25a58c84f0ba2_1771934147244.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Schaeffler India FY25 Profit Soars 22%; Recommends ₹35 Dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Schaeffler-India-FY25-Profit-Soars-22percent-Recommends-35-Dividend/699d912104a25a58c84f0b88</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Schaeffler-India-FY25-Profit-Soars-22percent-Recommends-35-Dividend/699d912104a25a58c84f0b88</guid><description>Schaeffler India's Board has approved audited FY25 results, reporting a consolidated revenue of ₹9,685.85 crore and a profit after tax of ₹1,150.35 crore. The company recommended a higher dividend of ₹35 per share, signalling robust performance and a commitment to shareholder returns. The Board also noted the upcoming resignation of a non-executive director.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:53:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d912104a25a58c84f0b87_1771934337853.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Interarch Building Solutions Seeks Shareholder Nod for ₹100 Cr QIP, Director Appointment</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Interarch-Building-Solutions-Seeks-Shareholder-Nod-for-100-Cr-QIP-Director-Appointment/699d90ab04a25a58c84f0a61</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Interarch-Building-Solutions-Seeks-Shareholder-Nod-for-100-Cr-QIP-Director-Appointment/699d90ab04a25a58c84f0a61</guid><description>Interarch Building Solutions Limited is requesting shareholder approval for key corporate actions, including raising up to ₹100 Crore through a Qualified Institutional Placement (QIP) and appointing Mr. Manish Kumar Garg as Executive Director. The QIP funds are earmarked for expansion in Pre-Engineered Buildings and Heavy Steel Fabrication projects. E-voting is scheduled from February 26 to March 27, 2026.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:51:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d90ab04a25a58c84f0a60_1771935135882.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ELANTAS Beck FY25 Profit ₹147.78 Cr; Board Recommends ₹7.50 Dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/ELANTAS-Beck-FY25-Profit-14778-Cr-Board-Recommends-750-Dividend/699d906e04a25a58c84f09db</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/ELANTAS-Beck-FY25-Profit-14778-Cr-Board-Recommends-750-Dividend/699d906e04a25a58c84f09db</guid><description>ELANTAS Beck India announced robust financial results for the year ended December 31, 2025, reporting revenue of ₹847.81 crore and a net profit of ₹147.78 crore. The Board of Directors recommended a final dividend of ₹7.50 per equity share, signaling confidence in performance. Board stability was further reinforced with the re-appointment of Mr. Nandkumar Dhekne as an Independent Director for a second term.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:50:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d906e04a25a58c84f09da_1771933940626.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ELANTAS Beck India Q3 FY26 Profit Jumps 32% To ₹39.37 Cr; FY25 Revenue Grows 11.5%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ELANTAS-Beck-India-Q3-FY26-Profit-Jumps-32percent-To-3937-Cr-FY25-Revenue-Grows-115percent/699d906a04a25a58c84f09c4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ELANTAS-Beck-India-Q3-FY26-Profit-Jumps-32percent-To-3937-Cr-FY25-Revenue-Grows-115percent/699d906a04a25a58c84f09c4</guid><description>ELANTAS Beck India reported a robust Q3 FY26, with net profit surging 32% year-on-year to ₹39.37 crore. The company also posted an 11.53% revenue growth for the full fiscal year FY25. A final dividend of ₹7.50 per share was recommended. However, the Ankleshwar plant's operational permit, valid only until October 3, 2026, remains a key concern.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:50:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d906a04a25a58c84f09c3_1771933912872.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndusInd Bank seeks nod for ex-SBI MD Arijit Basu as new Part-time Chairman</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IndusInd-Bank-seeks-nod-for-ex-SBI-MD-Arijit-Basu-as-new-Part-time-Chairman/699d8ee304a25a58c84f06af</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IndusInd-Bank-seeks-nod-for-ex-SBI-MD-Arijit-Basu-as-new-Part-time-Chairman/699d8ee304a25a58c84f06af</guid><description>IndusInd Bank has initiated a postal ballot to seek shareholder approval for appointing Arijit Basu, former MD of SBI and Chairman of HDB Financial Services, as its Non-Executive Independent Director and Part-time Chairman. His proposed tenure is three years, with an annual remuneration of ₹35 lakh plus sitting fees. This move signifies a leadership transition, aiming to leverage Basu's extensive banking experience.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:43:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d8ee304a25a58c84f06ae_1771933648389.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>StarlinePS EGM Approves ₹100 Cr Capital Hike, ₹55 Cr Preferential Issue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/StarlinePS-EGM-Approves-100-Cr-Capital-Hike-55-Cr-Preferential-Issue/699d8ed904a25a58c84f0694</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/StarlinePS-EGM-Approves-100-Cr-Capital-Hike-55-Cr-Preferential-Issue/699d8ed904a25a58c84f0694</guid><description>StarlinePS Enterprises Limited shareholders approved a significant ₹100 crore increase in authorized share capital and a preferential issue of equity shares and convertible warrants totaling ₹55 crore at an Extraordinary General Meeting (EGM) on February 24, 2026. This move aims to fund growth initiatives but may lead to dilution for existing shareholders, altering the company's ownership structure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:43:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d8ed904a25a58c84f0693_1771933937144.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Intellect Design Arena Wins Major AI Platform Mandate for Five Indian Financial Entities</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Intellect-Design-Arena-Wins-Major-AI-Platform-Mandate-for-Five-Indian-Financial-Entities/699d8ec804a25a58c84f067c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Intellect-Design-Arena-Wins-Major-AI-Platform-Mandate-for-Five-Indian-Financial-Entities/699d8ec804a25a58c84f067c</guid><description>Intellect Design Arena Ltd. has secured a significant deal to deploy its Purple Fabric AI platform for enterprise-scale transformation across five entities of a leading Indian financial services group. The mandate, awarded after an eight-month evaluation, marks a major milestone for Purple Fabric in India, underscoring growing confidence in AI solutions for regulated financial institutions and aligning with Intellect's growth strategy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:43:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d8ec804a25a58c84f067b_1771934916077.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>La Opala RG Promoter Boosts Stake to 46.77% in ₹1.87 Cr Deal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/La-Opala-RG-Promoter-Boosts-Stake-to-4677percent-in-187-Cr-Deal/699d8ec804a25a58c84f0666</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/La-Opala-RG-Promoter-Boosts-Stake-to-4677percent-in-187-Cr-Deal/699d8ec804a25a58c84f0666</guid><description>La Opala RG's promoter, Genesis Exports Private Limited, has increased its shareholding by acquiring 91,100 equity shares for approximately ₹1.87 crore. This move raises the promoter's total stake to 46.77%, signalling continued confidence and investment in the company. The transaction was disclosed on February 24, 2026, under SEBI (Prohibition of Insider Trading) Regulations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:43:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d8ec804a25a58c84f0665_1771933704316.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Oil Prices: Geopolitical Risk vs. Looming Supply Glut</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Oil-Prices-Geopolitical-Risk-vs-Looming-Supply-Glut/699d8e5b04a25a58c84f055e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Oil-Prices-Geopolitical-Risk-vs-Looming-Supply-Glut/699d8e5b04a25a58c84f055e</guid><description>Crude oil prices are currently buoyed by geopolitical tensions surrounding Iran, creating a 'geopolitical premium' that elevates benchmarks like Brent crude well above fundamental valuations. However, this premium faces headwinds from increasing global supply forecasts for 2026, substantial inventory builds, and strategic export management by key producers. Investors are weighing this risk against a backdrop of moderating demand growth and a forward-looking energy sector valuation that appears rich relative to historical averages.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:41:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d8e5b04a25a58c84f055d_1771933552405.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RVNL Secures ₹270 Cr Rail Contract Amid Margin Pressures</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/RVNL-Secures-270-Cr-Rail-Contract-Amid-Margin-Pressures/699d8e4f04a25a58c84f053d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/RVNL-Secures-270-Cr-Rail-Contract-Amid-Margin-Pressures/699d8e4f04a25a58c84f053d</guid><description>Rail Vikas Nigam Limited (RVNL) has been awarded a ₹270.22 crore contract by Central Railway for traction substation work on the Daund-Solapur section. The project is to be completed over 24 months on an EPC basis. This follows RVNL's Q3 FY26 results, which showed modest profit growth but also revealed narrowing margins and flat profit before tax, alongside a 16.2% decline in nine-month profit.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:41:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d8e4f04a25a58c84f053c_1771933582810.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Digital Backbone Faces Geopolitical Data Sovereignty Test</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Digital-Backbone-Faces-Geopolitical-Data-Sovereignty-Test/699d8c2304a25a58c84f01b7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Digital-Backbone-Faces-Geopolitical-Data-Sovereignty-Test/699d8c2304a25a58c84f01b7</guid><description>India's critical digital infrastructure, particularly submarine cables, faces escalating threats from natural disasters and geopolitical instability. TRAI Chairman Anil Kumar Lahoti emphasized the need for enhanced resilience and policy solutions. With AI driving exponential data growth and colossal investments in data centers, the nation's reliance on foreign cloud infrastructure and the subsequent risks to data sovereignty present a critical strategic challenge, potentially jeopardizing economic agency and national security.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:31:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d8c2304a25a58c84f01b6_1771932898124.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Trade Pivot: Capacity First for Climate Advantage</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Trade-Pivot-Capacity-First-for-Climate-Advantage/699d8c2004a25a58c84f01a0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Trade-Pivot-Capacity-First-for-Climate-Advantage/699d8c2004a25a58c84f01a0</guid><description>India's 2026 Union Budget signals a strategic shift, allocating significant funds for Carbon Capture, Utilisation, and Storage (CCUS) to decarbonize key export sectors. This initiative moves beyond previous Free Trade Agreements, which often saw market access precede necessary domestic capacity building, leading to widened trade deficits. The focus is now on developing exporter readiness for climate-aligned markets, notably the EU's carbon border mechanisms, to ensure competitive advantage.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:31:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d8c2004a25a58c84f019f_1771932914172.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Airports Expand: Capacity Boom or Debt Doom?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Airports-Expand-Capacity-Boom-or-Debt-Doom/699d8bfe04a25a58c84f0184</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Airports-Expand-Capacity-Boom-or-Debt-Doom/699d8bfe04a25a58c84f0184</guid><description>India's aviation infrastructure is entering a multi-airport era, with new facilities set to add 40 million annual passenger capacity, easing strain on congested metro hubs like Delhi and Mumbai. Crisil Ratings anticipates 8-9% passenger growth by FY30, driven by economic expansion. However, operators GMR Airports and Adani Airports grapple with significant debt loads and execution challenges, while near-term traffic growth remains subdued due to prior disruptions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:31:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d8bfe04a25a58c84f0183_1771933311784.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Apcotex ₹210 Cr Expansion; FY25 PAT ₹541 Cr, 9M-FY26 PAT ₹667 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Apcotex-210-Cr-Expansion-FY25-PAT-541-Cr-9M-FY26-PAT-667-Cr/699d8bf904a25a58c84f016d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Apcotex-210-Cr-Expansion-FY25-PAT-541-Cr-9M-FY26-PAT-667-Cr/699d8bf904a25a58c84f016d</guid><description>Apcotex Industries, a leading producer of synthetic rubber and latex, has initiated a significant capacity addition project worth ₹210 crore for Nitrile Rubber and Synthetic Latex. This strategic investment aims to meet burgeoning domestic and international demand across sectors like gloves, construction, and textiles, reinforcing its market position. While the company posted robust financial performance for FY25 and 9M-FY26, it faces inherent industry risks including competition and economic fluctuations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:31:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d8bf904a25a58c84f016c_1771932807603.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Panafic Industrials Acquires 19.78% Stake in Bazel International Via Debt Conversion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Panafic-Industrials-Acquires-1978percent-Stake-in-Bazel-International-Via-Debt-Conversion/699d8bf704a25a58c84f0157</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Panafic-Industrials-Acquires-1978percent-Stake-in-Bazel-International-Via-Debt-Conversion/699d8bf704a25a58c84f0157</guid><description>Panafic Industrials Limited has acquired a 19.78% equity stake in Bazel International Limited through a preferential allotment, converting an outstanding loan into shares. This strategic move transforms Panafic's role from creditor to a substantial minority shareholder in Bazel International, a company involved in trading, manufacturing, and real estate. The transaction, effective February 20, 2026, sees Bazel International's equity share capital increase to approximately ₹3.86 crore.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:31:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d8bf704a25a58c84f0156_1771934184152.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Powergrid Funding Hike Fuels India's Grid Race</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Powergrid-Funding-Hike-Fuels-Indias-Grid-Race/699d8b3404a25a58c84f0012</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Powergrid-Funding-Hike-Fuels-Indias-Grid-Race/699d8b3404a25a58c84f0012</guid><description>The Indian government has increased Power Grid Corporation of India Ltd.'s (Powergrid) equity investment ceiling per subsidiary to ₹7,500 crore. This move aims to fast-track large transmission projects, including UHVAC and HVDC corridors, crucial for integrating India's growing renewable energy capacity towards its 500 GW target by 2030. While enhancing Powergrid's capacity, it also signals an accelerated competitive push in the sector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:27:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d8b3404a25a58c84f0011_1771933463835.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Inheritance Allocation: Navigating Early 2026's Crossroads</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Inheritance-Allocation-Navigating-Early-2026s-Crossroads/699d8a9404a25a58c84eff7a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Inheritance-Allocation-Navigating-Early-2026s-Crossroads/699d8a9404a25a58c84eff7a</guid><description>Investing a Rs 10 lakh inheritance in early 2026 presents a strategic challenge, balancing the stability of Fixed Deposits (FDs) against the potential growth of Systematic Investment Plans (SIPs) and direct equities. With inflation concerns and a cautious market outlook, capital preservation versus wealth accumulation becomes a critical dichotomy. A diversified approach tailored to individual risk tolerance is paramount to navigate these competing objectives and maximize long-term financial outcomes.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:25:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d8a9404a25a58c84eff79_1771933018673.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MSME Survey: Manufacturing Fuels Growth Amid Sectoral Divergence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/MSME-Survey-Manufacturing-Fuels-Growth-Amid-Sectoral-Divergence/699d87e204a25a58c84efd3c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/MSME-Survey-Manufacturing-Fuels-Growth-Amid-Sectoral-Divergence/699d87e204a25a58c84efd3c</guid><description>The Small Industries Development Bank of India's (SIDBI) October-December 2025 survey highlights a widening gap among MSMEs. Manufacturing sentiment surged, but trading and services sectors saw moderation and rising profit margin concerns. Access to finance showed improvement, particularly for manufacturing firms, and exporters are anticipated to utilize government support schemes. Despite overall positive future expectations, structural weaknesses persist in non-manufacturing segments.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:13:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d87e204a25a58c84efd3b_1771931942659.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PC Jeweller Allots 10.7 Cr Shares Post Warrant Conversion; Capital Rises to ₹801 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/PC-Jeweller-Allots-107-Cr-Shares-Post-Warrant-Conversion-Capital-Rises-to-801-Cr/699d86d304a25a58c84efbf6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/PC-Jeweller-Allots-107-Cr-Shares-Post-Warrant-Conversion-Capital-Rises-to-801-Cr/699d86d304a25a58c84efbf6</guid><description>PC Jeweller Limited has successfully allotted 10.72 crore equity shares following the conversion of warrants, bringing in ₹45.20 crore. This transaction boosts the company's paid-up equity share capital to ₹801.68 crore. The move signals continued efforts to strengthen its financial base and capital structure.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:09:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d86d304a25a58c84efbf5_1771931846726.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian IT Stocks Tumble on AI Disruption Fears Despite Growth Forecasts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Stocks-Tumble-on-AI-Disruption-Fears-Despite-Growth-Forecasts/699d859904a25a58c84ef9e9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Stocks-Tumble-on-AI-Disruption-Fears-Despite-Growth-Forecasts/699d859904a25a58c84ef9e9</guid><description>Despite Nasscom projecting 6.1% revenue growth to $315 billion for India's IT sector in FY26 and a workforce expansion to 5.95 million, market sentiment turned sharply negative. Brokerage Jefferies downgraded TCS to 'Underperform' and Infosys and HCLTech to 'Hold', citing AI-driven structural shifts that could compress managed services revenue and increase cyclicality. The Nifty IT index has seen a significant decline, reflecting investor apprehension over AI's disruptive potential impacting traditional outsourcing models.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:03:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d859904a25a58c84ef9e8_1771931234115.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dhoot &amp; FourFront Forge EV Electronics Powerhouse</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dhoot-and-FourFront-Forge-EV-Electronics-Powerhouse/699d850004a25a58c84ef8e8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dhoot-and-FourFront-Forge-EV-Electronics-Powerhouse/699d850004a25a58c84ef8e8</guid><description>Dhoot Transmission Limited, with Bain Capital's support, is merging FourFront Limited to bolster its automotive electronics and electrical manufacturing platform. This integration unites Dhoot's global manufacturing scale with FourFront's Tier-1 expertise in electro-mechanical and power electronics solutions. The combined entity aims to capture significant growth in electric vehicle (EV) components and advanced automotive electronics, capitalizing on trends like electrification and ADAS, while navigating competitive pressures. This strategic consolidation seeks to create a robust end-to-end supplier for both ICE and EV platforms.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 11:01:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699d850004a25a58c84ef8e7_1771931174113.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>