<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:19:02 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India's Best-Selling Cars: Maruti Suzuki Loses Ground as Tata, Mahindra, Hyundai Race Ahead!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Best-Selling-Cars-Maruti-Suzuki-Loses-Ground-as-Tata-Mahindra-Hyundai-Race-Ahead/694e5280e10c98d0788e4dbb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Best-Selling-Cars-Maruti-Suzuki-Loses-Ground-as-Tata-Mahindra-Hyundai-Race-Ahead/694e5280e10c98d0788e4dbb</guid><description>Maruti Suzuki's dominance in India's top-selling car list is fading, shrinking from eight models in 2021 to six. Rivals Tata Motors and Mahindra &amp; Mahindra are making significant gains, with Tata's Punch topping the annual sales chart for the first time. Hyundai's Creta and Tata's Nexon are also strong performers in 2025, pushing Maruti down. Despite this, Maruti retains strength in CNG vehicles.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:05:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e5280e10c98d0788e4dba_1766740689927.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Year-End Jitters: US Policies Spark Global Turmoil! RBI Battles Weak Rupee &amp; Bond Market - What Investors Need to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Year-End-Jitters-US-Policies-Spark-Global-Turmoil-RBI-Battles-Weak-Rupee-and-Bond-Market-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/694e523ce10c98d0788e4cd1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Year-End-Jitters-US-Policies-Spark-Global-Turmoil-RBI-Battles-Weak-Rupee-and-Bond-Market-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/694e523ce10c98d0788e4cd1</guid><description>As the year closes, US policies like tariffs and visa tightening create global market turbulence, affecting emerging economies. India's rupee has seen its worst performance, prompting the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) to intervene heavily as a dollar seller and plan historically high bond purchases. Despite domestic investor faith providing some resilience, investor uncertainty persists for the new year.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:05:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e523ce10c98d0788e4cd0_1766740652607.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Investors Beware: Are You Chasing Stocks or Your Dreams? The Shocking Truth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indian-Investors-Beware-Are-You-Chasing-Stocks-or-Your-Dreams-The-Shocking-Truth/694e51d9e10c98d0788e4bee</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indian-Investors-Beware-Are-You-Chasing-Stocks-or-Your-Dreams-The-Shocking-Truth/694e51d9e10c98d0788e4bee</guid><description>Indian investors often chase high market returns, leading to anxiety and poor decisions. A flawed 'market-first' approach ignores personal needs. True financial well-being starts with a 'goal-first' strategy, calculating your 'Required Rate of Return' based on savings, goals, and time. This personalized approach reduces unnecessary risk and helps investors stay calm and focused during market volatility, turning investing from gambling into engineering for life goals.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:04:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e51d9e10c98d0788e4bed_1766740724933.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coal India's Top Job Shuffle: CMD B. Sairam Now CEO! What This Means for India's Energy Giant?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Coal-Indias-Top-Job-Shuffle-CMD-B-Sairam-Now-CEO-What-This-Means-for-Indias-Energy-Giant/694e51a5e10c98d0788e4b16</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Coal-Indias-Top-Job-Shuffle-CMD-B-Sairam-Now-CEO-What-This-Means-for-Indias-Energy-Giant/694e51a5e10c98d0788e4b16</guid><description>Coal India Limited has appointed its Chairman-cum-Managing Director, B. Sairam, as the company's Chief Executive Officer. This strategic move aims to bolster top-level leadership at India's largest coal producer. Sairam, a mining veteran with over three decades of experience, officially took on the CEO role from December 15, 2025, and his tenure extends until his retirement.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:02:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e51a5e10c98d0788e4b15_1766740526028.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Massive ₹391 Cr Order Boosts Bondada Engineering: NTPC Green Energy Deal Sparks Renewed Growth Hopes!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Massive-391-Cr-Order-Boosts-Bondada-Engineering-NTPC-Green-Energy-Deal-Sparks-Renewed-Growth-Hopes/694e5122e10c98d0788e4a14</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Massive-391-Cr-Order-Boosts-Bondada-Engineering-NTPC-Green-Energy-Deal-Sparks-Renewed-Growth-Hopes/694e5122e10c98d0788e4a14</guid><description>Bondada Engineering has secured a significant work order worth ₹391.38 crore from NTPC Green Energy for the engineering, procurement, and construction (EPC) of a 300 MW solar power project in Lalitpur, Uttar Pradesh. The project is slated for completion within 15 months. This major contract reinforces the company's execution capabilities and strengthens its engagement with prominent Public Sector Undertaking (PSU) clients, enhancing its order book visibility and medium-term revenue growth prospects in the utility-scale solar infrastructure sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 09:00:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e5122e10c98d0788e4a13_1766740491598.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Economy Set for Major 2026 Growth Surge: Report Reveals Key Drivers!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economy-Set-for-Major-2026-Growth-Surge-Report-Reveals-Key-Drivers/694e501ae10c98d0788e47fc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economy-Set-for-Major-2026-Growth-Surge-Report-Reveals-Key-Drivers/694e501ae10c98d0788e47fc</guid><description>A Standard Chartered report projects India's real GDP growth to become more broad-based in 2026, supported by robust monetary and fiscal interventions. Policy measures, including RBI rate cuts and liquidity injections alongside government income tax cuts and GST rationalisation, are expected to revive domestic demand. Inflation is forecast to trend below the Reserve Bank of India's target, while key risks involve global trade disruptions and tariffs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 08:57:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e501ae10c98d0788e47fb_1766740168675.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zee Media Stock Surge? Promoter Boosts Stake to 9.41% - Uncover the Impact!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Zee-Media-Stock-Surge-Promoter-Boosts-Stake-to-941percent-Uncover-the-Impact/694e4c7fe10c98d0788e4308</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Zee-Media-Stock-Surge-Promoter-Boosts-Stake-to-941percent-Uncover-the-Impact/694e4c7fe10c98d0788e4308</guid><description>AUV Innovations LLP, part of the promoter group for Zee Media Corporation Limited, has increased its shareholding to 9.41% after acquiring 1,51,15,614 equity shares on December 24, 2025. This open market purchase raises the promoter's stake from 6.99%, signaling increased confidence in the media company. Earlier smaller purchases below the disclosure threshold were also consolidated.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 08:40:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e4c7fe10c98d0788e4307_1766739236829.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Defence Stocks Skyrocket: ₹80,000 Crore Government Deal on the Horizon? Investor Frenzy!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/India-Defence-Stocks-Skyrocket-80000-Crore-Government-Deal-on-the-Horizon-Investor-Frenzy/694e4b58e10c98d0788e413c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/India-Defence-Stocks-Skyrocket-80000-Crore-Government-Deal-on-the-Horizon-Investor-Frenzy/694e4b58e10c98d0788e413c</guid><description>Indian defence stocks, including Paras Defence, BEL, HAL, and Mazagon Dock, are experiencing a significant rally ahead of a crucial Defence Acquisition Council meeting. The council is expected to clear defence procurement proposals worth approximately ₹80,000 crore, potentially boosting capabilities in air defence and surveillance. Optimism around the upcoming Union Budget's focus on domestic defence production is also fueling investor interest, with analysts recommending investments in key players like Mazagon Dock and Cochin Shipyard.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 08:35:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e4b58e10c98d0788e413b_1766738999955.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Insurance Reforms Stuck: Ambitious 2025 Plans Face Major Delays!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indias-Insurance-Reforms-Stuck-Ambitious-2025-Plans-Face-Major-Delays/694e4af3e10c98d0788e4068</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indias-Insurance-Reforms-Stuck-Ambitious-2025-Plans-Face-Major-Delays/694e4af3e10c98d0788e4068</guid><description>India's insurance sector is experiencing a significant gap between the Insurance Regulatory and Development Authority of India's (IRDAI) ambitious reform agenda for 2025 and actual implementation. Major proposals like composite licensing and 100% Foreign Direct Investment (FDI) are stalled due to legislative delays. Digital platforms such as Bima Sugam and bundled products like Bima Vistar are also facing significant hurdles related to coordination, industry readiness, and technical development, leaving investors and stakeholders questioning the delivery timeline.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 08:31:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e4af3e10c98d0788e4067_1766738817959.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-NZ FTA Unlocks New Visas: A Game Changer for Professionals Amidst Indian Mobility Slowdown?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-NZ-FTA-Unlocks-New-Visas-A-Game-Changer-for-Professionals-Amidst-Indian-Mobility-Slowdown/694e4a50e10c98d0788e3f36</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-NZ-FTA-Unlocks-New-Visas-A-Game-Changer-for-Professionals-Amidst-Indian-Mobility-Slowdown/694e4a50e10c98d0788e3f36</guid><description>The proposed New Zealand-India Free Trade Agreement introduces specialized work visas for Indian professionals, offering a vital new pathway. This comes as traditional visa approvals for Indians in New Zealand have significantly cooled, with work visa approvals dropping and residence visa approvals seeing a sharp decline. Student visa rejection rates are also rising, indicating a tightening environment despite continued demand. The FTA's mobility chapter aims to provide more predictable entry, especially for skilled sectors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 08:31:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e4a50e10c98d0788e3f35_1766738606452.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Max Healthcare's Big Leap: ₹200 Cr Hospital Planned for Dehradun!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Max-Healthcares-Big-Leap-200-Cr-Hospital-Planned-for-Dehradun/694e491ce10c98d0788e3cf6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Max-Healthcares-Big-Leap-200-Cr-Hospital-Planned-for-Dehradun/694e491ce10c98d0788e3cf6</guid><description>Max Healthcare Institute Limited is investing ₹170-200 crore to establish a new 130-bed hospital in Dehradun, Uttarakhand. Economic Laws Practice (ELP) provided comprehensive legal advisory for the long-term lease transaction, including land due diligence and finalising agreements. This strategic expansion strengthens Max Healthcare's presence in key regional markets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 08:30:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e491ce10c98d0788e3cf5_1766738292102.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Steel Production Crisis: Import Walls Hike Costs, GTRI Sounds Alarm!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Steel-Production-Crisis-Import-Walls-Hike-Costs-GTRI-Sounds-Alarm/694e4948e10c98d0788e3d79</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Steel-Production-Crisis-Import-Walls-Hike-Costs-GTRI-Sounds-Alarm/694e4948e10c98d0788e3d79</guid><description>A recent report by the Global Trade Research Initiative (GTRI) flags a critical policy contradiction in India's steel sector. While aiming to boost steel production, the government has implemented stringent import barriers on low ash metallurgical coke, a vital raw material. These curbs, including duties and quantitative restrictions, alongside flawed anti-dumping investigations, are significantly raising steelmaking costs. This impacts steel producers, MSMEs, and downstream industries, potentially slowing economic growth. GTRI urges a review of these policies for competitive steel production.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 08:27:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e4948e10c98d0788e3d78_1766738576656.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 2025 Auto Revolution: 9 Game-Changing Cars Redefining the Roads!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-2025-Auto-Revolution-9-Game-Changing-Cars-Redefining-the-Roads/694e48e4e10c98d0788e3c64</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-2025-Auto-Revolution-9-Game-Changing-Cars-Redefining-the-Roads/694e48e4e10c98d0788e3c64</guid><description>India's automobile sector in 2025 showcased maturity, driven by resilient passenger vehicle sales despite inflation. SUVs and electric vehicles led growth, with carmakers focusing on technology, safety, and electrification. Nine standout launches, including the Tata Sierra EV and Mahindra Thar Facelift, are reshaping market expectations and segments, signalling a significant shift towards future mobility.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 08:26:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e48e4e10c98d0788e3c63_1766738215575.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rs 1.5 Trillion Exodus! India's Top Companies See Record Promoter Sell-Off – What's Next for Your Investments?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rs-15-Trillion-Exodus-Indias-Top-Companies-See-Record-Promoter-Sell-Off-Whats-Next-for-Your-Investments/694e484ce10c98d0788e3aef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rs-15-Trillion-Exodus-Indias-Top-Companies-See-Record-Promoter-Sell-Off-Whats-Next-for-Your-Investments/694e484ce10c98d0788e3aef</guid><description>Indian promoters sold a record ₹1.5 trillion in stakes during 2025, marking the third consecutive year exceeding ₹1 trillion. This wave, driven by block deals and offer-for-sale routes, pushed promoter shareholding to an eight-year low. Key companies like Bharti Airtel, Interglobe Aviation (Indigo), AWL Agri Business, and Sagility saw significant promoter stake reductions, often linked to strategic reallocation or exit strategies rather than business distress.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 08:25:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e484ce10c98d0788e3aee_1766738073235.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gujarat Power Giant Surges: 600 MW Solar Power Project Fully Commissioned in Major Green Energy Push!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Gujarat-Power-Giant-Surges-600-MW-Solar-Power-Project-Fully-Commissioned-in-Major-Green-Energy-Push/694e4824e10c98d0788e3a8d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Gujarat-Power-Giant-Surges-600-MW-Solar-Power-Project-Fully-Commissioned-in-Major-Green-Energy-Push/694e4824e10c98d0788e3a8d</guid><description>Gujarat Industries Power Company Ltd (GIPCL) has successfully commissioned the final phase of its 600 MW solar power project located in Khavda, Gujarat. This milestone brings the total installed capacity at the Khavda Renewable Energy Park to 600 MW, significantly boosting the company's renewable energy portfolio and contributing to India's green energy goals.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 08:24:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e4824e10c98d0788e3a8c_1766738127015.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Defence Leap: Reforms Ignite Record Exports, Making India a Global Arms Supplier!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Defence-Leap-Reforms-Ignite-Record-Exports-Making-India-a-Global-Arms-Supplier/694e4791e10c98d0788e390c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Defence-Leap-Reforms-Ignite-Record-Exports-Making-India-a-Global-Arms-Supplier/694e4791e10c98d0788e390c</guid><description>India's defense sector underwent significant reforms in 2025, transforming it into a major exporter with record sales of ₹23,620 crore. The focus has shifted to advanced domains like AI, cyber, and space, with indigenous production now meeting 65% of the nation's defense needs. This 'Make in India' drive is propelling the country's defense industry onto the global stage.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 08:19:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e4791e10c98d0788e390b_1766738004797.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vodafone Idea's 2026 Masterplan: Can 5G and AI Save the Telecom Giant?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vodafone-Ideas-2026-Masterplan-Can-5G-and-AI-Save-the-Telecom-Giant/694e46f2e10c98d0788e3797</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vodafone-Ideas-2026-Masterplan-Can-5G-and-AI-Save-the-Telecom-Giant/694e46f2e10c98d0788e3797</guid><description>Vodafone Idea (Vi) has revealed its 2026 strategy, focusing on expanding 5G network coverage to more cities, enhancing its AI-powered 4G network, and introducing new consumer services like spam protection, international call display, roaming forex cards, and handset insurance. This plan aims to address financial challenges and intense market competition in India.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 08:17:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e46f2e10c98d0788e3796_1766737726482.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Karur Vysya Bank Soars 7% to Record High on Massive Volume While Market Falters!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Karur-Vysya-Bank-Soars-7percent-to-Record-High-on-Massive-Volume-While-Market-Falters/694e45cfe10c98d0788e3508</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Karur-Vysya-Bank-Soars-7percent-to-Record-High-on-Massive-Volume-While-Market-Falters/694e45cfe10c98d0788e3508</guid><description>Karur Vysya Bank shares surged 7% to a new high of ₹267.30 on significant volume amidst a declining market. The bank's strong performance is attributed to its diversified loan portfolio focusing on commercial, retail, and agriculture segments, improved net interest margins, and stable asset quality. Analysts maintain a positive outlook, with Emkay Global Financial Services retaining a 'BUY' rating and a target price of ₹270.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 08:02:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e45cfe10c98d0788e3507_1766737434741.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Explosive IPO Demand! Dhara Rail SUBSCRIPTION SURGES 21x on Final Day! Is 13% GMP Just the Beginning?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Explosive-IPO-Demand-Dhara-Rail-SUBSCRIPTION-SURGES-21x-on-Final-Day-Is-13percent-GMP-Just-the-Beginning/694e4562e10c98d0788e3423</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Explosive-IPO-Demand-Dhara-Rail-SUBSCRIPTION-SURGES-21x-on-Final-Day-Is-13percent-GMP-Just-the-Beginning/694e4562e10c98d0788e3423</guid><description>Dhara Rail Projects IPO is closing today with immense investor interest, reaching over 21 times subscription. Non-institutional investors led the charge, subscribing their portion 40 times, followed by strong retail and QIB participation. The grey market premium (GMP) stands at 13.5%, indicating positive investor sentiment for the company, which provides railway rolling stock and electrical services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 08:02:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e4562e10c98d0788e3422_1766737406048.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nvidia's Bold $20 Billion AI Play: Acquiring Future Tech with Groq Deal!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nvidias-Bold-20-Billion-AI-Play-Acquiring-Future-Tech-with-Groq-Deal/694e4451e10c98d0788e3201</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nvidias-Bold-20-Billion-AI-Play-Acquiring-Future-Tech-with-Groq-Deal/694e4451e10c98d0788e3201</guid><description>Chip giant Nvidia is reportedly entering a non-exclusive $20 billion licensing deal with AI hardware startup Groq. This major move in the AI boom allows Nvidia to leverage Groq's inference technology and integrate its chip design into future products. While Groq will continue to operate independently under a new CEO, key executives including its founder and CEO, Jonathan Ross, will join Nvidia to help develop and scale the licensed technology. This strategic approach secures cutting-edge AI capabilities and talent without a full acquisition, reflecting a broader industry trend.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 08:01:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e4451e10c98d0788e3200_1766737136312.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2026 Market Reset: Trust Mutual Fund CIO Sees 'Cleaner Setup' After 2025's Weak Run!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/2026-Market-Reset-Trust-Mutual-Fund-CIO-Sees-Cleaner-Setup-After-2025s-Weak-Run/694e43f6e10c98d0788e315b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/2026-Market-Reset-Trust-Mutual-Fund-CIO-Sees-Cleaner-Setup-After-2025s-Weak-Run/694e43f6e10c98d0788e315b</guid><description>Mihir Vora, Chief Investment Officer at Trust Mutual Fund, anticipates a 'cleaner setup' for markets in 2026 following a weak 2025. He notes that investor expectations have been reset after a year of underperformance, influenced by currency movements. Vora believes steady domestic flows and a potential return of foreign investors, possibly triggered by an India-US trade deal, could boost markets. He favors capital expenditure and financials, including private banks, and sees opportunities in select consumption, defence, and travel sectors. His long-term view on gold and silver remains positive despite potential short-term consolidation. For 2026, he suggests over 50% allocation to equities, 20-25% to Indian debt, and the remainder in gold and silver.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 08:01:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e43f6e10c98d0788e315a_1766737076997.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IT Stocks Wobble: Infosys Salary Hike Sparks Investor Jitters, Analysts Weigh In!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/IT-Stocks-Wobble-Infosys-Salary-Hike-Sparks-Investor-Jitters-Analysts-Weigh-In/694e42aee10c98d0788e2f59</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/IT-Stocks-Wobble-Infosys-Salary-Hike-Sparks-Investor-Jitters-Analysts-Weigh-In/694e42aee10c98d0788e2f59</guid><description>Indian IT stocks experienced a dip, with the Nifty IT index falling by 0.86% after Infosys announced increased entry-level salaries, offering up to ₹21 lakh per annum for specialized tech roles. Analysts suggest this move intensifies competition for digital talent, particularly in AI and cloud, potentially increasing operating costs. While some believe salary hikes will be offset by revenue growth, others note that global demand and deal pipelines remain key investor focuses. The sector also reacted to potential changes in US H-1B visa policies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 07:57:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e42aee10c98d0788e2f58_1766736651478.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jindal Steel's Massive Capacity Surge: Can New Output Overcome Falling Prices for Profit Boom?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jindal-Steels-Massive-Capacity-Surge-Can-New-Output-Overcome-Falling-Prices-for-Profit-Boom/694e42cfe10c98d0788e2fc0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jindal-Steels-Massive-Capacity-Surge-Can-New-Output-Overcome-Falling-Prices-for-Profit-Boom/694e42cfe10c98d0788e2fc0</guid><description>Jindal Steel Ltd is undergoing a significant capacity expansion, set to reach 15.6 mtpa by March, yet its stock has underperformed due to current earnings pressure. Falling domestic steel prices, driven by oversupply and weak demand, combined with rising input costs, are squeezing margins. Analysts predict Ebitda per tonne will bottom out in Q3FY26 before recovering, with future growth heavily reliant on ramping up new capacities. Nuvama forecasts a 17% CAGR in sales volumes from FY25-28, with cost efficiencies and value-added products also boosting earnings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 07:56:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e42cfe10c98d0788e2fbf_1766736701551.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Capital Infra Trust Bags ₹1,600 Crore Via QIP &amp; Preferential Issue; Trilegal Advises Landmark Deal!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Capital-Infra-Trust-Bags-1600-Crore-Via-QIP-and-Preferential-Issue-Trilegal-Advises-Landmark-Deal/694e425be10c98d0788e2e7f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Capital-Infra-Trust-Bags-1600-Crore-Via-QIP-and-Preferential-Issue-Trilegal-Advises-Landmark-Deal/694e425be10c98d0788e2e7f</guid><description>Capital Infra Trust has successfully raised ₹1,250 crore through a Qualified Institutions Placement (QIP) and an additional ₹345 crore via a preferential issue to Gawar Construction Limited. Leading law firm Trilegal advised Capital Infra Trust on both transactions, along with the QIP lead managers. The funds will be used for acquiring three target SPVs and repaying their existing debt.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 07:56:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e425be10c98d0788e2e7e_1766736557771.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Housing Market Shocks: Sales Plummet 14% Despite Record Value! What's Next for Property Prices?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Housing-Market-Shocks-Sales-Plummet-14percent-Despite-Record-Value-Whats-Next-for-Property-Prices/694e4244e10c98d0788e2e2d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Housing-Market-Shocks-Sales-Plummet-14percent-Despite-Record-Value-Whats-Next-for-Property-Prices/694e4244e10c98d0788e2e2d</guid><description>Indian housing sales in top 7 cities fell 14% to 3,95,625 units in 2025 from 4,59,645 units in 2024, mainly due to rising property prices and economic uncertainties. However, total sales value increased 6% to over ₹6 lakh crore. Average prices rose 8%, with Delhi-NCR seeing a significant 23% jump. Anarock suggests future demand revival depends on RBI rate cuts and developer price control.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 07:54:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e4244e10c98d0788e2e2c_1766736528844.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>World Falls For India's Banks! $15 Billion Pour In – Is This The Next Big Investment Story?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/World-Falls-For-Indias-Banks-15-Billion-Pour-In-Is-This-The-Next-Big-Investment-Story/694e41fbe10c98d0788e2dbe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/World-Falls-For-Indias-Banks-15-Billion-Pour-In-Is-This-The-Next-Big-Investment-Story/694e41fbe10c98d0788e2dbe</guid><description>In 2025, India's Banking, Financial Services, and Insurance (BFSI) sector attracted a record $14-15 billion in foreign investment, marking a significant shift towards deep strategic engagement. Major deals included Mitsubishi UFJ acquiring a 20% stake in Shriram Finance for $4.4 billion, Emirates NBD taking a 60% controlling stake in RBL Bank, and Sumitomo Mitsui Banking Corporation increasing its holding in Yes Bank to nearly 25%. This influx was driven by India's robust growth fundamentals, improving asset quality, and increased regulatory comfort, signaling a structural re-rating of the Indian financial system.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 07:53:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e41fbe10c98d0788e2dbd_1766736619525.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dilip Buildcon Lands Huge ₹5,250 Crore Project Bonanza: Investors Alert!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dilip-Buildcon-Lands-Huge-5250-Crore-Project-Bonanza-Investors-Alert/694e415ae10c98d0788e2ca1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dilip-Buildcon-Lands-Huge-5250-Crore-Project-Bonanza-Investors-Alert/694e415ae10c98d0788e2ca1</guid><description>Dilip Buildcon has secured two major infrastructure projects worth a combined value exceeding ₹5,250 crore. The company won a ₹3,400 crore road project in Bihar from Adani Road Transport and a ₹1,850 crore power transmission project in Karnataka from REC Power Development and Consultancy Limited. These significant wins are expected to bolster the company's order book and revenue outlook.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 07:52:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e415ae10c98d0788e2ca0_1766736298419.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Digital Boom Sparks Cyber Insurance Explosion: New Policies Cover Trolling, Stalking &amp; Identity Theft!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indias-Digital-Boom-Sparks-Cyber-Insurance-Explosion-New-Policies-Cover-Trolling-Stalking-and-Identity-Theft/694e40efe10c98d0788e2b83</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indias-Digital-Boom-Sparks-Cyber-Insurance-Explosion-New-Policies-Cover-Trolling-Stalking-and-Identity-Theft/694e40efe10c98d0788e2b83</guid><description>India is experiencing a rapid digital expansion, with high smartphone and internet penetration. This growth, however, increases cyber threats, leading to significant financial losses for enterprises. SBI General Insurance is addressing this by expanding its cyber protection with the Cyber VaultEdge product, now covering identity theft, social media trolling, bullying, and stalking, offering financial and emotional support to individuals. Cybersecurity budgets are also set to rise.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 07:51:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e40efe10c98d0788e2b82_1766736182249.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Motilal Oswal's Bold Stock Picks: TCS, SBI, Biocon &amp; More Revealed! Where Will Your Next Investment Soar?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Motilal-Oswals-Bold-Stock-Picks-TCS-SBI-Biocon-and-More-Revealed-Where-Will-Your-Next-Investment-Soar/694e3ccce10c98d0788e2628</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Motilal-Oswals-Bold-Stock-Picks-TCS-SBI-Biocon-and-More-Revealed-Where-Will-Your-Next-Investment-Soar/694e3ccce10c98d0788e2628</guid><description>Motilal Oswal Financial Services Research has identified top stock picks across large, mid, and small-cap segments. These include Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) for its AI ambitions, State Bank of India (SBI) for banking resilience, Biocon for pharmaceutical consolidation, Dalmia Bharat for cement sector strength, Astra Microwave Products for defense electronics, and Nuvama Wealth for financial services growth. The firm outlines strategic initiatives and financial targets justifying each recommendation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 07:27:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e3ccce10c98d0788e2627_1766735424570.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Emkay Global's Bold Prediction: India's Equity Savings Set to Skyrocket Past Gold!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Emkay-Globals-Bold-Prediction-Indias-Equity-Savings-Set-to-Skyrocket-Past-Gold/694e3bf4e10c98d0788e2472</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Emkay-Globals-Bold-Prediction-Indias-Equity-Savings-Set-to-Skyrocket-Past-Gold/694e3bf4e10c98d0788e2472</guid><description>Emkay Global analysts predict the recent dip in equity's share of Indian household savings is a temporary 'blip'. They forecast equities will rise to approximately 45% within a decade, driven by market gains and broader participation. Despite gold's sharp rise to 45.6%, Emkay believes its impact is minimal, with structural drivers for equities remaining strong. While foreign investment outlook is cautious due to rupee weakness, long-term domestic inflows are expected to be robust.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 07:27:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e3bf4e10c98d0788e2471_1766734989684.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBL Bank Stock Faces 'Triple Top' Warning: Experts Reveal What Investors Must Know Now!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBL-Bank-Stock-Faces-Triple-Top-Warning-Experts-Reveal-What-Investors-Must-Know-Now/694e3b55e10c98d0788e237b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBL-Bank-Stock-Faces-Triple-Top-Warning-Experts-Reveal-What-Investors-Must-Know-Now/694e3b55e10c98d0788e237b</guid><description>RBL Bank shares are showing a bearish 'Triple Top' technical pattern, signaling potential downside after a 9% drop from their all-time high. Despite this, the stock has surged 93% in 2025, and some analysts like Motilal Oswal maintain a 'BUY' rating with a target of ₹350. Recent F&amp;O data suggests possible short-covering, but a CFO resignation adds to recent news flow. Investors should watch the key support level for confirmation of the bearish signal.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 07:27:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e3b55e10c98d0788e237a_1766734812289.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Market Movers! Top Stocks Surge &amp; Plummet on Dec 26: Titan &amp; NTPC Shine, Sun Pharma &amp; Shriram Finance Dip!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Movers-Top-Stocks-Surge-and-Plummet-on-Dec-26-Titan-and-NTPC-Shine-Sun-Pharma-and-Shriram-Finance-Dip/694e3b39e10c98d0788e2304</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Movers-Top-Stocks-Surge-and-Plummet-on-Dec-26-Titan-and-NTPC-Shine-Sun-Pharma-and-Shriram-Finance-Dip/694e3b39e10c98d0788e2304</guid><description>On December 26, 2025, Indian stock markets saw mixed performance. Titan Company Ltd and NTPC Ltd led the gains, while Sun Pharmaceutical Industries Ltd and Shriram Finance Ltd were among the top losers. The Sensex ended down 0.37% at 85092.64, and the Nifty 50 closed down 0.32% at 26058.20.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 07:27:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e3b39e10c98d0788e2303_1766734723618.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Insurance 2026: AI Revolution, Climate Shocks, and Embedded Cover – Your Policy's Future is HERE!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Insurance-2026-AI-Revolution-Climate-Shocks-and-Embedded-Cover-Your-Policys-Future-is-HERE/694e3ae8e10c98d0788e227b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Insurance-2026-AI-Revolution-Climate-Shocks-and-Embedded-Cover-Your-Policys-Future-is-HERE/694e3ae8e10c98d0788e227b</guid><description>By 2026, the insurance industry will transform significantly, driven by AI adoption for efficiency and fraud detection, and the rise of embedded insurance bundled with everyday purchases. Health insurance will focus on prevention, while increasing climate risks will necessitate dynamic pricing and the growth of parametric insurance, especially in agriculture. These shifts promise simpler, quicker, and more relevant coverage for policyholders.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 07:24:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e3ae8e10c98d0788e227a_1766734992158.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shriram Finance Stock Drops 2% After $4.4B MUFG Deal; Profit Booking Hits After 16% Rally!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Shriram-Finance-Stock-Drops-2percent-After-44B-MUFG-Deal-Profit-Booking-Hits-After-16percent-Rally/694e3adce10c98d0788e2219</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Shriram-Finance-Stock-Drops-2percent-After-44B-MUFG-Deal-Profit-Booking-Hits-After-16percent-Rally/694e3adce10c98d0788e2219</guid><description>Shriram Finance shares fell approximately 2% on December 26, following a six-day rally that pushed the stock up 16% to a 52-week high. This dip is seen as profit booking after investors reacted to MUFG Bank's agreement to acquire a 20% stake for $4.4 billion (₹39,600 crore). The deal represents the largest Foreign Direct Investment in India's financial sector. Analysts remain positive about Shriram Finance's long-term growth and balance sheet, despite potential short-term earnings dilution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 07:22:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e3adce10c98d0788e2218_1766734757760.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI's Bold 2025: Surprise Rate Cuts Fuel Growth Despite Inflation Fears!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBIs-Bold-2025-Surprise-Rate-Cuts-Fuel-Growth-Despite-Inflation-Fears/694e3a98e10c98d0788e2006</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBIs-Bold-2025-Surprise-Rate-Cuts-Fuel-Growth-Despite-Inflation-Fears/694e3a98e10c98d0788e2006</guid><description>In 2025, the Reserve Bank of India, led by Governor Sanjay Malhotra, executed a significant monetary policy shift. Initially cautious, the RBI progressively eased its stance, culminating in a cumulative 125 basis point repo rate cut, bringing it down to 5.25% from 6.50%. This aggressive easing cycle, marked by a surprise 50 bps cut in June, aimed to actively support economic growth despite fluctuating inflation signals and global uncertainties, concluding the year with a measured cut focused on stimulating demand.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 07:22:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e3a98e10c98d0788e2005_1766734642944.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Pharma Revolution: Rs 4200 Cr Boost for Innovation &amp; Strict Quality Rules by 2026!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-Pharma-Revolution-Rs-4200-Cr-Boost-for-Innovation-and-Strict-Quality-Rules-by-2026/694e39e1e10c98d0788e1e0b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-Pharma-Revolution-Rs-4200-Cr-Boost-for-Innovation-and-Strict-Quality-Rules-by-2026/694e39e1e10c98d0788e1e0b</guid><description>India aims to become a global life sciences hub by 2026, moving beyond its 'pharmacy of the world' title. Key initiatives include mandating stringent Good Manufacturing Practices (GMP) for smaller drug makers from January 1, 2026, with potential shutdowns for non-compliance. A significant push for innovation is backed by a ₹4,200 crore R&amp;D fund. The roadmap also addresses critical public health issues like Tuberculosis, obesity, and air pollution, alongside expanding digital health services.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 07:22:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e39e1e10c98d0788e1e0a_1766734389237.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ElasticRun Powers Small Towns With Speedy FMCG &amp; Grocery Deliveries: The Next E-commerce Wave?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ElasticRun-Powers-Small-Towns-With-Speedy-FMCG-and-Grocery-Deliveries-The-Next-E-commerce-Wave/694e39c1e10c98d0788e1dbc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ElasticRun-Powers-Small-Towns-With-Speedy-FMCG-and-Grocery-Deliveries-The-Next-E-commerce-Wave/694e39c1e10c98d0788e1dbc</guid><description>Prosus-backed ElasticRun is significantly expanding its quick commerce operations, aiming to deliver FMCG and groceries in 2-4 hours in tier-2 and tier-3 towns. This strategy is expected to drive growth, boost private label adoption for higher margins, and move the company closer to profitability by FY26. Revenue grew 10% to ₹2,653 crore in FY25, with losses narrowing.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 07:22:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e39c1e10c98d0788e1dbb_1766734422493.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Highway Revolution: Barrier-Free Tolls, New Laws &amp; Record Roads by 2026!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Highway-Revolution-Barrier-Free-Tolls-New-Laws-and-Record-Roads-by-2026/694e3a07e10c98d0788e1ead</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Highway-Revolution-Barrier-Free-Tolls-New-Laws-and-Record-Roads-by-2026/694e3a07e10c98d0788e1ead</guid><description>India's road transport ministry is set to transform highway development by 2026. Key initiatives include implementing barrier-free tolling nationwide, significantly reducing toll collection costs and waiting times. A new Road Safety Bill is also being fast-tracked to address alarmingly high accident fatalities. Major expressways like the Delhi-Mumbai corridor are nearing completion, promising faster travel and improved logistics.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 07:20:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e3a07e10c98d0788e1eac_1766734550724.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Colgate India Hit with ₹267 Crore Tax Bill: What Investors Need to Know Now!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Colgate-India-Hit-with-267-Crore-Tax-Bill-What-Investors-Need-to-Know-Now/694e38c5e10c98d0788e1aa5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Colgate-India-Hit-with-267-Crore-Tax-Bill-What-Investors-Need-to-Know-Now/694e38c5e10c98d0788e1aa5</guid><description>Colgate-Palmolive (India) has received a significant tax demand order for ₹267.64 crore for the fiscal year 2021-22. The demand stems from adjustments related to inter-company pricing and disallowed expenses. The company stated it plans to file an appeal with the tax tribunal, emphasizing that the order will not impact its ongoing operations or financials.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 07:18:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e38c5e10c98d0788e1aa4_1766734095125.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Midwest Stock Hits All-Time High on Motilal Oswal 'Buy' Call; ₹2,000 Target Set!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Midwest-Stock-Hits-All-Time-High-on-Motilal-Oswal-Buy-Call-2000-Target-Set/694e35afe10c98d0788e169f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Midwest-Stock-Hits-All-Time-High-on-Motilal-Oswal-Buy-Call-2000-Target-Set/694e35afe10c98d0788e169f</guid><description>Midwest's stock reached an all-time high of ₹1,700.65 on Friday, December 26, 2025, after Motilal Oswal Financial Services initiated coverage with a 'Buy' rating and a ₹2,000 target price. The brokerage cited Midwest's leadership in premium black granite and its strategic diversification into quartz and heavy mineral sands for future growth.</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 06:54:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694e35afe10c98d0788e169e_1766733305975.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>