<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 06:27:36 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Vodafone Idea &amp; Indus Towers Skyrocket: 52-Week Highs Hit as Stocks Outperform Market Heavily!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vodafone-Idea-and-Indus-Towers-Skyrocket-52-Week-Highs-Hit-as-Stocks-Outperform-Market-Heavily/6954c1ef4342f77179ed8bc1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vodafone-Idea-and-Indus-Towers-Skyrocket-52-Week-Highs-Hit-as-Stocks-Outperform-Market-Heavily/6954c1ef4342f77179ed8bc1</guid><description>Vodafone Idea and Indus Towers shares surged to their 52-week highs, significantly outperforming the BSE Sensex in December 2025 and the calendar year 2025. Analysts at Ambit Capital have issued 'BUY' ratings, citing government support for Vodafone Idea and Indus Towers' growth potential, with price targets of ₹15.1 and ₹559 respectively. Expectations of a 15% tariff hike in early 2026 further fuel optimism for the telecom sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 06:10:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954c1ef4342f77179ed8bc0_1767162422867.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI Boosts Expertise: N Venkatram Joins as Part-Time Member!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Boosts-Expertise-N-Venkatram-Joins-as-Part-Time-Member/6954c0cd4342f77179ed893f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Boosts-Expertise-N-Venkatram-Joins-as-Part-Time-Member/6954c0cd4342f77179ed893f</guid><description>N Venkatram, Country Chair of CDPQ India, has been appointed as a Part-Time Member of the Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) for three years. With nearly four decades of experience in capital raising, mergers, acquisitions, governance, and strategy, his appointment aims to strengthen SEBI's regulatory oversight.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 06:09:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954c0cd4342f77179ed893e_1767162126768.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2026 Market Outlook: Selectivity is Key as F&amp;O Giants Debut &amp; Midcaps Face Wild Swings!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/2026-Market-Outlook-Selectivity-is-Key-as-FandO-Giants-Debut-and-Midcaps-Face-Wild-Swings/6954c05c4342f77179ed87bb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/2026-Market-Outlook-Selectivity-is-Key-as-FandO-Giants-Debut-and-Midcaps-Face-Wild-Swings/6954c05c4342f77179ed87bb</guid><description>India's 2026 market outlook is cautiously optimistic, emphasizing domestic consumption and infrastructure. Futures and Options trading welcomes Swiggy, Premier Energies, Waaree Energies, and Bajaj Holdings. 2025 saw significant midcap laggards like Oracle Financial Services and IREDA. Adani's Navi Mumbai Airport hit a passenger milestone, while Devyani International plans a stake sale in a subsidiary. SEBI mandates new certifications for alternative investment funds.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 06:09:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954c05c4342f77179ed87ba_1767162016027.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's IPO Frenzy: Record Funds Raised, But Only 50% Winners? Uncover the Truth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Indias-IPO-Frenzy-Record-Funds-Raised-But-Only-50percent-Winners-Uncover-the-Truth/6954c10a4342f77179ed89e0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Indias-IPO-Frenzy-Record-Funds-Raised-But-Only-50percent-Winners-Uncover-the-Truth/6954c10a4342f77179ed89e0</guid><description>India's IPO market hit a record Rs 1.95 lakh crore in FY2025 with over 365 IPOs, dominated by mainboard listings. However, the year favored existing investors, with Offer for Sale (OFS) comprising 64.78% of funds raised, limiting fresh capital for company growth. While BFSI led sector returns at 84.2%, only about half of the IPOs provided positive returns, highlighting the need for selective investing and strong fundamentals.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 06:05:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954c10a4342f77179ed89df_1767162367353.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shriram Finance Stock Set to Soar? Emkay Global Financial Smashes Buy Target at ₹1100!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Shriram-Finance-Stock-Set-to-Soar-Emkay-Global-Financial-Smashes-Buy-Target-at-1100/6954c0514342f77179ed8765</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Shriram-Finance-Stock-Set-to-Soar-Emkay-Global-Financial-Smashes-Buy-Target-at-1100/6954c0514342f77179ed8765</guid><description>Emkay Global Financial has issued a 'Buy' recommendation for Shriram Finance, setting a target price of ₹1,100. The report follows an analyst call where Shriram Finance detailed its growth strategy post the ₹396.2 billion MUFG deal, expected by FY26. Management anticipates a 100 basis point reduction in Cost of Funds over two years, aiming for 20% AUM growth and improved asset quality, suggesting a positive outlook for the NBFC.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 06:04:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954c0514342f77179ed8764_1767162058043.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Expert Warns: Goldmine in Financials &amp; Metals, But Avoid These Overpriced Stocks!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Expert-Warns-Goldmine-in-Financials-and-Metals-But-Avoid-These-Overpriced-Stocks/6954c00a4342f77179ed8659</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Expert-Warns-Goldmine-in-Financials-and-Metals-But-Avoid-These-Overpriced-Stocks/6954c00a4342f77179ed8659</guid><description>Market expert Deven Choksey identifies opportunities in financial services and metals, citing demand from data centers and power sectors. He is bullish on Shriram Finance, Bajaj Finance, Vedanta, Hindustan Zinc, and Hindustan Copper. However, he urges caution on defence and EMS stocks, warning that their high valuations (often 65-70x P/E) price in several years of future growth, limiting near-term potential.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 06:04:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954c00a4342f77179ed8658_1767161972666.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Privi Speciality Shares PLUMMET 14% After Massive ₹1,086 Cr Deal Shakes Investor Confidence!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Privi-Speciality-Shares-PLUMMET-14percent-After-Massive-1086-Cr-Deal-Shakes-Investor-Confidence/6954bfae4342f77179ed853a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Privi-Speciality-Shares-PLUMMET-14percent-After-Massive-1086-Cr-Deal-Shakes-Investor-Confidence/6954bfae4342f77179ed853a</guid><description>Privi Speciality Chemicals shares plunged nearly 14% on December 31 after a substantial transaction saw 38.8 lakh shares, representing 9.93% of the company's stake, change hands. The shares were traded at ₹2,799 each, a 12% discount to the previous closing price, for a total value of ₹1,086 crore. This significant block deal triggered a sharp sell-off in the stock.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 06:04:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954bfae4342f77179ed8539_1767161939701.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Deven Choksey's SHOCKING 2026 Pick for Reliance Industries: 60% Surge Predicted!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Deven-Chokseys-SHOCKING-2026-Pick-for-Reliance-Industries-60percent-Surge-Predicted/6954bf5e4342f77179ed8460</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Deven-Chokseys-SHOCKING-2026-Pick-for-Reliance-Industries-60percent-Surge-Predicted/6954bf5e4342f77179ed8460</guid><description>Market expert Deven Choksey has identified Reliance Industries Ltd (RIL) as his top stock pick for 2026, forecasting a potential 50-60% upside within two years. Choksey cited the upcoming separate listings of Jio Platforms and Reliance Retail, alongside the growth of Reliance's renewable energy business, as key drivers for this optimistic outlook. He believes the current valuation presents a good entry point for investors seeking a solid blue-chip stock.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 06:04:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954bf5e4342f77179ed845f_1767161777819.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shriram Finance: ICICI Securities Issues Strong BUY Signal with Rs 1225 Target – Is This Your Next Big Investment?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Shriram-Finance-ICICI-Securities-Issues-Strong-BUY-Signal-with-Rs-1225-Target-Is-This-Your-Next-Big-Investment/6954bf3a4342f77179ed8401</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Shriram-Finance-ICICI-Securities-Issues-Strong-BUY-Signal-with-Rs-1225-Target-Is-This-Your-Next-Big-Investment/6954bf3a4342f77179ed8401</guid><description>ICICI Securities has reiterated a 'BUY' recommendation for Shriram Finance, setting a target price of ₹1,225. The brokerage anticipates the company will lead the NBFC sector over the next five years, projecting improved profitability through a significant reduction in borrowing costs and accelerated credit growth. Shriram Finance plans to double its new vehicle loan portfolio, aiming for higher long-term returns.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 06:04:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954bf3a4342f77179ed8400_1767161912066.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Massive ₹421 Crore Orders for Apollo Micro Systems! Coal India Boosts Explosives Business</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Massive-421-Crore-Orders-for-Apollo-Micro-Systems-Coal-India-Boosts-Explosives-Business/6954bedd4342f77179ed82be</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Massive-421-Crore-Orders-for-Apollo-Micro-Systems-Coal-India-Boosts-Explosives-Business/6954bedd4342f77179ed82be</guid><description>Apollo Micro Systems' subsidiary, IDL Explosives, has secured significant new orders totaling ₹420.9 crore. This includes a ₹419.4 crore running contract from Coal India subsidiaries for bulk explosives and a ₹1.5 crore export order for cartridge explosives. These orders are expected to bolster the company's revenue and market position.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 05:59:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954bedd4342f77179ed82bd_1767161648450.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HDFC AMC Chief Navneet Munot: 2025 Set for India's BIGGEST Market &amp; Energy Turnaround!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/HDFC-AMC-Chief-Navneet-Munot-2025-Set-for-Indias-BIGGEST-Market-and-Energy-Turnaround/6954be474342f77179ed8087</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/HDFC-AMC-Chief-Navneet-Munot-2025-Set-for-Indias-BIGGEST-Market-and-Energy-Turnaround/6954be474342f77179ed8087</guid><description>Navneet Munot of HDFC Asset Management Company views 2025 as a pivotal year of structural shifts. He highlights Indian equities' decade-long positive performance, supported by strong macros and reviving earnings, alongside a vibrant IPO market. Munot notes SEBI's finfluencer crackdown and GST benefits for the middle class. A major theme is the energy sector's transformation, with renewables surpassing coal for the first time, signalling a shift towards sustainable, tech-driven power.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 05:59:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954be474342f77179ed8086_1767161575894.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coromandel International Stock Jumps 4% After Clarifying Unusual Trading Volume to NSE!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Coromandel-International-Stock-Jumps-4percent-After-Clarifying-Unusual-Trading-Volume-to-NSE/6954b9d34342f77179ed786a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Coromandel-International-Stock-Jumps-4percent-After-Clarifying-Unusual-Trading-Volume-to-NSE/6954b9d34342f77179ed786a</guid><description>Coromandel International's shares climbed 3.8% to an intraday high of ₹2,322.3 on December 31 after responding to the NSE's query about heavy trading volume. The company stated there is no pending material information and attributed the volume surge to market conditions, assuring compliance with disclosure norms.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 05:37:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954b9d34342f77179ed7869_1767160346285.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ZF Steering Gear ROCKETS 15% After Securing Massive ₹151 Crore Deal for Renewable Energy Project!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ZF-Steering-Gear-ROCKETS-15percent-After-Securing-Massive-151-Crore-Deal-for-Renewable-Energy-Project/6954b96d4342f77179ed7799</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ZF-Steering-Gear-ROCKETS-15percent-After-Securing-Massive-151-Crore-Deal-for-Renewable-Energy-Project/6954b96d4342f77179ed7799</guid><description>ZF Steering Gear shares surged over 15% to an intraday high of ₹852 following a significant order for its subsidiary, Drivesys Systems. The ₹151 crore deal involves manufacturing and supplying machined aluminum parts for a leading Indian conglomerate's renewable energy business, with execution expected within 15 months. This news boosted investor sentiment despite a recent net loss in Q2FY26.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 05:37:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954b96d4342f77179ed7798_1767160240473.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Stock Market Stars &amp; Slips: JSW Steel Soars, TCS Tumbles on December 31!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Stock-Market-Stars-and-Slips-JSW-Steel-Soars-TCS-Tumbles-on-December-31/6954b87b4342f77179ed75ab</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Stock-Market-Stars-and-Slips-JSW-Steel-Soars-TCS-Tumbles-on-December-31/6954b87b4342f77179ed75ab</guid><description>On December 31, 2025, the Indian stock market saw mixed movements. JSW Steel Ltd and Titan Company Ltd emerged as top gainers, while Tata Consultancy Services Ltd and Bajaj Finance Ltd were among the top losers. The Sensex closed up 0.15% at 84801.20, and the Nifty 50 rose 0.17% to 25984.15, indicating a slight positive trend despite individual stock declines.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 05:36:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954b87b4342f77179ed75aa_1767160015151.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global Investors Fleeing India? Expert Reveals Shocking Reason Linked to AI &amp; Debt Boom!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Investors-Fleeing-India-Expert-Reveals-Shocking-Reason-Linked-to-AI-and-Debt-Boom/6954b81b4342f77179ed742b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Investors-Fleeing-India-Expert-Reveals-Shocking-Reason-Linked-to-AI-and-Debt-Boom/6954b81b4342f77179ed742b</guid><description>Foreign capital is bypassing India not due to weak fundamentals, but because global investors are heavily focused on Artificial Intelligence (AI) and debt markets, according to EPFR Global's Cameron Brandt. This structural shift explains negative foreign portfolio investor (FPI) flows into Indian equities in December, as markets with strong AI narratives and fixed-income opportunities are attracting the bulk of capital. While diversified emerging market funds show growing interest, direct equity inflows remain subdued.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 05:36:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954b81b4342f77179ed742a_1767159902719.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India SHOCKS World! Overtakes China to Become Global Rice KING in Stunning Agricultural Upset!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/India-SHOCKS-World-Overtakes-China-to-Become-Global-Rice-KING-in-Stunning-Agricultural-Upset/6954b7ac4342f77179ed7318</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/India-SHOCKS-World-Overtakes-China-to-Become-Global-Rice-KING-in-Stunning-Agricultural-Upset/6954b7ac4342f77179ed7318</guid><description>India has officially become the world's largest rice producer, surpassing China for the first time. Data from the United States Department of Agriculture (USDA) confirms India's output at 152 million metric tonnes, exceeding China's 146 million metric tonnes. This achievement highlights the critical role of rice in India's economy, contributing significantly to its record agricultural exports. The success is partly attributed to historical advancements like the Green Revolution and crucial contributions from Taiwan, which provided key dwarf rice varieties.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 05:33:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954b7ac4342f77179ed7317_1767159920819.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Data Centre Boom Ignites: CapitaLand Secures S$150 Million for Major AI-Ready Expansion!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Data-Centre-Boom-Ignites-CapitaLand-Secures-S150-Million-for-Major-AI-Ready-Expansion/6954b6c44342f77179ed70c1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Data-Centre-Boom-Ignites-CapitaLand-Secures-S150-Million-for-Major-AI-Ready-Expansion/6954b6c44342f77179ed70c1</guid><description>CapitaLand Investment Limited has successfully raised S$150 million in equity at the first close of its CapitaLand India Data Centre Fund (CIDCF). The fund will acquire a 20.2% stake in three AI-ready data centre projects in Navi Mumbai, Chennai, and Hyderabad from CapitaLand India Trust for S$99.73 million. These developments, totaling 200 MW gross capacity, are strategically located and aim to meet the surging demand for digital infrastructure driven by cloud adoption and AI in India. CIDCF targets a S$300 million final close.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 05:29:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954b6c44342f77179ed70c0_1767159655553.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold &amp; Silver's Historic Rally: Best Year Since 1979 Unpacked! What Investors Must Know Next</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silvers-Historic-Rally-Best-Year-Since-1979-Unpacked-What-Investors-Must-Know-Next/6954b44d4342f77179ed661c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silvers-Historic-Rally-Best-Year-Since-1979-Unpacked-What-Investors-Must-Know-Next/6954b44d4342f77179ed661c</guid><description>Gold and silver are poised for their best annual performance since 1979, despite a recent pullback driven by increased margin requirements from CME Group. Factors like US tariff uncertainties, Middle East geopolitical tensions, and China's policy change on silver exports are supporting prices. Analysts foresee a steady short-term outlook with a positive bias for gold and a 'buy on dips' strategy for silver, anticipating it could retest $80/oz amid a widening global supply deficit.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 05:19:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954b44d4342f77179ed661b_1767158932279.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sensex Shatters Records: 10-Year Winning Streak Revealed! Discover India's Top Stock Millionaires!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Sensex-Shatters-Records-10-Year-Winning-Streak-Revealed-Discover-Indias-Top-Stock-Millionaires/6954b24a4342f77179ed6232</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Sensex-Shatters-Records-10-Year-Winning-Streak-Revealed-Discover-Indias-Top-Stock-Millionaires/6954b24a4342f77179ed6232</guid><description>India's benchmark Sensex is projected to close 2025 with an 8.3% gain, marking an unprecedented 10th consecutive year of positive returns. This decade-long rally, from 26,600 in 2016 to near 85,000, showcases Indian equities' resilience. Wealth creation was concentrated, with Tata Steel soaring over 500% and Bharti Airtel over 450%. Financials, IT, and consumer stocks led growth, bolstered by strong domestic inflows.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 05:03:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954b24a4342f77179ed6231_1767158654980.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Apollo Techno Industries IPO Surges 11.5% on Debut! Investors Cheer BSE SME Listing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Apollo-Techno-Industries-IPO-Surges-115percent-on-Debut-Investors-Cheer-BSE-SME-Listing/6954b1504342f77179ed5f90</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Apollo-Techno-Industries-IPO-Surges-115percent-on-Debut-Investors-Cheer-BSE-SME-Listing/6954b1504342f77179ed5f90</guid><description>Apollo Techno Industries' Initial Public Offering (IPO) successfully debuted on the BSE SME platform, opening at ₹145 per share. This marks an 11.54% premium, or ₹15 gain, over its IPO issue price of ₹130. The company raised ₹48 crore through its IPO, which saw strong investor demand, being oversubscribed by 50 times. The raised funds will primarily be used for working capital requirements and general corporate purposes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 05:03:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954b1504342f77179ed5f8f_1767158172354.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HFCL Shares Skyrocket 9% After F&amp;O Exit, But Is This Just a Blip in Its Worst Year Since 2008?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HFCL-Shares-Skyrocket-9percent-After-FandO-Exit-But-Is-This-Just-a-Blip-in-Its-Worst-Year-Since-2008/6954b1a74342f77179ed607c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HFCL-Shares-Skyrocket-9percent-After-FandO-Exit-But-Is-This-Just-a-Blip-in-Its-Worst-Year-Since-2008/6954b1a74342f77179ed607c</guid><description>HFCL shares jumped nearly 9% on December 31 with massive trading volumes following its exit from the Futures &amp; Options (F&amp;O) segment. Despite this sharp daily gain, the stock is heading for its worst calendar year since 2008, down approximately 40% year-to-date. The company now trades only in the cash market.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 05:03:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954b1a74342f77179ed607b_1767158351657.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zydus Wellness Rockets Up! Motilal Oswal Forecasts 80% Jump in 'Consensus Buy' Stock</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Zydus-Wellness-Rockets-Up-Motilal-Oswal-Forecasts-80percent-Jump-in-Consensus-Buy-Stock/6954b1e44342f77179ed6114</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Zydus-Wellness-Rockets-Up-Motilal-Oswal-Forecasts-80percent-Jump-in-Consensus-Buy-Stock/6954b1e44342f77179ed6114</guid><description>Motilal Oswal initiated coverage on Zydus Wellness with a 'Buy' rating and a ₹575 price target, projecting an 80% upside in a bull case scenario. The brokerage highlighted the company's diversified portfolio, leadership in consumer wellness categories, and expansion into emerging trends like high-protein snacking. Despite past muted earnings growth, Motilal Oswal expects significant improvement, citing an attractive valuation discount compared to FMCG peers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 05:03:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954b1e44342f77179ed6113_1767158323441.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Credit Card Shockers! Banks Revamp Fees &amp; Rewards for 2025 - What's Next for Your Wallet in 2026?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Credit-Card-Shockers-Banks-Revamp-Fees-and-Rewards-for-2025-Whats-Next-for-Your-Wallet-in-2026/6954b04c4342f77179ed5cf9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Credit-Card-Shockers-Banks-Revamp-Fees-and-Rewards-for-2025-Whats-Next-for-Your-Wallet-in-2026/6954b04c4342f77179ed5cf9</guid><description>Indian banks like SBI Cards, HDFC, and ICICI Bank have significantly altered credit card fees, rewards, and benefits throughout 2025. Changes include new charges on gaming, wallet loads, and revised lounge access. Looking ahead to 2026, artificial intelligence is set to revolutionize credit management, offering personalized guidance and optimized repayment schedules, promising a more proactive approach for millions of users.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 05:02:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954b04c4342f77179ed5cf8_1767158094646.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Motilal Oswal's Bold Call: Zydus Wellness Set for Major Surge? Buy Signal Issued with ₹575 Target!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Motilal-Oswals-Bold-Call-Zydus-Wellness-Set-for-Major-Surge-Buy-Signal-Issued-with-575-Target/6954b0014342f77179ed5bcb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Motilal-Oswals-Bold-Call-Zydus-Wellness-Set-for-Major-Surge-Buy-Signal-Issued-with-575-Target/6954b0014342f77179ed5bcb</guid><description>Motilal Oswal initiates coverage on Zydus Wellness with a strong 'Buy' recommendation and sets a target price of ₹575. The brokerage values the company's diverse portfolio, including leading brands like Sugar Free and Glucon-D, alongside recent acquisitions in high-protein snacks and digital nutrition. Motilal Oswal believes Zydus Wellness is well-positioned to leverage global megatrends in health and wellness, offering potential for user base expansion unlike many FMCG peers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 04:58:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954b0014342f77179ed5bca_1767157846395.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dhara Rail Projects IPO Soars: Shares Debut at 19% Premium on NSE Emerge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Dhara-Rail-Projects-IPO-Soars-Shares-Debut-at-19percent-Premium-on-NSE-Emerge/6954afbe4342f77179ed5b2a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Dhara-Rail-Projects-IPO-Soars-Shares-Debut-at-19percent-Premium-on-NSE-Emerge/6954afbe4342f77179ed5b2a</guid><description>Dhara Rail Projects' shares debuted on the NSE Emerge platform at Rs 150, a 19.05% premium to its IPO price band of Rs 120-126. The issue was subscribed 112 times. The company's market capitalization post-listing reached Rs 218.72 crore. This listing exceeded grey market expectations, which had predicted around 13% gains.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 04:58:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954afbe4342f77179ed5b29_1767157869289.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shock Drop! Admach Systems IPO Lists 20% Down: Investors Reel as Dream Debut Turns Nightmare!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Shock-Drop-Admach-Systems-IPO-Lists-20percent-Down-Investors-Reel-as-Dream-Debut-Turns-Nightmare/6954af954342f77179ed5a2c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Shock-Drop-Admach-Systems-IPO-Lists-20percent-Down-Investors-Reel-as-Dream-Debut-Turns-Nightmare/6954af954342f77179ed5a2c</guid><description>Admach Systems made a rough stock market debut on December 31, listing on the BSE SME platform at ₹191.20 per share, a significant 20% discount to its IPO price of ₹239. The company's market capitalization began at ₹129.50 crore, falling short of grey market expectations which had predicted a modest premium.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 04:58:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954af954342f77179ed5a2b_1767157772077.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Climate Battleground: Shifting From Promises to REAL Action! Will Delivery Save the Nation?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Indias-Climate-Battleground-Shifting-From-Promises-to-REAL-Action-Will-Delivery-Save-the-Nation/6954af464342f77179ed5944</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Indias-Climate-Battleground-Shifting-From-Promises-to-REAL-Action-Will-Delivery-Save-the-Nation/6954af464342f77179ed5944</guid><description>India's climate agenda is moving from setting targets to focusing on execution amidst funding gaps and weak global support. Challenges include renewable energy growth outstripping grid readiness and the need for a managed transition away from coal. Delivery in power, industry, and cities will determine India's climate credibility, with adaptation also crucial.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 04:58:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954af464342f77179ed5943_1767157888094.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Highway Budget Stalls? Investors Brace for Slowdown as Funds Lag!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Highway-Budget-Stalls-Investors-Brace-for-Slowdown-as-Funds-Lag/6954af014342f77179ed5859</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Highway-Budget-Stalls-Investors-Brace-for-Slowdown-as-Funds-Lag/6954af014342f77179ed5859</guid><description>India's Ministry of Road Transport and Highways (MoRTH) is likely to see a modest 1-2.5% budget allocation increase for 2026-27. This subdued hike reflects slower fund utilization in the current fiscal year and an increasing reliance on private and non-budgetary financing for road projects. The allocation is expected to be between ₹2.9-2.94 lakh crore.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 04:55:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954af014342f77179ed5858_1767157691884.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Warren Buffett Steps Down as Berkshire CEO After 60 Years! Greg Abel Takes Helm - What's Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Warren-Buffett-Steps-Down-as-Berkshire-CEO-After-60-Years-Greg-Abel-Takes-Helm-Whats-Next/6954adbf4342f77179ed552a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Warren-Buffett-Steps-Down-as-Berkshire-CEO-After-60-Years-Greg-Abel-Takes-Helm-Whats-Next/6954adbf4342f77179ed552a</guid><description>Legendary investor Warren Buffett is stepping down as CEO of Berkshire Hathaway after nearly six decades, passing the baton to Greg Abel, vice chairman of non-insurance operations. Buffett, 94, will remain Chairman. The transition, effective January 1, 2026, marks the end of an era for the $1 trillion conglomerate. Abel, Buffett's chosen successor, is expected to maintain the company's core value-investing philosophy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 04:51:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954adbf4342f77179ed5529_1767157321422.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ElasticRun Shocks Market: Loss Slashed 60% to ₹145 Cr as Revenue Surges!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ElasticRun-Shocks-Market-Loss-Slashed-60percent-to-145-Cr-as-Revenue-Surges/6954ad584342f77179ed540f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ElasticRun-Shocks-Market-Loss-Slashed-60percent-to-145-Cr-as-Revenue-Surges/6954ad584342f77179ed540f</guid><description>B2B ecommerce enabler ElasticRun significantly improved its financial performance in FY25, narrowing its net loss by 60% to ₹145.1 Cr from ₹359.6 Cr in FY24. The company also saw its operating revenue climb 8% to ₹2,653 Cr. This achievement is attributed to a focus on operational profitability and higher margins from local brand sales, though the company remains committed to growth over immediate EBITDA profitability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 04:49:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954ad584342f77179ed540e_1767157149854.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>New Year's Day Surprise: Indian Stock Market to Trade While World Sleeps! 2026 Holiday Details Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/New-Years-Day-Surprise-Indian-Stock-Market-to-Trade-While-World-Sleeps-2026-Holiday-Details-Revealed/6954accd4342f77179ed5305</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/New-Years-Day-Surprise-Indian-Stock-Market-to-Trade-While-World-Sleeps-2026-Holiday-Details-Revealed/6954accd4342f77179ed5305</guid><description>Indian stock markets, including the National Stock Exchange (NSE) and Bombay Stock Exchange (BSE), will be open for trading on January 1, 2026. This is in contrast to major global markets in China, Hong Kong, Japan, Singapore, France, Germany, the UK, and the US, which will remain closed for New Year's Day. The NSE has also published its 2026 holiday calendar, indicating 15 trading holidays throughout the year for equity, equity derivatives, and currency markets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 04:47:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954accd4342f77179ed5304_1767157022435.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>New India Assurance Stock Surges 2% as GST Tax Demands Dramatically Reduced!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/New-India-Assurance-Stock-Surges-2percent-as-GST-Tax-Demands-Dramatically-Reduced/6954aa344342f77179ed4d56</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/New-India-Assurance-Stock-Surges-2percent-as-GST-Tax-Demands-Dramatically-Reduced/6954aa344342f77179ed4d56</guid><description>The New India Assurance Company's share price rose by up to 2.28% on the last trading day of 2025, reaching an intraday high of ₹156.45. The surge followed disclosures about Goods and Services Tax (GST) orders. While initially facing potential demands totaling ₹2,298.06 crore from Mumbai, tax authorities confirmed only ₹1.10 crore. Another notice from New Delhi confirmed ₹69.17 crore. The company, India's largest government-owned insurer, is challenging these confirmed demands.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 04:29:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954aa344342f77179ed4d55_1767156350411.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Frenzy Ignites Asia's Strongest Stock Surge in 8 Years! Gold &amp; Silver Skyrocket!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Frenzy-Ignites-Asias-Strongest-Stock-Surge-in-8-Years-Gold-and-Silver-Skyrocket/6954a9824342f77179ed4bd9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Frenzy-Ignites-Asias-Strongest-Stock-Surge-in-8-Years-Gold-and-Silver-Skyrocket/6954a9824342f77179ed4bd9</guid><description>Asian stock markets are set for their strongest annual jump in eight years, primarily driven by investor enthusiasm for artificial intelligence chip stocks. Precious metals, particularly silver and gold, have also seen significant rallies, capping a year of remarkable returns despite global economic uncertainties and geopolitical tensions. Investors are now looking towards next year with AI remaining a key theme, but with a focus shifting towards adoption and return on investment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 04:29:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954a9824342f77179ed4bd8_1767156177337.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold's Astonishing 2025 Surge: Its Strongest Run in Over 40 Years! What Drove This Massive Rally?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Golds-Astonishing-2025-Surge-Its-Strongest-Run-in-Over-40-Years-What-Drove-This-Massive-Rally/6954a8cf4342f77179ed4a73</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Golds-Astonishing-2025-Surge-Its-Strongest-Run-in-Over-40-Years-What-Drove-This-Massive-Rally/6954a8cf4342f77179ed4a73</guid><description>Gold achieved its strongest annual performance in over four decades during 2025, surging 66-74% and marking its best year since 1979. Global uncertainty, geopolitical risks, and shifting monetary policy expectations, including rate cuts in India and the US, fueled a broad reallocation towards the safe-haven asset. Structural demand from central banks and increased investor exposure via ETFs also underpinned the rally. Analysts remain constructive, with UBS predicting prices could reach $5,000 per ounce by September 2026.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 04:28:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954a8cf4342f77179ed4a72_1767155990156.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>China Factory Output Unexpectedly Grows, Snapping Eight-Month Slump on Festive Demand!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/China-Factory-Output-Unexpectedly-Grows-Snapping-Eight-Month-Slump-on-Festive-Demand/6954a87c4342f77179ed49cc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/China-Factory-Output-Unexpectedly-Grows-Snapping-Eight-Month-Slump-on-Festive-Demand/6954a87c4342f77179ed49cc</guid><description>China's factory activity surged unexpectedly in December, ending an eight-month contraction with the official PMI rising to 50.1, surpassing forecasts. This growth, driven by domestic orders and festive stockpiling ahead of the Lunar New Year, offers optimism for the nation's $19 trillion economy, though export demand remains sluggish.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 04:28:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954a87c4342f77179ed49cb_1767155910132.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Steel Stocks Surge! Govt Safeguard Duty Sparks Rally in Tata, JSW, Jindal Shares</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Steel-Stocks-Surge-Govt-Safeguard-Duty-Sparks-Rally-in-Tata-JSW-Jindal-Shares/6954a7cb4342f77179ed45c4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Steel-Stocks-Surge-Govt-Safeguard-Duty-Sparks-Rally-in-Tata-JSW-Jindal-Shares/6954a7cb4342f77179ed45c4</guid><description>India's government has imposed a three-year safeguard duty of up to 12% on certain steel imports, significantly boosting sentiment for domestic steelmakers. Shares of major companies including Tata Steel, JSW Steel, and Jindal Steel saw gains of 2-4% in early trading as the move is expected to improve pricing power and protect local producers from cheaper foreign competition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 04:24:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954a7cb4342f77179ed45c3_1767155809331.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Affordable Housing Powerhouse: Is Aadhar Housing Finance The Next Big Stock Market Winner? Investors Watch Closely!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Affordable-Housing-Powerhouse-Is-Aadhar-Housing-Finance-The-Next-Big-Stock-Market-Winner-Investors-Watch-Closely/6954a73d4342f77179ed4496</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Affordable-Housing-Powerhouse-Is-Aadhar-Housing-Finance-The-Next-Big-Stock-Market-Winner-Investors-Watch-Closely/6954a73d4342f77179ed4496</guid><description>Aadhar Housing Finance is poised for significant growth in India's affordable housing sector, driven by government initiatives like 'Housing for All' and PM Awas Yojana. Despite competition, the company's focus on EWS/LIG segments, stable asset quality, and reasonable valuation at 2.0x FY28e P/B ratio make it an attractive long-term investment. With an AUM of ₹27,554 crore and targeting 18-20% loan growth, Aadhar Housing Finance is well-positioned to capitalize on structural tailwinds.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 04:24:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954a73d4342f77179ed4495_1767155586157.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Top Refiner Strikes New Deal: First Colombian Oil Arrives as Russian Imports Face Sanctions!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Top-Refiner-Strikes-New-Deal-First-Colombian-Oil-Arrives-as-Russian-Imports-Face-Sanctions/6954a6ba4342f77179ed4084</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Top-Refiner-Strikes-New-Deal-First-Colombian-Oil-Arrives-as-Russian-Imports-Face-Sanctions/6954a6ba4342f77179ed4084</guid><description>Indian Oil Corporation has purchased its inaugural shipment of Colombian crude oil under a contract with Ecopetrol. This strategic move diversifies India's top refiner's supplies, reducing reliance on Russian oil amid escalating U.S. and European sanctions. The deal involves 2 million barrels of Castilla crude for late February delivery, with an option for up to 12 million barrels.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 04:20:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954a6ba4342f77179ed4083_1767155462921.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Record Bond Sell-Off! Foreign Investors Flee India as Rupee Plummets, Returns Slashed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Record-Bond-Sell-Off-Foreign-Investors-Flee-India-as-Rupee-Plummets-Returns-Slashed/6954a2094342f77179ed3717</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Record-Bond-Sell-Off-Foreign-Investors-Flee-India-as-Rupee-Plummets-Returns-Slashed/6954a2094342f77179ed3717</guid><description>Foreign investors are exiting Indian sovereign bonds at a record pace in December, with outflows reaching ₹14,300 crore ($1.6 billion). This sell-off, the largest since 2020, is driven by the Indian rupee's sharp depreciation, which is severely eroding returns for global funds. Concerns about the Reserve Bank of India nearing the end of its interest-rate cut cycle and rising inflation forecasts also contribute to the negative sentiment, pushing up India's borrowing costs.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:56:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954a2094342f77179ed3716_1767154629611.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>V-Mart Set for Massive Comeback? Analysts Reveal Key to Soaring Profits &amp; Store Boom!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/V-Mart-Set-for-Massive-Comeback-Analysts-Reveal-Key-to-Soaring-Profits-and-Store-Boom/6954a1f94342f77179ed36ba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/V-Mart-Set-for-Massive-Comeback-Analysts-Reveal-Key-to-Soaring-Profits-and-Store-Boom/6954a1f94342f77179ed36ba</guid><description>V-Mart Retail is showing strong signs of recovery with improving store productivity and expanding margins, according to Motilal Oswal analysts. The company is benefiting from increased disposable incomes in rural India and the shift towards organized retail. Analysts predict robust revenue growth of 18% annually until FY28, driven by store expansion and operational efficiency, leading to a significant earnings recovery. Motilal Oswal maintains a 'Buy' rating with a target price of ₹1,040.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 03:56:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954a1f94342f77179ed36b9_1767154509747.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>