<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:58:31 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Kajaria Ceramics Sees Margin Surge Amid Flat Revenue and Fraud Probe</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kajaria-Ceramics-Sees-Margin-Surge-Amid-Flat-Revenue-and-Fraud-Probe/6980487547db7081af6801d2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kajaria-Ceramics-Sees-Margin-Surge-Amid-Flat-Revenue-and-Fraud-Probe/6980487547db7081af6801d2</guid><description>Kajaria Ceramics reported flat consolidated revenue of INR 1,168 crores for Q3 FY26 YoY, impacted by stagnant tile volumes and the closure of Ply sales. However, EBITDA margin improved significantly by 442 basis points to 17.2%. PAT rose 13% to INR 88 crores, adjusted for exceptional items. Working capital days increased to 64. Management guided for 17-18% margins, double-digit sanitaryware growth, and JV consolidation, even as a fraud investigation by EY is ongoing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:47:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Motors PV Zooms 3% on Record Jan Sales, Intl Business Surges 251%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-PV-Zooms-3percent-on-Record-Jan-Sales-Intl-Business-Surges-251percent/6980486347db7081af68008b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Tata-Motors-PV-Zooms-3percent-on-Record-Jan-Sales-Intl-Business-Surges-251percent/6980486347db7081af68008b</guid><description>Tata Motors Passenger Vehicles (PV) shares climbed 3.4% to ₹356.4 after the company reported robust January sales figures. Total sales jumped 47.1% year-on-year to 71,066 units. Domestic PV sales grew 46.1%, while the international business saw a remarkable 251.7% surge. EV sales also increased 72.7%.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:46:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Power Grid Hikes Capex Guidance Amid 7% Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Power-Grid-Hikes-Capex-Guidance-Amid-7percent-Revenue-Growth/6980483747db7081af67ffbb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Power-Grid-Hikes-Capex-Guidance-Amid-7percent-Revenue-Growth/6980483747db7081af67ffbb</guid><description>Power Grid Corporation posted robust Q3 FY26 results with a 7% YoY consolidated revenue jump to ₹12,599 crore and 8% PAT growth to ₹4,185 crore. For 9MFY26, revenue grew 2% YoY to ₹35,714 crore, though EBITDA saw a 1% dip. Significantly, the company revised its FY26 Capex guidance upwards to ₹32,000 crore, signaling strong future expansion driven by India's energy transition and increasing demand.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:46:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>January Auto Boom: MOFSL Picks MSIL, M&amp;M, TVS on Strong Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/January-Auto-Boom-MOFSL-Picks-MSIL-MandM-TVS-on-Strong-Demand/698047f547db7081af67fe79</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/January-Auto-Boom-MOFSL-Picks-MSIL-MandM-TVS-on-Strong-Demand/698047f547db7081af67fe79</guid><description>The Indian automotive sector commenced 2026 with robust January sales figures, showing significant year-on-year growth across passenger vehicles, two-wheelers, commercial vehicles, and tractors. This strong demand, buoyed by GST rationalization and new model introductions, led Motilal Oswal Financial Services to reiterate its positive outlook on key manufacturers, maintaining Maruti Suzuki India as its top pick, with Mahindra &amp; Mahindra and TVS Motor Company also receiving favorable mentions for their performance drivers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:45:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Vaibhav Global Hits Record ₹1066 Cr Revenue, Q3 Profit Surges 41%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Vaibhav-Global-Hits-Record-1066-Cr-Revenue-Q3-Profit-Surges-41percent/698047df47db7081af67fd90</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Vaibhav-Global-Hits-Record-1066-Cr-Revenue-Q3-Profit-Surges-41percent/698047df47db7081af67fd90</guid><description>Vaibhav Global's Q3 FY26 revenue hit a record INR1,066 cr, a 9.1% YoY growth, surpassing guidance amid geopolitical challenges. PAT soared 41% YoY to INR90 cr, driven by strong margin expansion (EBITDA margin at 13.2%) and operational efficiencies. The company maintained a healthy net cash position of INR213 cr and declared an interim dividend. Future guidance targets 9-11% revenue growth for FY27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:44:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ion Exchange Q3 Profit Plummets 58% as Margins Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ion-Exchange-Q3-Profit-Plummets-58percent-as-Margins-Squeeze/698047c147db7081af67fc75</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ion-Exchange-Q3-Profit-Plummets-58percent-as-Margins-Squeeze/698047c147db7081af67fc75</guid><description>Ion Exchange posted a 6.4% YoY revenue increase to ₹7,344 million in Q3 FY26. However, PAT plummeted 58.5% YoY to ₹206 million due to significant margin compression (EBITDA margin fell 285 bps to 8.07%) and an exceptional item. Deferred international dispatches impacted performance, although the order book remains robust at ₹2,833 crore.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:44:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IKIO Technologies Surges on Diversification, Revenue Jumps 20%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/IKIO-Technologies-Surges-on-Diversification-Revenue-Jumps-20percent/6980474647db7081af67fb25</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/IKIO-Technologies-Surges-on-Diversification-Revenue-Jumps-20percent/6980474647db7081af67fb25</guid><description>IKIO Technologies posted a strong Q3FY26, with revenue up 20% YoY to ₹1,456 Mn, fueled by its "Other Business" segment (70% of sales). EBITDA surged 47% to ₹219 Mn with margins expanding 280 bps YoY. The company acquired Gravus Tech and commercialized new plant capacity, signalling robust growth plans and diversification success.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:42:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Budget 2026: STT Hike Triggers Market Plunge, FPI Woes Persist</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-STT-Hike-Triggers-Market-Plunge-FPI-Woes-Persist/698046d747db7081af67f9ef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-STT-Hike-Triggers-Market-Plunge-FPI-Woes-Persist/698046d747db7081af67f9ef</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026's announcement of increased Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on derivatives triggered a significant market sell-off. This policy move exacerbates concerns over sustained Foreign Portfolio Investor (FPI) outflows and the Indian Rupee's depreciation, which impacts returns for foreign investors. Fund managers, like Samir Arora of Helios Capital, are adopting a cautious investment strategy, emphasizing market direction over stock-specific performance amidst prevailing sentiment and policy clarity issues.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:40:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lupin Strikes Global Health Deal, US Oncology Launch</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupin-Strikes-Global-Health-Deal-US-Oncology-Launch/6980467247db7081af67f82f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupin-Strikes-Global-Health-Deal-US-Oncology-Launch/6980467247db7081af67f82f</guid><description>Lupin Ltd. has forged a key collaboration with TB Alliance to advance an investigational tuberculosis drug, Telacebec. Concurrently, the company launched its generic Dasatinib Tablets in the U.S. market, targeting a segment with estimated annual sales of $930 million. These moves signal Lupin's strategic push into complex therapies, though the stock saw a slight decline on the announcement.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:38:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bajaj Housing Finance Faces Scrutiny Ahead of Q3 Results</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bajaj-Housing-Finance-Faces-Scrutiny-Ahead-of-Q3-Results/6980465b47db7081af67f78d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bajaj-Housing-Finance-Faces-Scrutiny-Ahead-of-Q3-Results/6980465b47db7081af67f78d</guid><description>Bajaj Housing Finance Ltd. faces investor scrutiny ahead of its third-quarter earnings report, with shares down significantly from their IPO highs despite reported operational growth. Gross disbursements rose to ₹16,535 crore and assets under management (AUM) grew 23% to ₹1.33 lakh crore. However, the stock has shed over 53% from its peak, trading at ₹88.3, reflecting caution on core income and asset quality.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:38:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>GST Rewritten: Indian Brokers Serving FPIs Now Face Zero-Rated Exports</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/GST-Rewritten-Indian-Brokers-Serving-FPIs-Now-Face-Zero-Rated-Exports/6980461947db7081af67f5f6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/GST-Rewritten-Indian-Brokers-Serving-FPIs-Now-Face-Zero-Rated-Exports/6980461947db7081af67f5f6</guid><description>The Finance Bill 2026 has introduced a significant shift in Goods and Services Tax (GST) regulations for Indian brokers serving Foreign Portfolio Investors (FPIs). Services previously subject to an 18% GST are now poised to become zero-rated exports. This change reclassifies the 'place of supply' to align with international norms, aiming to reduce compliance burdens. However, industry experts are seeking official clarification on payment mechanisms, particularly concerning Special Non-Resident Rupee (SNRR) accounts, to ensure this benefit is fully realized.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:37:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Defense Stocks Slip on Budget's Policy Vacuum</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defense-Stocks-Slip-on-Budgets-Policy-Vacuum/6980460947db7081af67f522</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defense-Stocks-Slip-on-Budgets-Policy-Vacuum/6980460947db7081af67f522</guid><description>Defense sector shares experienced a notable downturn on Monday, February 2, 2026, as the Nifty Defence index shed 1.76%. This followed an earlier 5.6% decline on February 1st, indicating investor disappointment over the Union Budget's perceived lack of significant policy reforms, despite an 18% increase in defense capital expenditure for FY27. Hindustan Aeronautics (HAL) dropped approximately 3%, and Bharat Dynamics (BDL) saw a nearly 6% decline, with 16 out of 18 index constituents trading in negative territory.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:36:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Budget: Infrastructure Focus Amidst Fiscal Strain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-Infrastructure-Focus-Amidst-Fiscal-Strain/698045e347db7081af67f40e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-Infrastructure-Focus-Amidst-Fiscal-Strain/698045e347db7081af67f40e</guid><description>The recent Union Budget signals a strategic pivot towards infrastructure as the primary economic growth engine, with substantial allocations to roads, railways, water, and housing. Simultaneously, the government is boosting outlays for labor, small businesses, and skill development to address job creation concerns. However, these initiatives operate under considerable fiscal pressure, marked by escalating interest payments that consume over a quarter of the budget, limiting flexibility for other critical sectors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:36:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CONCOR: Volume Surge Masks Profit Dip, Cement Logistics Beckons</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/CONCOR-Volume-Surge-Masks-Profit-Dip-Cement-Logistics-Beckons/6980458547db7081af67f2bf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/CONCOR-Volume-Surge-Masks-Profit-Dip-Cement-Logistics-Beckons/6980458547db7081af67f2bf</guid><description>Container Corporation of India (CONCOR) posted a 4% year-on-year dip in net profit to ₹329 crore in Q3 FY26, yet underlying operational strength was evident. Revenue rose 5% to ₹2,302 crore, with operating profit climbing 10% and margins improving to 22%, driven by an 11% surge in throughput. The company is actively pursuing bulk cement transportation opportunities, ordering 1,000 tank containers and signing MOUs with major cement producers, signaling a strategic diversification beyond traditional container freight.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:34:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Glycols Splits Units: Bio-Pharma and Spirits Spin-Off</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Glycols-Splits-Units-Bio-Pharma-and-Spirits-Spin-Off/6980456547db7081af67f1dd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Glycols-Splits-Units-Bio-Pharma-and-Spirits-Spin-Off/6980456547db7081af67f1dd</guid><description>India Glycols Limited is executing a strategic demerger, separating its bio-pharma and spirits &amp; biofuel undertakings into two distinct publicly traded entities: Ennature Bio Pharma Limited and IGL Spirits Limited. This move aims to unlock focused growth potential and enhance shareholder value by allowing each business vertical to pursue independent strategies. Legal firm Khaitan &amp; Co is advising on the complex restructuring.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:34:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Supreme Court to Rule on Patent vs. Competition Law</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Indias-Supreme-Court-to-Rule-on-Patent-vs-Competition-Law/6980450547db7081af67f060</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Indias-Supreme-Court-to-Rule-on-Patent-vs-Competition-Law/6980450547db7081af67f060</guid><description>The Supreme Court of India is set to adjudicate the critical question of whether the Competition Commission of India (CCI) has the authority to investigate alleged anti-competitive practices arising from the exercise of patent rights. This comes after lower tribunals, including the National Company Law Appellate Tribunal (NCLAT), previously asserted the primacy of the Patents Act, 1970, over competition law in such matters. The landmark decision could reshape regulatory oversight for intellectual property-heavy sectors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:32:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Boosts Nuclear Power with Duty Exemption</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Boosts-Nuclear-Power-with-Duty-Exemption/698044f147db7081af67efb7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Boosts-Nuclear-Power-with-Duty-Exemption/698044f147db7081af67efb7</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman announced in the Union Budget 2026 an extension of the basic customs duty exemption on imports for nuclear power projects until 2035. This policy aims to accelerate India's ambitious nuclear capacity expansion targets, including NTPC's goal of contributing 30 GW by 2047. The exemption covers all nuclear plants and components, signaling robust government support for clean energy transition.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:32:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Manufacturing PMI Edges Up, Growth Sustained Amidst Muted Confidence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Manufacturing-PMI-Edges-Up-Growth-Sustained-Amidst-Muted-Confidence/6980447647db7081af67ee65</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Manufacturing-PMI-Edges-Up-Growth-Sustained-Amidst-Muted-Confidence/6980447647db7081af67ee65</guid><description>India's manufacturing sector saw an uptick in January, with the HSBC Purchasing Managers’ Index (PMI) rising to 55.4 from 55.0 in December 2025. This expansion was fueled by stronger new orders, increased output, and higher employment. However, input cost pressures are rising, and business confidence and future output expectations have dipped to multi-month lows, indicating a complex economic picture.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:30:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Maruti Suzuki Hits Record Sales; Q3 Profit Misses, Stock Pressured</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-Suzuki-Hits-Record-Sales-Q3-Profit-Misses-Stock-Pressured/6980443247db7081af67ece5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Maruti-Suzuki-Hits-Record-Sales-Q3-Profit-Misses-Stock-Pressured/6980443247db7081af67ece5</guid><description>Maruti Suzuki India achieved a record 2,36,963 unit sales in January 2026, a 12% year-on-year increase, driven by strong domestic demand and a near doubling of exports. However, the company's third-quarter net profit rose only 3.7% to ₹3,794 crore, significantly missing analyst expectations due to a ₹593.9 crore provision for new labor codes and subdued prior-period exports. Despite record quarterly net sales, profitability concerns weighed on investor sentiment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:29:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Silverline Launches AI Platform, Projects $65M Revenue in 5 Years</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Silverline-Launches-AI-Platform-Projects-65M-Revenue-in-5-Years/6980440047db7081af67ebd6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Silverline-Launches-AI-Platform-Projects-65M-Revenue-in-5-Years/6980440047db7081af67ebd6</guid><description>Silverline Technologies has launched its proprietary AI-enabled web platform, 'Silver AI,' aiming to bolster its position in digital solutions. The company projects significant growth, forecasting $65 million in revenue by Year 5 with healthy EBITDA margins, tapping into the booming AI chatbot market. Key revenue streams are expected from SaaS subscriptions and enterprise contracts, with an aggressive product roadmap targeting rapid feature deployment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:28:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Scrap Duty Waiver Fuels Recycling, Critical Minerals Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Budget-2026-Scrap-Duty-Waiver-Fuels-Recycling-Critical-Minerals-Push/6980431347db7081af67e8b4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Budget-2026-Scrap-Duty-Waiver-Fuels-Recycling-Critical-Minerals-Push/6980431347db7081af67e8b4</guid><description>A strategic budgetary adjustment in India aims to transform the critical minerals and battery recycling sectors. By eliminating duties on imported lithium-ion battery scrap and processing equipment, the government seeks to enhance raw material availability, spur domestic investment in recycling facilities, and reduce reliance on global suppliers. This move is central to India's broader strategy for energy transition and securing supply chains for high-tech manufacturing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:28:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980431347db7081af67e8b3_1770013632943.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Acquirers Launch ₹4.2Cr Open Offer for Distressed STGL, Eye FMCG Pivot</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Acquirers-Launch-42Cr-Open-Offer-for-Distressed-STGL-Eye-FMCG-Pivot/6980438a47db7081af67ea34</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Acquirers-Launch-42Cr-Open-Offer-for-Distressed-STGL-Eye-FMCG-Pivot/6980438a47db7081af67ea34</guid><description>A consortium of new entities and an individual is launching a ₹4.20 crore open offer to acquire up to 26% of Switching Technologies Gunther Limited (STGL) at ₹66 per share. The acquirers plan a radical shift from STGL's current advanced switching business to food processing and FMCG, while STGL faces severe financial distress with negative net worth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hester Biosciences Q3: Poultry Soars, Animal Health Dips, PAT Surges 140%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Hester-Biosciences-Q3-Poultry-Soars-Animal-Health-Dips-PAT-Surges-140percent/6980429847db7081af67e752</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Hester-Biosciences-Q3-Poultry-Soars-Animal-Health-Dips-PAT-Surges-140percent/6980429847db7081af67e752</guid><description>Hester Biosciences reported a mixed Q3 FY26. Poultry Healthcare soared 32% YoY, driven by market penetration and a new H9N2 vaccine license. However, Animal Healthcare declined 38% due to delayed government programs. Standalone PAT surged 140% YoY on favorable product mix and cost control. Consolidated revenue grew 22% YoY, with management focused on reducing tender dependence and boosting exports.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:26:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980429847db7081af67e751_1770013530951.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bajaj Finance Earnings Near: Market Awaits Q3 Results Amid Stock Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bajaj-Finance-Earnings-Near-Market-Awaits-Q3-Results-Amid-Stock-Slump/6980422247db7081af67e5ca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bajaj-Finance-Earnings-Near-Market-Awaits-Q3-Results-Amid-Stock-Slump/6980422247db7081af67e5ca</guid><description>Bajaj Finance Ltd. is set to announce its third-quarter financial results for fiscal year 2026 on February 3rd. The non-banking financial company, which previously reported a robust Q2 performance, is now under investor scrutiny as its stock has experienced a recent downturn. The market awaits key figures amidst a generally positive outlook for the Indian NBFC sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:24:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980422247db7081af67e5c9_1770013413429.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget Fallout: RBI Buoys Rupee Amid Market Jitters</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-Fallout-RBI-Buoys-Rupee-Amid-Market-Jitters/698040d447db7081af67e189</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-Fallout-RBI-Buoys-Rupee-Amid-Market-Jitters/698040d447db7081af67e189</guid><description>India's federal budget has cast a shadow over financial markets, with equities and sovereign bonds succumbing to pressure following the announcement. The Indian rupee, having neared an all-time low, received a boost from decisive intervention by the Reserve Bank of India. Investors remain cautious due to a lack of bold reforms and increased government borrowing, while analysts foresee continued pressure on the currency.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:21:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698040d447db7081af67e188_1770013289083.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Latent View Analytics Surges 8% on Record Q3 Revenue, AI Mission Hopes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Latent-View-Analytics-Surges-8percent-on-Record-Q3-Revenue-AI-Mission-Hopes/6980412b47db7081af67e2e9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Latent-View-Analytics-Surges-8percent-on-Record-Q3-Revenue-AI-Mission-Hopes/6980412b47db7081af67e2e9</guid><description>Latent View Analytics shares surged 8% with high trading volumes, extending a three-day rally. The AI-driven analytics firm posted a robust 22% year-on-year revenue increase in Q3FY26, propelled by strong performance in financial services and technology practices. Government incentives for India's AI Mission and cloud infrastructure further bolstered investor confidence.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:18:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6980412b47db7081af67e2e8_1770013112588.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bank of Baroda Slumps as Margin Squeeze Sparks Analyst Downgrades</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bank-of-Baroda-Slumps-as-Margin-Squeeze-Sparks-Analyst-Downgrades/698040b847db7081af67e099</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bank-of-Baroda-Slumps-as-Margin-Squeeze-Sparks-Analyst-Downgrades/698040b847db7081af67e099</guid><description>Bank of Baroda shares experienced a significant sell-off, falling as much as 7% on Monday, February 2, 2026, following the release of its third-quarter financial results for FY26. The decline was triggered by analysts' concerns over a shrinking net interest margin (NIM) and stagnant net interest income (NII), despite a reported increase in net profit. Several brokerages responded by downgrading their ratings and revising target prices, citing ongoing pressures in the banking sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:18:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698040b847db7081af67e098_1770012972078.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Agarwal Ind. Secures ₹218 Cr BPCL Bitumen Supply Contract</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Agarwal-Ind-Secures-218-Cr-BPCL-Bitumen-Supply-Contract/6980414f47db7081af67e414</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Agarwal-Ind-Secures-218-Cr-BPCL-Bitumen-Supply-Contract/6980414f47db7081af67e414</guid><description>Agarwal Industrial Corporation Limited has bagged a substantial tender from Bharat Petroleum Corporation Limited (BPCL) for supplying Bulk Bitumen worth an estimated ₹218.59 Crores. The one-year contract, commencing January 2026, covers approximately 42,800 metric tonnes for Kakinada and Mangalore. This win reinforces AICL's position in the bitumen supply chain and offers significant revenue visibility for FY27.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:16:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lupin Launches US Generic Drug, Eyes $930M Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupin-Launches-US-Generic-Drug-Eyes-930M-Market/69803e5e47db7081af67d9b6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupin-Launches-US-Generic-Drug-Eyes-930M-Market/69803e5e47db7081af67d9b6</guid><description>Lupin Limited has launched Dasatinib Tablets in the United States following FDA approval. This generic drug, bioequivalent to Sprycel®, targets chronic myeloid leukemia (CML) and acute lymphoblastic leukemia (ALL). With an estimated annual sale of USD 930 million for the reference drug in the U.S., the launch presents a significant market opportunity for Lupin. The company developed the product in partnership with Pharmascience Inc.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:14:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69803e5e47db7081af67d9b5_1770012843439.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KOSPI Tumbles Amidst AI Spending Doubts and Fed Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/KOSPI-Tumbles-Amidst-AI-Spending-Doubts-and-Fed-Fears/69803edb47db7081af67dbc1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/KOSPI-Tumbles-Amidst-AI-Spending-Doubts-and-Fed-Fears/69803edb47db7081af67dbc1</guid><description>The South Korean benchmark KOSPI index experienced a sharp 5.5% decline, its steepest single-day fall since November 21. Heavyweight technology stocks, including Samsung Electronics and SK Hynix, registered losses exceeding 4%. This sell-off was triggered by concerns over the sustainability of AI-driven spending, amplified by remarks from Nvidia's CEO, and further exacerbated by uncertainty surrounding the nomination of Kevin Warsh as the next US Federal Reserve Chair. The broader Asian market also felt the pressure, with the MSCI Asia Pacific Index down 1.7%.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:14:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69803edb47db7081af67dbc0_1770012778531.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Crypto Tumbles: Warsh Nomination, ETF Outflows Spark Sell-off</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Crypto-Tumbles-Warsh-Nomination-ETF-Outflows-Spark-Sell-off/69803f7647db7081af67de88</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Crypto-Tumbles-Warsh-Nomination-ETF-Outflows-Spark-Sell-off/69803f7647db7081af67de88</guid><description>Cryptocurrencies experienced a sharp decline, with Bitcoin briefly falling below $75,000 and Ethereum near $2,200. The sell-off was fueled by speculation around a hawkish Federal Reserve nominee, substantial outflows from U.S. spot Bitcoin ETFs, and escalating geopolitical tensions. Cascading liquidations in leveraged positions exacerbated the downward pressure across the market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:11:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69803f7647db7081af67de87_1770012685793.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Plunges 37% Amidst Fed Nomination, Margin Call Frenzy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Plunges-37percent-Amidst-Fed-Nomination-Margin-Call-Frenzy/69803f5347db7081af67dd6e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Plunges-37percent-Amidst-Fed-Nomination-Margin-Call-Frenzy/69803f5347db7081af67dd6e</guid><description>Silver experienced a dramatic 37% price collapse on February 2, 2026, plummeting from record highs above $120/oz to approximately $79-$85/oz. This sharp decline was fueled by the nomination of Kevin Warsh as Federal Reserve chair, triggering expectations of tighter monetary policy and a strengthening US dollar, alongside aggressive CME margin calls forcing liquidation of leveraged positions. The extreme volatility reinforces concerns voiced by ICICI Prudential AMC's S. Naren, who advises caution on precious metals and favors diversified multi-asset strategies.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:10:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69803f5347db7081af67dd6d_1770012597790.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget STT Hike Rattles Indian Markets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-STT-Hike-Rattles-Indian-Markets/69803e7e47db7081af67da41</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-STT-Hike-Rattles-Indian-Markets/69803e7e47db7081af67da41</guid><description>Indian stock markets experienced significant volatility and decline following the Budget 2026 announcement, primarily driven by an unexpected increase in Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on futures and options. The market sell-off, which began during a special Sunday trading session on February 1, continued into Monday, February 2, exacerbated by weak global cues and substantial selling by foreign and domestic institutional investors. Major indices like the Sensex and Nifty saw sharp drops as trading costs increased, impacting investor sentiment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:08:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69803e7e47db7081af67da40_1770012428055.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Mfg PMI Ticks Up Amidst Lingering Caution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Mfg-PMI-Ticks-Up-Amidst-Lingering-Caution/69803d6e47db7081af67d606</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Mfg-PMI-Ticks-Up-Amidst-Lingering-Caution/69803d6e47db7081af67d606</guid><description>India's manufacturing activity edged higher in January, as indicated by the HSBC India Manufacturing PMI rising to 55.4. However, this modest gain did not translate into increased business optimism or significant hiring. While domestic demand showed improvement, weak export orders and rising input costs coupled with stagnant output prices paint a picture of cautious growth and potential margin pressures for manufacturers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:02:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69803d6e47db7081af67d605_1770012153637.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Manufacturing Recovers: PMI Rises to 55.4 in January</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Manufacturing-Recovers-PMI-Rises-to-554-in-January/69803de147db7081af67d828</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Manufacturing-Recovers-PMI-Rises-to-554-in-January/69803de147db7081af67d828</guid><description>India's manufacturing PMI surged to 55.4 in January, signaling renewed expansion after a December dip. Increased new orders, output, and employment fueled the rebound, according to HSBC. However, business confidence has fallen to a three-and-a-half-year low, with muted expectations for future production. Moderate input cost increases coupled with easing factory-gate price growth squeezed manufacturers' margins slightly. This sector performance occurs within a broader context of robust third-quarter economic growth projections.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:02:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Duty Changes Reshape Consumer Costs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/India-Budget-2026-Duty-Changes-Reshape-Consumer-Costs/69803c8247db7081af67d452</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/India-Budget-2026-Duty-Changes-Reshape-Consumer-Costs/69803c8247db7081af67d452</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 has enacted substantial changes to customs duties, affecting a wide array of consumer goods. Personal imports face a duty hike from 10% to 11%, making foreign shopping pricier. Conversely, essential sectors like healthcare see significant relief with 17 additional cancer drugs exempted from duty. Electronics and household appliances show mixed impacts, with some items becoming more expensive due to duty on parts, while others, like microwave ovens, are slated for price reductions following duty cuts on components. This budget signals a strategic recalibration of import costs, balancing support for domestic manufacturing with consumer affordability in key areas.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:02:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69803c8247db7081af67d451_1770012007473.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Industry Cheers Growth, Markets Wary of Debt</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Industry-Cheers-Growth-Markets-Wary-of-Debt/69803d9447db7081af67d70b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Industry-Cheers-Growth-Markets-Wary-of-Debt/69803d9447db7081af67d70b</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 has garnered broad industry approval for its strategic emphasis on long-term structural growth, policy continuity, and enhanced investment attractiveness. Leaders highlighted significant boosts to manufacturing, defence, and infrastructure sectors. However, market experts raised concerns regarding elevated government borrowing and increased Securities Transaction Tax (STT), signaling potential headwinds for capital markets and upward pressure on bond yields.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:00:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Shifts Fiscal Focus as Demographics Age</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Shifts-Fiscal-Focus-as-Demographics-Age/69803b9047db7081af67d256</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Shifts-Fiscal-Focus-as-Demographics-Age/69803b9047db7081af67d256</guid><description>India's 16th Finance Commission has adjusted its tax devolution formula, significantly lowering the weight given to demographic performance. This recalibration reflects growing concerns that the nation risks 'ageing before becoming rich,' a shift from previous policies focused solely on population control. States are increasingly preoccupied with declining fertility rates and potential labor shortages, prompting a broader re-evaluation of fiscal incentives and long-term growth strategies.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 05:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Courts MNCs with GCC Tax Reforms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Courts-MNCs-with-GCC-Tax-Reforms/69803a2947db7081af67cf6d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Courts-MNCs-with-GCC-Tax-Reforms/69803a2947db7081af67cf6d</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026-27 introduces substantial transfer pricing reforms aimed at attracting Global Capability Centers (GCCs). The safe harbour framework's threshold has surged from ₹300 crore to ₹2,000 crore, with a simplified, uniform margin of 15.5% for IT services. These changes, alongside automated approvals and faster Advance Pricing Agreements, are designed to provide greater tax certainty and foster significant multinational investment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 05:52:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69803a2947db7081af67cf6c_1770011285296.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>E To E Infrastructure Lands ₹81 Cr in Rail Contracts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/E-To-E-Infrastructure-Lands-81-Cr-in-Rail-Contracts/698037cb47db7081af67cb75</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/E-To-E-Infrastructure-Lands-81-Cr-in-Rail-Contracts/698037cb47db7081af67cb75</guid><description>E To E Transportation Infrastructure Limited has significantly bolstered its order backlog, securing new domestic works contracts totaling approximately ₹81.31 crore from Southern Railway and South Central Railway divisions. The Thiruvananthapuram division awarded ₹20.6 crore for signalling and telecommunication works at Kumbalam station, while the Secunderabad division contracted ₹60.71 crore for an Automatic Block Signalling system installation. These awards contribute to a cumulative order intake of ₹215.71 crore (including GST) between October 2025 and February 2026 for the rail engineering firm.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 05:51:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698037cb47db7081af67cb74_1770011488739.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>