<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:37:17 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Cipla Faces USFDA OAI at Supplier; Lanreotide Injection Supply Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Cipla-Faces-USFDA-OAI-at-Supplier-Lanreotide-Injection-Supply-Risk/6999a49e730b6847a517713e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Cipla-Faces-USFDA-OAI-at-Supplier-Lanreotide-Injection-Supply-Risk/6999a49e730b6847a517713e</guid><description>Cipla announced a USFDA inspection at its key supplier Pharmathen International S.A.'s facility in Greece resulted in an 'Official Action Indicated' (OAI) classification. This finding suggests significant regulatory violations, potentially disrupting the supply chain for Lanreotide Injection, a critical product for Cipla USA Inc. The company is awaiting Pharmathen's corrective actions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:27:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999a49e730b6847a517713d_1771676973131.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rudra Ecovation Shareholders Meet on Shiva Texfabs Amalgamation Scheme</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Rudra-Ecovation-Shareholders-Meet-on-Shiva-Texfabs-Amalgamation-Scheme/6999a497730b6847a5177128</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Rudra-Ecovation-Shareholders-Meet-on-Shiva-Texfabs-Amalgamation-Scheme/6999a497730b6847a5177128</guid><description>Rudra Ecovation Limited shareholders met virtually on February 21, 2026, to vote on its amalgamation with Shiva Texfabs Limited. The scheme, approved by boards and progressing through regulatory steps including NCLT orders, aims to leverage synergies and strengthen market position in sustainable textiles. E-voting results are awaited, marking a crucial step before final approvals.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:27:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999a497730b6847a5177127_1771676937551.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NSE IPO Legal Roadblock Cleared, Substantive Claims Unresolved</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/NSE-IPO-Legal-Roadblock-Cleared-Substantive-Claims-Unresolved/6999a464730b6847a51770e7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/NSE-IPO-Legal-Roadblock-Cleared-Substantive-Claims-Unresolved/6999a464730b6847a51770e7</guid><description>The National Stock Exchange's (NSE) long-awaited initial public offering (IPO) has overcome a significant legal hurdle as the Delhi High Court dismissed a petition challenging the Securities and Exchange Board of India's (SEBI) no-objection certificate (NOC). The court's decision, however, was based on territorial jurisdiction rather than the merits of the petitioner's serious allegations concerning corporate action adjustments and potential financial improprieties. This procedural victory clears the path for an Offer for Sale (OFS), but the unaddressed claims introduce a lingering risk profile.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:26:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999a464730b6847a51770e6_1771676895106.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Exhicon subsidiary UHPL secures DGCA AOP for helicopter operations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Exhicon-subsidiary-UHPL-secures-DGCA-AOP-for-helicopter-operations/6999a420730b6847a517705e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Exhicon-subsidiary-UHPL-secures-DGCA-AOP-for-helicopter-operations/6999a420730b6847a517705e</guid><description>Exhicon Events Media Solutions is expanding into active helicopter flying operations via its subsidiary, United Helicharters Private Limited (UHPL). UHPL has received an Air Operator Permit (AOP) from the DGCA, valid for five years, marking a strategic pivot from aviation support to commercial charter services.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:25:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999a420730b6847a517705d_1771676858836.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Chrome Silicon Q3 Loss Widens as Operations Remain Suspended, Audit Flags Mount</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Chrome-Silicon-Q3-Loss-Widens-as-Operations-Remain-Suspended-Audit-Flags-Mount/6999a420730b6847a5177048</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Chrome-Silicon-Q3-Loss-Widens-as-Operations-Remain-Suspended-Audit-Flags-Mount/6999a420730b6847a5177048</guid><description>Chrome Silicon Limited reported a net loss of ₹2.13 crore for the quarter ending December 31, 2025, on a total income of ₹5.34 crore. Total income plummeted 77.32% year-on-year. Crucially, manufacturing operations have been suspended since May 2025 due to market volatility. The company's auditors have raised significant qualifications regarding the accuracy of financial statements, including unverified inventories and assets, unconfirmed liabilities, and uncertain loan recoverability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:25:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999a420730b6847a5177047_1771676826623.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Pharma: Td Vaccine Launch Signals Sector Maturation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Pharma-Td-Vaccine-Launch-Signals-Sector-Maturation/6999a3aa730b6847a5176f9b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Pharma-Td-Vaccine-Launch-Signals-Sector-Maturation/6999a3aa730b6847a5176f9b</guid><description>Union Health Minister J.P. Nadda launched India's indigenously manufactured Tetanus and adult Diphtheria (Td) vaccine, a significant step for national health security and the 'Atmanirbhar Bharat' vision. The Central Research Institute will supply 55 lakh doses to the Universal Immunization Programme by April 2026, bolstering domestic production capabilities. This event aligns with robust growth projections for India's pharmaceutical sector, driven by strong domestic demand and government incentives, reinforcing its global "pharmacy of the world" status, though challenges in scaling and market competition persist for the broader industry.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:23:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999a3aa730b6847a5176f9a_1771676717908.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-France Strategic Partnership Deepens: Defense, Tech Deals Signal New Era</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-France-Strategic-Partnership-Deepens-Defense-Tech-Deals-Signal-New-Era/6999a1c5730b6847a5176e53</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-France-Strategic-Partnership-Deepens-Defense-Tech-Deals-Signal-New-Era/6999a1c5730b6847a5176e53</guid><description>The India-France relationship has been elevated to a "Special Global Strategic Partnership," marked by significant defense agreements, including a substantial Rafale jet contract and helicopter production, alongside increased cooperation in critical minerals, AI, and innovation. This strategic deepening aims to bolster industrial self-reliance, enhance regional security in the Indo-Pacific, and navigate a complex global order, reflecting a long-term co-development vision.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:15:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999a1c5730b6847a5176e52_1771676273656.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Tariff Ruling Sparks Volatility; India Rallies AI &amp; Defence Investments</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Tariff-Ruling-Sparks-Volatility-India-Rallies-AI-and-Defence-Investments/6999a159730b6847a5176df4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Tariff-Ruling-Sparks-Volatility-India-Rallies-AI-and-Defence-Investments/6999a159730b6847a5176df4</guid><description>Indian equity markets experienced their sharpest decline since Budget Day on February 19, 2026, with the Nifty 50 falling 1.6% and the Sensex dropping 1.5%. This came after a US Supreme Court ruling struck down President Trump's tariffs, though he quickly announced new ones. Simultaneously, India hosted its AI Impact Summit, securing over $360 billion in investment commitments, and advanced talks on the Rafale jet deal, signaling robust domestic growth potential amidst global trade uncertainty.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:13:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999a159730b6847a5176df3_1771676122265.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rishab Special Yarns to become IMPERA WORLDWIDE; approves Rights Issue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Rishab-Special-Yarns-to-become-IMPERA-WORLDWIDE-approves-Rights-Issue/69999fea730b6847a5176d40</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Rishab-Special-Yarns-to-become-IMPERA-WORLDWIDE-approves-Rights-Issue/69999fea730b6847a5176d40</guid><description>Rishab Special Yarns Limited has announced a significant board resolution to change its name to IMPERA WORLDWIDE LIMITED, subject to shareholder approval. The company also greenlit an increase in its authorised share capital and a proposal for a Rights Issue to raise funds. The board appointed SHRAVAN A. GUPTA &amp; ASSOCIATES as scrutinizer for the upcoming postal ballot process.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 12:07:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69999fea730b6847a5176d3f_1771675731949.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Manufacturing Ambition Meets US Tariff Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Manufacturing-Ambition-Meets-US-Tariff-Volatility/69999e0a730b6847a5176c1c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Manufacturing-Ambition-Meets-US-Tariff-Volatility/69999e0a730b6847a5176c1c</guid><description>Despite ongoing volatility from US trade tariff announcements, India's manufacturing sector is poised for significant expansion, driven by government initiatives and a strategic focus on domestic production and global supply chain diversification. Companies like Kirloskar Brothers demonstrate resilience against prior tariff pressures, while financial entities like JM Financial navigate market flux. Current valuations and mixed analyst sentiment for key players underscore the dynamic operational environment as India aims to leverage global shifts into a manufacturing powerhouse.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 11:59:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69999e0a730b6847a5176c1b_1771675282301.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Triveni Turbine Faces Tariff Headwinds, Valuation in Focus</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Triveni-Turbine-Faces-Tariff-Headwinds-Valuation-in-Focus/69999e07730b6847a5176c05</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Triveni-Turbine-Faces-Tariff-Headwinds-Valuation-in-Focus/69999e07730b6847a5176c05</guid><description>Triveni Turbine confronts challenges from fluctuating US tariff policies, impacting its global supply chain visibility and cross-border pricing. Despite a 150-day tariff window, long-term planning remains difficult. The company's stock has fallen over 17% in the past year, with a market capitalization of approximately ₹15,608.42 crore. While the Indian manufacturing sector shows resilience, Triveni Turbine's valuation is under review amidst these trade uncertainties and varying analyst outlooks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 11:59:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69999e07730b6847a5176c04_1771675309036.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Power &amp; Instrumentation Q3 FY26 Revenue Surges 43%; Bags ₹124 Cr Orders</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Power-and-Instrumentation-Q3-FY26-Revenue-Surges-43percent-Bags-124-Cr-Orders/69999ca0730b6847a5176b11</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Power-and-Instrumentation-Q3-FY26-Revenue-Surges-43percent-Bags-124-Cr-Orders/69999ca0730b6847a5176b11</guid><description>Power &amp; Instrumentation (Gujarat) Limited posted robust Q3 FY26 results with consolidated income up 43.18% YoY to ₹48.89 Cr, boosted by ₹124.17 Cr in new contracts, including significant RDSS projects. The company targets 30-35% revenue growth over five years and is expanding into specialized manufacturing like busduct systems. Strong order book provides visibility, though working capital remains a monitor point.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 11:53:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69999ca0730b6847a5176b10_1771674961413.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NCC Limited gets Delhi HC interim relief on NHAI debarment order</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCC-Limited-gets-Delhi-HC-interim-relief-on-NHAI-debarment-order/6999959a730b6847a5176903</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCC-Limited-gets-Delhi-HC-interim-relief-on-NHAI-debarment-order/6999959a730b6847a5176903</guid><description>NCC Limited has received a significant reprieve as the Delhi High Court granted interim protection, putting a debarment order from the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) on hold. This interim relief is effective until March 10, 2026, allowing NCC to continue its operations without immediate restrictions while it pursues further legal recourse.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 11:23:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999959a730b6847a5176902_1771673143662.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Navigates US Tariffs With Strategic Trade Realignment</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Navigates-US-Tariffs-With-Strategic-Trade-Realignment/699994b6730b6847a5176837</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Navigates-US-Tariffs-With-Strategic-Trade-Realignment/699994b6730b6847a5176837</guid><description>New Delhi is meticulously assessing the implications of recent US Supreme Court tariff rulings and President Trump's subsequent announcements. The Indian government's commerce ministry is studying these developments to understand potential impacts on the nation's export competitiveness and overall trade balance. This strategic review signals India's intent to adapt its economic policies and safeguard national interests in response to evolving international trade regulations. The move underscores a broader effort to enhance economic resilience through proactive trade recalibrations.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 11:19:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699994b6730b6847a5176836_1771672867408.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>R&amp;B Denims Bags ₹216 Cr Orders; 12M Meters Denim Fabric to be Supplied</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/RandB-Denims-Bags-216-Cr-Orders-12M-Meters-Denim-Fabric-to-be-Supplied/6999942f730b6847a51767d4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/RandB-Denims-Bags-216-Cr-Orders-12M-Meters-Denim-Fabric-to-be-Supplied/6999942f730b6847a51767d4</guid><description>R&amp;B Denims Limited announced a significant win with new sales orders worth ₹215.88 crore for approximately 12 million meters of denim fabric. These orders are slated for execution within the next six months, significantly boosting the company's revenue visibility and order book position. The development underscores strong demand traction and the company's growing execution capabilities in the competitive textile market.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 11:17:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999942f730b6847a51767d3_1771672764171.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gulf Oil Lubricants Secures Mahindra Deal, Fuels EV Ambitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Gulf-Oil-Lubricants-Secures-Mahindra-Deal-Fuels-EV-Ambitions/699990ed730b6847a517669a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Gulf-Oil-Lubricants-Secures-Mahindra-Deal-Fuels-EV-Ambitions/699990ed730b6847a517669a</guid><description>Gulf Oil Lubricants India Limited (GOLIL) has inked its longest-ever multi-year partnership renewal with Mahindra &amp; Mahindra's Farm Equipment Sector. This strategic alliance solidifies GOLIL's dominant position in the agricultural lubricant market, providing a stable revenue stream. The deepened bond is crucial for funding the company's aggressive diversification into electric vehicle (EV) mobility solutions and battery replacement segments, signaling a dual-pronged growth strategy.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 11:03:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699990ed730b6847a5176699_1771671917922.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Motherson Group Bets Big on $108B Target Amidst Diversification Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Motherson-Group-Bets-Big-on-108B-Target-Amidst-Diversification-Risks/69998e1a730b6847a517655d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Motherson-Group-Bets-Big-on-108B-Target-Amidst-Diversification-Risks/69998e1a730b6847a517655d</guid><description>Motherson Group Chairman Vivek Chaand Sehgal has reiterated the ambitious goal of achieving $108 billion in revenue by 2030, coupled with a challenging 40% return on capital employed (ROCE). The conglomerate reported ₹1.13 trillion (approximately $13.6 billion) in revenue for FY25, a 15% increase year-on-year. This expansion strategy involves a significant pivot beyond its core automotive components business into consumer electronics, medical equipment, and drone parts manufacturing. The company's largest factory has already shifted production to consumer electronics, signaling a major operational realignmen t. This aggressive push, however, introduces substantial execution risks and a heightened competitive profile in new markets, even as analysts maintain a generally positive outlook.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:51:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69998e1a730b6847a517655c_1771671204862.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hilltone Gases Adds CO2, Argon; Targets 25% Margin Boost and 15% Logistics Cut</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hilltone-Gases-Adds-CO2-Argon-Targets-25percent-Margin-Boost-and-15percent-Logistics-Cut/69998e19730b6847a5176546</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hilltone-Gases-Adds-CO2-Argon-Targets-25percent-Margin-Boost-and-15percent-Logistics-Cut/69998e19730b6847a5176546</guid><description>Hilltone Software &amp; Gases Limited is expanding its Industrial Gases division by adding Carbon Dioxide (CO2) and Argon, investing in new storage and bottling infrastructure. The company expects this move to improve supply reliability, enhance customer service, and control procurement, with a target of a 25% gross profit margin improvement in the vertical and a 15% reduction in logistics costs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:51:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69998e19730b6847a5176545_1771671173510.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tax Savings: ELSS, ULIPs, NPS Costs &amp; Risks Revealed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Tax-Savings-ELSS-ULIPs-NPS-Costs-and-Risks-Revealed/69998c65730b6847a5176457</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Tax-Savings-ELSS-ULIPs-NPS-Costs-and-Risks-Revealed/69998c65730b6847a5176457</guid><description>With the financial year-end approaching, high-income earners find the Old Tax Regime (OTR) appealing due to various deductions. However, a critical examination of investment vehicles like Equity Linked Savings Schemes (ELSS), Unit Linked Insurance Plans (ULIPs), and the National Pension System (NPS) is essential. While offering tax advantages, these instruments carry distinct risks, significant charges, and evolving regulatory landscapes that can dilute net returns, making a 'penny saved' potentially costlier than anticipated.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:43:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69998c65730b6847a5176456_1771670795195.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fineotex Chemical Q3 Revenue Surges 46%; Acquires US Oilfield Firm</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Fineotex-Chemical-Q3-Revenue-Surges-46percent-Acquires-US-Oilfield-Firm/699989e0730b6847a5176353</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Fineotex-Chemical-Q3-Revenue-Surges-46percent-Acquires-US-Oilfield-Firm/699989e0730b6847a5176353</guid><description>Fineotex Chemical Limited reported a robust 46% year-on-year revenue growth to INR 190.46 crore for Q3 FY26. This surge was driven by its strategic acquisition of US-based CrudeChem Technologies (CCT), which significantly expanded its presence in the oil and gas sector. Despite the strong top-line performance, gross margins compressed to approximately 36% due to integration costs and temporary pricing adjustments. The company, however, remains debt-free with strong cash reserves, positioning it for future expansion and a target of INR 1,000 crore revenue in FY27.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:33:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699989e0730b6847a5176352_1771670095032.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global AI Accord: India Summit Sparks $270B Investment, Risks Remain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Global-AI-Accord-India-Summit-Sparks-270B-Investment-Risks-Remain/6999853c730b6847a517619a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Global-AI-Accord-India-Summit-Sparks-270B-Investment-Risks-Remain/6999853c730b6847a517619a</guid><description>The India AI Impact Summit concluded with 86 nations signing a declaration for responsible AI, signaling broad global agreement. Over $270 billion in investment commitments, split between infrastructure ($250B+) and venture capital ($20B), highlight strong global confidence in India's AI ecosystem. Despite the accord, significant hurdles remain in truly democratizing AI and bridging the global 'AI divide'.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:13:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999853c730b6847a5176199_1771668912894.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ashoka Buildcon-Railtel Bags ₹1136 Cr Maharashtra IGR IT Project LOI</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Ashoka-Buildcon-Railtel-Bags-1136-Cr-Maharashtra-IGR-IT-Project-LOI/69998318730b6847a51760c2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Ashoka-Buildcon-Railtel-Bags-1136-Cr-Maharashtra-IGR-IT-Project-LOI/69998318730b6847a51760c2</guid><description>Ashoka Buildcon, in consortium with Railtel Corporation of India, has received a Letter of Intent (LOI) from the Maharashtra government for a project valued at an estimated ₹1136.18 crore. The five-year contract will focus on the modernization, operation, and maintenance of IT infrastructure for the state's Inspector General of Registration (IGR) offices. This award marks a significant expansion of Ashoka Buildcon's service offerings into government IT infrastructure management.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 10:04:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69998318730b6847a51760c1_1771668352225.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian IT Valuations Face Pressure Amid Growth Slowdown</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Valuations-Face-Pressure-Amid-Growth-Slowdown/699981b5730b6847a5175fa9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Valuations-Face-Pressure-Amid-Growth-Slowdown/699981b5730b6847a5175fa9</guid><description>Nilesh Shah of Envision Capital suggests Indian IT companies trading at 19-20 times earnings should adjust to around 15 times, reflecting projected 5-8% rupee growth. Current sector valuations are seen as disconnected from this muted outlook, with a potential need for further multiple contraction to align with historical norms and peer growth.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:58:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699981b5730b6847a5175fa8_1771668029133.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-Brazil Trade Surge: Critical Minerals &amp; Global South Power</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-Brazil-Trade-Surge-Critical-Minerals-and-Global-South-Power/699981b3730b6847a5175f92</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-Brazil-Trade-Surge-Critical-Minerals-and-Global-South-Power/699981b3730b6847a5175f92</guid><description>India and Brazil are forging a new strategic economic alliance, setting an ambitious target to exceed $20 billion in bilateral trade within five years. This collaboration centers on critical minerals, aiming to diversify supply chains and reduce reliance on dominant global processors. Discussions also encompass artificial intelligence and strengthening the collective voice of the Global South amidst evolving geopolitical dynamics. The partnership underscores a move towards greater South-South economic cooperation.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:58:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699981b3730b6847a5175f91_1771668019585.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Crypto Paradox: High Adoption, Regulatory Void</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Indias-Crypto-Paradox-High-Adoption-Regulatory-Void/69998099730b6847a5175ed2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Indias-Crypto-Paradox-High-Adoption-Regulatory-Void/69998099730b6847a5175ed2</guid><description>India's approach to cryptocurrency is a paradox: while users rank globally high in adoption, comprehensive legislation remains absent. The government cautions against 'stateless' digital assets, yet the underlying blockchain technology is embraced. This regulatory ambiguity, coupled with a 30% crypto tax, creates an environment where virtual digital asset providers are reporting entities under anti-money laundering laws, but the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) still deliberates a potential ban. This oscillation between tolerance and distrust highlights significant risks from illicit activities, hacks, and market manipulation.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:53:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69998099730b6847a5175ed1_1771667709721.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MAS Financial: INR 1 Lakh Cr AUM Target by 2036; Eyes 25% Annual Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/MAS-Financial-INR-1-Lakh-Cr-AUM-Target-by-2036-Eyes-25percent-Annual-Growth/69997f8f730b6847a5175e20</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/MAS-Financial-INR-1-Lakh-Cr-AUM-Target-by-2036-Eyes-25percent-Annual-Growth/69997f8f730b6847a5175e20</guid><description>MAS Financial Services has laid out an ambitious 'Vision 2036' strategy, targeting INR 1 lakh crore in Assets Under Management (AUM) by 2036, a nearly seven-fold increase from current levels. The non-banking financial company (NBFC) plans to achieve this through a 20-25% annual AUM growth, driven by a strategic pivot towards direct sourcing, which now accounts for 65% of its business. The company also aims for improved profitability metrics, including an ROA of 2.75-3.00% and ROE of 15-17%, while keeping 20-25% of AUM off-book via co-lending and direct assignment.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:49:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69997f8f730b6847a5175e1f_1771667486423.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Market Hours Debate: Clarity Over Speed Amid Policy Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Market-Hours-Debate-Clarity-Over-Speed-Amid-Policy-Shifts/69997d73730b6847a5175d1e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Market-Hours-Debate-Clarity-Over-Speed-Amid-Policy-Shifts/69997d73730b6847a5175d1e</guid><description>Fund manager Samir Arora is urging Indian regulators to reconsider demands for extended stock market hours during major economic announcements. He argues that a deeper comprehension of policy changes is paramount, using the recent US tariff framework and subsequent legal clarifications as a prime example of persistent uncertainty that makes immediate trading risky. The debate highlights a fundamental tension between the velocity of information and the necessity for analytical rigor in financial markets. This perspective contrasts with ongoing proposals by exchanges to lengthen trading sessions, which SEBI has so far resisted due to a lack of consensus among market participants.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:40:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69997d73730b6847a5175d1d_1771666967789.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vikram Solar ₹2000cr Pact; Secures 2GW High-Efficiency Cells from Jupiter</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Vikram-Solar-2000cr-Pact-Secures-2GW-High-Efficiency-Cells-from-Jupiter/69997d3a730b6847a5175cd8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Vikram-Solar-2000cr-Pact-Secures-2GW-High-Efficiency-Cells-from-Jupiter/69997d3a730b6847a5175cd8</guid><description>Vikram Solar Limited has signed a strategic agreement with Jupiter International Limited to procure 2 GW of high-efficiency TopCon and mono PERC solar cells, valued at approximately ₹2000 crore. Finalized on February 20, 2026, this deal enhances Vikram Solar's domestic supply chain for critical ALMM-compliant components, bolstering its manufacturing capabilities.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:39:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69997d3a730b6847a5175cd7_1771666854595.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MIDHANI Q3 PAT Surges 115% QoQ to ₹27.46 Cr; Turnover Grows 31%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/MIDHANI-Q3-PAT-Surges-115percent-QoQ-to-2746-Cr-Turnover-Grows-31percent/69997c53730b6847a5175c2a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/MIDHANI-Q3-PAT-Surges-115percent-QoQ-to-2746-Cr-Turnover-Grows-31percent/69997c53730b6847a5175c2a</guid><description>Mishra Dhatu Nigam (MIDHANI) reported a strong Q3 FY26 with Profit After Tax (PAT) soaring to ₹27.46 crore, a 115% increase from the previous quarter. Turnover grew by 31.44% to ₹275.66 crore, boosted by significant order book expansion to ₹2,594 crore. Key supplies for the Ayodhya Ram Mandir and technical certifications underscore its critical role in defense and infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:35:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69997c53730b6847a5175c29_1771666620213.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MOIL Wins ₹58 Cr GST Appeal, Demand &amp; Penalty Quashed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/MOIL-Wins-58-Cr-GST-Appeal-Demand-and-Penalty-Quashed/69997a68730b6847a5175b6e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/MOIL-Wins-58-Cr-GST-Appeal-Demand-and-Penalty-Quashed/69997a68730b6847a5175b6e</guid><description>MOIL Limited has secured a significant legal victory, with the appellate authority quashing a GST demand of ₹20.29 crore, an equivalent penalty, and an estimated ₹15-18 crore in interest. This ruling effectively nullifies a potential total liability of ₹55-58 crore, removing a major financial overhang for the state-owned mining company. While the order provides substantial relief, the possibility of further appeals by the tax department remains a point to monitor.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:27:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69997a68730b6847a5175b6d_1771666130316.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IEA Pact Boosts Critical Minerals; US Climate Dissent Signals Rifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/IEA-Pact-Boosts-Critical-Minerals-US-Climate-Dissent-Signals-Rifts/69997993730b6847a5175ac5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/IEA-Pact-Boosts-Critical-Minerals-US-Climate-Dissent-Signals-Rifts/69997993730b6847a5175ac5</guid><description>Energy ministers from 54 nations reinforced global cooperation on critical minerals and energy security, agreeing to expand the IEA's Critical Minerals Security Programme. Despite US pressure to de-emphasize climate action, ministers reaffirmed commitments to decarbonization goals. The meeting also saw Colombia invited as the 33rd member, Brazil begin accession, and Vietnam join as an Association country. The Clean Cooking Alliance will integrate into the IEA, establishing it as a key forum for universal access to modern cooking energy. However, the US stance signals a potential fragmentation of global energy strategy, prioritizing national security and industrial competitiveness over unified climate objectives.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:23:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69997993730b6847a5175ac4_1771665954483.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Quality Care India Targets Nagpur with ₹600 Cr PPP Hospital Amidst Sector Consolidation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Quality-Care-India-Targets-Nagpur-with-600-Cr-PPP-Hospital-Amidst-Sector-Consolidation/69997889730b6847a5175a1a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Quality-Care-India-Targets-Nagpur-with-600-Cr-PPP-Hospital-Amidst-Sector-Consolidation/69997889730b6847a5175a1a</guid><description>Quality Care India is set to invest ₹600 crore in a 350+ bed multi-speciality hospital in Nagpur, leveraging a public-private partnership (PPP) with Maha-Metro. This project targets strengthening healthcare in Central India, creating over 1,500 jobs, and aligns with broader industry trends of expansion into Tier-2 cities and consolidation within the sector, highlighted by its proposed merger with Aster DM Healthcare.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:19:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69997889730b6847a5175a19_1771665666942.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Electricity Mumbai's Credit Rating Upgraded to Crisil AAA</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Adani-Electricity-Mumbais-Credit-Rating-Upgraded-to-Crisil-AAA/69997797730b6847a517596d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Adani-Electricity-Mumbais-Credit-Rating-Upgraded-to-Crisil-AAA/69997797730b6847a517596d</guid><description>Adani Electricity Mumbai Limited (AEML), a unit of Adani Energy Solutions, received a credit rating upgrade to 'Crisil AAA' for its proposed NCDs, from 'Crisil AA+/Positive' with a Stable Outlook. This highest rating signifies improved financial standing and is expected to lower borrowing costs for future funding.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:15:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69997797730b6847a517596c_1771665420361.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Akme Fintrade OKs ₹85.75 Cr Warrant Issue; EGM on March 20</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Akme-Fintrade-OKs-8575-Cr-Warrant-Issue-EGM-on-March-20/69997721730b6847a51758fd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Akme-Fintrade-OKs-8575-Cr-Warrant-Issue-EGM-on-March-20/69997721730b6847a51758fd</guid><description>Akme Fintrade's Board has approved a preferential issue of up to 12.25 crore warrants at ₹7 each, aiming to raise ₹85.75 crore. These warrants are convertible into equity shares within 18 months. Shareholder approval is slated for an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM) on March 20, 2026. This capital infusion is crucial for the NBFC's expansion plans.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:13:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69997721730b6847a51758fc_1771665292292.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Steel: EU Carbon Tax Boost or Costly Burden?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-EU-Carbon-Tax-Boost-or-Costly-Burden/6999764a730b6847a5175840</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-EU-Carbon-Tax-Boost-or-Costly-Burden/6999764a730b6847a5175840</guid><description>Tata Steel Ltd. anticipates the European Union's Carbon Border Adjustment Mechanism (CBAM) will benefit its operations, positioning it as an 'equalisation tax' rather than a detriment. Managing Director TV Narendran highlighted that the company's significant European production footprint shields it from import tariffs. However, the global steel sector faces considerable disruption, with ongoing discussions and potential retaliatory measures from trading partners. Tata Steel's long-term decarbonization strategy in Europe, including phasing out blast furnaces by 2035, aligns with the EU's climate goals, yet the substantial investment required and evolving policy landscape present critical future considerations.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:09:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999764a730b6847a517583f_1771665071149.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UVS Hospitality Acquires Calcio Restaurants for ₹350 Cr; Plans ₹47 Cr Fundraise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/UVS-Hospitality-Acquires-Calcio-Restaurants-for-350-Cr-Plans-47-Cr-Fundraise/699975ba730b6847a517579e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/UVS-Hospitality-Acquires-Calcio-Restaurants-for-350-Cr-Plans-47-Cr-Fundraise/699975ba730b6847a517579e</guid><description>UVS Hospitality and Services Limited is set to acquire up to 51% of Calcio Restaurants Private Limited in a substantial ₹350.27 crore share swap deal. The company also plans to raise ₹47.48 crore via a preferential issue and warrants. This strategic move aims to consolidate operations and bolster its presence in the hospitality and restaurant sector.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 09:07:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699975ba730b6847a517579d_1771664928267.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani's NMIA Rolls Out DigiYatra Amidst Sector Growth Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Adanis-NMIA-Rolls-Out-DigiYatra-Amidst-Sector-Growth-Concerns/6999710a730b6847a5175601</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Adanis-NMIA-Rolls-Out-DigiYatra-Amidst-Sector-Growth-Concerns/6999710a730b6847a5175601</guid><description>Navi Mumbai International Airport (NMIA), operated by Adani Airport Holdings Ltd. (AAHL), has launched its DigiYatra biometric system. This integration utilizes facial recognition for contactless, paperless passenger processing, aiming to reduce wait times and improve efficiency. NMIA is a key component of AAHL's expanding network and its significant expansion plans for India's growing aviation market. The rollout occurs as the broader Indian aviation sector navigates challenges including slowing growth and operational disruptions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:47:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999710a730b6847a5175600_1771663770053.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dr. Reddy's Secures First Abatacept Biosimilar Approval</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Dr-Reddys-Secures-First-Abatacept-Biosimilar-Approval/69996a03730b6847a51753f3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Dr-Reddys-Secures-First-Abatacept-Biosimilar-Approval/69996a03730b6847a51753f3</guid><description>Dr. Reddy's Laboratories has achieved a significant regulatory milestone with the U.S. FDA accepting its Biologics License Application (BLA) for DRL-AB, a proposed biosimilar to Orencia® (abatacept). This marks the first such submission for an abatacept biosimilar, positioning Dr. Reddy's as a first-mover in the United States. The approval, expected to bring a cost-effective alternative for rheumatoid arthritis and other autoimmune conditions, underscores the company's growing capabilities in complex biologics and intensifies the competitive landscape for originator biologics.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:17:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69996a03730b6847a51753f2.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal Rocked by US Tariff Ruling</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Rocked-by-US-Tariff-Ruling/69996990730b6847a5175387</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Rocked-by-US-Tariff-Ruling/69996990730b6847a5175387</guid><description>The nascent India-US interim trade agreement faces significant headwinds following the US Supreme Court's invalidation of executive tariff authority. Indian opposition parties are demanding a renegotiation, citing risks to farmers and political motivations. While the US administration signals intent to reintroduce tariffs via alternative statutes, the ruling exposes the trade pact's structural fragility, amplifying concerns about its durability and India's strategic trade policy adjustments.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:15:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69996990730b6847a5175386.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Stays Put: Liquidity Focus Signals New Policy Era</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Stays-Put-Liquidity-Focus-Signals-New-Policy-Era/69996849730b6847a517529f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Stays-Put-Liquidity-Focus-Signals-New-Policy-Era/69996849730b6847a517529f</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) is expected to hold its benchmark repo rate steady at 5.25% through FY2026-27, signaling a prolonged pause. This strategy emphasizes proactive liquidity management and effective policy transmission over further rate adjustments. Bolstered by robust domestic demand and favorable trade agreements, India's growth outlook remains strong, projected to exceed 6.8% in FY27. While inflation is expected to rise from historic lows, it is anticipated to stay within the RBI's target band, suggesting minimal immediate pressure for rate hikes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 08:09:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69996849730b6847a517529e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>