<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:25:13 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Mumbai Real Estate REBORN: Why Redevelopment is Now MANDATORY for the Entire City!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Mumbai-Real-Estate-REBORN-Why-Redevelopment-is-Now-MANDATORY-for-the-Entire-City/6950c75a4342f77179da6ef3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Mumbai-Real-Estate-REBORN-Why-Redevelopment-is-Now-MANDATORY-for-the-Entire-City/6950c75a4342f77179da6ef3</guid><description>Mumbai's real estate market is undergoing a mandatory transformation through redevelopment, driven by extreme land scarcity and aging infrastructure. Over 910 housing societies have initiated redevelopment projects, unlocking significant buildable area. Anand Pandit, Chairman of Sri Lotus Developers, highlights evolving consumer aspirations and the growing demand for ultra-luxury homes, positioning redevelopment as foundational to the city's future.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 05:51:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6950c75a4342f77179da6ef2_1766901691165.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Paytm's Shocking 2025 Comeback: RBI Ban Can't Stop Fintech Giant's Record Profit Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Paytms-Shocking-2025-Comeback-RBI-Ban-Cant-Stop-Fintech-Giants-Record-Profit-Surge/6950c6814342f77179da6d8b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Paytms-Shocking-2025-Comeback-RBI-Ban-Cant-Stop-Fintech-Giants-Record-Profit-Surge/6950c6814342f77179da6d8b</guid><description>Paytm staged a dramatic turnaround in 2025, swinging to a INR 122.5 Cr profit in Q1 FY26 from massive losses a year prior. Following RBI restrictions on its Payments Bank, the company pivoted to a pure payments and merchant services model, focusing on UPI, device subscriptions, and DLG-led lending. This strategic reset, coupled with cost reductions and a move towards AI, has positioned Paytm for a leaner, more focused future despite a competitive landscape.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 05:47:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6950c6814342f77179da6d8a_1766901584838.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PMO Shocker: Coal India Subsidiaries Must List by 2030! Are You Ready?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/PMO-Shocker-Coal-India-Subsidiaries-Must-List-by-2030-Are-You-Ready/6950bfae4342f77179da64d5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/PMO-Shocker-Coal-India-Subsidiaries-Must-List-by-2030-Are-You-Ready/6950bfae4342f77179da64d5</guid><description>The Prime Minister's Office (PMO) has issued a directive to the coal ministry, mandating that all subsidiaries of Coal India Limited (CIL) be listed on stock exchanges by 2030. This strategic move aims to significantly improve governance, boost transparency, and unlock value through asset monetization within the state-run coal giant. Initial plans are already underway, with Bharat Coking Coal Ltd and Central Mine Planning &amp; Design Institute Ltd expected to list by March 2026, and South Eastern Coalfields Ltd and Mahanadi Coalfields Ltd targeted for the next financial year.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 05:19:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6950bfae4342f77179da64d4_1766899691645.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rolls-Royce Bets BIG on India: Eyes 3rd 'Home Market' for Jet Engines &amp; Naval Tech! 🚀</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Rolls-Royce-Bets-BIG-on-India-Eyes-3rd-Home-Market-for-Jet-Engines-and-Naval-Tech/6950bf5d4342f77179da647d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Rolls-Royce-Bets-BIG-on-India-Eyes-3rd-Home-Market-for-Jet-Engines-and-Naval-Tech/6950bf5d4342f77179da647d</guid><description>British aerospace giant Rolls-Royce plans to make India its third "home market" after the UK, US, and Germany. The company intends a significant investment to boost jet engine development for India's AMCA program and enhance naval propulsion capabilities. Rolls-Royce will sign MoUs with Indian defence PSUs for tank and combat vehicle engines, aligning with India's push for indigenous defense manufacturing and advanced engineering.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 05:18:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6950bf5d4342f77179da647c_1766899646705.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rolls-Royce Eyes India as Third Global Hub: Massive Investment Planned for Jet Engines &amp; Naval Power!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Rolls-Royce-Eyes-India-as-Third-Global-Hub-Massive-Investment-Planned-for-Jet-Engines-and-Naval-Power/6950bf5b4342f77179da6450</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Rolls-Royce-Eyes-India-as-Third-Global-Hub-Massive-Investment-Planned-for-Jet-Engines-and-Naval-Power/6950bf5b4342f77179da6450</guid><description>British aero-engine maker Rolls-Royce is planning a major investment in India, aiming to make it its third 'home market' outside the UK, US, and Germany. The company seeks to unlock opportunities in jet engines, naval propulsion, and advanced engineering, prioritizing the development of next-generation aero engines for India's AMCA program and bolstering naval capabilities.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 05:17:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6950bf5b4342f77179da644f_1766899996849.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bollywood's Blockbuster Freeze: Is Star Power on Pause? Why New Film Projects Are Vanishing in 2025!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Bollywoods-Blockbuster-Freeze-Is-Star-Power-on-Pause-Why-New-Film-Projects-Are-Vanishing-in-2025/6950b84a4342f77179da6007</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Bollywoods-Blockbuster-Freeze-Is-Star-Power-on-Pause-Why-New-Film-Projects-Are-Vanishing-in-2025/6950b84a4342f77179da6007</guid><description>Bollywood is experiencing a major slowdown in new film projects for 2025, with popular actors like Aamir Khan and Alia Bhatt holding back on signing new deals. This caution stems from unpredictable box office revenues, decreased interest from OTT platforms, and the high cost of star fees. Industry experts note a significant drop in new announcements, impacting the volume of star-led Hindi films. While a few successes offer hope, the high risk of theatrical releases is forcing a 'no risk' policy, with a wait-and-watch approach until 2026 for potential market recovery.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 04:48:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6950b84a4342f77179da6006_1766897817153.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Retirement Revolution: 2025 Reforms Unlock Your Pension's Future!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Retirement-Revolution-2025-Reforms-Unlock-Your-Pensions-Future/6950b8384342f77179da5fdc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Retirement-Revolution-2025-Reforms-Unlock-Your-Pensions-Future/6950b8384342f77179da5fdc</guid><description>India's changing demographics necessitate a new approach to retirement planning, moving away from family reliance. Landmark reforms in 2025 have reshaped the National Pension System (NPS) and Employees' Provident Fund (EPF). NPS now offers increased equity options up to 100% and greater withdrawal flexibility, while EPF has tightened full withdrawal rules to ensure long-term corpus growth. These changes emphasize the need for intentional, structured retirement planning for millions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 04:48:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6950b8384342f77179da5fdb_1766897784914.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Border Clash Fallout: Indians Ditch Thailand, Cambodia for New Year Escapes!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Border-Clash-Fallout-Indians-Ditch-Thailand-Cambodia-for-New-Year-Escapes/6950b6f14342f77179da5ea0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Border-Clash-Fallout-Indians-Ditch-Thailand-Cambodia-for-New-Year-Escapes/6950b6f14342f77179da5ea0</guid><description>Indian travellers are rerouting New Year plans away from Thailand and Cambodia due to ongoing border violence. Travel executives report a 10-35% drop in enquiries and bookings for these popular destinations. Destinations like Vietnam, Sri Lanka, Japan, and parts of West Asia are gaining traction, with travellers prioritizing safety, visa ease, and value amid rising airfares.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 04:39:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6950b6f14342f77179da5e9f_1766897528058.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Chatbots Spark Alarming Psychosis Cases: Doctors Raise Urgent Mental Health Concerns!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Chatbots-Spark-Alarming-Psychosis-Cases-Doctors-Raise-Urgent-Mental-Health-Concerns/6950a91b4342f77179da5371</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Chatbots-Spark-Alarming-Psychosis-Cases-Doctors-Raise-Urgent-Mental-Health-Concerns/6950a91b4342f77179da5371</guid><description>Top psychiatrists are increasingly linking AI chatbot use, like OpenAI's ChatGPT, to psychosis cases. Experts have documented dozens of patients exhibiting delusions and severe mental distress after prolonged AI conversations. While companies like OpenAI are enhancing safety features, these incidents highlight potential risks of highly interactive AI, prompting concerns about societal impact and leading to wrongful death lawsuits.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 03:41:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6950a91b4342f77179da5370_1766894042917.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2026 में किस सेक्टर पर दांव? Devina Mehra ने बताई IT, Currency Risks की पूरी कहानी!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/2026-म-कस-सकटर-पर-दव-Devina-Mehra-न-बतई-IT-Currency-Risks-क-पर-कहन/6950a2444342f77179da4d7a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/2026-म-कस-सकटर-पर-दव-Devina-Mehra-न-बतई-IT-Currency-Risks-क-पर-कहन/6950a2444342f77179da4d7a</guid><description>First Global की Devina Mehra का 2026 के लिए बड़ा विश्लेषण: इंडेक्स टारगेट पर ध्यान देने के बजाय IT सर्विसेज जैसे सेक्टर्स पर फोकस करें। उन्होंने करेंसी उतार-चढ़ाव, GST और टैरिफ जैसे पॉलिसी जोखिमों को निवेश के लिए महत्वपूर्ण बताया है।</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 03:12:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6950a2444342f77179da4d79_1766892421851.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Budget 2026-27: Demand-Led Growth &amp; RBI Synergy to Power Economy - EY Forecasts!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-2026-27-Demand-Led-Growth-and-RBI-Synergy-to-Power-Economy-EY-Forecasts/69509a1e4342f77179da48a6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-2026-27-Demand-Led-Growth-and-RBI-Synergy-to-Power-Economy-EY-Forecasts/69509a1e4342f77179da48a6</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026-27 is poised to boost growth by fostering domestic demand through fiscal measures, aligning with the RBI's supportive monetary policy. EY's report forecasts sustained 6.5% growth, dependent on private investment and eased supply chains. The government aims to meet its 4.4% fiscal deficit target via expenditure cuts and non-tax revenue, despite potential tax collection challenges.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 02:38:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69509a1e4342f77179da48a5_1766890086068.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI BOOM SHAKEN? Michael Burry's Massive Bet Against Nvidia &amp; Palantir Sparks Bubble Fears!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-BOOM-SHAKEN-Michael-Burrys-Massive-Bet-Against-Nvidia-and-Palantir-Sparks-Bubble-Fears/6950996a4342f77179da47b8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-BOOM-SHAKEN-Michael-Burrys-Massive-Bet-Against-Nvidia-and-Palantir-Sparks-Bubble-Fears/6950996a4342f77179da47b8</guid><description>Investor Michael Burry, famous for his "Big Short" bet, is now targeting AI giants Nvidia and Palantir Technologies, warning of a market bubble. He has placed significant bets against these companies, drawing parallels to the dot-com era. While his timing is often debated, Burry's contrarian stance is capturing attention from investors anxious about the rapid rise of AI stocks and their valuation disconnect from reality.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 02:33:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6950996a4342f77179da47b7_1766889954576.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Electric Trucks Revolution: Battery Swapping Ignites India's Logistics Green Transformation!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Electric-Trucks-Revolution-Battery-Swapping-Ignites-Indias-Logistics-Green-Transformation/69508dd44342f77179da2a4e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Electric-Trucks-Revolution-Battery-Swapping-Ignites-Indias-Logistics-Green-Transformation/69508dd44342f77179da2a4e</guid><description>Battery swapping technology, previously for two-wheelers, is now being deployed for 55-tonne electric trucks in India by Blue Energy Motors and Montra Electric. This innovation aims to achieve price parity with diesel trucks by removing battery costs and drastically reducing charging times, promising to decarbonize India's massive freight sector and boost operational efficiency in logistics.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 01:45:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69508dd44342f77179da2a4d_1766887022622.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Beyond Buffett: Greg Abel's 5 Bold Moves to Shape Berkshire Hathaway's $334B Future!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Beyond-Buffett-Greg-Abels-5-Bold-Moves-to-Shape-Berkshire-Hathaways-334B-Future/69508d194342f77179da299f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Beyond-Buffett-Greg-Abels-5-Bold-Moves-to-Shape-Berkshire-Hathaways-334B-Future/69508d194342f77179da299f</guid><description>Warren Buffett is transitioning leadership at Berkshire Hathaway, with Greg Abel set to become CEO by year-end 2025. Abel, a trained accountant and former head of Berkshire Hathaway Energy, is expected to bring a more active management style and potentially shift investment focus toward technology and renewables, leveraging the company's record $334 billion cash pile. His tenure, beginning January 1, 2026, marks a new chapter focused on operational rigor and substance over showmanship, aiming to maintain the conglomerate's growth engine.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 01:41:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69508d194342f77179da299e_1766886752534.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Railways Unleashes Mega Safety Budget! ₹1.3 Lakh Crore Boost for 'Kavach' — Top Stocks to Watch Now!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indian-Railways-Unleashes-Mega-Safety-Budget-13-Lakh-Crore-Boost-for-Kavach-Top-Stocks-to-Watch-Now/6950870e4342f77179da25ed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indian-Railways-Unleashes-Mega-Safety-Budget-13-Lakh-Crore-Boost-for-Kavach-Top-Stocks-to-Watch-Now/6950870e4342f77179da25ed</guid><description>Indian Railways is planning a record rail safety budget exceeding ₹1.3 lakh crore for FY27, a significant increase aimed at enhancing safety and preventing accidents. This allocation, potentially half of the total railway capex, is expected to strongly benefit companies manufacturing the indigenous 'Kavach' train collision avoidance system. Key players like HBL Engineering, Kernex Microsystems, and Concord Control Systems are poised to be major beneficiaries.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 01:14:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6950870e4342f77179da25ec_1766885211311.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hidden Indian Gems: 2 Debt-Free Smallcaps Poised for 2026 Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hidden-Indian-Gems-2-Debt-Free-Smallcaps-Poised-for-2026-Growth/695086784342f77179da2525</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hidden-Indian-Gems-2-Debt-Free-Smallcaps-Poised-for-2026-Growth/695086784342f77179da2525</guid><description>Two smallcap companies, Jyoti Resins and Adhesives Ltd. and Garuda Construction and Engineering Ltd., are gaining investor attention for their robust financial health and growth potential. Both operate with virtually no debt, boasting high Return on Capital Employed (ROCE) significantly above industry medians. Jyoti Resins, known for its EURO 7000 adhesive brand, has seen over 800% stock growth since 2020. Garuda Construction, a civil engineering specialist, has demonstrated impressive EBITDA and profit growth. With ambitious expansion plans, these firms are recommended for investor watchlists targeting 2026.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 01:14:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695086784342f77179da2524_1766885134676.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Rally Cools! 3 Indian Micro-Cap Stocks Poised for Explosive 2026 Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Gold-Rally-Cools-3-Indian-Micro-Cap-Stocks-Poised-for-Explosive-2026-Growth/695086274342f77179da24bc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Gold-Rally-Cools-3-Indian-Micro-Cap-Stocks-Poised-for-Explosive-2026-Growth/695086274342f77179da24bc</guid><description>While gold and silver saw massive rallies in 2025, India's major stock indices like Nifty 50 and BSE Sensex delivered modest returns. Amidst this, three micro-cap stocks—Strides Pharma Science Ltd, Cemindia Projects Ltd, and Sandur Manganese and Iron Ores Ltd—have been identified using key technical indicators as potential outperformers for 2026. These selections, based on signals like RSI, MACD, and ADX, suggest significant long-term potential, especially after notable price breakouts and consolidation phases.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 01:14:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695086274342f77179da24bb_1766885006222.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Wines Conquer Global Markets: Fruit-Based Brews Spark Export Boom!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indian-Wines-Conquer-Global-Markets-Fruit-Based-Brews-Spark-Export-Boom/695079e74342f77179da1ff9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indian-Wines-Conquer-Global-Markets-Fruit-Based-Brews-Spark-Export-Boom/695079e74342f77179da1ff9</guid><description>India's non-grape wines, made from fruits like jamun, mango, and apple, are achieving significant export success, reaching markets like the US, UAE, and UK. Exports surged to a record $6.7 million in the first seven months of the fiscal year, more than doubling the previous year's performance. This growth is driven by companies like Sula Vineyards and newer players, as they focus on international markets due to tepid domestic sales.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 00:21:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695079e74342f77179da1ff8_1766881855363.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>