<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:45:25 +0000</pubDate><item><title>UltraTech Cement acquires 26% stake in green energy firm for ₹15.12 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/UltraTech-Cement-acquires-26percent-stake-in-green-energy-firm-for-1512-Cr/69a583293d2913aa7c229a4a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/UltraTech-Cement-acquires-26percent-stake-in-green-energy-firm-for-1512-Cr/69a583293d2913aa7c229a4a</guid><description>UltraTech Cement is acquiring a 26% equity stake in AMPIN C&amp;I Power Forty Four Private Limited for up to ₹15.12 crore. This strategic move secures green energy supply for its operations, aids in optimising energy costs, and ensures compliance with captive power consumption regulations. The target company operates a 45 MWp solar power project with battery storage.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:31:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a583293d2913aa7c229a49_1772454775900.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Defence &amp; Tech Stocks Shine Amid Market Gloom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Defence-and-Tech-Stocks-Shine-Amid-Market-Gloom/69a582a63d2913aa7c229987</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Defence-and-Tech-Stocks-Shine-Amid-Market-Gloom/69a582a63d2913aa7c229987</guid><description>Despite a broad market downturn on March 2, 2026, triggered by Middle East tensions and rising oil prices, Paras Defence and Space Technologies, Sterlite Technologies, and IdeaForge Technology exhibited strong price-volume breakouts. These companies demonstrated resilience, suggesting sector-specific strength or positive catalysts are overriding general market fear and volatility, evidenced by significant trading volumes accompanying price increases.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:29:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a582a63d2913aa7c229986_1772455261765.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ind-Swift Labs GBU Earns EcoVadis Silver Medal; Ranks Top 15% Globally</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Ind-Swift-Labs-GBU-Earns-EcoVadis-Silver-Medal-Ranks-Top-15percent-Globally/69a582183d2913aa7c2298a9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Ind-Swift-Labs-GBU-Earns-EcoVadis-Silver-Medal-Ranks-Top-15percent-Globally/69a582183d2913aa7c2298a9</guid><description>Ind-Swift Laboratories' Global Business Unit (GBU) has achieved the prestigious EcoVadis Silver Medal, positioning it among the top 15% of organisations assessed worldwide. This recognition highlights strong performance in sustainability, ethics, environment, labour, and procurement, enhancing its global standing and appeal to ESG-focused investors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:27:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a582183d2913aa7c2298a8_1772454739086.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hitkit Global: Shah Family Exits 11.09% Stake on March 2, 2026</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Hitkit-Global-Shah-Family-Exits-1109percent-Stake-on-March-2-2026/69a5812a3d2913aa7c229785</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Hitkit-Global-Shah-Family-Exits-1109percent-Stake-on-March-2-2026/69a5812a3d2913aa7c229785</guid><description>Prakash Shah and his associate, Mrs. Suman Prakash Shah, have divested their entire combined 11.09% stake in Hitkit Global Solutions Ltd. The substantial exit occurred on March 2, 2026, reducing their holding to zero from 59,75,490 shares. This move comes after a period where the same individuals had increased their stake, and amidst past regulatory scrutiny for the company.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:23:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a5812a3d2913aa7c229784_1772454961584.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lemon Tree Eyes Global Markets: Asset-Light Shift Fuels Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Lemon-Tree-Eyes-Global-Markets-Asset-Light-Shift-Fuels-Expansion/69a57fc13d2913aa7c22950d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Lemon-Tree-Eyes-Global-Markets-Asset-Light-Shift-Fuels-Expansion/69a57fc13d2913aa7c22950d</guid><description>Lemon Tree Hotels is accelerating its international expansion over the next three to five years, targeting destinations frequented by Indian travelers. This strategy is underpinned by a significant shift towards an asset-light operational model. The company aims to leverage the projected growth of India as a major global outbound tourism market, while also seeking to unlock value through a proposed split into two publicly traded entities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:17:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a57fc13d2913aa7c22950c_1772454781496.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shantai Industries: Open Offer for 25.60% Stake at ₹21 Per Share Launched</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Shantai-Industries-Open-Offer-for-2560percent-Stake-at-21-Per-Share-Launched/69a57fc03d2913aa7c2294f6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Shantai-Industries-Open-Offer-for-2560percent-Stake-at-21-Per-Share-Launched/69a57fc03d2913aa7c2294f6</guid><description>A group of five acquirers, led by Radhe Dhokla Private Limited, has launched an open offer to acquire up to 19,20,000 equity shares of Shantai Industries Limited, representing 25.60% of the voting capital. The offer price is ₹21 per share, valuing the transaction at ₹4.03 crore. This move follows the acquirers' acquisition of a 74.40% controlling stake from existing promoters, signalling a complete change in management and control.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:17:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a57fc03d2913aa7c2294f5_1772454541595.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shanti Educational Initiatives to Merge with Grew Energy, Diversify into Renewables</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Shanti-Educational-Initiatives-to-Merge-with-Grew-Energy-Diversify-into-Renewables/69a57ecf3d2913aa7c2293bb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Shanti-Educational-Initiatives-to-Merge-with-Grew-Energy-Diversify-into-Renewables/69a57ecf3d2913aa7c2293bb</guid><description>Shanti Educational Initiatives Limited has approved a significant scheme of arrangement to sell its education business via slump sale to a subsidiary and then amalgamate with Grew Energy Private Limited. This strategic move aims to diversify the company's operations into the high-growth renewable energy sector, mitigating business risks and enhancing financial stability. Shareholder participation in the consolidated entity's diversified operations is a key outcome, pending regulatory approvals.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:13:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a57ecf3d2913aa7c2293ba_1772454101581.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RailTel Board to Consider 2nd Interim Dividend for FY26 on March 9</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/RailTel-Board-to-Consider-2nd-Interim-Dividend-for-FY26-on-March-9/69a57d733d2913aa7c2291ea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/RailTel-Board-to-Consider-2nd-Interim-Dividend-for-FY26-on-March-9/69a57d733d2913aa7c2291ea</guid><description>RailTel Corporation's Board of Directors is set to convene on March 9, 2026, to deliberate on the declaration of a second interim dividend for the Financial Year 2025-26. The company, which has already closed its trading window since March 3, 2026, will also fix the record date for this potential payout. This move highlights the company's commitment to shareholder returns, aligning with its consistent dividend history.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:07:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a57d733d2913aa7c2291e9_1772453881685.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Infotech And Communications Ltd Q3 FY26 Revenue ₹196 Cr; Profit Surges 60% YoY</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infotech-And-Communications-Ltd-Q3-FY26-Revenue-196-Cr-Profit-Surges-60percent-YoY/69a57d6b3d2913aa7c2291c0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infotech-And-Communications-Ltd-Q3-FY26-Revenue-196-Cr-Profit-Surges-60percent-YoY/69a57d6b3d2913aa7c2291c0</guid><description>Infotech And Communications Ltd reported robust Q3 and 9M FY26 financial results, marked by a significant 46.06% year-on-year revenue jump to ₹196 crore in Q3. Profit after tax surged 60.64% YoY to ₹6.49 crore. The company attributes growth to new client acquisitions and strong order execution, while strategically pivoting towards a solution-driven model with expansion into new geographies.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:07:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a57d6b3d2913aa7c2291bf_1772454063465.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ansal Housing Defaults ₹49.64 Cr Principal; Total Debt ₹233 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Ansal-Housing-Defaults-4964-Cr-Principal-Total-Debt-233-Cr/69a57cef3d2913aa7c229120</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Ansal-Housing-Defaults-4964-Cr-Principal-Total-Debt-233-Cr/69a57cef3d2913aa7c229120</guid><description>Ansal Housing Limited has disclosed a default of ₹49.64 crore on the principal of a project funding loan from Suraksha Asset Reconstruction Private Limited. The company carries a total financial indebtedness of ₹233.12 crore, raising concerns about its debt servicing capabilities. This event highlights ongoing financial pressures faced by the developer.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:05:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a57cef3d2913aa7c22911f_1772453253736.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Deputy MD Nitin Chugh Departs; Contract Concludes on March 2, 2026</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Deputy-MD-Nitin-Chugh-Departs-Contract-Concludes-on-March-2-2026/69a57c8c3d2913aa7c229077</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Deputy-MD-Nitin-Chugh-Departs-Contract-Concludes-on-March-2-2026/69a57c8c3d2913aa7c229077</guid><description>State Bank of India (SBI) announced that Shri Nitin Chugh, Deputy Managing Director &amp; Head of Digital Banking and Transformation, has been relieved from his services on March 2, 2026. His departure marks the conclusion of his contractual period. Chugh played a key role in steering SBI's digital initiatives, including the YONO platform. The transition highlights the importance of leadership continuity in the bank's ongoing digital transformation efforts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 12:03:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a57c8c3d2913aa7c229076_1772453370120.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IVP Ltd. Q3 FY26 PAT Surges 145%; Revenue Grows 12%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/IVP-Ltd-Q3-FY26-PAT-Surges-145percent-Revenue-Grows-12percent/69a57bbc3d2913aa7c228ee8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/IVP-Ltd-Q3-FY26-PAT-Surges-145percent-Revenue-Grows-12percent/69a57bbc3d2913aa7c228ee8</guid><description>IVP Ltd. reported a robust Q3 FY26 with PAT soaring 145% YoY to ₹4.63 crore on 12% revenue growth. The company is optimistic about leveraging its product portfolio for market expansion, though global headwinds and industry challenges remain potential pressure points.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:59:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a57bbc3d2913aa7c228ee7_1772452860795.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RailTel Fined ₹10.8 Lakhs By NSE, BSE For Board Compliance Lapses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/RailTel-Fined-108-Lakhs-By-NSE-BSE-For-Board-Compliance-Lapses/69a57bb23d2913aa7c228ecd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/RailTel-Fined-108-Lakhs-By-NSE-BSE-For-Board-Compliance-Lapses/69a57bb23d2913aa7c228ecd</guid><description>RailTel Corporation of India has been levied a total penalty of ₹10.85 lakh by the NSE and BSE for non-compliance with SEBI's board composition norms for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company attributes the issue to the Government's control over director appointments via the Ministry of Railways, stating the fines have no financial or operational impact.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:59:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a57bb23d2913aa7c228ecc_1772452851227.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Capri Loans Partners PCAF for Climate Finance Transparency</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Capri-Loans-Partners-PCAF-for-Climate-Finance-Transparency/69a57b173d2913aa7c228e2a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Capri-Loans-Partners-PCAF-for-Climate-Finance-Transparency/69a57b173d2913aa7c228e2a</guid><description>Capri Loans has joined the global Partnership for Carbon Accounting Financials (PCAF), a move signaling its commitment to climate transparency and sustainable finance. The NBFC will adopt PCAF's methodology to measure and disclose financed emissions across its extensive lending portfolio, aiming to integrate climate risk assessment into its decision-making processes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:57:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a57b173d2913aa7c228e29_1772452967092.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shanti Edu Initiatives board okays biz restructuring, diversifies into energy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Shanti-Edu-Initiatives-board-okays-biz-restructuring-diversifies-into-energy/69a579503d2913aa7c228c11</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Shanti-Edu-Initiatives-board-okays-biz-restructuring-diversifies-into-energy/69a579503d2913aa7c228c11</guid><description>Shanti Educational Initiatives Limited announced a Composite Scheme of Arrangement, involving the slump sale of its education business to a subsidiary and amalgamation with renewable energy firm Grew Energy Private Limited. This strategic move aims to create a diversified business structure combining education and green energy sectors, subject to necessary regulatory and shareholder approvals.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:49:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a579503d2913aa7c228c10_1772452293212.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Bets Big on Green Steel &amp; Hydrogen Future</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Bets-Big-on-Green-Steel-and-Hydrogen-Future/69a578da3d2913aa7c228b50</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Bets-Big-on-Green-Steel-and-Hydrogen-Future/69a578da3d2913aa7c228b50</guid><description>Tata Steel announced a substantial ₹11,000 crore investment in Jharkhand for advanced green steel technology, aiming to pioneer low-carbon production methods with potential industry-wide benefits. Concurrently, Tata Motors plans investments in hydrogen trucks at its Jamshedpur facility, signaling a broader strategic push into future mobility solutions. These moves align with global decarbonization trends and the evolving automotive and steel sectors, though execution and market adoption remain critical factors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:47:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a578da3d2913aa7c228b4f_1772452190536.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Exports Show Strategic Resilience Amid Global Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Exports-Show-Strategic-Resilience-Amid-Global-Headwinds/69a578793d2913aa7c228a5c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Exports-Show-Strategic-Resilience-Amid-Global-Headwinds/69a578793d2913aa7c228a5c</guid><description>India's export engine surged to $720.76 billion (April-Jan 2025-26), a 6.15% increase, primarily powered by services (+10.57%) and diversified merchandise sectors. This resilience, crucial against global trade uncertainties and US tariffs, is attributed to strategic market diversification, new trade agreements, and a focus on higher-value manufacturing. Despite a widening merchandise deficit, services surplus and strong economic forecasts underpin a robust external sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:46:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a578793d2913aa7c228a5b_1772452393774.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian EV Market: Mid-Premium SUVs Drive Growth, Mass Segment Lags</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indian-EV-Market-Mid-Premium-SUVs-Drive-Growth-Mass-Segment-Lags/69a578693d2913aa7c2289df</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indian-EV-Market-Mid-Premium-SUVs-Drive-Growth-Mass-Segment-Lags/69a578693d2913aa7c2289df</guid><description>Electric four-wheeler (e4w) registrations in India jumped 50% year-over-year in February 2026, reaching 13,185 units, driven by new model introductions and broader OEM participation. However, growth is concentrated in the mid-premium SUV segment, leaving the mass market constrained by affordability. Tata Motors maintained its leadership with robust growth, while JSW MG saw a significant market share decline. VinFast and Hyundai secured fourth and fifth positions, respectively, with new entrants like Maruti Suzuki rapidly gaining ground.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:45:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a578693d2913aa7c2289de_1772452034737.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Raajmarg InvIT Upsizes IPO to ₹6000 Cr Amidst Infrastructure Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Raajmarg-InvIT-Upsizes-IPO-to-6000-Cr-Amidst-Infrastructure-Boom/69a5785d3d2913aa7c22898f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Raajmarg-InvIT-Upsizes-IPO-to-6000-Cr-Amidst-Infrastructure-Boom/69a5785d3d2913aa7c22898f</guid><description>The Raajmarg Infra Investment Trust (RIIT) has increased its initial public offering size to ₹6,000 crore from ₹5,700 crore, with the public issue opening on March 11 and closing on March 13. This upsized offering, managed by NHAI, reflects robust investor interest in India's highway development and aims to attract retail participation in national infrastructure assets. The trust will invest in five operational toll road assets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:45:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a5785d3d2913aa7c22898e_1772452042610.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SITI Networks Discloses ₹1,206 Cr Default Amid Ongoing Insolvency</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/SITI-Networks-Discloses-1206-Cr-Default-Amid-Ongoing-Insolvency/69a577c73d2913aa7c2288d5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/SITI-Networks-Discloses-1206-Cr-Default-Amid-Ongoing-Insolvency/69a577c73d2913aa7c2288d5</guid><description>SITI Networks Limited has formally disclosed a significant default on interest and principal payments for loans totalling ₹1,206.03 crore. This disclosure comes as the company continues its Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP), initiated in February 2023. The ongoing legal proceedings and financial distress highlight a critical situation for the media distribution company.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:43:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a577c73d2913aa7c2288d4_1772451936838.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>DCM Shriram Fine Chemicals Posts ₹1.62 Cr Net Loss Post-Listing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/DCM-Shriram-Fine-Chemicals-Posts-162-Cr-Net-Loss-Post-Listing/69a577523d2913aa7c228841</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/DCM-Shriram-Fine-Chemicals-Posts-162-Cr-Net-Loss-Post-Listing/69a577523d2913aa7c228841</guid><description>DCM Shriram Fine Chemicals has reported its first unaudited financial results post-listing for Q3 FY26, revealing a standalone net loss of ₹1.62 crore. This follows a Composite Scheme of Arrangement effective December 17, 2025, which led to the restatement of prior periods. While the nine-month period (9M FY26) registered a slim standalone profit of ₹0.21 crore, the quarterly loss highlights the immediate financial implications of the significant corporate restructuring.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:41:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a577523d2913aa7c228840_1772452053688.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zinema Media to Raise ₹19.3Cr via Preferential Issue, Acquires 60% in Beontyme Tech</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Zinema-Media-to-Raise-193Cr-via-Preferential-Issue-Acquires-60percent-in-Beontyme-Tech/69a570ed3d2913aa7c22834f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Zinema-Media-to-Raise-193Cr-via-Preferential-Issue-Acquires-60percent-in-Beontyme-Tech/69a570ed3d2913aa7c22834f</guid><description>Zinema Media &amp; Entertainment Limited announced its board's approval for a preferential issuance of 1.93 crore equity shares to raise ₹19.30 crore. Concurrently, the company plans to acquire up to a 60% stake in Beontyme Technologies Private Limited for ₹63 crore via a share swap. Both proposals are subject to shareholder and regulatory approvals, with an Extraordinary General Meeting (EGM) scheduled for March 28, 2026.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:13:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a570ed3d2913aa7c22834e_1772450091128.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Factory Output Slows Sharply: Demand Weakness Lingers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Factory-Output-Slows-Sharply-Demand-Weakness-Lingers/69a5705c3d2913aa7c22820a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Factory-Output-Slows-Sharply-Demand-Weakness-Lingers/69a5705c3d2913aa7c22820a</guid><description>India's industrial production growth decelerated to 4.8% in January 2026, a stark drop from December's 7.8%. This slowdown was predominantly driven by the manufacturing sector, which grew by only 4.8%, alongside a dip in mining output. Crucially, consumer non-durables contracted, indicating a broad-based demand weakening that contrasts with earlier optimistic sector forecasts and existing valuation multiples.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:11:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a5705c3d2913aa7c228209_1772450021729.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SJ Corp EOGM Approves Preferential Issue, Fishfa Rubbers Acquisition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SJ-Corp-EOGM-Approves-Preferential-Issue-Fishfa-Rubbers-Acquisition/69a5704d3d2913aa7c2281e2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SJ-Corp-EOGM-Approves-Preferential-Issue-Fishfa-Rubbers-Acquisition/69a5704d3d2913aa7c2281e2</guid><description>SJ Corporation Ltd. shareholders overwhelmingly approved key resolutions at an EOGM on March 2, 2026. The decisions pave the way for a preferential equity share issue and the acquisition of Fishfa Rubbers Limited, signaling a strategic diversification. Two directors were also regularized. This move marks a significant transformation for the company, moving beyond its traditional jewelry and real estate businesses.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:11:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a5704d3d2913aa7c2281e1_1772449992433.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ABDL Invests ₹45 Cr in Kion for 200 KLPD Distillery Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ABDL-Invests-45-Cr-in-Kion-for-200-KLPD-Distillery-Expansion/69a570483d2913aa7c2281cc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ABDL-Invests-45-Cr-in-Kion-for-200-KLPD-Distillery-Expansion/69a570483d2913aa7c2281cc</guid><description>Allied Blenders and Distillers (ABDL) announced plans to acquire up to a 50% stake in Kion Blenders Industries (KION) for up to ₹45 crore. This strategic move aims to establish a new 200 KLPD distillery in Andhra Pradesh as part of a ₹300 crore project, significantly enhancing ABDL's distillation capacity and supply chain security for its alcohol-based products. KION will become a subsidiary upon completion of the acquisition, expected by June 2026.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:11:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a570483d2913aa7c2281cb_1772449981041.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lotus Eye Hospital: Promoter Stake Jumps to 35.01% in ₹100 Cr Buy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lotus-Eye-Hospital-Promoter-Stake-Jumps-to-3501percent-in-100-Cr-Buy/69a56ef03d2913aa7c22802f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lotus-Eye-Hospital-Promoter-Stake-Jumps-to-3501percent-in-100-Cr-Buy/69a56ef03d2913aa7c22802f</guid><description>Lotus Eye Hospital and Institute Limited has seen a significant promoter stake reshuffle. Sangeetha Sundaramoorthy has acquired shares worth ₹100 crore, increasing her holding to 35.01% from 28.14%. This consolidation of promoter ownership could signal strengthened strategic direction and confidence from key stakeholders.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:05:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a56ef03d2913aa7c22802e_1772450521977.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IRFC Stock Tumbles as Muted OFS Highlights Regulatory Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IRFC-Stock-Tumbles-as-Muted-OFS-Highlights-Regulatory-Hurdles/69a56e6c3d2913aa7c227f5d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IRFC-Stock-Tumbles-as-Muted-OFS-Highlights-Regulatory-Hurdles/69a56e6c3d2913aa7c227f5d</guid><description>Indian Railway Finance Corporation (IRFC) Ltd. shares experienced a significant decline, dropping nearly 4% on Monday, March 2, 2026, to Rs 98.74. This slump follows the conclusion of the government's Offer for Sale (OFS), which saw muted investor participation and failed to meet its intended stake sale target. The divestment, aimed at complying with Minimum Public Shareholding (MPS) rules, managed to sell only 1.71% of the company's equity, leaving IRFC with a substantial deficit to meet regulatory requirements. The weak demand for the OFS signals potential valuation concerns and adds to the stock's ongoing pressure, despite the railway sector's robust long-term growth narrative.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:03:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a56e6c3d2913aa7c227f5c_1772449576162.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Home First Finance: Fidelity International raises stake to 9.50% in open market buys</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Home-First-Finance-Fidelity-International-raises-stake-to-950percent-in-open-market-buys/69a56e683d2913aa7c227f46</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Home-First-Finance-Fidelity-International-raises-stake-to-950percent-in-open-market-buys/69a56e683d2913aa7c227f46</guid><description>Fidelity International, through its entities FMR LLC and FIL, has significantly boosted its stake in Home First Finance Company India Limited. The asset manager acquired over 2.49 million shares in open market transactions between August 2025 and February 2026. This move increases Fidelity's total holding to 9.50%, up from 7.17%, signaling growing investor confidence in the housing finance company.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:03:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a56e683d2913aa7c227f45_1772449495675.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rose Merc Ltd Shareholders Approve Capital Hike, New Business Ventures</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Rose-Merc-Ltd-Shareholders-Approve-Capital-Hike-New-Business-Ventures/69a56e113d2913aa7c227e70</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Rose-Merc-Ltd-Shareholders-Approve-Capital-Hike-New-Business-Ventures/69a56e113d2913aa7c227e70</guid><description>Rose Merc Limited shareholders have greenlit a significant business overhaul, approving a ₹5 Crore increase in authorised share capital to ₹25 Crore. The company will now venture into trading precious stones and jewellery, alongside real estate acquisition and development. Key management changes, including the regularization of an Executive Director and designation updates, were also ratified.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 11:01:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a56e113d2913aa7c227e6f_1772449648432.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IPO Debut Disaster: Clean Max, Shree Ram Twistex Crash Amid Market Selloff</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/IPO-Debut-Disaster-Clean-Max-Shree-Ram-Twistex-Crash-Amid-Market-Selloff/69a56da33d2913aa7c227db2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/IPO-Debut-Disaster-Clean-Max-Shree-Ram-Twistex-Crash-Amid-Market-Selloff/69a56da33d2913aa7c227db2</guid><description>Brookfield-backed Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions and cotton yarn manufacturer Shree Ram Twistex experienced catastrophic trading debuts on Monday, March 2, 2026. Clean Max closed 18.5% down, valuing the firm at ₹10,045 crore, while Shree Ram Twistex plunged 31.4% below its issue price. The dismal listings underscore a turbulent 2026 for primary markets, driven by global equity sell-offs and heightened investor caution towards IPO valuations, particularly for companies with high leverage or facing sector-specific headwinds.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 10:59:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a56da33d2913aa7c227db1_1772449296141.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Eyes Chinese FDI for Manufacturing Boost Amid Security Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Eyes-Chinese-FDI-for-Manufacturing-Boost-Amid-Security-Hurdles/69a56c8c3d2913aa7c227c52</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Eyes-Chinese-FDI-for-Manufacturing-Boost-Amid-Security-Hurdles/69a56c8c3d2913aa7c227c52</guid><description>Amidst a diplomatic thaw, India is reviewing Press Note 3 (2020) to potentially relax foreign direct investment rules for Chinese entities. The proposed 'de-minimis' threshold aims to streamline approvals for non-sensitive sectors, bolstering manufacturing in areas like electronics and auto components. This strategic recalibration seeks to leverage the 'China Plus One' trend and narrow India's substantial trade deficit with China, but faces significant hurdles due to national security concerns and past investment caution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 10:55:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a56c8c3d2913aa7c227c51_1772449320779.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nissan India's Feb Sales Surge Driven by Exports, Domestic Demand Trails</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Nissan-Indias-Feb-Sales-Surge-Driven-by-Exports-Domestic-Demand-Trails/69a56b993d2913aa7c227ae1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Nissan-Indias-Feb-Sales-Surge-Driven-by-Exports-Domestic-Demand-Trails/69a56b993d2913aa7c227ae1</guid><description>Nissan Motor India reported a 23% year-on-year sales increase in February, reaching 10,565 units. This growth was primarily fueled by a substantial surge in exports, which accounted for 8,335 units, significantly overshadowing domestic wholesale volumes of 2,230 units. Nissan India MD Saurabh Vatsa highlighted the consolidated performance, emphasizing stable underlying demand and continued strength in exports, underscoring India's strategic importance for the company's global operations. This export-led expansion contrasts with the performance of major domestic players who saw stronger growth in their home markets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 10:51:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a56b993d2913aa7c227ae0_1772448781223.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IIFL Finance Eyes $750M Social Bonds Amidst Funding Diversification</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IIFL-Finance-Eyes-750M-Social-Bonds-Amidst-Funding-Diversification/69a56aba3d2913aa7c227a31</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IIFL-Finance-Eyes-750M-Social-Bonds-Amidst-Funding-Diversification/69a56aba3d2913aa7c227a31</guid><description>IIFL Finance is preparing to raise as much as $750 million through its inaugural dollar-denominated social bonds and an overseas loan in March 2026. This strategic move aims to broaden its funding mix, with proceeds earmarked for social initiatives including loans to women entrepreneurs. The company's Assets Under Management (AUM) have seen substantial growth, reaching ₹490.27 billion by December 31, 2025, predominantly from gold loans. This fundraising effort aligns with India's growing focus on sustainable finance and SEBI's new framework for ESG debt securities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 10:47:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a56aba3d2913aa7c227a30_1772448867814.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AVI Products India Open Offer: PPMS Real Estates Buys 26% at ₹33</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/AVI-Products-India-Open-Offer-PPMS-Real-Estates-Buys-26percent-at-33/69a56a2f3d2913aa7c22794c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/AVI-Products-India-Open-Offer-PPMS-Real-Estates-Buys-26percent-at-33/69a56a2f3d2913aa7c22794c</guid><description>PPMS Real Estates LLP has initiated an open offer to acquire up to 26.00% of AVI Products India Limited's equity at ₹33 per share, requiring ₹2.84 crore in total funding. This strategic move by PPMS signals an intent to secure substantial shareholding and potentially take control of AVI Products India, with future diversification into real estate being a consideration. The offer period is set to run from April 16 to April 29, 2026.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 10:45:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a56a2f3d2913aa7c22794b_1772448418480.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Ports Feb cargo jumps 16% YoY; YTD volumes up 11%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Adani-Ports-Feb-cargo-jumps-16percent-YoY-YTD-volumes-up-11percent/69a569463d2913aa7c227891</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Adani-Ports-Feb-cargo-jumps-16percent-YoY-YTD-volumes-up-11percent/69a569463d2913aa7c227891</guid><description>Adani Ports and Special Economic Zone Limited (APSEZ) reported robust operational performance for February 2026, handling 42.5 million metric tonnes (MMT) of cargo, a significant 16% year-on-year increase. Year-to-date (YTD) cargo volumes reached 454.7 MMT, showing an 11% YoY growth. The company also saw its logistics rail volume increase by 10% YTD, underscoring strong operational execution and integrated logistics capabilities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 10:41:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a569463d2913aa7c227890_1772448414193.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>M&amp;M Sheds Loss-Maker, Boosts Focus on Core Growth Segments</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/MandM-Sheds-Loss-Maker-Boosts-Focus-on-Core-Growth-Segments/69a567763d2913aa7c2276e3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/MandM-Sheds-Loss-Maker-Boosts-Focus-on-Core-Growth-Segments/69a567763d2913aa7c2276e3</guid><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra's Japan-based associate, Mitsubishi Mahindra Agricultural Machinery (MAM), will cease its agricultural machinery operations by H1 FY2027 due to sustained losses. This strategic withdrawal is expected to eliminate recurring annual deficits, allowing M&amp;M to sharpen its focus on its high-performing automotive and farm equipment businesses. While MAM will maintain spare parts and warranty services, its core operations, which contributed a minor 1.13% to M&amp;M's consolidated turnover in FY25 despite a Rs 227.42 crore loss, will wind down. This move aligns with M&amp;M's strategy to enhance financial discipline and capital allocation efficiency across its diversified portfolio.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 10:33:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a567763d2913aa7c2276e2_1772447760799.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sterlite Tech Surges to 2-Year High Amidst Margin Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Sterlite-Tech-Surges-to-2-Year-High-Amidst-Margin-Woes/69a566e73d2913aa7c227608</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Sterlite-Tech-Surges-to-2-Year-High-Amidst-Margin-Woes/69a566e73d2913aa7c227608</guid><description>Sterlite Technologies shares surged Monday, reaching a two-year peak of ₹172.65 and defying a broader market downturn. This rally follows a 100% increase in five weeks. While revenue recovered to ₹1,174 crore in Q3FY26 and the order book remains robust at ₹5,325 crore, the company's EBITDA margin compressed to 11.2% due to tariff headwinds. Sterlite's P/E ratio remains volatile, often negative, a stark contrast to some peers, raising valuation questions despite future growth prospects.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 10:31:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a566e73d2913aa7c227607_1772447618825.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Groww Pivots to WealthTech: Valuation Concerns Amidst Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Groww-Pivots-to-WealthTech-Valuation-Concerns-Amidst-Expansion/69a566783d2913aa7c227514</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Groww-Pivots-to-WealthTech-Valuation-Concerns-Amidst-Expansion/69a566783d2913aa7c227514</guid><description>Investment platform Groww is aggressively expanding its offerings beyond core broking, launching new wealth management platforms (Prime and W) and AI-driven advisory services. While this pivot aims to capture new growth avenues, a recent UBS initiation with a 'Neutral' rating highlights concerns that Groww's current valuation of 37 times one-year forward earnings may already price in these positives. The company faces a highly competitive landscape and the inherent challenges of transitioning to higher-margin, service-intensive financial products.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 10:29:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a566783d2913aa7c227513_1772447469382.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MAS Financial Secures RBI Factoring License; Eyes New Business Vertical</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/MAS-Financial-Secures-RBI-Factoring-License-Eyes-New-Business-Vertical/69a566713d2913aa7c2274fa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/MAS-Financial-Secures-RBI-Factoring-License-Eyes-New-Business-Vertical/69a566713d2913aa7c2274fa</guid><description>MAS Financial Services Limited has received a Certificate of Registration from the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) to commence factoring operations. This approval marks a significant strategic expansion into a new financial service vertical. The company plans to launch this business line in due course, dependent on market conditions and suitable opportunities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 10:29:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a566713d2913aa7c2274f9_1772447726040.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hormuz Tensions Threaten India's Fertilizer Supply, Stocks Under Pressure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Hormuz-Tensions-Threaten-Indias-Fertilizer-Supply-Stocks-Under-Pressure/69a566703d2913aa7c2274e4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Hormuz-Tensions-Threaten-Indias-Fertilizer-Supply-Stocks-Under-Pressure/69a566703d2913aa7c2274e4</guid><description>Escalating tensions around the Strait of Hormuz pose a significant threat to India's fertilizer imports, essential for the upcoming Kharif season. Approximately one-third of global fertilizer trade, including key components like urea and DAP, transits this vital chokepoint. This vulnerability exacerbates India's already high import dependence and strains government subsidy budgets. Major players Coromandel International, Deepak Fertilisers, and Deepak Nitrite face market scrutiny as supply chain disruptions could drive up costs and impact domestic agricultural output.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 10:29:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a566703d2913aa7c2274e3_1772447486867.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>