<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 18:28:46 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Pace Digitek Secures Rs 31,287 Mn Orders, Eyes Global Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Pace-Digitek-Secures-Rs-31287-Mn-Orders-Eyes-Global-Expansion/698780fcb81b2b81dcfcd5dc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Pace-Digitek-Secures-Rs-31287-Mn-Orders-Eyes-Global-Expansion/698780fcb81b2b81dcfcd5dc</guid><description>Pace Digitek reported robust Q3 FY2026 results, with consolidated revenue up 13.5% YoY to ₹6,440 Mn and PAT growing 11.3% YoY to ₹788 Mn. Despite a dip in consolidated margins, strong standalone performance, a record order book of ₹84,678 Mn, and aggressive expansion plans in BESS and international markets signal significant future growth potential.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 18:14:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698780fcb81b2b81dcfcd5db_1770488357465.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Forbes Founder Arrested in Rs 500 Cr Gurugram Property Scam</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Forbes-Founder-Arrested-in-Rs-500-Cr-Gurugram-Property-Scam/69878090b81b2b81dcfcd4c8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Forbes-Founder-Arrested-in-Rs-500-Cr-Gurugram-Property-Scam/69878090b81b2b81dcfcd4c8</guid><description>Gurugram police arrested Dhruv Dutt Sharma, founder of 32nd Avenue, for a massive property scam. Sharma allegedly sold a single commercial property floor multiple times to over 25 buyers between 2021 and 2023, defrauding them of approximately Rs 500 crore. Trom Ventures Private Limited filed the initial complaint after its payment for a Rs 2.5 crore unit went unregistered. Sharma admitted to the sales during initial questioning.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 18:12:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69878090b81b2b81dcfcd4c7_1770488136864.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jinkushal Industries Posts 27% YoY Revenue Growth, Eyes Margin Boost Via Inventory Build-up</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jinkushal-Industries-Posts-27percent-YoY-Revenue-Growth-Eyes-Margin-Boost-Via-Inventory-Build-up/6987807cb81b2b81dcfcd3ac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jinkushal-Industries-Posts-27percent-YoY-Revenue-Growth-Eyes-Margin-Boost-Via-Inventory-Build-up/6987807cb81b2b81dcfcd3ac</guid><description>Jinkushal Industries reported a strong Q3 FY26 with standalone turnover up 27% YoY to ₹180.32 crore, driven by exports. The company is building a record ₹70 crore inventory overseas to improve delivery and margins. Despite temporary demand dips in Mexico, strategic market diversification and IPO fund deployment signal long-term growth focus.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 18:12:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6987807cb81b2b81dcfcd3ab_1770488028094.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal: MedTech Gains Tariff Relief, Pharma Faces Probe</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-US-Trade-Deal-MedTech-Gains-Tariff-Relief-Pharma-Faces-Probe/69877f1cb81b2b81dcfcd22d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-US-Trade-Deal-MedTech-Gains-Tariff-Relief-Pharma-Faces-Probe/69877f1cb81b2b81dcfcd22d</guid><description>An interim trade agreement between India and the United States offers a significant boost to India's medical technology (MedTech) sector, with Poly Medicure Ltd. poised to benefit from reduced US import tariffs. While pharmaceutical exports, particularly generics, also see provisional tariff exemptions, their final status hinges on an ongoing US national security investigation (Section 232). The pact aims to bolster bilateral trade and cooperation but introduces a layer of regulatory uncertainty for the pharmaceutical segment.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 18:06:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69877f1cb81b2b81dcfcd22c_1770487671978.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Advance Agrolife Pivots to Manufacturing, Revenue Surges 25%, Margins Eye Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Advance-Agrolife-Pivots-to-Manufacturing-Revenue-Surges-25percent-Margins-Eye-Gains/69877dacb81b2b81dcfcd09b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Advance-Agrolife-Pivots-to-Manufacturing-Revenue-Surges-25percent-Margins-Eye-Gains/69877dacb81b2b81dcfcd09b</guid><description>Advance Agrolife Limited posted robust financial results for Q3 and nine months ended December 31, 2025. Total income jumped 18% YoY in Q3 FY26 to ₹1338.0 million and 25% YoY for 9MFY26 to ₹5153.9 million. EBITDA grew 16% YoY in Q3 and 20% YoY in 9MFY26. Profit After Tax (PAT) saw an 8% YoY rise in Q3 and 15% YoY in 9MFY26. The company is undertaking a strategic pivot towards backward integration and technical manufacturing, aiming to reduce costs and capture full margins. Significant capacity expansions and a strong push into export markets are key future drivers, supported by recent government duties on imports.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 18:00:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69877dacb81b2b81dcfcd09a_1770487300313.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's New Tax Rules: Simplification or Digital Strain?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-New-Tax-Rules-Simplification-or-Digital-Strain/69877bc9b81b2b81dcfccf07</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-New-Tax-Rules-Simplification-or-Digital-Strain/69877bc9b81b2b81dcfccf07</guid><description>India's Central Board of Direct Taxes has released draft Income-tax Rules, 2026, proposing a significant reduction in rules and forms under the new Income-tax Act, 2025, effective April 1, 2026. These changes emphasize technology-driven 'smart forms' and simplified language to reduce taxpayer burden and ambiguity. Public feedback is open until February 22, 2026, a critical period for shaping the practical application of this tax overhaul.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:52:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69877bc9b81b2b81dcfccf06_1770486852184.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Fortifies 'Chicken's Neck' with Underground Rail Project</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/India-Fortifies-Chickens-Neck-with-Underground-Rail-Project/69877a64b81b2b81dcfccda6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/India-Fortifies-Chickens-Neck-with-Underground-Rail-Project/69877a64b81b2b81dcfccda6</guid><description>Indian Railways is undertaking a significant infrastructure project, constructing a 35.76 km underground railway line through the strategically vital Siliguri Corridor, often termed the "Chicken's Neck." This initiative aims to bolster secure and uninterrupted connectivity to India's northeastern states, utilizing modern engineering and technology to enhance resilience against natural disasters and security threats. The project underscores a broader national strategy to strengthen regional infrastructure, aligning with substantial capital allocations towards railway development in the 2026-27 Union Budget. Beyond its immediate security implications, the project signals a push towards enhanced logistics efficiency and regional economic integration, potentially stimulating ancillary industries and investments in the sector.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:46:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69877a64b81b2b81dcfccda5_1770486464836.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI GPU Surge: NVIDIA Dominance &amp; Geopolitical Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-GPU-Surge-NVIDIA-Dominance-and-Geopolitical-Risks/69877272b81b2b81dcfccb25</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-GPU-Surge-NVIDIA-Dominance-and-Geopolitical-Risks/69877272b81b2b81dcfccb25</guid><description>India is poised to quintuple its installed graphics processing unit (GPU) capacity from 38,000 to 100,000 by the end of 2026, a significant expansion driven by the IndiaAI Mission. While this initiative aims to bolster domestic AI capabilities and sovereign compute, it directly intensifies demand for global chip manufacturers, most notably NVIDIA. This surge occurs amidst a rapidly growing global AI chip market projected to reach over $975 billion in 2026, with NVIDIA commanding substantial market share. However, the strategy exposes India to geopolitical dependencies and highlights value concentration with hardware providers, while Indian IT firms face potential headwinds from regulatory shifts and visa restrictions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:12:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69877272b81b2b81dcfccb24.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>R R Kabel Surges with Record Q3 Results, Wires &amp; Cables Drive Stellar Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/R-R-Kabel-Surges-with-Record-Q3-Results-Wires-and-Cables-Drive-Stellar-Growth/6987717bb81b2b81dcfcc9f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/R-R-Kabel-Surges-with-Record-Q3-Results-Wires-and-Cables-Drive-Stellar-Growth/6987717bb81b2b81dcfcc9f0</guid><description>R R Kabel Limited has reported its strongest-ever 9-month performance, culminating in a record Q3 FY26. Revenue surged 42.3% year-on-year to INR 2,536 crore, fueled by exceptional growth in the Wires &amp; Cables segment, which saw a 48.6% YoY increase. EBITDA jumped 86% YoY to INR 206 crore, and Profit After Tax (PAT) soared 72.4% YoY to INR 118 crore. The company is aggressively curtailing losses in its FMEG segment, targeting EBIT breakeven by Q4 FY26. Management expressed cautious optimism for the medium term, citing strong Indian demand driven by infrastructure and housing, and is investing INR 1,200 crore in capacity expansion, primarily for cables.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 17:08:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6987717bb81b2b81dcfcc9ef_1770484197403.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Budget 2026-27 Eyes Electronics Boom With Tax Gambit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Budget-2026-27-Eyes-Electronics-Boom-With-Tax-Gambit/69876897b81b2b81dcfcc6df</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Budget-2026-27-Eyes-Electronics-Boom-With-Tax-Gambit/69876897b81b2b81dcfcc6df</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026-27 aims to supercharge its electronics manufacturing sector by introducing a "safe harbour" regime for component warehousing. This policy proposes an effective tax rate of approximately 0.7%, a significant reduction expected to lure multinational corporations. By offering predictable low taxation and diminished regulatory friction, the initiative seeks to enhance India's appeal as a global manufacturing hub, positioning it more favourably against established competitors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:30:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69876897b81b2b81dcfcc6de_1770482077170.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Oswal Pumps Q3 Revenue Jumps 31.9% on PM KUSUM, Debt Slashed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Oswal-Pumps-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-319percent-on-PM-KUSUM-Debt-Slashed/69876835b81b2b81dcfcc58c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Oswal-Pumps-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-319percent-on-PM-KUSUM-Debt-Slashed/69876835b81b2b81dcfcc58c</guid><description>Oswal Pumps delivered a robust Q3 FY26, with operating income up 31.9% YoY to ₹5,011 million, driven by PM KUSUM scheme execution. Nine-month revenue surged 45.9% YoY. The company achieved sequential EBITDA margin improvement to 25.4% despite competitive pricing, and PAT grew 13.9% YoY. Net debt saw significant reduction, though the cash conversion cycle lengthened to 177 days due to payment delays. Management expects normalization and plans substantial capacity expansion.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:28:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69876835b81b2b81dcfcc58b_1770481914373.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UGRO Capital: AUM Surges 40%, PAT Up 23% Amid Rising Leverage</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/UGRO-Capital-AUM-Surges-40percent-PAT-Up-23percent-Amid-Rising-Leverage/6987681cb81b2b81dcfcc47c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/UGRO-Capital-AUM-Surges-40percent-PAT-Up-23percent-Amid-Rising-Leverage/6987681cb81b2b81dcfcc47c</guid><description>UGRO Capital reported robust Q3 FY26 results with Assets Under Management (AUM) soaring 40% YoY to ₹15,454 Cr and Profit After Tax (PAT) up 23% to ₹46.3 Cr. However, the company's leverage increased to 3.8x, and key profitability metrics like ROA and ROE saw a year-on-year decline. UGRO Capital also launched an Environmental &amp; Social Management System (ESMS) to bolster ESG compliance.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:28:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6987681cb81b2b81dcfcc47b_1770481794303.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Oswal Pumps Surges on Revenue Growth, But Margins Take a Hit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Oswal-Pumps-Surges-on-Revenue-Growth-But-Margins-Take-a-Hit/6987663ab81b2b81dcfcc12c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Oswal-Pumps-Surges-on-Revenue-Growth-But-Margins-Take-a-Hit/6987663ab81b2b81dcfcc12c</guid><description>Oswal Pumps Limited reported a stellar 33.4% year-on-year revenue growth in Q3 FY26, reaching ₹5,077 million, driven by government solar schemes like PM KUSUM. However, profitability faced pressure, with EBITDA margins shrinking to 26.3% from 31.3% YoY, and PAT margins declining to 18.0% from 21.1%. Management cited competitive tender pricing as a cause but expressed confidence in value-engineering initiatives to bolster margins sequentially and in the medium term. The company boasts a strong order book exceeding 24,500 pumps, with a near-term pipeline of over 25,000 units, positioning it to capitalize on sustained government focus on renewable irrigation solutions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:20:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6987663ab81b2b81dcfcc12b_1770481313628.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>New Chairman for Hari Govind International Post Takeover</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/New-Chairman-for-Hari-Govind-International-Post-Takeover/698763e5b81b2b81dcfcbf81</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/New-Chairman-for-Hari-Govind-International-Post-Takeover/698763e5b81b2b81dcfcbf81</guid><description>HARI GOVIND INTERNATIONAL LIMITED announced the appointment of Mr. Shaju Thomas as Chairman &amp; Managing Director for a five-year term, effective February 7, 2026. This follows a takeover and change in control. Mr. Thomas, who leads the Popees Group with extensive experience in children's apparel, is expected to drive the company's future strategy. He is married to Non-Executive Director Mrs. Linta Purayidathil Jose.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:10:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698763e5b81b2b81dcfcbf80_1770480714610.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Halves Tariffs on India: Geopolitics &amp; Trade Pivot Emerge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Halves-Tariffs-on-India-Geopolitics-and-Trade-Pivot-Emerge/69876305b81b2b81dcfcbe00</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Halves-Tariffs-on-India-Geopolitics-and-Trade-Pivot-Emerge/69876305b81b2b81dcfcbe00</guid><description>Washington has significantly reduced import tariffs on Indian labor-intensive goods, lowering them from 50% to 18%, effective February 7, 2026. This move, framed as an interim trade agreement, is explicitly tied to India's commitment to curb Russian oil purchases. While Indian exporters gain immediate relief, the deal underscores a delicate geopolitical balancing act for New Delhi, which prioritizes energy security. Reciprocal concessions from India include substantial purchases of U.S. products and duty reductions on American industrial and agricultural goods.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 16:06:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69876305b81b2b81dcfcbdff_1770480503652.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Surges on Profit Jump, Lifts FY26 Credit Growth Guidance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Surges-on-Profit-Jump-Lifts-FY26-Credit-Growth-Guidance/69875e42b81b2b81dcfcbbe6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SBI-Surges-on-Profit-Jump-Lifts-FY26-Credit-Growth-Guidance/69875e42b81b2b81dcfcbbe6</guid><description>State Bank of India (SBI) has boosted its FY26 credit growth forecast to 13-15% following a robust December quarter. Net profit surged 24.5% year-on-year to ₹21,028 crore, surpassing expectations. Chairman C S Setty cited broad-based loan growth across retail, agriculture, MSME, and corporate segments, coupled with improving asset quality, as key drivers for the upgraded outlook.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:46:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69875e42b81b2b81dcfcbbe5_1770479275456.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Captain Polyplast Hits Record Revenue, Profit on Mega Orders &amp; Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Captain-Polyplast-Hits-Record-Revenue-Profit-on-Mega-Orders-and-Expansion/69875a9fb81b2b81dcfcb987</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Captain-Polyplast-Hits-Record-Revenue-Profit-on-Mega-Orders-and-Expansion/69875a9fb81b2b81dcfcb987</guid><description>Captain Polyplast Ltd. achieved record Q3 FY26 performance, with total income soaring 40% YoY to ₹127.22 Cr and net profit surging 41% YoY to ₹9.47 Cr. The company secured ₹35.86 Cr in orders from MSEDCL and anticipates commencing operations at its new Ahmedabad plant by Q1 FY26, signaling robust growth and expanded capacity.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:30:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69875a9fb81b2b81dcfcb986_1770478424434.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hari Govind International to become Popees Baby Care Post-Takeover, New MD Appointed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Hari-Govind-International-to-become-Popees-Baby-Care-Post-Takeover-New-MD-Appointed/69875a81b81b2b81dcfcb8a6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Hari-Govind-International-to-become-Popees-Baby-Care-Post-Takeover-New-MD-Appointed/69875a81b81b2b81dcfcb8a6</guid><description>Hari Govind International Limited is set to become Popees Baby Care Limited, pending approvals, following a significant takeover. The board approved the name change and appointed Shaju Thomas as Chairman-cum-Managing Director, alongside other key management roles, signalling a strategic pivot. A new corporate office in Kozhikode is also planned.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:30:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69875a81b81b2b81dcfcb8a5_1770478330343.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MPS Infotecnics Faces Delisting Threat Amidst Severe Audit Crisis</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MPS-Infotecnics-Faces-Delisting-Threat-Amidst-Severe-Audit-Crisis/698756c8b81b2b81dcfcb666</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MPS-Infotecnics-Faces-Delisting-Threat-Amidst-Severe-Audit-Crisis/698756c8b81b2b81dcfcb666</guid><description>MPS Infotecnics Limited disclosed a grim financial update, with Q3 FY26 revenue down 43.6% YoY to ₹6.26 Lacs and net loss widening to ₹87.22 Lacs. The nine-month loss also surged to ₹2.69 Cr. Compounding these woes, auditors issued critical qualifications on asset valuations, unsupported loans, disputed bank balances, and severe compliance failures. The company now faces delisting proceedings from NSE and BSE, signaling an acute crisis for shareholders.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:14:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698756c8b81b2b81dcfcb665_1770477426095.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sportking India Q3 PAT Surges 33% on Strong Demand; Rs 1000 Cr Expansion Launched</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sportking-India-Q3-PAT-Surges-33percent-on-Strong-Demand-Rs-1000-Cr-Expansion-Launched/6987564bb81b2b81dcfcb512</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sportking-India-Q3-PAT-Surges-33percent-on-Strong-Demand-Rs-1000-Cr-Expansion-Launched/6987564bb81b2b81dcfcb512</guid><description>Sportking India Limited reported a robust 33% year-on-year surge in Q3 FY26 net profit to ₹24.6 Crs, alongside a 10.8% rise in EBITDA to ₹65.6 Crs, supported by margin expansion. For the nine months of FY26, while revenue saw a marginal 1.9% YoY dip to ₹1,859.1 Crs, PAT grew 11.8% to ₹87.0 Crs, and EBITDA rose 3.8% to ₹200.5 Crs, reflecting improved operational efficiency. The company has commenced its significant ₹1,000 Crs greenfield capacity expansion program.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:12:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6987564bb81b2b81dcfcb511_1770477246400.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MPS Infotecnics Plunges into Losses, Faces Imminent Delisting as Auditors Raise Alarms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MPS-Infotecnics-Plunges-into-Losses-Faces-Imminent-Delisting-as-Auditors-Raise-Alarms/698755d4b81b2b81dcfcb3bd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/MPS-Infotecnics-Plunges-into-Losses-Faces-Imminent-Delisting-as-Auditors-Raise-Alarms/698755d4b81b2b81dcfcb3bd</guid><description>MPS Infotecnics' Q3 FY26 results show widening losses and minimal revenue. Auditors issued a qualified conclusion citing significant asset impairment concerns, disputed bank balances, and uncertain loans. Both NSE and BSE have initiated delisting proceedings due to severe non-compliance and outstanding dues, with strict deadlines to avert delisting. The outlook is extremely bleak.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:10:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698755d4b81b2b81dcfcb3bc_1770477122506.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Spirits Industry Faces Imports Amid Tariff Cuts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Spirits-Industry-Faces-Imports-Amid-Tariff-Cuts/6987555cb81b2b81dcfcb295</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Spirits-Industry-Faces-Imports-Amid-Tariff-Cuts/6987555cb81b2b81dcfcb295</guid><description>Confederation of Indian Alcoholic Beverage Companies (CIABC) is urging the Indian government to ensure a level playing field as new trade agreements with the US, EU, and UK lead to significant import duty reductions on alcoholic beverages. While welcoming phased reductions, CIABC highlights that high domestic operational costs, complex licensing regimes, and state-level tax disparities already place Indian manufacturers at a disadvantage, raising concerns that these structural issues will be amplified by increased foreign competition. Major players like Sula Vineyards and Radico Khaitan face a complex market environment.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:08:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6987555cb81b2b81dcfcb294_1770476988311.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SNL Bearings Revenue Up 14%, But Profits Sink Amid Margin Compression</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SNL-Bearings-Revenue-Up-14percent-But-Profits-Sink-Amid-Margin-Compression/6987537cb81b2b81dcfcb0b7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SNL-Bearings-Revenue-Up-14percent-But-Profits-Sink-Amid-Margin-Compression/6987537cb81b2b81dcfcb0b7</guid><description>SNL Bearings Limited has reported its Q3 FY26 results, with revenue from operations climbing 14.26% year-on-year to ₹1,426 Lakhs. However, this top-line growth was overshadowed by a 8.93% decline in Profit After Tax (PAT) to ₹265 Lakhs and a significant compression in PAT margins from 23.32% to 18.58%. On a nine-month basis, revenue grew 10.75%, but PAT saw a modest 3.47% rise. The company also approved an ₹8 Crore capacity enhancement plan financed by internal accruals.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 15:00:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6987537cb81b2b81dcfcb0b6_1770476499971.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KDJ Holidayscapes Faces Auditor's Disclaimer Amid IBC Proceedings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/KDJ-Holidayscapes-Faces-Auditors-Disclaimer-Amid-IBC-Proceedings/6987521ab81b2b81dcfcaeb0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/KDJ-Holidayscapes-Faces-Auditors-Disclaimer-Amid-IBC-Proceedings/6987521ab81b2b81dcfcaeb0</guid><description>KDJ Holidayscapes &amp; Resorts has refiled its financial results for Q3 FY25 due to a typo. However, auditors have issued a disclaimer of conclusion on the standalone and consolidated statements, citing inability to obtain sufficient audit evidence amid ongoing Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code proceedings. Consolidated revenue plunged 66.6% YoY to ₹7.88 Cr, though net loss narrowed to ₹(7.88) Cr. The company's future hinges on the IBC resolution plan's execution.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:54:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6987521ab81b2b81dcfcaeaf_1770476402258.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Pact Faces Geopolitical Test Amid Russian Oil Mandate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Pact-Faces-Geopolitical-Test-Amid-Russian-Oil-Mandate/69874fbdb81b2b81dcfcab8e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Pact-Faces-Geopolitical-Test-Amid-Russian-Oil-Mandate/69874fbdb81b2b81dcfcab8e</guid><description>The United States and India have finalized a trade agreement framework, reducing tariffs on Indian goods to 18% and committing India to substantial US product purchases. However, a critical condition requiring India to cease Russian oil imports introduces significant geopolitical friction and economic challenges, testing the nation's commitment to strategic autonomy. While India has not confirmed an outright ban, the move highlights the US leveraging trade policy to influence India's foreign energy sourcing and geopolitical alignments.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:44:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69874fbdb81b2b81dcfcab8d_1770476088936.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KSH International Posts 58% Revenue Surge in Q3, But Profits Slip; Expands Capacity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KSH-International-Posts-58percent-Revenue-Surge-in-Q3-But-Profits-Slip-Expands-Capacity/69874ee3b81b2b81dcfca953</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KSH-International-Posts-58percent-Revenue-Surge-in-Q3-But-Profits-Slip-Expands-Capacity/69874ee3b81b2b81dcfca953</guid><description>KSH International reported a robust 58.52% year-on-year revenue growth to ₹8,177.69 Mn in Q3 FY2026, fueled by volume increases and a favorable product mix. Despite the top-line performance, Profit After Tax (PAT) declined 9.33% YoY to ₹233.26 Mn, impacted by non-recurring and exceptional items, along with higher finance costs. The company bolstered its operational capacity by adding 2,400 MTPA of specialized winding wire capacity and significantly reduced debt by repaying ₹226 Crore.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:40:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69874ee3b81b2b81dcfca952.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KSH International Posts Record Q3 Revenue, Eyes Growth Fueled by New Capacity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KSH-International-Posts-Record-Q3-Revenue-Eyes-Growth-Fueled-by-New-Capacity/69874ecbb81b2b81dcfca8ec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KSH-International-Posts-Record-Q3-Revenue-Eyes-Growth-Fueled-by-New-Capacity/69874ecbb81b2b81dcfca8ec</guid><description>KSH International Limited achieved record-breaking Q3 FY2026 results, with revenue soaring 58.5% YoY to ₹8,177.7 million and EBITDA climbing 22.8% to ₹493.7 million. Sales volumes increased 23.6% YoY. The company significantly reduced debt by ₹2,259.77 million, bringing its debt-to-equity ratio to 0.42x. Management anticipates sustained growth driven by structural demand in renewables, data centers, EVs, and railways, supported by new operational capacity.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:40:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69874ecbb81b2b81dcfca8eb.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Tax Overhaul: Simplification Fuels Digital Push, Risks Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Tax-Overhaul-Simplification-Fuels-Digital-Push-Risks-Loom/69874d68b81b2b81dcfca688</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Tax-Overhaul-Simplification-Fuels-Digital-Push-Risks-Loom/69874d68b81b2b81dcfca688</guid><description>India is poised to enact a sweeping overhaul of its Income Tax Act and rules, effective April 1, 2026. The Central Board of Direct Taxes (CBDT) proposes to slash the number of rules by nearly 35% and forms by over half, simplifying compliance for taxpayers. This significant recalibration emphasizes technological integration and streamlined processes, aiming to create a more efficient and intuitive tax administration. However, the transition introduces new digital dependencies and potential implementation risks that warrant scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:34:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69874d68b81b2b81dcfca687_1770475567923.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI Leverages Data, AI for Indian Capital Market Stability</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Leverages-Data-AI-for-Indian-Capital-Market-Stability/69874cecb81b2b81dcfca52d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Leverages-Data-AI-for-Indian-Capital-Market-Stability/69874cecb81b2b81dcfca52d</guid><description>Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) Chairman Tuhin Kanta Pandey has underscored the indispensable role of data infrastructure, cybersecurity, and standardized reporting in fortifying India's rapidly growing capital markets. The regulator is actively transforming oversight mechanisms, shifting towards a proactive, data-driven approach that leverages artificial intelligence and advanced analytics to preemptively manage risks and ensure market integrity. Initiatives like XBRL filings and Unified Distilled File Formats (UDiFF) are streamlining operations and enhancing transparency for intermediaries and investors alike.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:32:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69874cecb81b2b81dcfca52c_1770475403479.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Suraj Industries Buys VRV Foods, Expands Liquor Business</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Suraj-Industries-Buys-VRV-Foods-Expands-Liquor-Business/69874bf8b81b2b81dcfca30e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Suraj-Industries-Buys-VRV-Foods-Expands-Liquor-Business/69874bf8b81b2b81dcfca30e</guid><description>Suraj Industries Limited announced its Board's approval to acquire 56.25 lakh equity shares of VRV Foods Limited for Rs. 37.13 crore, making VRV Foods a subsidiary. VRV Foods, with a 32% market share in Himachal Pradesh's country liquor segment, reported FY25 turnover of Rs. 122.90 crore and PAT of Rs. 3.16 crore. The acquisition aims to bolster Suraj Industries' liquor operations. Several other corporate actions, including a land lease agreement and revised inter-corporate loan limits, were also approved, pending shareholder nod.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:28:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69874bf8b81b2b81dcfca30d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Suraj Industries Buys VRV Foods for ₹37 Cr, Bolsters Liquor Business</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Suraj-Industries-Buys-VRV-Foods-for-37-Cr-Bolsters-Liquor-Business/69874b88b81b2b81dcfca1b8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Suraj-Industries-Buys-VRV-Foods-for-37-Cr-Bolsters-Liquor-Business/69874b88b81b2b81dcfca1b8</guid><description>Suraj Industries is acquiring VRV Foods for ₹37.13 Crore, a move that will make the Himachal Pradesh-based country liquor manufacturer a subsidiary. VRV Foods holds an estimated 32% market share in its segment and reported a turnover of ₹122.90 Crore in FY25. This acquisition significantly enhances Suraj Industries' scale and profitability in the liquor business. The Board also approved a 15-year rent agreement with subsidiary Carya Chemicals and Fertilizers and increased inter-corporate finance limits to ₹500 Crore. Shareholder approval is required for the VRV Foods acquisition and alterations to the rights issue object.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:26:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69874b88b81b2b81dcfca1b7_1770475263724.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Medi Assist Healthcare Posts 24% Revenue Growth, Becomes Debt-Free</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Medi-Assist-Healthcare-Posts-24percent-Revenue-Growth-Becomes-Debt-Free/6987492cb81b2b81dcfc9e82</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Medi-Assist-Healthcare-Posts-24percent-Revenue-Growth-Becomes-Debt-Free/6987492cb81b2b81dcfc9e82</guid><description>Medi Assist Healthcare Services Limited posted robust Q3 FY26 results, achieving 24.0% YoY operating revenue growth for the nine-month period. Margins improved by 154 bps QoQ overall, with a significant 557 bps QoQ jump in the Paramount TPA segment. The company holds INR 200.1 Cr in free cash and is set to become debt-free from January 2026, supported by an 81.5% YoY surge in technology revenue.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:16:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6987492cb81b2b81dcfc9e81.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KSH International IPO Success Marred by Q3 Profit Dip; Revenue Soars</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KSH-International-IPO-Success-Marred-by-Q3-Profit-Dip-Revenue-Soars/698748b7b81b2b81dcfc9d14</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KSH-International-IPO-Success-Marred-by-Q3-Profit-Dip-Revenue-Soars/698748b7b81b2b81dcfc9d14</guid><description>KSH International Limited reported a strong nine-month performance for FY26, with revenue up 47% YoY to INR 20,886.29 million and PAT rising 52.6% YoY to INR 755.99 million. However, Q3 FY26 saw a mixed trend: revenue surged 58.9% YoY to INR 8,177.69 million, but PAT declined 9.0% YoY to INR 233.26 million due to an exceptional item. PAT margins compressed in Q3. The company recently completed its IPO, significantly increasing equity share capital.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:14:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698748b7b81b2b81dcfc9d13_1770475111633.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ganesha Ecosphere Q3 Profit Plummets 81%, Standalone Unit Roars Back</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Ganesha-Ecosphere-Q3-Profit-Plummets-81percent-Standalone-Unit-Roars-Back/6987456bb81b2b81dcfc9908</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Ganesha-Ecosphere-Q3-Profit-Plummets-81percent-Standalone-Unit-Roars-Back/6987456bb81b2b81dcfc9908</guid><description>Ganesha Ecosphere's consolidated net profit plunged 81.1% YoY to ₹4.8 Crore in Q3FY26, hit by weak rPET demand linked to regulatory ambiguity. Revenue fell 10.2% to ₹357.2 Crore. In contrast, its standalone business surged QoQ, with PAT up 103.8% and EBITDA up 125.6%, as the company strategically targets higher-margin products amid a positive PET market outlook.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 14:00:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6987456bb81b2b81dcfc9907_1770474854905.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Max Estates Q3 Margins Crash 80%, Despite Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Max-Estates-Q3-Margins-Crash-80percent-Despite-Revenue-Growth/6987447cb81b2b81dcfc972a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Max-Estates-Q3-Margins-Crash-80percent-Despite-Revenue-Growth/6987447cb81b2b81dcfc972a</guid><description>Max Estates reported a 24% YoY revenue jump to ₹150 crore for 9M FY26, driven by a 38% surge in lease rentals. However, Q3 FY26 saw a dramatic 80% year-on-year drop in EBITDA margins to a mere 5.9% from 29.3%, despite revenue of ₹49.8 crore. The company holds robust liquidity with ₹1,284 crore cash against ₹414 crore net debt and boasts a ₹14,500-₹15,000 crore project pipeline, including launches in Noida.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:56:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6987447cb81b2b81dcfc9729_1770474693470.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ganesha Ecosphere Q3 PAT Plunges 84% on Consolidated Basis</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Ganesha-Ecosphere-Q3-PAT-Plunges-84percent-on-Consolidated-Basis/69874310b81b2b81dcfc9498</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Ganesha-Ecosphere-Q3-PAT-Plunges-84percent-on-Consolidated-Basis/69874310b81b2b81dcfc9498</guid><description>Ganesha Ecosphere Limited reported challenging Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) plummeting 84.01% year-on-year to ₹474.84 Lakhs. Standalone revenue grew 1.84% to ₹27,294.53 Lakhs, but standalone PAT fell 18.55%. The company also reported a significant 81.08% drop in consolidated PAT for the nine-month period. Increased expenses and recognition of incremental impact from new Labour Codes contributed to the profit erosion. No management guidance was provided.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:50:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69874310b81b2b81dcfc9497_1770474547762.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bella Casa Fashion Revenue Surges 17%, Now Net Debt-Free</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Bella-Casa-Fashion-Revenue-Surges-17percent-Now-Net-Debt-Free/69874225b81b2b81dcfc927a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Bella-Casa-Fashion-Revenue-Surges-17percent-Now-Net-Debt-Free/69874225b81b2b81dcfc927a</guid><description>Bella Casa Fashion &amp; Retail Ltd. reported robust financial results for 9M FY26, with revenue up 17% YoY and PAT soaring 36% to ₹15.6 crore. The company achieved a significant milestone by becoming net debt-free in Q3 FY26. Management highlighted strong revenue visibility, driven by order commitments and a strategic push into export markets, supported by investments aimed at doubling production capacity and land acquisition for future growth.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:46:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69874225b81b2b81dcfc9279_1770474384940.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Megastar Foods Q3 Profit Surges 680%, But Debt and Inventory Rise Sharply</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Megastar-Foods-Q3-Profit-Surges-680percent-But-Debt-and-Inventory-Rise-Sharply/69874131b81b2b81dcfc9094</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Megastar-Foods-Q3-Profit-Surges-680percent-But-Debt-and-Inventory-Rise-Sharply/69874131b81b2b81dcfc9094</guid><description>Megastar Foods reported a stellar Q3 FY26 with PAT soaring 680% YoY to ₹306 lakhs on 52.3% revenue growth. The nine-month period also saw robust performance. However, the balance sheet shows a significant increase in borrowings, current liabilities, and inventory, alongside a sharp drop in the current ratio, flagging potential financial risks. Full-year FY25 PAT saw a 40% decline.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:42:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69874131b81b2b81dcfc9093_1770474192167.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Max Estates Surges on Strong Pre-Sales and Commercial Leasing Momentum</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Max-Estates-Surges-on-Strong-Pre-Sales-and-Commercial-Leasing-Momentum/698740bcb81b2b81dcfc8f24</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Max-Estates-Surges-on-Strong-Pre-Sales-and-Commercial-Leasing-Momentum/698740bcb81b2b81dcfc8f24</guid><description>Max Estates Limited (MEL) reported strong financial performance for 9M FY26, driven by robust residential pre-sales exceeding INR 1,900 crore in Gurugram and significant commercial leasing momentum, including a major LOI for Max District, Gurugram. The company secured over INR 270 crore in gross rentals from this pre-leasing deal, three years ahead of project completion, at a substantial premium. With INR 150 crore in revenue and INR 20 crore PAT for the period, MEL maintains a healthy net debt position of INR 414 crore against INR 1,284 crore cash.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:40:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698740bcb81b2b81dcfc8f23.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GIC Re Posts 36% Profit Surge, Eyes Global Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/GIC-Re-Posts-36percent-Profit-Surge-Eyes-Global-Expansion/69874047b81b2b81dcfc8df4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/GIC-Re-Posts-36percent-Profit-Surge-Eyes-Global-Expansion/69874047b81b2b81dcfc8df4</guid><description>GIC Re reported robust Nine Months FY26 results, with Profit After Tax soaring 35.84% YoY to ₹6,137.94 crore. Gross Premium grew 7.11% to ₹32,976.26 crore, supported by an improved Incurred Claims Ratio of 86.93% and a reduced Combined Ratio of 106.88%. The company is actively scaling its international business, aiming for a 60:40 domestic:international risk portfolio, and enhancing its solvency ratio to 3.87.</description><pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 13:38:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69874047b81b2b81dcfc8df3.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>