<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:50:07 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Sonata Software Q3: Revenue Climbs, But Profitability Faces Pressure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Sonata-Software-Q3-Revenue-Climbs-But-Profitability-Faces-Pressure/6985e0cae769d12df1d6e2d3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Sonata-Software-Q3-Revenue-Climbs-But-Profitability-Faces-Pressure/6985e0cae769d12df1d6e2d3</guid><description>Sonata Software posted a robust Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue at ₹3,080.6 Cr, up 8.36% YoY, driven by major BFSI wins and AI focus. However, consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) declined 0.58% YoY to ₹104.36 Cr, and margins compressed to 3.39%. Standalone PAT saw a significant 458% YoY jump to ₹33.04 Cr. The company declared a ₹1.25 interim dividend and maintains a marginal net debt position of ₹12 Cr.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:38:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Jana SFB's Profit Plummets 91%, Eyes Guarantee Programs for RoA Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Jana-SFBs-Profit-Plummets-91percent-Eyes-Guarantee-Programs-for-RoA-Boost/6985e069e769d12df1d6e0fc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Jana-SFBs-Profit-Plummets-91percent-Eyes-Guarantee-Programs-for-RoA-Boost/6985e069e769d12df1d6e0fc</guid><description>Jana Small Finance Bank reported a drastic 91.2% year-on-year decline in net profit to ₹9.7 crore for Q3 FY26, primarily driven by elevated credit provisioning. Despite this, core income remained resilient with Net Interest Income (NII) up 13.8% to ₹675 crore and deposits growing 30% to ₹33,733 crore. Asset quality saw sequential improvement with Gross NPAs falling to 2.59%. Management anticipates credit costs to moderate, while future eligibility for guarantee programs starting FY27 offers a pathway to improve Return on Assets by 50-70 basis points.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:36:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>PFC Acquires REC Stake, Merger Talks Gain Momentum Post-Budget</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/PFC-Acquires-REC-Stake-Merger-Talks-Gain-Momentum-Post-Budget/6985e03be769d12df1d6e029</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/PFC-Acquires-REC-Stake-Merger-Talks-Gain-Momentum-Post-Budget/6985e03be769d12df1d6e029</guid><description>Power Finance Corporation Ltd (PFC) has acquired a 52.63% stake in Rural Electrification Corporation Ltd (REC) following board approval. This move positions REC as PFC's subsidiary and advances merger plans initially flagged in the Union Budget 2026. The decision comes after the Cabinet Committee on Economic Affairs (CCEA) granted 'in principle' approval for the consolidation of these public sector NBFCs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:36:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>BLS International Profit Soars 35% on Mega Visa, Aadhaar Deals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BLS-International-Profit-Soars-35percent-on-Mega-Visa-Aadhaar-Deals/6985dfc2e769d12df1d6de5f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BLS-International-Profit-Soars-35percent-on-Mega-Visa-Aadhaar-Deals/6985dfc2e769d12df1d6de5f</guid><description>BLS International Services Ltd. reported a robust third quarter with net profit soaring 34.8% year-on-year to ₹162.7 crore, driven by a 43.6% revenue surge to ₹736.5 crore. The company secured major global visa contracts from the Slovak Republic and the Republic of Cyprus, alongside significant domestic Aadhaar and visa processing deals. However, EBITDA margins compressed by 390 basis points to 26.9%.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:34:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Capri Global Capital Hits Record Profit, Boosts AUM Target</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Capri-Global-Capital-Hits-Record-Profit-Boosts-AUM-Target/6985df7fe769d12df1d6dcda</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Capri-Global-Capital-Hits-Record-Profit-Boosts-AUM-Target/6985df7fe769d12df1d6dcda</guid><description>Capri Global Capital delivered its strongest quarter yet in Q3 FY26, reporting a record profit of INR255 crore, a 99% year-on-year surge. Assets Under Management (AUM) climbed 47% YoY to INR30,406 crore, fueled by robust growth in Gold Loans (+80% YoY). The company also revised its FY28 AUM target upwards to INR55,000 crore, signaling strong confidence in its technology-driven expansion and high-yield product strategy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:33:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Auditor Qualifies NECCLTD's Accounts Amidst Mixed Q3 Results</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Auditor-Qualifies-NECCLTDs-Accounts-Amidst-Mixed-Q3-Results/6985df5fe769d12df1d6dbf6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Auditor-Qualifies-NECCLTDs-Accounts-Amidst-Mixed-Q3-Results/6985df5fe769d12df1d6dbf6</guid><description>North Eastern Carrying Corporation (NECCLTD) reported a mixed financial performance for Q3 FY26. While Net Profit After Tax (PAT) more than doubled to ₹3.45 Cr (up 90% YoY) due to a sharp 64.7% reduction in tax expenses, the company saw a marginal revenue dip YoY and a significant 9.0% drop in Profit Before Tax (PBT). For the nine months ended December 2025, revenue declined 10.1% and PAT fell 17.2%. Compounding concerns, statutory auditors issued a qualified opinion on the financial statements, citing issues with doubtful debts policy, lease accounting, and the need for balance confirmation. Borrowings also increased by 13.3%.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:32:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Whirlpool India Q3 Profit Dips, Buys Subsidiary Stake, Promoter Holding Slashed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Whirlpool-India-Q3-Profit-Dips-Buys-Subsidiary-Stake-Promoter-Holding-Slashed/6985dee7e769d12df1d6da19</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Whirlpool-India-Q3-Profit-Dips-Buys-Subsidiary-Stake-Promoter-Holding-Slashed/6985dee7e769d12df1d6da19</guid><description>Whirlpool of India reported mixed Q3 FY26 results, with standalone revenue and profit growing slightly, but consolidated profit declining 6.1% YoY to ₹41.80 crore, partly due to an exceptional charge from new Labour Codes. The company approved acquiring the remaining 3.18% stake in Elica PB Whirlpool Kitchen Appliances, aiming for full ownership, and noted a significant dilution in promoter holding from 51% to 39.76%. No forward guidance was provided.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:30:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sonata Software Q3 PAT Soars 21%, Declares ₹1.25 Interim Dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Sonata-Software-Q3-PAT-Soars-21percent-Declares-125-Interim-Dividend/6985ded3e769d12df1d6d937</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Sonata-Software-Q3-PAT-Soars-21percent-Declares-125-Interim-Dividend/6985ded3e769d12df1d6d937</guid><description>Sonata Software delivered robust Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) before exceptional items climbing 21.4% year-on-year to ₹127.5 crore. Revenue rose 8.4% year-on-year to ₹3,080.6 crore, driven by a significant 68.6% quarter-on-quarter surge in its Domestic Products &amp; Services segment. The company declared a third interim dividend of ₹1.25 per equity share and highlighted its strategic investments in Artificial Intelligence, which now contributes approximately 14% to its order book.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Dhanuka Agritech: Buy Rating Amidst Q3 Slump Signals Valuation Opportunity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Dhanuka-Agritech-Buy-Rating-Amidst-Q3-Slump-Signals-Valuation-Opportunity/6985dde0e769d12df1d6d6f4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Dhanuka-Agritech-Buy-Rating-Amidst-Q3-Slump-Signals-Valuation-Opportunity/6985dde0e769d12df1d6d6f4</guid><description>Dhanuka Agritech's rating was upgraded to 'Buy' despite a weaker-than-expected third quarter. Profitability was compressed by 8% revenue decline and negative operating leverage, attributed to excess rainfall and subdued crop prices impacting pesticide demand. However, the stock's significant correction over nine months has led to compelling valuations at approximately 17.5x FY26E EPS, presenting a potential rebound opportunity. Operational advancements, including new molecule commercialization and a robust product pipeline for FY27, support a forward-looking outlook.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:26:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Godawari Power Tumbles on Profit Drop, Bets on Logistics and Renewables</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Godawari-Power-Tumbles-on-Profit-Drop-Bets-on-Logistics-and-Renewables/6985dd87e769d12df1d6d58b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Godawari-Power-Tumbles-on-Profit-Drop-Bets-on-Logistics-and-Renewables/6985dd87e769d12df1d6d58b</guid><description>Godawari Power and Ispat Limited reported a significant YoY decline in Q3 FY26 net profit, with standalone PAT down 40.2% and consolidated PAT down 5.3%. Revenue also saw a YoY dip. Despite the financial headwinds, the company is strategically pivoting, approving the purchase of railway wagons for ₹120 Cr, exploring logistics as a business line, and investing an additional ₹200 Cr in its renewable energy subsidiary for a BESS plant. It also divested its stake in Ardent Steels for ₹90.87 Cr.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:24:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Akme Fintrade Profit Soars 365% Amid Auditor Resignation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Akme-Fintrade-Profit-Soars-365percent-Amid-Auditor-Resignation/6985dd6fe769d12df1d6d4a7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Akme-Fintrade-Profit-Soars-365percent-Amid-Auditor-Resignation/6985dd6fe769d12df1d6d4a7</guid><description>Akme Fintrade India Ltd. reported a phenomenal Q3 FY26 with Profit After Tax (PAT) surging 365.5% year-on-year to ₹289.99 Cr, driven by a 38.2% rise in revenue to ₹3,726.39 Cr. The company's PAT margin expanded significantly to 7.78%. Despite robust financial performance and healthy NBFC ratios, the firm disclosed the resignation of its internal auditor, citing time constraints, a development that warrants investor attention.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:24:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sonata Software Q3 PAT Surges 21.4% YoY on Strong Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Sonata-Software-Q3-PAT-Surges-214percent-YoY-on-Strong-Revenue-Growth/6985dd0fe769d12df1d6d2ea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Sonata-Software-Q3-PAT-Surges-214percent-YoY-on-Strong-Revenue-Growth/6985dd0fe769d12df1d6d2ea</guid><description>Sonata Software reported strong Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated PAT before exceptional items rising 21.4% YoY to ₹127.5 crore and 6.1% QoQ. Consolidated revenue surged 45.4% QoQ to ₹3,080.6 crore, while EBITDA grew 15.9% QoQ to ₹200.2 crore. An exceptional item of ₹31.3 crore impacted net PAT. The company declared a third interim dividend of ₹1.25 per share and re-appointed Srikar Reddy as Executive Vice Chairman.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:22:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Fairchem Organics Plunges to Q3 Loss on Revenue Drop; Liabilities Rise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Fairchem-Organics-Plunges-to-Q3-Loss-on-Revenue-Drop-Liabilities-Rise/6985dcf2e769d12df1d6d237</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Fairchem-Organics-Plunges-to-Q3-Loss-on-Revenue-Drop-Liabilities-Rise/6985dcf2e769d12df1d6d237</guid><description>Fairchem Organics Limited reported a sharp downturn for Q3 FY26, swinging to a net loss of ₹9.71 Lakhs from a profit of ₹351.78 Lakhs in the prior year. Revenue from operations declined 11.86% year-on-year to ₹10,013.40 Lakhs. For the nine-month period, Profit After Tax (PAT) plummeted 91.34% to ₹184.87 Lakhs. An exceptional charge of ₹88.27 Lakhs impacted results, while segment liabilities increased significantly. The company successfully completed its buyback program.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:22:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Chemicals Posts Loss Amid Global Soda Ash Glut, Bets on India Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Tata-Chemicals-Posts-Loss-Amid-Global-Soda-Ash-Glut-Bets-on-India-Growth/6985dcaee769d12df1d6d0bc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Tata-Chemicals-Posts-Loss-Amid-Global-Soda-Ash-Glut-Bets-on-India-Growth/6985dcaee769d12df1d6d0bc</guid><description>Tata Chemicals reported a consolidated net loss before exceptional items of INR 15 crore for Q3 FY26, a sharp reversal from profit in the prior year, as global soda ash markets grapple with tepid demand, oversupply, and pricing pressure. While consolidated revenue dipped 1% YoY, standalone operations saw a 3% revenue jump and 21% PAT growth. The company is focusing on cost discipline, strengthening its balance sheet, and investing INR 1,425 crore in domestic capacity for salt, silica, and dense ash, while strategically withdrawing from unprofitable export markets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:21:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sonata Software Surges 45% QoQ Revenue, Secures Major BFSI Deal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Sonata-Software-Surges-45percent-QoQ-Revenue-Secures-Major-BFSI-Deal/6985dc89e769d12df1d6cf5f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Sonata-Software-Surges-45percent-QoQ-Revenue-Secures-Major-BFSI-Deal/6985dc89e769d12df1d6cf5f</guid><description>Sonata Software posted robust Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated revenue surging 45.4% quarter-on-quarter to ₹3,080.6 crores. Profit After Tax (PAT) before exceptional items grew 6.1% QoQ and 21.4% YoY to ₹127.5 crores. The company announced a third interim dividend of ₹1.25 per share and highlighted significant progress in international IT services, including a large BFSI sector deal with a Fortune 500 fintech client. Strategic investments in AI are also bolstering the order book.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:20:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Whirlpool India Ceases Subsidiary Status After Promoter Stake Dilution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Whirlpool-India-Ceases-Subsidiary-Status-After-Promoter-Stake-Dilution/6985dc7be769d12df1d6cedf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Whirlpool-India-Ceases-Subsidiary-Status-After-Promoter-Stake-Dilution/6985dc7be769d12df1d6cedf</guid><description>Whirlpool of India Limited has undergone a significant structural change, ceasing to be a subsidiary of Whirlpool Mauritius Limited following a dilution of its ultimate holding company's (Whirlpool Corporation) stake to 39.76%. This governance shift coincides with mixed financial results for Q3 FY26, showing YoY revenue growth but a decline in consolidated PAT due to a substantial exceptional item. The company also approved acquiring a further 3.18% stake in its subsidiary, Elica PB Whirlpool Kitchen Appliances Private Limited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:20:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sonata Software Lands $129M Deals, Pivots to AI-Driven 'Change-Run' Services</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Sonata-Software-Lands-129M-Deals-Pivots-to-AI-Driven-Change-Run-Services/6985dc36e769d12df1d6cd64</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Sonata-Software-Lands-129M-Deals-Pivots-to-AI-Driven-Change-Run-Services/6985dc36e769d12df1d6cd64</guid><description>Sonata Software reported a strong Q3 FY'26, securing two major deals worth $129 million and boosting domestic revenue by 68.5% QoQ. The IT services firm is strategically pivoting to "Change-Run" services, emphasizing AI, Automation, and Cloud Modernization. Cloud &amp; Data services now drive 63% of revenue, with BFSI and HLS verticals showing significant scaling.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:19:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Fairchem Organics Sees Steep Profit Fall, Revenue Declines 11.8% YoY</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Fairchem-Organics-Sees-Steep-Profit-Fall-Revenue-Declines-118percent-YoY/6985dc20e769d12df1d6cc90</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Fairchem-Organics-Sees-Steep-Profit-Fall-Revenue-Declines-118percent-YoY/6985dc20e769d12df1d6cc90</guid><description>Fairchem Organics Limited reported a challenging third quarter for FY26, with revenue from operations falling 11.84% year-on-year to ₹10,013.40 Lakhs. Profitability took a severe hit, with the company posting a net loss of ₹9.71 Lakhs compared to a profit of ₹351.78 Lakhs in the prior year's quarter. This downturn was exacerbated by an exceptional item related to new Labour Codes. The company also successfully completed a share buyback program of ₹34 Crores.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:18:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>VXL Instruments Board Meeting Called Amidst Insolvency Proceedings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/VXL-Instruments-Board-Meeting-Called-Amidst-Insolvency-Proceedings/6985dc08e769d12df1d6cbac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/VXL-Instruments-Board-Meeting-Called-Amidst-Insolvency-Proceedings/6985dc08e769d12df1d6cbac</guid><description>VXL Instruments Limited has notified the BSE about a board meeting on February 13, 2026, to approve unaudited financial results for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. The company is currently undergoing Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP) under the NCLT, with the Resolution Professional (RP) Jayanti Lal Jain managing its affairs. Key SEBI (LODR) regulations regarding board committees are currently inapplicable, with the RP assuming these duties.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:18:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Pidilite Industries: A Decade of Growth and Strategic Expansion for Future Dominance.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Pidilite-Industries-A-Decade-of-Growth-and-Strategic-Expansion-for-Future-Dominance/6985dbbbe769d12df1d6ca33</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Pidilite-Industries-A-Decade-of-Growth-and-Strategic-Expansion-for-Future-Dominance/6985dbbbe769d12df1d6ca33</guid><description>Pidilite Industries unveils a decade of robust growth, with Net Sales reaching ₹13,094 Cr and EBITDA ₹3,013 Cr in FY24. The company highlights sustained EBITDA margins of 17-23%, significant Capex of over ₹2,700 Cr, strategic JVs, acquisitions (Araldite, Tenax), and international expansion in Africa and the Middle East. Pidilite is poised to leverage digital, AI, and sustainability for future growth in new markets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:16:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Godawari Power Posts Mixed Q3, Diversifies into Logistics &amp; Green Energy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Godawari-Power-Posts-Mixed-Q3-Diversifies-into-Logistics-and-Green-Energy/6985db8ae769d12df1d6c934</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Godawari-Power-Posts-Mixed-Q3-Diversifies-into-Logistics-and-Green-Energy/6985db8ae769d12df1d6c934</guid><description>Godawari Power and Ispat reported a mixed third quarter. Standalone Profit After Tax (PAT) rose 9.4% YoY to ₹148.54 Cr, driven by improved margins. However, consolidated PAT declined 13.4% YoY to ₹154.83 Cr. The company approved buying 40 railway wagons for ₹120 Cr and expanding into logistics services. It also sanctioned an additional ₹200 Cr investment for a Battery Energy Storage System (BESS) plant in its subsidiary, GNEPL, and plans to divest its stake in Ardent Steels.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>REC, PFC Merger Gets In-Principle Nod For PSU Power Sector Overhaul</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/REC-PFC-Merger-Gets-In-Principle-Nod-For-PSU-Power-Sector-Overhaul/6985daeae769d12df1d6c747</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/REC-PFC-Merger-Gets-In-Principle-Nod-For-PSU-Power-Sector-Overhaul/6985daeae769d12df1d6c747</guid><description>REC Limited's Board has granted in-principle approval for a merger with Power Finance Corporation Limited (PFC). This strategic move aligns with the Union Budget 2026-27's call to restructure public sector NBFCs for enhanced scale and efficiency. REC will now develop a detailed proposal, ensuring the merged entity remains a recognized 'Government Company'. The restructuring aims to bolster the financial capabilities and market presence of key players in the power sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:13:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>KRN Heat Exchanger Surges on Revenue, but Margins Show Pressure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KRN-Heat-Exchanger-Surges-on-Revenue-but-Margins-Show-Pressure/6985dac0e769d12df1d6c66b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KRN-Heat-Exchanger-Surges-on-Revenue-but-Margins-Show-Pressure/6985dac0e769d12df1d6c66b</guid><description>KRN Heat Exchanger &amp; Refrigeration Ltd. reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated revenue soaring 37.46% YoY to ₹15,322.76 Lakhs. Consolidated PAT grew 25.76% YoY. However, Q3 consolidated PAT margins dipped to 14.79% from 16.17% YoY. Standalone revenue also surged, but margins compressed. IPO proceeds are being utilized for expansion. No forward guidance was provided.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:12:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>PFC Board Approves In-Principle Merger With Subsidiary REC Limited</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PFC-Board-Approves-In-Principle-Merger-With-Subsidiary-REC-Limited/6985da78e769d12df1d6c4d4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PFC-Board-Approves-In-Principle-Merger-With-Subsidiary-REC-Limited/6985da78e769d12df1d6c4d4</guid><description>Power Finance Corporation Ltd. (PFC) has received in-principle board approval to merge with its subsidiary, REC Limited. This strategic move follows PFC's recent acquisition of a majority stake in REC and aims to bolster scale and efficiency for Public Sector NBFCs, as envisioned in the Union Budget 2026-27. The combined entity will retain its status as a 'Government Company'.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:11:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Trade Deal Boosts Rupee, but Friday Weakness Signals Caution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Trade-Deal-Boosts-Rupee-but-Friday-Weakness-Signals-Caution/6985da55e769d12df1d6c3bc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Trade-Deal-Boosts-Rupee-but-Friday-Weakness-Signals-Caution/6985da55e769d12df1d6c3bc</guid><description>The Indian rupee recorded its strongest weekly performance in over three years, propelled by a landmark trade agreement with the United States. This pact reduced US tariffs on Indian imports significantly. Despite this optimism, the rupee weakened on Friday, succumbing to dollar demand and likely foreign portfolio outflows, triggering stop-losses. India's central bank maintained its key repo rate at 5.25% with a neutral stance, offering stability. Analysts suggest sustained rupee appreciation hinges on consistent foreign capital inflows and clear trade deal implementation, as global factors and investor sentiment remain key determinants.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:11:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Stocks: FPI 'Pain Trade' Fuels Re-rating Hopes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Stocks-FPI-Pain-Trade-Fuels-Re-rating-Hopes/6985da2ce769d12df1d6c307</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Stocks-FPI-Pain-Trade-Fuels-Re-rating-Hopes/6985da2ce769d12df1d6c307</guid><description>Morgan Stanley forecasts a sustained market re-rating for India, citing a confluence of weak past returns, attractive valuations, robust policy support, and subdued foreign investor positioning. The brokerage anticipates a sharp earnings turnaround, driven by coordinated government and Reserve Bank of India stimulus measures. This environment is expected to create a 'pain trade' for under-positioned foreign portfolio investors (FPIs), potentially leading to significant capital inflows. The report also highlights a structural shift towards a lower-volatility growth regime, supported by services export strength and fiscal consolidation, underpinning a bullish outlook for the BSE Sensex.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:10:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IndiGo Targets Shanghai: Betting Big on India-China Air Travel Revival</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Targets-Shanghai-Betting-Big-on-India-China-Air-Travel-Revival/6985d9f7e769d12df1d6c176</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IndiGo-Targets-Shanghai-Betting-Big-on-India-China-Air-Travel-Revival/6985d9f7e769d12df1d6c176</guid><description>InterGlobe Aviation Ltd., operating as IndiGo, is poised to launch direct flights between New Delhi and Shanghai, pending regulatory approval for late March or early April. This strategic move capitalizes on the resurgent India-China air travel market, fueled by improving bilateral relations and strong demographic and economic potential. IndiGo's CEO highlights significant market opportunities, backed by the airline's successful re-establishment of routes to China and its focus on capturing growing business travel demand.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:09:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RBI Direct Lending to REITs: Funding Shift Amidst Sector Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/RBI-Direct-Lending-to-REITs-Funding-Shift-Amidst-Sector-Growth/6985d9cbe769d12df1d6c08f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/RBI-Direct-Lending-to-REITs-Funding-Shift-Amidst-Sector-Growth/6985d9cbe769d12df1d6c08f</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's decision to permit direct bank lending to Real Estate Investment Trusts (REITs) marks a significant shift from traditional capital markets funding. While this move aims to enhance financing efficiency and provide access to more stable, long-term capital for India's growing REIT sector, it introduces a new layer of banking sector scrutiny. REITs may now face more stringent loan covenants and increased sensitivity to monetary policy changes, potentially altering their risk profiles beyond typical market-based debt.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Shree Cement Q3: Profit Soars, But Margin Pressure Mounts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Shree-Cement-Q3-Profit-Soars-But-Margin-Pressure-Mounts/6985d9ace769d12df1d6bf8f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Shree-Cement-Q3-Profit-Soars-But-Margin-Pressure-Mounts/6985d9ace769d12df1d6bf8f</guid><description>Shree Cement announced a robust third-quarter performance with net profit surging 37.9% year-on-year to ₹266.7 crore. Revenue climbed 5% to ₹4,800 crore, supported by stable volumes and improving demand. However, operating profitability faced headwinds, with EBITDA declining 1.9% and margins narrowing to 19.7% from 21.1%, partly due to a ₹55.99 crore provision for additional employee benefit obligations linked to new labor codes. The company reaffirms its full-year sales guidance of over 36 million tonnes and long-term capacity target of 80 million tonnes by 2029, focusing on organic growth.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:08:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Kalyan Jewellers Profit Leaps 90% to ₹416 Cr on Revenue Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Kalyan-Jewellers-Profit-Leaps-90percent-to-416-Cr-on-Revenue-Surge/6985d936e769d12df1d6be05</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Kalyan-Jewellers-Profit-Leaps-90percent-to-416-Cr-on-Revenue-Surge/6985d936e769d12df1d6be05</guid><description>Kalyan Jewellers India Ltd. reported a robust 90% year-on-year jump in net profit to ₹416.2 crore for the third quarter. Revenue climbed 42% to ₹10,343 crore, driven by strong operational efficiencies and expanding EBITDA margins to 7.3%. India operations saw an 84% profit increase, while international and Candere brands also posted significant gains.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:06:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Smoggy Economy: Pollution Costs Businesses Billions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Indias-Smoggy-Economy-Pollution-Costs-Businesses-Billions/6985d85be769d12df1d6ba4a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Indias-Smoggy-Economy-Pollution-Costs-Businesses-Billions/6985d85be769d12df1d6ba4a</guid><description>India's air quality crisis, highlighted by the January 2026 CREA report, carries a substantial economic toll. Businesses face annual losses of approximately $95 billion due to reduced productivity, absenteeism, and decreased consumer activity. This pervasive environmental challenge is increasingly influencing investor sentiment and corporate strategy, pushing ESG (Environmental, Social, and Governance) considerations to the forefront of financial decision-making.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:02:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Execution Paralysis: A Silent Tax on Commerce</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Indias-Execution-Paralysis-A-Silent-Tax-on-Commerce/6985d811e769d12df1d6b86f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Indias-Execution-Paralysis-A-Silent-Tax-on-Commerce/6985d811e769d12df1d6b86f</guid><description>A staggering 8.82 lakh execution petitions clog India's civil justice system, turning judicial mandates into hollow victories. This systemic gridlock significantly harms economic output, with delays potentially costing 1-2% of GDP annually. Despite reforms aimed at speeding up commercial disputes, the crucial phase of decree execution remains mired in antiquated procedures, eroding investor confidence and contract sanctity.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:01:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>JJG Aero Nets $30M Series B, Targets Global Aerospace Component Leadership</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/JJG-Aero-Nets-30M-Series-B-Targets-Global-Aerospace-Component-Leadership/6985d7c1e769d12df1d6b73d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/JJG-Aero-Nets-30M-Series-B-Targets-Global-Aerospace-Component-Leadership/6985d7c1e769d12df1d6b73d</guid><description>JJG Aero Private Limited has secured $30 million in Series B funding, led by Norwest Capital LLC, to boost its production of high-precision machined components for aero-engines and airframes. This capital will strengthen its role as a supplier to global aerospace OEMs and Tier-1 manufacturers, advancing India's advanced manufacturing capabilities under the 'Make in India' initiative. CMS INDUSLAW advised on the transaction.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CL Educate Swings to Net Loss Despite 37% Revenue Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/CL-Educate-Swings-to-Net-Loss-Despite-37percent-Revenue-Surge/6985d791e769d12df1d6b615</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/CL-Educate-Swings-to-Net-Loss-Despite-37percent-Revenue-Surge/6985d791e769d12df1d6b615</guid><description>CL Educate Limited reported a consolidated net loss of ₹15.7 Cr for Q3 FY2026, a significant reversal from a ₹4.4 Cr profit a year ago, despite a robust 37.2% YoY revenue increase to ₹266.2 Cr. The top-line growth was propelled by its Assessments (DEX) and MarTech businesses. However, substantially higher finance costs, depreciation, and one-time exceptional expenses of ₹5.3 Cr led to the profitability deterioration. The EdTech segment also continued its downturn.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 11:59:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Chemicals Bets ₹515 Cr on Tamil Nadu Salt Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Chemicals-Bets-515-Cr-on-Tamil-Nadu-Salt-Expansion/6985d755e769d12df1d6b4d3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Chemicals-Bets-515-Cr-on-Tamil-Nadu-Salt-Expansion/6985d755e769d12df1d6b4d3</guid><description>Tata Chemicals is investing ₹515 crore to establish a new greenfield Iodised Vacuum Salt Dried (IVSD) manufacturing facility in Tamil Nadu's Ramanathapuram district. Approved on February 2, 2026, the plant will add 210 kilo tonnes per annum (KTPA) capacity. This strategic move aims to diversify production, bolster its supply chain, and significantly reduce logistics costs by locating closer to key southern Indian markets, complementing its existing 1.6 million tonne capacity in Gujarat.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 11:58:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985d755e769d12df1d6b4d2_1770382142885.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sanghvi Movers Q3 Profit Plummets 57% Despite Strong Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sanghvi-Movers-Q3-Profit-Plummets-57percent-Despite-Strong-Revenue-Growth/6985d6ebe769d12df1d6b370</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sanghvi-Movers-Q3-Profit-Plummets-57percent-Despite-Strong-Revenue-Growth/6985d6ebe769d12df1d6b370</guid><description>Sanghvi Movers reported a sharp 57% YoY drop in consolidated Q3 PAT to ₹30.77 Cr, despite an 8.7% revenue increase to ₹737.77 Cr. The decline was driven by a ₹3.78 Cr crane damage write-off, input tax credit reversal, higher employee costs, and reduced other income, causing PAT margins to compress significantly to 4.2% from 10.5% YoY.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 11:56:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Steel Posts Stellar Q3 Results, EBITDA Soars 39% on Record Deliveries</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Results-EBITDA-Soars-39percent-on-Record-Deliveries/6985d663e769d12df1d6b1d1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Results-EBITDA-Soars-39percent-on-Record-Deliveries/6985d663e769d12df1d6b1d1</guid><description>Tata Steel delivered a robust financial performance in Q3 FY26, reporting a 39% year-on-year surge in consolidated EBITDA to Rs 8,309 crores, driven by a record 6.04 million tons in quarterly deliveries. Consolidated revenue grew 6.3% to Rs 57,002 crores. India operations led the charge with a 14% delivery increase. The company is aggressively pursuing growth via capacity expansions and strategic acquisitions, alongside significant cost transformation savings.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 11:54:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985d663e769d12df1d6b1d0_1770381951379.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PFC Acquires REC: PSU NBFC Consolidation Sparks Synergy Play</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PFC-Acquires-REC-PSU-NBFC-Consolidation-Sparks-Synergy-Play/6985d631e769d12df1d6b055</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PFC-Acquires-REC-PSU-NBFC-Consolidation-Sparks-Synergy-Play/6985d631e769d12df1d6b055</guid><description>Power Finance Corporation (PFC) has secured a controlling 52.63% stake in REC Limited, establishing REC as its subsidiary. This move aligns with the Union Budget 2026-27's mandate to scale up credit disbursement and technological adoption within public sector non-banking financial companies (NBFCs). PFC's board approved the acquisition on February 6, 2026, paving the way for a potential future merger, aiming for greater operational synergy and financial capacity for infrastructure financing.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 11:53:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985d631e769d12df1d6b054_1770381768710.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI's REIT Lending Rule: Safeguards Dilute Funding Boost Hopes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/RBIs-REIT-Lending-Rule-Safeguards-Dilute-Funding-Boost-Hopes/6985d5ede769d12df1d6af3d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/RBIs-REIT-Lending-Rule-Safeguards-Dilute-Funding-Boost-Hopes/6985d5ede769d12df1d6af3d</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's plan to allow commercial banks to lend directly to Real Estate Investment Trusts (REITs) signals regulatory maturity but is tempered by "appropriate prudential safeguards." While industry anticipates improved funding access and lower borrowing costs, the actual benefit hinges on these unspecified risk management protocols and the REITs' ability to secure genuinely long-term capital, potentially addressing existing tenure mismatches with shorter-term capital market instruments. This move aligns with broader efforts to deepen yield markets and monetize assets, but its impact remains contingent on execution within a sensitive interest rate environment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 11:52:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985d5ede769d12df1d6af3c_1770381590217.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sonata Software Sees 45% Revenue Surge, Declares Dividend Amidst PAT Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Sonata-Software-Sees-45percent-Revenue-Surge-Declares-Dividend-Amidst-PAT-Concerns/6985d5a9e769d12df1d6ae0a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Sonata-Software-Sees-45percent-Revenue-Surge-Declares-Dividend-Amidst-PAT-Concerns/6985d5a9e769d12df1d6ae0a</guid><description>Sonata Software reported a robust Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue surging 45.4% QoQ to ₹3,080.6 crores and PAT growing 6.1% QoQ and 21.4% YoY to ₹127.5 crores (before exceptional items). The company secured a large BFSI deal and declared an interim dividend of ₹1.25 per share. However, standalone PAT saw a sharp QoQ decline due to lower 'Other Income', and consolidated EBITDA margins compressed sequentially. Exceptional items related to new labour codes impacted reported PAT.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 11:51:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6985d5a9e769d12df1d6ae09_1770381413913.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>