<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:49:16 +0000</pubDate><item><title>AI No-Code Pioneer Emergent Hits $50M ARR</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-No-Code-Pioneer-Emergent-Hits-50M-ARR/69833cf6f5a3f0ebac9a91c4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-No-Code-Pioneer-Emergent-Hits-50M-ARR/69833cf6f5a3f0ebac9a91c4</guid><description>AI software creation platform Emergent rapidly achieved $50 million in annual recurring revenue within seven months, positioning it among India's fastest-scaling startups. The company's no-code platform empowers non-technical users to build production-ready applications, directly addressing a significant market gap and challenging traditional software development costs. Its unique multi-agent system effectively functions as a cloud-based development team, differentiating it from existing AI coding assistants.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:38:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69833cf6f5a3f0ebac9a91c3_1770208582915.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India MF Growth: Jio-BlackRock Tech Edge Forces Bank Shake-up</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-MF-Growth-Jio-BlackRock-Tech-Edge-Forces-Bank-Shake-up/69833c4bf5a3f0ebac9a8f67</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-MF-Growth-Jio-BlackRock-Tech-Edge-Forces-Bank-Shake-up/69833c4bf5a3f0ebac9a8f67</guid><description>K.V. Kamath predicts Indian mutual fund AUM will more than double in five years, propelled by Jio Financial Services and BlackRock's alliance leveraging the Aladdin platform. This venture, approved in May 2025 and launched July 2025, forces banks to innovate as sector AUM reached ₹80.23 lakh crore by Dec 2025. Equity funds quadrupled, with flexi-cap funds leading growth. Analysts foresee AUM exceeding ₹300 lakh crore by 2035 via rising SIPs and broader penetration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:37:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69833c4bf5a3f0ebac9a8f66_1770208631494.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Subam Papers Raises ₹1044 Cr Via Preferential Issue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Subam-Papers-Raises-1044-Cr-Via-Preferential-Issue/69833a6bf5a3f0ebac9a7842</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Subam-Papers-Raises-1044-Cr-Via-Preferential-Issue/69833a6bf5a3f0ebac9a7842</guid><description>Subam Papers Limited has approved a significant preferential allotment, agreeing to issue 26,32,800 warrants and 42,34,400 equity shares at ₹152.00 each. This move aims to raise ₹1,043.81 crore. Key allottees include promoters Thirupathi Balakumar, Alagarsamy Sudha, BMM Paper Board Private Limited, alongside public investors Madhuri Madhusudan Kela and Invicta Continuum Fund I. Warrants are convertible into equity within 18 months, with a partial payment received and balance due on exercise. All allotted securities are subject to SEBI lock-in regulations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:36:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69833a6bf5a3f0ebac9a7841_1770208511705.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Metropolis Healthcare Posts 25.7% YoY Revenue Growth, Approves 3:1 Bonus Issue</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Metropolis-Healthcare-Posts-257percent-YoY-Revenue-Growth-Approves-31-Bonus-Issue/69833bd4f5a3f0ebac9a8ded</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Metropolis-Healthcare-Posts-257percent-YoY-Revenue-Growth-Approves-31-Bonus-Issue/69833bd4f5a3f0ebac9a8ded</guid><description>Metropolis Healthcare Limited reported a strong Q3 FY26 consolidated performance, with revenue from operations rising 25.7% year-on-year to ₹405.91 crore and Profit After Tax (PAT) surging 33.7% YoY to ₹42.08 crore. The Board approved a significant 3:1 bonus equity share issue. However, standalone results showed a sequential decline, with revenue down 5.9% and PAT down 31.2% QoQ, partly due to an exceptional item for Labour Codes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:34:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69833bd4f5a3f0ebac9a8dec_1770208461773.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KPIL Posts Stellar Q3 Results, Boosts Growth, Slashes Debt</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KPIL-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Results-Boosts-Growth-Slashes-Debt/69833b4ef5a3f0ebac9a8baf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KPIL-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Results-Boosts-Growth-Slashes-Debt/69833b4ef5a3f0ebac9a8baf</guid><description>Kalpataru Projects International (KPIL) reported robust Q3 FY26 standalone results, with revenue up 20% YoY to ₹5,788 Cr and PAT growing 34% YoY to ₹211 Cr. Consolidated PAT surged 72% YoY to ₹600 Cr for 9M FY26. The company showcased improved financial health, slashing consolidated net debt by 29% QoQ to ₹2,240 Cr and improving net working capital by 15 days. A strong order book of ₹63,287 Cr and positive management outlook underpin future growth prospects.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:32:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69833b4ef5a3f0ebac9a8bae_1770208279983.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NHPC Q3 Profit Jumps 39% On Deferrals, But Revenue Dips; Debt Rises</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/NHPC-Q3-Profit-Jumps-39percent-On-Deferrals-But-Revenue-Dips-Debt-Rises/69833a8cf5a3f0ebac9a78f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/NHPC-Q3-Profit-Jumps-39percent-On-Deferrals-But-Revenue-Dips-Debt-Rises/69833a8cf5a3f0ebac9a78f0</guid><description>NHPC reported a 38.7% YoY consolidated profit jump to ₹320.60 Cr in Q3 FY26, heavily boosted by ₹437.14 Cr in regulatory deferral account balances. However, revenue from operations fell 2.9% YoY to ₹2,220.73 Cr, with margins compressing significantly. The company declared a 14% interim dividend but saw its standalone Debt-to-Equity ratio climb to 1.05 and consolidated ratio to 1.17, indicating rising leverage. Nine-month performance showed growth, but quarterly trends raise concerns amid no forward guidance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:31:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69833a8cf5a3f0ebac9a78ef_1770208267759.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rane Madras Q3 Earnings Surge: Revenue Up 21%, PAT Jumps 76x</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rane-Madras-Q3-Earnings-Surge-Revenue-Up-21percent-PAT-Jumps-76x/6983283ff5a3f0ebac9a25bc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rane-Madras-Q3-Earnings-Surge-Revenue-Up-21percent-PAT-Jumps-76x/6983283ff5a3f0ebac9a25bc</guid><description>Rane (Madras) Limited posted robust Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated revenue climbing 21.3% YoY to ₹1,019.1 crore and Profit After Tax (PAT) skyrocketing 76 times to ₹30.5 crore from ₹0.4 crore in Q3 FY25. This surge was fuelled by strong sales across domestic, international, and aftermarket segments. The company also announced a ₹361.18 crore land sale in Velachery. Management did not provide forward-looking guidance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983283ff5a3f0ebac9a25bb_1770208093225.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Overhauls Forex Guarantees: Clarity, Compliance Drive New Era</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Overhauls-Forex-Guarantees-Clarity-Compliance-Drive-New-Era/69833ac1f5a3f0ebac9a892f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Overhauls-Forex-Guarantees-Clarity-Compliance-Drive-New-Era/69833ac1f5a3f0ebac9a892f</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India has launched the Foreign Exchange Management (Guarantees) Regulations, 2026, replacing the previous 2000 framework. This significant update moves from a fragmented, approval-centric system to a comprehensive, principle-based approach. Key changes include enhanced clarity on roles, expanded automatic permissions, and a structured reporting mechanism. The new regulations aim to boost regulatory certainty, streamline cross-border guarantee transactions, and foster an environment conducive to ease of doing business while maintaining oversight.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:29:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69833ac1f5a3f0ebac9a892e_1770208178703.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trent's Profit Surges 36% in Q3; Zudio Drives Expansion Amid Retail Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Trents-Profit-Surges-36percent-in-Q3-Zudio-Drives-Expansion-Amid-Retail-Boom/69833b24f5a3f0ebac9a8a9c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Trents-Profit-Surges-36percent-in-Q3-Zudio-Drives-Expansion-Amid-Retail-Boom/69833b24f5a3f0ebac9a8a9c</guid><description>Trent Ltd reported a 36% year-on-year increase in standalone net profit to ₹640 crore for Q3 FY26, alongside 16% revenue growth. The strong performance, driven by its Zudio and Westside brands, highlights the resilience of India's retail sector. While expansion continues, investor scrutiny will likely focus on margin sustainability and competitive positioning.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:29:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69833b24f5a3f0ebac9a8a9b_1770208145180.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bajaj Finserv: Underlying Strength Beats One-Time Charges</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bajaj-Finserv-Underlying-Strength-Beats-One-Time-Charges/69832740f5a3f0ebac9a2184</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bajaj-Finserv-Underlying-Strength-Beats-One-Time-Charges/69832740f5a3f0ebac9a2184</guid><description>Bajaj Finserv reported consolidated profit after tax of ₹2,229 crore for Q3 FY26, flat year-on-year due to ₹1,671 crore in accelerated ECL provisions and a ₹379 crore labor code charge. However, underlying performance was robust, with adjusted profit rising 32% to ₹2,936 crore. Total income grew 24% to ₹39,708 crore. The company also finalized its acquisition of Allianz SE's stake in its insurance subsidiaries. Bajaj Finance saw adjusted profit up 23% to ₹5,227 crore, Bajaj Housing Finance profit rose 21% to ₹665 crore, while Bajaj General Insurance's premium grew 12% and Bajaj Life Insurance showed strong VNB growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:28:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69832740f5a3f0ebac9a2183_1770208031071.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rane Madras Q3 Profit Skyrockets 7500%+ on 21% Revenue Jump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rane-Madras-Q3-Profit-Skyrockets-7500percent-on-21percent-Revenue-Jump/698327dbf5a3f0ebac9a23fd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rane-Madras-Q3-Profit-Skyrockets-7500percent-on-21percent-Revenue-Jump/698327dbf5a3f0ebac9a23fd</guid><description>Rane (Madras) Limited reported a stellar Q3 FY26 performance with consolidated revenue surging 21.3% year-on-year to ₹1,019.1 Crore. Profit After Tax (PAT) saw a remarkable jump of over 7500% to ₹30.5 Crore from ₹0.4 Crore in the prior year. EBITDA grew 36.8% YoY to ₹94.8 Crore, with margins improving by 106 basis points to 9.3% due to better fixed cost leverage. Growth was driven by robust demand across domestic OE, international, and aftermarket segments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:26:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698327dbf5a3f0ebac9a23fc_1770207893143.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Medanta Q3 PAT Down 33.5% On Rs 36.6 Cr Exceptional Costs Despite Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Medanta-Q3-PAT-Down-335percent-On-Rs-366-Cr-Exceptional-Costs-Despite-Revenue-Growth/698327a9f5a3f0ebac9a232a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Medanta-Q3-PAT-Down-335percent-On-Rs-366-Cr-Exceptional-Costs-Despite-Revenue-Growth/698327a9f5a3f0ebac9a232a</guid><description>Global Health Limited (Medanta) reported a 19.0% year-on-year increase in consolidated revenue to ₹112.10 crore for Q3 FY26. However, consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) declined sharply by 33.5% to ₹9.50 crore, significantly impacted by ₹36.60 crore in exceptional items related to new labour codes. Standalone PAT also saw a substantial YoY drop. For the nine months ended December 31, 2025, consolidated revenue grew 17.7% to ₹325.11 crore, with PAT rising 8.5% to ₹41.24 crore.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:22:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698327a9f5a3f0ebac9a2329_1770207766842.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India AlcoBev: FTA Catalyzes Premium Shift, USL Leads Amidst Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/India-AlcoBev-FTA-Catalyzes-Premium-Shift-USL-Leads-Amidst-Valuation-Concerns/69833a0af5a3f0ebac9a76cc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/India-AlcoBev-FTA-Catalyzes-Premium-Shift-USL-Leads-Amidst-Valuation-Concerns/69833a0af5a3f0ebac9a76cc</guid><description>India's alcoholic beverage industry is undergoing a significant shift from volume-driven to value-driven premiumisation. The India-UK Free Trade Agreement, set to reduce import duties on spirits, is a key catalyst, making luxury brands more accessible and benefiting domestic players. United Spirits (USL) is identified as a primary beneficiary, holding a dominant share in the high-margin premium segment. However, elevated valuations for leading companies like USL and Radico Khaitan warrant careful consideration of future growth prospects.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:22:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Subam Papers Raises ₹104 Crore via Preferential Issue at ₹152</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Subam-Papers-Raises-104-Crore-via-Preferential-Issue-at-152/698339cff5a3f0ebac9a7511</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Subam-Papers-Raises-104-Crore-via-Preferential-Issue-at-152/698339cff5a3f0ebac9a7511</guid><description>Subam Papers Limited announced the board's approval for a preferential issue, aiming to raise ₹1,04,38,14,400 (~₹104.38 crore). The company will allot 26,32,800 warrants and 42,34,400 equity shares at ₹152.00 each, including a ₹142.00 premium. Promoters like Thirupathi Balakumar and public investors including Madhuri Madhusudan Kela are among the allottees. The warrants, convertible into equity, have an 18-month tenure. An initial payment of ₹38 per warrant has been made, with the balance due upon exercise.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:21:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Emami Bets Big on Quick Commerce for FMCG Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Emami-Bets-Big-on-Quick-Commerce-for-FMCG-Growth/698339b9f5a3f0ebac9a74a0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Emami-Bets-Big-on-Quick-Commerce-for-FMCG-Growth/698339b9f5a3f0ebac9a74a0</guid><description>Emami Limited reported strong Q3FY26 results, with consolidated sales rising 10-11% and net profit by 14-15%. A key driver is the rapid expansion of its quick commerce channel, which doubled sales and now constitutes 20% of its e-commerce business. This strategic embrace of ultra-fast delivery is positioned to capture evolving consumer demand and potentially offer margin advantages, distinguishing it within the broader FMCG sector. The company's market capitalization stands at approximately ₹21,080 crore with a P/E ratio around 28x, appearing more attractive than many larger FMCG peers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:21:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Medanta Revenue Surges 19%, But Exceptional Items Dent Q3 Profit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Medanta-Revenue-Surges-19percent-But-Exceptional-Items-Dent-Q3-Profit/69832700f5a3f0ebac9a1ff7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Medanta-Revenue-Surges-19percent-But-Exceptional-Items-Dent-Q3-Profit/69832700f5a3f0ebac9a1ff7</guid><description>Global Health Limited (Medanta) reported a 19.0% YoY increase in consolidated revenue to ₹112.10 crore for Q3 FY26. However, consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) declined 33.5% to ₹9.50 crore, primarily due to ₹36.60 crore in exceptional items related to new labour codes. Standalone PAT also fell significantly by 39.1%. For the nine-month period, revenue grew 17.7% and PAT saw a modest 8.5% rise, indicating Q3's PAT dip was largely event-driven.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:20:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69832700f5a3f0ebac9a1ff6_1770207631809.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Cigarette Tax Hike Fuels Illicit Trade, Risks FCV Sector</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/India-Cigarette-Tax-Hike-Fuels-Illicit-Trade-Risks-FCV-Sector/69833981f5a3f0ebac9a7386</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/India-Cigarette-Tax-Hike-Fuels-Illicit-Trade-Risks-FCV-Sector/69833981f5a3f0ebac9a7386</guid><description>An escalated excise duty and health cess on cigarettes, effective February 1, are projected to significantly boost illicit trade and depress Flue-Cured Virginia (FCV) tobacco offtake by 20%. This policy shift exacerbates long-standing tax disparities, impacting millions in the agricultural sector and potentially widening the fiscal gap despite revenue aims.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:20:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Steel Q3 FY26: Margin Pressure Looms Despite Revenue Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-Q3-FY26-Margin-Pressure-Looms-Despite-Revenue-Outlook/698326e1f5a3f0ebac9a1f77</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-Q3-FY26-Margin-Pressure-Looms-Despite-Revenue-Outlook/698326e1f5a3f0ebac9a1f77</guid><description>Tata Steel is set to release its Q3 FY26 financial results on February 6th. While revenue growth is anticipated, driven by higher volumes and a robust Indian market outlook, profitability may face headwinds. Analysts are closely watching for margin pressures stemming from increased raw material costs and fluctuating steel prices, alongside the impact of new European Union regulations on its international operations. The company's stock has shown strong year-long performance, but the focus is shifting to operational efficiency and sustainable earnings.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:18:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698326e1f5a3f0ebac9a1f76_1770207475656.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KPIL's Q3 Revenue Surges 16%, But Margins Face Pressure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KPILs-Q3-Revenue-Surges-16percent-But-Margins-Face-Pressure/698338bbf5a3f0ebac9a7194</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/KPILs-Q3-Revenue-Surges-16percent-But-Margins-Face-Pressure/698338bbf5a3f0ebac9a7194</guid><description>Kalpataru Projects International (KPIL) posted robust Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated revenue jumping 16% YoY to ₹6,665 Cr and nine-month PAT soaring 72% YoY to ₹600 Cr. However, consolidated EBITDA margins contracted 70 bps YoY to 7.7% due to legacy project costs. The company's order book remains strong at ₹63,287 Cr, offering three years of visibility, and net debt saw a significant QoQ reduction.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:16:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>OCCL Posts Strong Q3 Growth, Eyes Global Opportunities Amidst Price Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/OCCL-Posts-Strong-Q3-Growth-Eyes-Global-Opportunities-Amidst-Price-Headwinds/698338a2f5a3f0ebac9a70e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/OCCL-Posts-Strong-Q3-Growth-Eyes-Global-Opportunities-Amidst-Price-Headwinds/698338a2f5a3f0ebac9a70e1</guid><description>OCCL Limited reported a robust third quarter for FY26, with revenue from operations growing 18.7% year-on-year to ₹114.17 Cr. EBITDA climbed 26% to ₹20.2 Cr, accompanied by an improved margin of 17.6%. Profit After Tax (PAT) surged 24.3% YoY to ₹6.53 Cr. For the nine months, PAT stood at ₹28.4 Cr. Management remains cautiously optimistic on exports and domestic demand, though high sulphur prices pose a margin challenge.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:16:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Unicorn India Ventures Closes ₹1,200 Cr Fund for Deeptech, AI, Semiconductors</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Unicorn-India-Ventures-Closes-1200-Cr-Fund-for-Deeptech-AI-Semiconductors/6983388df5a3f0ebac9a703a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Unicorn-India-Ventures-Closes-1200-Cr-Fund-for-Deeptech-AI-Semiconductors/6983388df5a3f0ebac9a703a</guid><description>Deeptech-focused Unicorn India Ventures has successfully closed its third fund at ₹1,200 crore, exceeding its initial ₹1,000 crore target. The fund will invest in semiconductors, spacetech, and AI infrastructure, areas identified for long-term structural growth. The firm plans to back approximately 20 startups with an average cheque size of ₹10-15 crore, and has already seen early success with several portfolio companies securing follow-on funding. Notably, 33% of the capital originates from international limited partners, marking a significant inflow into the Indian startup ecosystem.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:16:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Aadhar Housing Finance Posts 23% PAT Growth, Eyes ₹30K Crore AUM</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Aadhar-Housing-Finance-Posts-23percent-PAT-Growth-Eyes-30K-Crore-AUM/69832658f5a3f0ebac9a1da8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Aadhar-Housing-Finance-Posts-23percent-PAT-Growth-Eyes-30K-Crore-AUM/69832658f5a3f0ebac9a1da8</guid><description>Aadhar Housing Finance Limited reported robust 3Q FY'26 results, with Profit After Tax (PAT) surging 23% year-on-year to ₹294 crore and Assets Under Management (AUM) growing 20% to ₹28,790 crore. The company maintained strong asset quality with GNPA at 1.38% and reiterated confidence in its growth trajectory, targeting over ₹30,000 crore AUM by FY'26 end.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:16:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69832658f5a3f0ebac9a1da7_1770207323041.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RITES Sets Record Order Book, Q3 EBITDA Soars 19% YoY</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/RITES-Sets-Record-Order-Book-Q3-EBITDA-Soars-19percent-YoY/69833812f5a3f0ebac9a6ecc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/RITES-Sets-Record-Order-Book-Q3-EBITDA-Soars-19percent-YoY/69833812f5a3f0ebac9a6ecc</guid><description>RITES Limited reported robust Q3FY26 results, achieving its highest-ever order book at ₹9,262 crore. Consolidated EBITDA surged 18.9% year-on-year to ₹144 crore, while PAT grew 5.2% to ₹107 crore. The company added over ₹1,100 crore in new orders and recommended an interim dividend of ₹1.90 per share. Strategic MoUs with Botswana and APEDB signal future growth potential.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:14:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Asian Granito Profit Surges 292%; Vietnam Expansion Amidst IT Probe</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Asian-Granito-Profit-Surges-292percent-Vietnam-Expansion-Amidst-IT-Probe/69832617f5a3f0ebac9a1c60</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Asian-Granito-Profit-Surges-292percent-Vietnam-Expansion-Amidst-IT-Probe/69832617f5a3f0ebac9a1c60</guid><description>Asian Granito India Ltd. (AGL) announced a significant profit turnaround, with consolidated net profit surging to ₹1,854.19 Lakhs in Q3 FY26 from a loss of ₹406.53 Lakhs YoY. Consolidated revenue grew 15.80% to ₹42,393.49 Lakhs. The company also secured Board approval for a Wholly Owned Subsidiary in Vietnam for trading large format slabs, signaling strategic expansion. However, an ongoing Income Tax department search operation, initiated in May 2022, continues to be a point of note, with management asserting no material impact.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:13:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69832617f5a3f0ebac9a1c5f_1770207194336.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gujarat Terce Labs Q3: Profit Dives 27% Despite Margin Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Gujarat-Terce-Labs-Q3-Profit-Dives-27percent-Despite-Margin-Gains/698337c2f5a3f0ebac9a6d2c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Gujarat-Terce-Labs-Q3-Profit-Dives-27percent-Despite-Margin-Gains/698337c2f5a3f0ebac9a6d2c</guid><description>Gujarat Terce Laboratories reported a 3% YoY revenue decline to ₹1,229.35 lacs in Q3 FY26, driven by a strategic rationalization of low-margin businesses. Despite this, EBITDA rose 8% YoY to ₹124.86 lacs, with margins expanding to 10.16%. However, net profit (PAT) tumbled 27% YoY to ₹74.06 lacs, and cash profit saw a significant drop. Management emphasizes long-term, quality-led growth and brand strengthening, while the business remains self-funded.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:12:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>HORIBA Bets on India's Deep-Tech Talent for Diamond Semiconductor Edge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/HORIBA-Bets-on-Indias-Deep-Tech-Talent-for-Diamond-Semiconductor-Edge/698337a2f5a3f0ebac9a6c4a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/HORIBA-Bets-on-Indias-Deep-Tech-Talent-for-Diamond-Semiconductor-Edge/698337a2f5a3f0ebac9a6c4a</guid><description>HORIBA India finalized the acquisition of Pristine Deeptech Private Limited, integrating the R&amp;D startup to forge a dedicated advanced-materials research hub. This strategic move bolsters HORIBA's capabilities in lab-grown diamond technologies for semiconductor and quantum applications. The combined expertise aims to accelerate the development of diamond-based components, enhancing HORIBA's position in the evolving high-tech materials sector and leveraging India's burgeoning innovation ecosystem.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:12:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Rane Madras Revenue Up 21%, PAT Soars on Margin Gains; Sells Land for ₹361 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Rane-Madras-Revenue-Up-21percent-PAT-Soars-on-Margin-Gains-Sells-Land-for-361-Cr/698325f0f5a3f0ebac9a1b5c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Rane-Madras-Revenue-Up-21percent-PAT-Soars-on-Margin-Gains-Sells-Land-for-361-Cr/698325f0f5a3f0ebac9a1b5c</guid><description>Rane (Madras) Limited reported a robust Q3 FY26, with revenue climbing 21.3% YoY to ₹1,019.1 Cr. Profit After Tax (PAT) surged an extraordinary 7,645.3% to ₹30.5 Cr, driven by a low base and prior-year tax adjustments. EBITDA grew 36.8% to ₹94.8 Cr, and EBITDA margins improved by 106 bps to 9.3%. The company also announced the sale of 3.48 acres of land for ₹361.18 Cr.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:12:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698325f0f5a3f0ebac9a1b5b_1770207075299.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mitsu Chem Plast Surges on Profit Growth, Targets INR 1000 Cr Revenue by FY28</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Mitsu-Chem-Plast-Surges-on-Profit-Growth-Targets-INR-1000-Cr-Revenue-by-FY28/6983376cf5a3f0ebac9a6b3f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Mitsu-Chem-Plast-Surges-on-Profit-Growth-Targets-INR-1000-Cr-Revenue-by-FY28/6983376cf5a3f0ebac9a6b3f</guid><description>Mitsu Chem Plast reported a stellar Q3 FY26, with net profit rocketing 217% year-on-year to INR 4.71 Cr, driven by a 73% EBITDA surge and expanding margins. The company reaffirmed its ambitious INR 1,000 Cr revenue target by FY28, bolstered by ongoing capacity expansions, a strategic shift towards higher-margin niche products, and anticipated growth in export markets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:11:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank of Baroda Profit Up 4.5%, Advances Surge 14.7% on Strong Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bank-of-Baroda-Profit-Up-45percent-Advances-Surge-147percent-on-Strong-Demand/6983374af5a3f0ebac9a6a58</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bank-of-Baroda-Profit-Up-45percent-Advances-Surge-147percent-on-Strong-Demand/6983374af5a3f0ebac9a6a58</guid><description>Bank of Baroda reported a Q3 net profit of ₹5,055 crore, a 4.5% year-on-year increase. The bank saw robust growth in advances (14.7% YoY) and deposits (10.3% YoY), driven by strong performance in Retail, Agriculture, and MSME segments. Asset quality remained robust with declining NPAs. Management is optimistic about exceeding credit growth targets and has revised credit cost guidance downwards, projecting healthy ROE and ROA.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:10:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Hero MotoCorp Q3: Growth Amidst Sector Boom, Margin Watch</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hero-MotoCorp-Q3-Growth-Amidst-Sector-Boom-Margin-Watch/6983372af5a3f0ebac9a697d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hero-MotoCorp-Q3-Growth-Amidst-Sector-Boom-Margin-Watch/6983372af5a3f0ebac9a697d</guid><description>Hero MotoCorp is poised to release its Q3 FY26 financial results following a record Q2. Analysts anticipate sustained revenue and profit growth, driven by strong sector demand and potential price increases. Key to investor scrutiny will be margin performance against competitive pressures and the impact of the company's premiumization strategy. Performance will be benchmarked against stellar results from peers like Bajaj Auto and TVS Motor.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:10:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>SCI Secures ₹199 Cr Tax Refund Post Favorable ITAT Ruling</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/SCI-Secures-199-Cr-Tax-Refund-Post-Favorable-ITAT-Ruling/6983255ff5a3f0ebac9a1957</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/SCI-Secures-199-Cr-Tax-Refund-Post-Favorable-ITAT-Ruling/6983255ff5a3f0ebac9a1957</guid><description>The Shipping Corporation of India Limited (SCI) announced receiving a ₹199.76 crore income tax refund, inclusive of ₹85.75 crore interest. This follows a favorable ruling by the Income Tax Appellate Tribunal (ITAT) for the financial year 2009-10, positively impacting SCI's liquidity and financial health.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:10:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983255ff5a3f0ebac9a1956_1770206955145.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Infra Industries Posts 99% Revenue Jump, But Trading Remains Suspended Amidst Losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Infra-Industries-Posts-99percent-Revenue-Jump-But-Trading-Remains-Suspended-Amidst-Losses/698336d1f5a3f0ebac9a684a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Infra-Industries-Posts-99percent-Revenue-Jump-But-Trading-Remains-Suspended-Amidst-Losses/698336d1f5a3f0ebac9a684a</guid><description>Infra Industries Limited reported a sharp 99.6% year-over-year revenue increase to ₹52.09 Cr in Q3 FY26. Despite this growth, the company continued to post net losses, though the Q3 loss narrowed to ₹3.33 Cr from ₹7.98 Cr. However, for the nine-month period, net losses widened to ₹182.13 Cr, and the company's 'Other Equity' has turned negative. Crucially, trading in Infra Industries shares remains suspended due to procedural reasons.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:08:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>V-Guard Q3 Revenue Surges 10.6%, But Margins Squeeze on Input Costs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/V-Guard-Q3-Revenue-Surges-106percent-But-Margins-Squeeze-on-Input-Costs/698336b8f5a3f0ebac9a67bd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/V-Guard-Q3-Revenue-Surges-106percent-But-Margins-Squeeze-on-Input-Costs/698336b8f5a3f0ebac9a67bd</guid><description>V-Guard Industries posted a 10.6% year-on-year revenue growth to INR 1,404 crore in Q3 FY26, primarily fueled by its Electricals segment. However, gross margins contracted by 100 basis points due to a mixed product portfolio, leading to a 5.2% YoY decline in Profit After Tax to INR 57 crore, excluding an exceptional item of INR 22.11 crore. Underlying PAT grew by a robust 22% YoY. Management anticipates margin recovery in FY27, driven by commodity price stabilization and new product traction, including BLDC fans and the impending commercialization of Gegadyne's battery technology.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:08:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Buy vs. Rent: Strategic Wealth Equation Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/India-Buy-vs-Rent-Strategic-Wealth-Equation-Shifts/6983362bf5a3f0ebac9a64a1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/India-Buy-vs-Rent-Strategic-Wealth-Equation-Shifts/6983362bf5a3f0ebac9a64a1</guid><description>Prospective Indian homebuyers face a crucial buy-or-rent decision. Owning offers asset appreciation, but renting frees capital for investment, potentially yielding higher financial returns. Metro areas present lower rental yields versus higher property appreciation, while Tier-2 cities offer better yield dynamics. Navigating this choice requires assessing hidden ownership costs against rental savings, crucial for long-term wealth creation strategy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:07:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Emami Q3 Profit Surges 14.5%, Declares ₹6 Dividend Amid Mixed Nine-Month Show</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Emami-Q3-Profit-Surges-145percent-Declares-6-Dividend-Amid-Mixed-Nine-Month-Show/6983254ff5a3f0ebac9a18be</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Emami-Q3-Profit-Surges-145percent-Declares-6-Dividend-Amid-Mixed-Nine-Month-Show/6983254ff5a3f0ebac9a18be</guid><description>Emami Limited reported robust Q3 FY2026 results, with consolidated revenue climbing 10.70% YoY to ₹1,151.8 Cr and Profit After Tax (PAT) soaring 14.51% YoY to ₹319.5 Cr. The company declared a ₹6 interim dividend. However, the nine-month performance showed marginal revenue growth of 0.29% and a slight PAT dip of 1.32%, highlighting a contrasting trend. The results include an exceptional item of ₹1,015 lacs related to New Labour Codes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:07:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6983254ff5a3f0ebac9a18bd_1770206828039.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Stylam Industries inks Japan JV, eyes Rs 1600 Cr revenue post-expansion.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Stylam-Industries-inks-Japan-JV-eyes-Rs-1600-Cr-revenue-post-expansion/69832487f5a3f0ebac9a16da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Stylam-Industries-inks-Japan-JV-eyes-Rs-1600-Cr-revenue-post-expansion/69832487f5a3f0ebac9a16da</guid><description>Stylam Industries reported Q3 FY26 revenue up 8.18% YoY to Rs 271 Cr, with PAT margins climbing to 16.97% aided by reduced forward contract losses. A landmark strategic partnership with Japan's Aica Kogyo and a Rs 320 Cr capacity expansion set to commission by March 2026 are key growth drivers. Management guides for Rs 1500-1600 Cr revenue in FY27, targeting enhanced domestic market share and export penetration.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69832487f5a3f0ebac9a16d9_1770206721662.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>OCCL Posts Strong Q3 Growth Amidst Margin Pressures</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/OCCL-Posts-Strong-Q3-Growth-Amidst-Margin-Pressures/698335f9f5a3f0ebac9a637e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/OCCL-Posts-Strong-Q3-Growth-Amidst-Margin-Pressures/698335f9f5a3f0ebac9a637e</guid><description>OCCL Limited reported an 18.7% YoY increase in Q3 FY26 revenue to ₹114.6 Cr and a 24.3% YoY rise in PAT to ₹6.5 Cr. For the nine months ended December 31, 2025, revenue surged 79.1% YoY to ₹358.7 Cr, with PAT up 123% YoY to ₹28.4 Cr. However, direct comparison for the 9-month period is impacted by a demerger effective July 1, 2024. Management highlighted strong domestic demand driven by the auto sector and positive export outlook from trade agreements, but noted high sulphur prices as a margin challenge.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:05:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Trent Q3 Earnings Soar Driven By Fashion, Cons. PAT Growth Moderates</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Trent-Q3-Earnings-Soar-Driven-By-Fashion-Cons-PAT-Growth-Moderates/698335d0f5a3f0ebac9a6280</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Trent-Q3-Earnings-Soar-Driven-By-Fashion-Cons-PAT-Growth-Moderates/698335d0f5a3f0ebac9a6280</guid><description>Trent Limited reported stellar Q3 FY26 results driven by its fashion retail segments. Standalone revenue jumped 16% YoY to ₹5,259 Cr, with PAT surging 41% to ₹660 Cr. Consolidated revenue grew 15% to ₹5,345 Cr, but PAT growth was a more modest 7% to ₹531 Cr. The company sees a positive outlook for fashion, while the Star business faces competitive pressures and slower expansion.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:04:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>TeamLease Profit Soars on Margin Gains Amid Workforce Cuts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TeamLease-Profit-Soars-on-Margin-Gains-Amid-Workforce-Cuts/69832461f5a3f0ebac9a1605</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TeamLease-Profit-Soars-on-Margin-Gains-Amid-Workforce-Cuts/69832461f5a3f0ebac9a1605</guid><description>TeamLease Services reported a 46.8% year-on-year net profit increase to ₹41.7 crore for Q3 FY26, fueled by margin expansion to 1.4% and operational leverage. Despite a modest 3% revenue growth to ₹3,013 crore, the company reduced its associate base by approximately 27,000. Strong performance in Specialised Staffing, driven by global capability centres, offset declines in General Staffing due to BFSI insourcing. The company received a ₹106.1 crore tax refund, bolstering its net free cash to ₹430 crore. Shares surged over 8% post-announcement before settling higher.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:03:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69832461f5a3f0ebac9a1604_1770206597378.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ellenbarrie Q3 Profit Falls Sequentially on Lower Argon, Eyes Recovery</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ellenbarrie-Q3-Profit-Falls-Sequentially-on-Lower-Argon-Eyes-Recovery/69833564f5a3f0ebac9a6084</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ellenbarrie-Q3-Profit-Falls-Sequentially-on-Lower-Argon-Eyes-Recovery/69833564f5a3f0ebac9a6084</guid><description>Ellenbarrie Industrial Gases reported Q3 FY26 with Revenue at ₹813 million and PAT at ₹261 million. While YoY growth was healthy, the quarter saw a sequential revenue decline of 9% and EBITDA drop of 25%, with margins compressing to 31% from 38%. This was driven by lower Argon realisations and elevated one-off costs. Management expressed optimism, stating the "worst is over," and highlighted new plant commissioning and future expansions, targeting a 20-25% revenue CAGR and a long-term EBITDA margin of around 40%.</description><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:02:44 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>