<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 01:47:55 +0000</pubDate><item><title>AI Capex Tide Shifts Retail Valuation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Capex-Tide-Shifts-Retail-Valuation/699273e52e6a0b8ae17c757f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Capex-Tide-Shifts-Retail-Valuation/699273e52e6a0b8ae17c757f</guid><description>Global markets show consolidation with divergent economic signals from Japan and the US. Surging AI capital expenditures and reduced share buybacks are reshaping corporate investment, driving a rotation into defensive sectors. Walmart, having crossed the $1 trillion market capitalization threshold, is being evaluated against peers like Target, which trades at a significantly lower valuation multiple, prompting an analysis of future growth drivers and shareholder return strategies in a rapidly evolving corporate investment landscape.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 01:33:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699273e52e6a0b8ae17c757e_1771205732227.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold's Bubble Warning: China's Speculation Sparks Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Golds-Bubble-Warning-Chinas-Speculation-Sparks-Volatility/699273642e6a0b8ae17c74ec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Golds-Bubble-Warning-Chinas-Speculation-Sparks-Volatility/699273642e6a0b8ae17c74ec</guid><description>Gold experienced extreme volatility following record highs, driven largely by speculative trading in China. Regulatory bodies are intervening by raising margin requirements to curb excessive leverage. This surge coincides with China's strategic move to reduce U.S. Treasury holdings and increase gold reserves, signaling a broader de-dollarization effort. Analysts warn of a potential speculative bubble, questioning gold's traditional safe-haven status amidst these shifting dynamics.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 01:31:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699273642e6a0b8ae17c74eb_1771205605213.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Oil Prices Caught: Geopolitics vs. Supply Glut</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Oil-Prices-Caught-Geopolitics-vs-Supply-Glut/6992735f2e6a0b8ae17c74d5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Oil-Prices-Caught-Geopolitics-vs-Supply-Glut/6992735f2e6a0b8ae17c74d5</guid><description>Oil prices remain stable as escalating US-Iran tensions and the ongoing Ukraine conflict inject geopolitical premiums, counterbalanced by a persistent global supply surplus. The International Energy Agency forecasts a significant oversupply in 2026, creating a complex market equilibrium. Traders await OPEC+'s March 1 decision on potential April output adjustments, while macroeconomic factors like US dollar strength and AI-driven demand shifts add further layers to the outlook.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 01:31:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992735f2e6a0b8ae17c74d4_1771205605108.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Solar Ambitions Stymied by Bank Hesitation, Utility Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Indias-Solar-Ambitions-Stymied-by-Bank-Hesitation-Utility-Fears/699271b82e6a0b8ae17c73da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Indias-Solar-Ambitions-Stymied-by-Bank-Hesitation-Utility-Fears/699271b82e6a0b8ae17c73da</guid><description>India's flagship rooftop solar initiative, PM Surya Ghar, is significantly underperforming against its targets. Despite substantial subsidies, banks are hesitant to lend, citing documentation issues and requiring collateral, while state utilities resist promoting the scheme due to potential revenue loss. These financial and structural hurdles are slowing installations, jeopardizing India's clean energy capacity goals and potentially prolonging its dependence on coal power.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 01:24:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699271b82e6a0b8ae17c73d9_1771205213843.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Power Crunch: C2i Semiconductors Targets Efficiency</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Power-Crunch-C2i-Semiconductors-Targets-Efficiency/69926f322e6a0b8ae17c72f2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Power-Crunch-C2i-Semiconductors-Targets-Efficiency/69926f322e6a0b8ae17c72f2</guid><description>Indian startup C2i Semiconductors has raised $15 million to develop integrated power solutions for AI data centers, targeting the 15-20% energy waste in power conversion. With data center electricity demand soaring, C2i's 'grid-to-GPU' system aims to improve efficiency and reduce operational costs. This funding highlights investor confidence in India's growing semiconductor ecosystem and C2i's potential to disrupt established power management markets dominated by large players.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 01:13:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69926f322e6a0b8ae17c72f1.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fractal Analytics IPO Debuts Amid AI Sector Skepticism</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Fractal-Analytics-IPO-Debuts-Amid-AI-Sector-Skepticism/69926dbe2e6a0b8ae17c724a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Fractal-Analytics-IPO-Debuts-Amid-AI-Sector-Skepticism/69926dbe2e6a0b8ae17c724a</guid><description>Fractal Analytics, a pure-play AI firm, debuts on February 16 with grey market signals indicating a potential discount. The ₹2,834 crore IPO, subscribed 2.66 times, enters a market wary of AI sector valuations and the disruptive potential of advanced AI. Management had previously reduced the issue size, signaling prudence amidst this evolving landscape. Investors are advised a balanced approach, weighing the company's growth prospects against elevated risks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 01:07:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69926dbe2e6a0b8ae17c7249_1771204153838.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>High Yields vs. Structural Risk: MPS, Alldigi Stock Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/High-Yields-vs-Structural-Risk-MPS-Alldigi-Stock-Woes/69926bd72e6a0b8ae17c717e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/High-Yields-vs-Structural-Risk-MPS-Alldigi-Stock-Woes/69926bd72e6a0b8ae17c717e</guid><description>MPS Ltd and Alldigi Tech Ltd, known for their high dividend yields and strong capital efficiency, are experiencing sharp stock price corrections. MPS faces a structural reset due to margin compression and a director resignation, while Alldigi contends with a substantial GST demand and increased global revenue reliance. Despite robust ROCE and near debt-free status for MPS, and a strong yield for Alldigi, these underlying issues are overshadowing income generation. The market's focus shifts from dividends to the resolution of these critical business challenges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 00:59:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69926bd72e6a0b8ae17c717d_1771203737704.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Blackstone Backs Neysa's $1.2B India AI Infrastructure Play</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Blackstone-Backs-Neysas-12B-India-AI-Infrastructure-Play/699268212e6a0b8ae17c7036</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Blackstone-Backs-Neysas-12B-India-AI-Infrastructure-Play/699268212e6a0b8ae17c7036</guid><description>AI cloud provider Neysa has secured $1.2 billion in a deal led by Blackstone, combining $600 million in equity with plans for $600 million in debt financing. The capital infusion is earmarked for deploying over 20,000 GPUs in India. This strategic move aims to bolster the nation's sovereign compute capabilities and AI ecosystem, aligning with government initiatives and favorable policy environments, positioning Neysa as a key infrastructure player in India's burgeoning AI sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 00:43:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699268212e6a0b8ae17c7035_1771202746844.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KKR Bets Big on India Amid Diversification Drive</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/KKR-Bets-Big-on-India-Amid-Diversification-Drive/6992663e2e6a0b8ae17c6f21</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/KKR-Bets-Big-on-India-Amid-Diversification-Drive/6992663e2e6a0b8ae17c6f21</guid><description>KKR co-founder Henry Kravis announced plans to deploy up to $20 billion in India over the next decade, driven by robust economic growth and evolving entrepreneurial standards. This initiative aligns with KKR's broader strategic shift towards a diversified, multi-asset class platform, encompassing private equity, infrastructure, and credit, with a market cap of $70 billion. The firm emphasizes a disciplined approach to AI infrastructure ("picks and shovels"), navigating public market scrutiny on private credit by leveraging its extensive AUM of approximately $900 billion and a long-term value creation focus.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 00:35:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992663e2e6a0b8ae17c6f20_1771202245228.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>KKR Bets Big on India: Private Credit Fuels Global Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/KKR-Bets-Big-on-India-Private-Credit-Fuels-Global-Expansion/6992663c2e6a0b8ae17c6f0a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/KKR-Bets-Big-on-India-Private-Credit-Fuels-Global-Expansion/6992663c2e6a0b8ae17c6f0a</guid><description>KKR is strategically deepening its commitment to India, a key growth market, by substantially increasing private credit investments. This move leverages India's robust economic expansion and the escalating demand for alternative financing, particularly for small and medium-sized enterprises. The firm's enhanced focus on infrastructure and private credit underscores its strategy to capture opportunities within India's evolving financial landscape. This expansion diversifies KKR's global portfolio while addressing critical financing gaps.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 00:35:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992663c2e6a0b8ae17c6f09_1771202239350.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Fears Rock IT; Market Resilience Emerges Amidst Divergence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Fears-Rock-IT-Market-Resilience-Emerges-Amidst-Divergence/6992606e2e6a0b8ae17c6da3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Fears-Rock-IT-Market-Resilience-Emerges-Amidst-Divergence/6992606e2e6a0b8ae17c6da3</guid><description>The Indian market faces a stark divergence as the Information Technology sector experiences a significant downturn, driven by advancements in Artificial Intelligence that challenge traditional business models. The Nifty IT Index dropped sharply, invalidating recent gains. However, this sector-specific sell-off masks underlying strength in cyclical sectors like Auto, Metals, and Consumer Durables, which remain above key technical averages. Healthcare stocks show robust reversal signals. Foreign Institutional Investors (FIIs) exhibit a cautious yet nuanced stance, with increased shorts tempered by substantial long position additions. PSU Banks present a mixed picture, with profit-taking evident in some while others maintain momentum.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 00:10:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6992606e2e6a0b8ae17c6da2_1771200788731.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PFRDA Navigates State OPS Defiance, Eyes NPS Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/PFRDA-Navigates-State-OPS-Defiance-Eyes-NPS-Growth/69925faf2e6a0b8ae17c6cf0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/PFRDA-Navigates-State-OPS-Defiance-Eyes-NPS-Growth/69925faf2e6a0b8ae17c6cf0</guid><description>Pension Fund Regulatory and Development Authority (PFRDA) Chairperson Sivasubramanian Ramann has reiterated that the Old Pension Scheme (OPS) is fiscally unsustainable for state governments, even as some states continue to explore its reintroduction. Ramann clarified that while states may offer OPS, contributions to the National Pension Scheme (NPS) must not cease, emphasizing NPS as a crucial funded account. PFRDA is actively pursuing strategies to expand NPS subscriber base and AUM, including product innovation and targeted outreach, aiming for universal pension coverage amidst a dynamic regulatory and fiscal environment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 00:07:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69925faf2e6a0b8ae17c6cef_1771200561117.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Fuel Demand Surges: Import Risks Escalate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Fuel-Demand-Surges-Import-Risks-Escalate/69925f3b2e6a0b8ae17c6c8f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Fuel-Demand-Surges-Import-Risks-Escalate/69925f3b2e6a0b8ae17c6c8f</guid><description>India's refined petroleum product consumption is projected to hit a record 250.8 million tonnes in FY27, a 2.8% rise fueled by demand across sectors like transportation and aviation. This trajectory positions India as a primary driver of global oil demand growth. However, the nation's reliance on imports, exceeding 88%, heightens vulnerability to price volatility and supply disruptions, creating a dual challenge of meeting demand while managing external economic risks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 00:05:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69925f3b2e6a0b8ae17c6c8e_1771200474477.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>