<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:51:48 +0000</pubDate><item><title>ASMS Ventures into HealthTech, But Valuation &amp; Legacy Woes Linger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/ASMS-Ventures-into-HealthTech-But-Valuation-and-Legacy-Woes-Linger/69a52f223d2913aa7c2235c1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/ASMS-Ventures-into-HealthTech-But-Valuation-and-Legacy-Woes-Linger/69a52f223d2913aa7c2235c1</guid><description>Avio Smart Market Stack Limited (ASMS) has entered a strategic partnership with Huwel Lifesciences, acquiring a minority stake to expand into the promising tuberculosis diagnostics market. This diversification leverages Huwel's cost-effective Quantiplus® MTB FAST platform. However, ASMS shares dipped amidst concerns over its high valuation, the historical volatility of its legacy operations, and a lack of analyst coverage, signaling market caution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:33:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a52f223d2913aa7c2235c0_1772433321176.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fino Payments Bank Uploads Investor Call Audio Recording</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Fino-Payments-Bank-Uploads-Investor-Call-Audio-Recording/69a52ea93d2913aa7c2234e0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Fino-Payments-Bank-Uploads-Investor-Call-Audio-Recording/69a52ea93d2913aa7c2234e0</guid><description>Fino Payments Bank has released the audio recording of its Group Investor call held on March 02, 2026. This move enhances transparency for investors navigating recent developments, including the ongoing GST investigation impacting the company. Access to such calls is crucial for understanding management's perspective on operational continuity and regulatory challenges.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:31:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a52ea93d2913aa7c2234df_1772433168827.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Strait of Hormuz Tensions Hit Indian Ports: Stocks Fluctuate Amid Trade Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Strait-of-Hormuz-Tensions-Hit-Indian-Ports-Stocks-Fluctuate-Amid-Trade-Risk/69a52e373d2913aa7c22340a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Strait-of-Hormuz-Tensions-Hit-Indian-Ports-Stocks-Fluctuate-Amid-Trade-Risk/69a52e373d2913aa7c22340a</guid><description>Escalating Middle East conflict has triggered disruptions in key global shipping lanes, including the Strait of Hormuz and Bab el-Mandab. This poses significant risks to India's substantial export-import trade, which relies heavily on these routes for approximately 31% of its cargo exposure to the MENA region. Indian port operators and logistics firms, including Adani Ports, JSW Infrastructure, GMR Airports, Aegis Logistics, and Gujarat Pipavav Port, experienced stock price volatility on March 2, 2026, reflecting heightened investor caution over potential impacts on freight rates, transit times, and cargo volumes. The event also amplifies concerns over India's energy import security and inflation, given the nation's reliance on Middle Eastern oil and LNG.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:29:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a52e363d2913aa7c223409_1772433346245.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Wood's $10K Gold Target: Extreme Bullishness Meets Analyst Consensus</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Woods-10K-Gold-Target-Extreme-Bullishness-Meets-Analyst-Consensus/69a52e343d2913aa7c2233f1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Woods-10K-Gold-Target-Extreme-Bullishness-Meets-Analyst-Consensus/69a52e343d2913aa7c2233f1</guid><description>Christopher Wood of Jefferies projects an extraordinary $10,000 per ounce for gold, a target far exceeding current market levels and the projections of many peers. His ambitious forecast, rooted in gold's role as a premier long-term hedge, overlooks potential near-term profit-taking. While other analysts remain bullish, their targets fall considerably short of Wood's extreme outlook. This divergence highlights the speculative fervor surrounding gold amidst persistent inflation and geopolitical uncertainty.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:29:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a52e343d2913aa7c2233f0_1772433127490.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Edelweiss Flexi Cap Fund: Alpha Chasing Amidst Market Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Edelweiss-Flexi-Cap-Fund-Alpha-Chasing-Amidst-Market-Headwinds/69a52e333d2913aa7c2233da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Edelweiss-Flexi-Cap-Fund-Alpha-Chasing-Amidst-Market-Headwinds/69a52e333d2913aa7c2233da</guid><description>Edelweiss Mutual Fund’s Flexi Cap Fund has delivered a robust CAGR of 13.19% since inception. Recent performance metrics show 1-year returns of 18.55%, 3-year at 21.44%, and 5-year at 17.77%, outperforming the NIFTY 500 TRI benchmark. However, the fund's expense ratio of 1.89% for regular plans, significant concentration in banking, and tactical portfolio shifts warrant caution as the market pivots towards sector-specific opportunities and passive investment efficiency.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:29:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a52e333d2913aa7c2233d9_1772433108809.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-France Tax Treaty Overhaul: Capital Gains &amp; Dividend Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-France-Tax-Treaty-Overhaul-Capital-Gains-and-Dividend-Shifts/69a52cf83d2913aa7c223214</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-France-Tax-Treaty-Overhaul-Capital-Gains-and-Dividend-Shifts/69a52cf83d2913aa7c223214</guid><description>India and France have significantly updated their 1992 Double Taxation Avoidance Convention (DTAC). Effective from February 23, 2026, the protocol grants India broader powers to tax capital gains on share sales by French entities, removes the Most-Favoured-Nation (MFN) clause, and introduces a split dividend tax structure: 5% for stakes of 10% or more and 15% for smaller holdings. This recalibration signals India's ongoing strategy to bolster source-based taxation and curb treaty abuse.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:23:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a52cf83d2913aa7c223213_1772432714733.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Asia Braces for Inflation Shock as Oil Surges Amid Middle East Conflict</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Asia-Braces-for-Inflation-Shock-as-Oil-Surges-Amid-Middle-East-Conflict/69a52c733d2913aa7c223138</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Asia-Braces-for-Inflation-Shock-as-Oil-Surges-Amid-Middle-East-Conflict/69a52c733d2913aa7c223138</guid><description>Heightened Middle East hostilities, including the reported death of Iran's Supreme Leader and attacks on commercial shipping, have triggered a sharp surge in global oil prices, with Brent crude breaching $78 per barrel. Asian equity markets reacted negatively, while gold and the US dollar climbed as investors sought safe havens. Advanced Asian economies face significant inflation risks due to their heavy reliance on imported energy and critical trade route disruptions, forcing central banks to reconsider interest rate policies. Emerging markets, meanwhile, are exposed to renewed debt pressures from rising commodity costs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:21:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a52c733d2913aa7c223137_1772432660158.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IIFL Targets Wealth Growth Amid Fierce Talent War</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IIFL-Targets-Wealth-Growth-Amid-Fierce-Talent-War/69a52bdd3d2913aa7c223041</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IIFL-Targets-Wealth-Growth-Amid-Fierce-Talent-War/69a52bdd3d2913aa7c223041</guid><description>Nirmal Jain's IIFL Group aims to dramatically expand its wealth management division, targeting an 80-100% increase in its ₹600 billion ($6.6 billion) asset book and tripling its advisor force within two years. This ambitious growth strategy hinges on navigating India's rapidly expanding high-net-worth individual (HNWI) population. However, the plan faces significant headwinds from a hyper-competitive talent market, escalating compensation demands, and operational scrutiny faced by related entities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:19:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a52bdd3d2913aa7c223040_1772432546132.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mapmy India Completes ₹2 Cr Investment in Prashant Survey, Gains 20% Profit Share</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mapmy-India-Completes-2-Cr-Investment-in-Prashant-Survey-Gains-20percent-Profit-Share/69a52bdb3d2913aa7c223025</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mapmy-India-Completes-2-Cr-Investment-in-Prashant-Survey-Gains-20percent-Profit-Share/69a52bdb3d2913aa7c223025</guid><description>C.E. Info Systems Limited (Mapmy India) has finalized its strategic investment of ₹2 crore into Prashant Advanced Survey LLP. This move grants the company a 20% share in the LLP's profits, bolstering its presence in the advanced surveying and geospatial mapping sector. The investment follows a prior disclosure and marks a significant step in Mapmy India's diversification strategy beyond core mapping services.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:19:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a52bdb3d2913aa7c223024_1772432481075.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Chatha Foods Targets ₹550 Cr Revenue via Expansion, New Facilities</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Chatha-Foods-Targets-550-Cr-Revenue-via-Expansion-New-Facilities/69a52bd83d2913aa7c22300f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Chatha-Foods-Targets-550-Cr-Revenue-via-Expansion-New-Facilities/69a52bd83d2913aa7c22300f</guid><description>Chatha Foods outlined an ambitious expansion strategy, projecting revenue to surge from ₹325 Cr in the next fiscal year to over ₹550 Cr by FY29. The company plans significant manufacturing capacity increases, enhanced product offerings across vegetarian and non-vegetarian segments, and is pursuing key certifications like BRC and FDA to fuel growth and tap export markets. Achieving these targets hinges on successful new facility commissioning and onboarding major QSR clients.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:19:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a52bd83d2913aa7c22300e_1772432695181.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GTL Ltd: Bombay HC Quashes CBI FIR; Ends Investigation Over Alleged Bank Fraud</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GTL-Ltd-Bombay-HC-Quashes-CBI-FIR-Ends-Investigation-Over-Alleged-Bank-Fraud/69a528933d2913aa7c222d93</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GTL-Ltd-Bombay-HC-Quashes-CBI-FIR-Ends-Investigation-Over-Alleged-Bank-Fraud/69a528933d2913aa7c222d93</guid><description>GTL Limited has received a significant legal reprieve as the Bombay High Court quashed a Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI) First Information Report (FIR) dated January 21, 2023. The FIR alleged bank fraud exceeding ₹4,000 crore. The court found no offense made out warranting the continuation of the investigation, providing substantial relief to the company.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:05:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a528933d2913aa7c222d92_1772431615783.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tech Mahindra, Orange Business Eye 5-Year Digital Transformation Partnership</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tech-Mahindra-Orange-Business-Eye-5-Year-Digital-Transformation-Partnership/69a528903d2913aa7c222d7d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tech-Mahindra-Orange-Business-Eye-5-Year-Digital-Transformation-Partnership/69a528903d2913aa7c222d7d</guid><description>Tech Mahindra and Orange Business are in exclusive negotiations for a 5-year global strategic partnership aimed at accelerating enterprise digital transformation. The deal includes outsourcing of certain support functions from Orange Business to Tech Mahindra, focusing on AI and automation. Specific sensitive segments and the French market are excluded.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:05:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a528903d2913aa7c222d7c_1772431605720.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Juniper Hotels Q3 FY26 Profit ₹65 Cr; Policy Updates &amp; Fire Loss Addressed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Juniper-Hotels-Q3-FY26-Profit-65-Cr-Policy-Updates-and-Fire-Loss-Addressed/69a528183d2913aa7c222cd4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Juniper-Hotels-Q3-FY26-Profit-65-Cr-Policy-Updates-and-Fire-Loss-Addressed/69a528183d2913aa7c222cd4</guid><description>Juniper Hotels reported a Q3 FY26 consolidated profit of ₹65.42 crore on revenue of ₹295.13 crore. The company also updated its SEBI-related policies and disclosed a ₹10.14 crore loss from a Bangalore property fire, expecting insurance recovery. The impact of new labour codes is also being assessed.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 06:03:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a528183d2913aa7c222cd3_1772431725478.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MCX Surges on Geopolitical Fears; Valuation Concerns Emerge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/MCX-Surges-on-Geopolitical-Fears-Valuation-Concerns-Emerge/69a5273a3d2913aa7c222b4d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/MCX-Surges-on-Geopolitical-Fears-Valuation-Concerns-Emerge/69a5273a3d2913aa7c222b4d</guid><description>MCX shares surged on March 2, 2026, driven by rising gold and silver prices fueled by escalating US-Iran tensions. The exchange saw increased trading activity, with analysts like Rajesh Palviya from Axis Securities projecting a target of ₹2,650, contingent on sustaining ₹2,460. However, MCX's high valuation and the volatile nature of its commodity-driven business raise questions about long-term sustainability amidst broader market caution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 05:59:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a5273a3d2913aa7c222b4c_1772431348212.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dixon Tech Faces PLI 2.0 Test Amidst JV Delays, China Cost Gap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dixon-Tech-Faces-PLI-20-Test-Amidst-JV-Delays-China-Cost-Gap/69a527283d2913aa7c222b32</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dixon-Tech-Faces-PLI-20-Test-Amidst-JV-Delays-China-Cost-Gap/69a527283d2913aa7c222b32</guid><description>Nomura sees Dixon Technologies poised for PLI 2.0 gains via component joint ventures. However, reliance on government approvals for the display and Vivo JVs, coupled with an ongoing cost disadvantage against China, introduces execution risk. While PLI 2.0 aims to boost exports and domestic value, the scheme's structure and Dixon's current export mix will determine benefit quantum. The stock's recent dip contrasts with the brokerage's 'Buy' call, suggesting market caution on these contingent factors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 05:59:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a527283d2913aa7c222b31_1772431278192.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>West Asia Crisis: India's Export Lifeline Faces Strain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/West-Asia-Crisis-Indias-Export-Lifeline-Faces-Strain/69a526cb3d2913aa7c222a72</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/West-Asia-Crisis-Indias-Export-Lifeline-Faces-Strain/69a526cb3d2913aa7c222a72</guid><description>Geopolitical fallout from the US-Israel-Iran conflict is causing growing congestion at Jawaharlal Nehru Port Trust (JNPT), severely impacting India's perishable goods exports. Exporters face escalating daily costs for refrigerated containers, with potential for offloading expenses and spoilage if disruptions persist. The crisis highlights broader vulnerabilities in India's global supply chain, affecting nearly 56% of its trade with major markets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 05:57:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a526cb3d2913aa7c222a71_1772431475269.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Muthoot Finance Rallies on MS Upgrade; Geopolitical Tailwinds Meet Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Muthoot-Finance-Rallies-on-MS-Upgrade-Geopolitical-Tailwinds-Meet-Risks/69a526b33d2913aa7c222a51</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Muthoot-Finance-Rallies-on-MS-Upgrade-Geopolitical-Tailwinds-Meet-Risks/69a526b33d2913aa7c222a51</guid><description>Muthoot Finance shares gained over 2% on March 2 following a Morgan Stanley upgrade to "overweight," citing geopolitical uncertainty as a positive driver. The brokerage set a ₹4,500 price target, implying 34% upside. Despite a recent stock correction, the upgrade arrives as the gold loan NBFC navigates rising credit costs and competitive pressures, with Q3 FY26 profit surging 95% year-on-year to ₹2,656 crore. Muthoot's superior return metrics and market position contrast with peers like Manappuram Finance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 05:57:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a526b33d2913aa7c222a50_1772431178572.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hyundai India: Demand Surges, But Margins &amp; Market Share Face Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-India-Demand-Surges-But-Margins-and-Market-Share-Face-Scrutiny/69a525583d2913aa7c222821</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-India-Demand-Surges-But-Margins-and-Market-Share-Face-Scrutiny/69a525583d2913aa7c222821</guid><description>Hyundai Motor India (HMIL) posted a record 66,134 total sales in February 2026, driven by robust domestic demand and a significant 24.8% surge in exports. Management remains optimistic, citing healthy retail sales for SUVs and compacts, bolstered by its newly launched Venue and an aggressive product pipeline targeting 26 new models by 2030. However, near-term earnings face pressure from new plant start-up costs, and the company contends with market share erosion against aggressive domestic competitors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 05:51:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a525583d2913aa7c222820_1772430923718.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bharti Airtel's NBFC Bet: Growth vs. Capital Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Bharti-Airtels-NBFC-Bet-Growth-vs-Capital-Concerns/69a525583d2913aa7c22280a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Bharti-Airtels-NBFC-Bet-Growth-vs-Capital-Concerns/69a525583d2913aa7c22280a</guid><description>Bharti Airtel's shares tumbled approximately 6%, erasing INR 700 billion in market capitalization, following the announcement of a significant INR 200 billion capital outlay for its new Non-Banking Financial Company (NBFC) subsidiary. The move shifts investor focus to capital allocation, despite assurances from the Chairman regarding the company's prudent financial history and future growth prospects. Analysts maintain a 'BUY' rating, citing attractive valuations post-correction, though risks associated with diversification and capital deployment persist.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 05:51:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a525583d2913aa7c222809_1772430883468.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shriram Pistons Aggressively Diversifies: Valuation Hurdles Emerge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Shriram-Pistons-Aggressively-Diversifies-Valuation-Hurdles-Emerge/69a5254c3d2913aa7c2227eb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Shriram-Pistons-Aggressively-Diversifies-Valuation-Hurdles-Emerge/69a5254c3d2913aa7c2227eb</guid><description>Shriram Pistons &amp; Rings is undertaking a significant strategic pivot with its acquisition of Antolin India, aiming to transform its revenue mix towards engine-agnostic products. While analysts project robust growth and target ₹4,650, the company now confronts considerable integration challenges, intense market competition, and a valuation that some analysts deem premium, testing its diversification strategy's efficacy.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 05:51:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a5254c3d2913aa7c2227ea_1772430925677.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GTL Infra's CBI FIR Quashed by Bombay High Court; Legal Overhang Cleared</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/GTL-Infras-CBI-FIR-Quashed-by-Bombay-High-Court-Legal-Overhang-Cleared/69a525473d2913aa7c2227d4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/GTL-Infras-CBI-FIR-Quashed-by-Bombay-High-Court-Legal-Overhang-Cleared/69a525473d2913aa7c2227d4</guid><description>The Bombay High Court has quashed a Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI) First Information Report (FIR) against GTL Infrastructure Limited, registered in August 2023. The court ruled that no offense was made out warranting the continuation of the investigation, providing significant relief to the telecom tower company by removing a major legal overhang. This decision stems from a judgment delivered on February 27, 2026.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 05:51:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a525473d2913aa7c2227d3_1772430827939.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Mfg PMI Surges on Domestic Demand, Exports Lag</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Mfg-PMI-Surges-on-Domestic-Demand-Exports-Lag/69a523e93d2913aa7c222684</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Mfg-PMI-Surges-on-Domestic-Demand-Exports-Lag/69a523e93d2913aa7c222684</guid><description>India's manufacturing sector saw its strongest upturn in production volumes in four months in February, with the Purchasing Managers' Index (PMI) climbing to 56.9, bolstered by robust domestic demand. However, new export orders continued a deceleration that began in mid-2025, growing at the slowest pace in 17 months. This divergence resulted in only a marginal, albeit four-month high, expansion in factory employment, as companies managed increasing backlogs. While overall sentiment remains positive, the contrast between domestic strength and external weakness warrants scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 05:45:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a523e93d2913aa7c222683_1772430437790.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>L&amp;T Plunges Amidst ME Tensions; Underlying Strength Eyed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/LandT-Plunges-Amidst-ME-Tensions-Underlying-Strength-Eyed/69a51fc53d2913aa7c22235d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/LandT-Plunges-Amidst-ME-Tensions-Underlying-Strength-Eyed/69a51fc53d2913aa7c22235d</guid><description>Larsen &amp; Toubro (L&amp;T) experienced a sharp 7% intraday decline on March 2, 2026, its steepest drop in eleven months, driven by escalating Middle East geopolitical tensions. Investors are scrutinizing the impact on the company's substantial regional exposure, which accounts for 75% of its international order book. Despite this sell-off, L&amp;T benefits from strong domestic capital expenditure and a positive outlook for India's capital goods sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 05:27:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a51fc53d2913aa7c22235c_1772429413068.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Middle East Conflict Fuels Oil Shock, Exposing Indian Sector Weaknesses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Middle-East-Conflict-Fuels-Oil-Shock-Exposing-Indian-Sector-Weaknesses/69a51fbe3d2913aa7c222345</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Middle-East-Conflict-Fuels-Oil-Shock-Exposing-Indian-Sector-Weaknesses/69a51fbe3d2913aa7c222345</guid><description>Surging oil prices stemming from Middle East conflict have triggered sharp declines across Indian commodity-linked sectors. Airlines, tyre manufacturers, paint companies, and shipping firms face immediate cost pressures due to fuel and raw material price hikes. While some sectors may pass on partial costs, deeper analysis reveals structural vulnerabilities and limited hedging capabilities, posing sustained margin risks and an uneven recovery outlook. Market sentiment remains cautious, hinging on the duration of geopolitical instability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 05:27:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a51fbe3d2913aa7c222344_1772429667153.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Geopolitical Shock Sends Oil Soaring, Fed Policy in Focus</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Geopolitical-Shock-Sends-Oil-Soaring-Fed-Policy-in-Focus/69a51fb13d2913aa7c222309</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Geopolitical-Shock-Sends-Oil-Soaring-Fed-Policy-in-Focus/69a51fb13d2913aa7c222309</guid><description>Attacks on Iran triggered immediate market turmoil, with oil prices jumping sharply and safe-haven assets like gold rallying. The conflict injects fresh inflation fears, potentially forcing the Federal Reserve to delay anticipated interest rate cuts. This geopolitical event marks a significant shift, diverting attention from AI trends to energy security concerns and global economic stability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 05:27:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a51fb13d2913aa7c222308_1772429530742.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>China's MiniMax Disrupts AI Market with Aggressive Pricing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Chinas-MiniMax-Disrupts-AI-Market-with-Aggressive-Pricing/69a51f423d2913aa7c22222d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Chinas-MiniMax-Disrupts-AI-Market-with-Aggressive-Pricing/69a51f423d2913aa7c22222d</guid><description>MiniMax has launched its M2.5 generative AI model, positioning itself as a formidable competitor to OpenAI and Anthropic by offering its services at a fraction of the cost. This disruptive pricing strategy, coupled with significant investor backing and a focus on enterprise applications, is driving rapid adoption. UBS initiated coverage with a buy rating, highlighting MiniMax's potential to capture substantial market share in the global enterprise AI sector. The move intensifies competition in the burgeoning Chinese and global AI markets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 05:25:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a51f423d2913aa7c22222c_1772429388529.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Oil Sector: Upstream Booms, Downstream Bleeds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Oil-Sector-Upstream-Booms-Downstream-Bleeds/69a51f3a3d2913aa7c222216</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Oil-Sector-Upstream-Booms-Downstream-Bleeds/69a51f3a3d2913aa7c222216</guid><description>India's upstream oil and gas companies are shielded by stable crude prices near $75 per barrel, averting windfall taxes and supporting exploration for entities like ONGC and Oil India. Conversely, downstream operators and city gas distributors, including HPCL and BPCL, confront significant margin pressures due to escalating liquified natural gas (LNG) costs. Analyst Probal Sen notes short-term sector caution but maintains a constructive long-term view, emphasizing demand growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 05:25:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a51f3a3d2913aa7c222215_1772429235767.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Paras Defence: Geopolitics Boosts Defense, Chip Ambitions Clash</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Paras-Defence-Geopolitics-Boosts-Defense-Chip-Ambitions-Clash/69a51f333d2913aa7c2221f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Paras-Defence-Geopolitics-Boosts-Defense-Chip-Ambitions-Clash/69a51f333d2913aa7c2221f9</guid><description>Paras Defence shares jumped amid escalating West Asian geopolitical tensions, a common tailwind for defense stocks. Simultaneously, the company announced its strategic expansion into the semiconductor sector with the incorporation of Paras Semiconductors Pvt Ltd, aiming for advanced OSAT facilities. This dual catalyst of defensive strength and high-tech ambition is now a key focus for investors assessing the company's diversified future.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 05:25:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a51f333d2913aa7c2221f8_1772429522681.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Trade Deficit Balloons Amid Hormuz Threat, RBI Faces Policy Dilemma</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Trade-Deficit-Balloons-Amid-Hormuz-Threat-RBI-Faces-Policy-Dilemma/69a51e4b3d2913aa7c22208e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Trade-Deficit-Balloons-Amid-Hormuz-Threat-RBI-Faces-Policy-Dilemma/69a51e4b3d2913aa7c22208e</guid><description>Escalating Middle East tensions and the potential blockade of the Strait of Hormuz pose a significant threat to India's energy security. The narrow waterway, crucial for nearly 50% of India's crude oil imports, faces disruption risks that could drive oil prices above $90 per barrel. Such a surge threatens to widen India's already substantial trade deficit by 30%, exacerbate inflation, and potentially force the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) into a hawkish monetary policy stance. Key sectors like chemicals, aviation, and downstream oil industries face considerable headwinds, while global markets brace for inflationary pressures.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 05:21:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a51e4b3d2913aa7c22208d_1772429028300.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cummins India Valuation Sparks Debate Amidst Growth Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cummins-India-Valuation-Sparks-Debate-Amidst-Growth-Surge/69a51e423d2913aa7c222074</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cummins-India-Valuation-Sparks-Debate-Amidst-Growth-Surge/69a51e423d2913aa7c222074</guid><description>Motilal Oswal reiterates a positive stance on Cummins India, citing robust demand from power generation, particularly data centers, and improving industrial segments. However, the company's high valuation, with a P/E ratio significantly above peers, is drawing caution. While some analysts foresee continued upside driven by India's capex boom and data center expansion, others point to risks from evolving energy solutions and potential export challenges, leading to mixed analyst sentiment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 05:21:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a51e423d2913aa7c222073_1772428994177.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Equities Plunge: Duration Risk Fuels Deeper Economic Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Equities-Plunge-Duration-Risk-Fuels-Deeper-Economic-Fears/69a51ce23d2913aa7c221f2d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Equities-Plunge-Duration-Risk-Fuels-Deeper-Economic-Fears/69a51ce23d2913aa7c221f2d</guid><description>Indian equities experienced a sharp sell-off Monday, driven by escalating Middle East tensions and surging crude oil prices. The benchmark Sensex and Nifty50 indices saw significant declines, with broader market capitalization falling by ₹3 lakh crore. Beyond the immediate risk-off sentiment, the market faces deeper concerns over the duration of elevated energy costs and their compounding impact on India's trade deficit, inflation, and currency.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 05:15:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a51ce23d2913aa7c221f2c_1772428646747.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Crude Reliance Fuels VIX Spike Amid Middle East Crisis</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Crude-Reliance-Fuels-VIX-Spike-Amid-Middle-East-Crisis/69a518e53d2913aa7c221c7a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Crude-Reliance-Fuels-VIX-Spike-Amid-Middle-East-Crisis/69a518e53d2913aa7c221c7a</guid><description>Escalating Middle East conflict and a sharp rise in crude oil prices have propelled India's volatility index (India VIX) to a nine-month peak above 16. This surge reflects heightened market apprehension, amplified by India's significant reliance on imported energy, which poses substantial macroeconomic risks including inflation, current account deficit widening, and currency depreciation. The market anticipates a volatile trading environment as investors reassess geopolitical risks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:58:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a518e53d2913aa7c221c79_1772427610963.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GPIL Capacity Boost: Efficiency Gain or Premium Valuation?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GPIL-Capacity-Boost-Efficiency-Gain-or-Premium-Valuation/69a518dc3d2913aa7c221c63</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GPIL-Capacity-Boost-Efficiency-Gain-or-Premium-Valuation/69a518dc3d2913aa7c221c63</guid><description>Godawari Power and Ispat Ltd (GPIL) has received approval to immediately increase production capacity at its Raipur plant, notably without requiring additional capital expenditure. This move aims to enhance operational efficiency and output in its Sponge Iron and HB Wire divisions. While this capex-light expansion supports GPIL's integrated business model, it occurs against a backdrop of robust historical stock performance and a sector poised for growth, prompting scrutiny of its current market valuation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:58:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a518dc3d2913aa7c221c62_1772427648705.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Geopolitical Crisis Drives Gold-Silver ETFs Skyward; Equities Stumble</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Geopolitical-Crisis-Drives-Gold-Silver-ETFs-Skyward-Equities-Stumble/69a518aa3d2913aa7c221bdf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Geopolitical-Crisis-Drives-Gold-Silver-ETFs-Skyward-Equities-Stumble/69a518aa3d2913aa7c221bdf</guid><description>Escalating West Asian geopolitical tensions have triggered a flight to safety, propelling Indian gold and silver exchange-traded funds (ETFs) into sharp rallies. This surge contrasts sharply with a downturn in domestic equity benchmarks, as investors prioritize tangible assets over riskier ventures. The concurrent spike in crude oil prices further amplifies global economic anxieties, suggesting a complex, volatile market environment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:57:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a518aa3d2913aa7c221bde_1772427571839.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Clean Max IPO Tanks: Debt Focus Sinks Retail Interest</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Clean-Max-IPO-Tanks-Debt-Focus-Sinks-Retail-Interest/69a518a13d2913aa7c221bc5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Clean-Max-IPO-Tanks-Debt-Focus-Sinks-Retail-Interest/69a518a13d2913aa7c221bc5</guid><description>Renewable energy firm Clean Max Enviro Energy saw its shares debut on stock exchanges at a discount, opening 9% below its issue price. The IPO garnered a lackluster 94% subscription, with retail investors showing minimal interest (6%). A significant portion of the ₹3,100 crore raised will be used for debt repayment, signaling a priority on financial deleveraging over aggressive growth, a strategy that appears to have deterred smaller investors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:57:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a518a13d2913aa7c221bc4_1772427587416.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI Tightens Insider Trading Grip, Eases Foreign Investment</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Tightens-Insider-Trading-Grip-Eases-Foreign-Investment/69a518303d2913aa7c221b27</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Tightens-Insider-Trading-Grip-Eases-Foreign-Investment/69a518303d2913aa7c221b27</guid><description>India's market regulator, SEBI, is intensifying its crackdown on insider trading, investigating a record number of cases and taking action against prominent institutions. Concurrently, SEBI is streamlining foreign investment processes, aiming to boost capital inflows. This dual approach comes as retail investors face significant losses in the derivatives market and foreign portfolio investors divest equities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:55:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a518303d2913aa7c221b26_1772427489636.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Banks: Liquidity Injected, Deposits Lag, Rates Climb</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Banks-Liquidity-Injected-Deposits-Lag-Rates-Climb/69a517483d2913aa7c221947</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Banks-Liquidity-Injected-Deposits-Lag-Rates-Climb/69a517483d2913aa7c221947</guid><description>Despite the Reserve Bank of India's substantial liquidity injections, Indian banks are struggling to attract sufficient deposits. Credit growth continues to outpace deposit mobilization, pushing the credit-to-deposit ratio to record highs and keeping short-term interest rates elevated, including one-year Certificate of Deposit rates hovering around 6.90%. This dynamic suggests that monetary policy measures are not effectively translating into lower funding costs for banks, impacting overall financial system resilience.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:51:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a517483d2913aa7c221946_1772427230359.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shree Ram Twistex Slumps 32% on Debut Amid Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Shree-Ram-Twistex-Slumps-32percent-on-Debut-Amid-Valuation-Concerns/69a517393d2913aa7c221930</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Shree-Ram-Twistex-Slumps-32percent-on-Debut-Amid-Valuation-Concerns/69a517393d2913aa7c221930</guid><description>Shree Ram Twistex commenced trading on March 2, 2026, with shares listing at a steep discount exceeding 32% on both BSE and NSE. This sharp decline occurred despite the company's Initial Public Offering (IPO) being oversubscribed 43.66 times. The substantial gap between IPO demand and listing performance signals investor apprehension regarding the company's valuation and the broader textile sector's economic outlook.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:51:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a517393d2913aa7c22192f_1772427190260.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HYPE Token Surges Amid Geopolitical Hedging, Outpacing Bearish Crypto Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/HYPE-Token-Surges-Amid-Geopolitical-Hedging-Outpacing-Bearish-Crypto-Market/69a517393d2913aa7c22191a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/HYPE-Token-Surges-Amid-Geopolitical-Hedging-Outpacing-Bearish-Crypto-Market/69a517393d2913aa7c22191a</guid><description>Hyperliquid's HYPE token demonstrated remarkable resilience, surging over the weekend as traders utilized the decentralized exchange for geopolitical hedging. Robust trading volumes translated into significant fee generation and token burns, pushing HYPE's performance beyond that of Bitcoin and the broader market. Despite an impending token unlock, market participants appear confident in the protocol's fundamental strength and deflationary tokenomics. Meanwhile, Jupiter's JUP token also signals a trend towards supply discipline.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:51:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a517393d2913aa7c221919_1772427231860.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hormuz Blockade Threat: Global Oil Supply Faces Acute Vulnerability</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Hormuz-Blockade-Threat-Global-Oil-Supply-Faces-Acute-Vulnerability/69a516503d2913aa7c221805</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Hormuz-Blockade-Threat-Global-Oil-Supply-Faces-Acute-Vulnerability/69a516503d2913aa7c221805</guid><description>Heightened geopolitical tensions in the Middle East have sent oil prices surging. Analysts warn that a potential closure of the Strait of Hormuz, a critical global energy chokepoint, could lead to severe supply disruptions. With limited onshore storage and insufficient alternative export routes, the market faces acute vulnerability to immediate price spikes, underscoring systemic fragilities in global energy security.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2026 04:47:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69a516503d2913aa7c221804_1772426999756.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>