<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 03:53:23 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India's Paint War Heats Up: New Giants Challenge Old Guard, Profit Margins Squeezed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Paint-War-Heats-Up-New-Giants-Challenge-Old-Guard-Profit-Margins-Squeezed/694f55f54342f77179d8b591</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Paint-War-Heats-Up-New-Giants-Challenge-Old-Guard-Profit-Margins-Squeezed/694f55f54342f77179d8b591</guid><description>India's ₹70,000 crore paint market is undergoing a major disruption. Deep-pocketed conglomerates like Aditya Birla Group's Birla Opus and JSW Paints, through acquisition, are challenging established players like Asian Paints and Berger Paints. This surge in competition has led companies to prioritize market share, often at the expense of near-term profitability. While analysts predict growth revival in 2026, the competitive intensity is expected to persist, reshaping the industry landscape.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 03:35:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f55f54342f77179d8b590_1766807090476.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US TRAVEL CHAOS: Massive Storms Ground Flights, Shut Roads Coast-to-Coast – Millions Stranded!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/US-TRAVEL-CHAOS-Massive-Storms-Ground-Flights-Shut-Roads-Coast-to-Coast-Millions-Stranded/694f52744342f77179d8adad</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/US-TRAVEL-CHAOS-Massive-Storms-Ground-Flights-Shut-Roads-Coast-to-Coast-Millions-Stranded/694f52744342f77179d8adad</guid><description>Severe storms are crippling travel across the United States during the busy post-holiday period. Over 1,600 flights have been canceled, with JetBlue Airways Corp. and Delta Air Lines Inc. heavily affected, especially in New York, Philadelphia, and Boston. California faces road closures from rain and mudslides, while the Midwest deals with ice. Millions of Americans traveling by road are also at risk from hazardous conditions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 03:22:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f52744342f77179d8adac_1766806241079.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Stocks: $1 Trillion Flees Active Funds as Tech Giants Rule Market Records!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/US-Stocks-1-Trillion-Flees-Active-Funds-as-Tech-Giants-Rule-Market-Records/694f528f4342f77179d8ade3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/US-Stocks-1-Trillion-Flees-Active-Funds-as-Tech-Giants-Rule-Market-Records/694f528f4342f77179d8ade3</guid><description>In 2025, US equity funds experienced an unprecedented $1 trillion in outflows as investors struggled to keep pace with a market dominated by a handful of megacap technology stocks. This trend fueled a massive shift towards passive exchange-traded funds, leaving active managers in a difficult position to justify their fees when a narrow group of companies consistently outperformed benchmarks.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 03:22:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f528f4342f77179d8ade2_1766806283009.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>China's Rare Earth Ban Sparks Crisis: India's Auto Industry Scrambles for Survival!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Chinas-Rare-Earth-Ban-Sparks-Crisis-Indias-Auto-Industry-Scrambles-for-Survival/694f4dff4342f77179d8aa13</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Chinas-Rare-Earth-Ban-Sparks-Crisis-Indias-Auto-Industry-Scrambles-for-Survival/694f4dff4342f77179d8aa13</guid><description>China's April 2025 ban on rare-earth magnet exports sent shockwaves through India's auto industry, exposing critical supply chain vulnerabilities. Companies like Mahindra and Mahindra, Bajaj Auto, and Maruti Suzuki faced production risks. In response, India approved a ₹7,280 crore package to boost domestic magnet production and is pushing for supply chain diversification, learning vital lessons from geopolitical dependencies.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 03:02:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f4dff4342f77179d8aa12_1766805070473.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Beyond Gold: Copper's Explosive Rise as AI and EVs Fuel Demand!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Beyond-Gold-Coppers-Explosive-Rise-as-AI-and-EVs-Fuel-Demand/694f469c4342f77179d8a3fe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Beyond-Gold-Coppers-Explosive-Rise-as-AI-and-EVs-Fuel-Demand/694f469c4342f77179d8a3fe</guid><description>Metals like silver, gold, platinum, and palladium have seen significant price surges recently. While precious metals benefit from economic uncertainty and fears of currency devaluation, industrial metals such as copper, cobalt, and uranium are being driven by strong demand from technology sectors like AI data centers, electric vehicles, and nuclear power. Analysts are now increasingly bullish on copper, citing supply issues and renewed Chinese buying, with many recommending specific mining stocks for 2026.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 02:27:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f469c4342f77179d8a3fd_1766803205495.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold &amp; Silver Rally to End? Experts Warn of Volatility and Slower Gains Ahead!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-Rally-to-End-Experts-Warn-of-Volatility-and-Slower-Gains-Ahead/694f46994342f77179d8a3d3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-Rally-to-End-Experts-Warn-of-Volatility-and-Slower-Gains-Ahead/694f46994342f77179d8a3d3</guid><description>After stellar gains in 2025, experts are cautioning investors about gold and silver for 2026. They anticipate more modest returns, potentially driven by lower central bank purchases, a stronger U.S. dollar, and moderating safe-haven demand. Indian investors are advised to brace for volatility, with silver expected to face sharper corrections. Portfolio allocation adjustments are recommended to manage expectations.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 02:27:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f46994342f77179d8a3d2_1766803242173.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Massive ₹23,000 Crore Orders Ignite Indian Infrastructure Stocks: L&amp;T, Dilip Buildcon Bag Mega Deals!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Massive-23000-Crore-Orders-Ignite-Indian-Infrastructure-Stocks-LandT-Dilip-Buildcon-Bag-Mega-Deals/694f45a44342f77179d89fdc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Massive-23000-Crore-Orders-Ignite-Indian-Infrastructure-Stocks-LandT-Dilip-Buildcon-Bag-Mega-Deals/694f45a44342f77179d89fdc</guid><description>Indian companies secured over ₹23,000 crore in new orders this week, spanning solar power, roads, infrastructure, and green hydrogen. Key players like Larsen &amp; Toubro and Dilip Buildcon announced significant project wins, bolstering their order books and signaling strong sector activity. Vikran Engineering, Bondada Engineering, Ceigall India, and KPI Green Energy also reported substantial contracts, collectively boosting the outlook for the infrastructure and renewable energy sectors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 02:23:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f45a44342f77179d89fdb_1766802922529.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Regulator Slaps ₹1 Crore Fine on Reliance General Insurance for Hidden Commissions!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Regulator-Slaps-1-Crore-Fine-on-Reliance-General-Insurance-for-Hidden-Commissions/694f44ff4342f77179d8935f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Regulator-Slaps-1-Crore-Fine-on-Reliance-General-Insurance-for-Hidden-Commissions/694f44ff4342f77179d8935f</guid><description>India's insurance regulator, Irdai, has imposed a ₹1 crore penalty on Reliance General Insurance. The fine, issued in Hyderabad, stems from the insurer channeling unauthorized payouts to brokers, agents, and unlicensed entities under the guise of marketing and consumer awareness expenses during FY19 to FY21. These payments were deemed disguised commissions by the regulator.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 02:17:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f44ff4342f77179d8935e_1766802759062.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GOLD &amp; SILVER SHATTER RECORDS! Prices Skyrocket to Unprecedented Highs - What's Driving the Surge?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/GOLD-and-SILVER-SHATTER-RECORDS-Prices-Skyrocket-to-Unprecedented-Highs-Whats-Driving-the-Surge/694f44b14342f77179d88b12</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/GOLD-and-SILVER-SHATTER-RECORDS-Prices-Skyrocket-to-Unprecedented-Highs-Whats-Driving-the-Surge/694f44b14342f77179d88b12</guid><description>Gold and silver prices have hit new all-time highs, with silver surging over ₹32,000 per kg in four sessions to reach ₹2.35 lakh per kg, while gold surpassed ₹1.42 lakh per 10 grams. This rally is driven by geopolitical tensions in Venezuela and Nigeria, increasing haven appeal, robust industrial demand from sectors like semiconductors and EVs, and a multi-year supply deficit. Silver's year-to-date rise of approximately 160% significantly outpaces gold's 80% gain.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 02:17:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f44b14342f77179d88b11_1766802936105.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Insurance Revolution: New Risk-Based Rules &amp; Profit Reporting To Reshape Industry – What Investors MUST Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indias-Insurance-Revolution-New-Risk-Based-Rules-and-Profit-Reporting-To-Reshape-Industry-What-Investors-MUST-Know/694f445b4342f77179d88593</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indias-Insurance-Revolution-New-Risk-Based-Rules-and-Profit-Reporting-To-Reshape-Industry-What-Investors-MUST-Know/694f445b4342f77179d88593</guid><description>India's insurance sector is set for a major overhaul with the IRDAI implementing Risk-Based Capital (RBC) norms and Ind AS 117 accounting standards from April 2026. RBC will tie capital requirements directly to an insurer's risk profile, moving away from uniform solvency thresholds. Ind AS 117 will change revenue and profit recognition, recognizing them over the policy term instead of upfront. These changes aim to bring greater discipline to pricing, reserving, and overall business strategy, potentially impacting product attractiveness and requiring weaker companies to seek capital or consolidate. Investors can expect clearer insights into true profitability and risk management.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 02:17:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f445b4342f77179d88592_1766802840267.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Irdai Gains Superpowers: New Bill to End Insurance Mis-selling &amp; Boost Transparency!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Irdai-Gains-Superpowers-New-Bill-to-End-Insurance-Mis-selling-and-Boost-Transparency/694f43054342f77179d8847a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Irdai-Gains-Superpowers-New-Bill-to-End-Insurance-Mis-selling-and-Boost-Transparency/694f43054342f77179d8847a</guid><description>Insurance regulations are tightening as the Insurance Regulatory and Development Authority of India (Irdai) gains enhanced powers from the Sabka Bima Sabki Raksha (Amendment of Insurance Laws) Bill, 2025. Stricter norms on commission disclosure and conflicts of interest will improve transparency and reduce mis-selling, especially impacting bancassurance and other intermediaries.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 02:15:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f43054342f77179d88479_1766802254600.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Surges for 2026! Unlock Hidden Wealth with These Funds?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Surges-for-2026-Unlock-Hidden-Wealth-with-These-Funds/694f3a134342f77179d87e3a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Surges-for-2026-Unlock-Hidden-Wealth-with-These-Funds/694f3a134342f77179d87e3a</guid><description>Silver is transitioning from a traditional hedge to a key investment theme for 2026, driven by its dual role in precious metals and industrial demand. Its growing importance in renewable energy, EVs, and electronics, coupled with resilient Indian consumer demand, makes silver mutual funds an attractive option for systematic, long-term portfolio diversification beyond traditional assets.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 01:37:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f3a134342f77179d87e39_1766799963805.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2026 Investor Alert: Ditch 'Search' for Mutual Funds, Embrace 'Research' to Unlock Real Wealth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/2026-Investor-Alert-Ditch-Search-for-Mutual-Funds-Embrace-Research-to-Unlock-Real-Wealth/694f3a374342f77179d87e7e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/2026-Investor-Alert-Ditch-Search-for-Mutual-Funds-Embrace-Research-to-Unlock-Real-Wealth/694f3a374342f77179d87e7e</guid><description>As 2026 approaches, investors must differentiate between 'search' and 'research' when picking mutual funds. Relying solely on past returns ('search') is a trap, as it ignores risks and the 'why' behind performance. True 'research' involves understanding a fund's strategy, behavior, and suitability. This deeper analysis, often guided by financial advisors, is crucial for building robust portfolios and achieving long-term wealth creation, moving beyond misleading trailing return data.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 01:37:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f3a374342f77179d87e7d_1766800046411.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unicorns Ignite India's Market: New Tech IPOs Push Total Cap Past $140 Billion!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Unicorns-Ignite-Indias-Market-New-Tech-IPOs-Push-Total-Cap-Past-140-Billion/694f39134342f77179d87d4a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Unicorns-Ignite-Indias-Market-New-Tech-IPOs-Push-Total-Cap-Past-140-Billion/694f39134342f77179d87d4a</guid><description>India's new-age tech sector saw a significant surge in 2025, driven by 18 successful IPOs. These new listings, along with investor enthusiasm, pushed the cumulative market capitalization of listed new-age tech companies to $143 billion. The market cap of the 18 new IPOs alone jumped 33% from their listing valuation. While some companies like Ather Energy, Groww, and Paytm showed strong performance, others faced challenges. The trend indicates continued investor confidence in high-growth tech narratives.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 01:33:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f39134342f77179d87d49_1766799708623.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Market EXPOSED: Is It A Giant Bubble? 6 Gurus Predict 2026 Chaos!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Market-EXPOSED-Is-It-A-Giant-Bubble-6-Gurus-Predict-2026-Chaos/694f344b4342f77179d87a39</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Market-EXPOSED-Is-It-A-Giant-Bubble-6-Gurus-Predict-2026-Chaos/694f344b4342f77179d87a39</guid><description>Indian markets are near 26,000, sparking debate about a potential "epic bubble." While some experts like Siddhartha Bhaiya express concern, most leading market gurus, including Manish Sonthalia, Sandip Sabharwal, and Ajay Bagga, believe India is not in a bubble, though certain sectors might be overvalued. Experts foresee double-digit returns in 2026, driven by strong GDP growth, earnings recovery, and potential policy support, despite ongoing Foreign Institutional Investor (FII) outflows.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 01:11:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f344b4342f77179d87a38_1766798583545.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global Economy in Crisis: US &amp; China Blamed for Sabotage, Developing Nations Suffer Most!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Economy-in-Crisis-US-and-China-Blamed-for-Sabotage-Developing-Nations-Suffer-Most/694f33784342f77179d87946</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Economy-in-Crisis-US-and-China-Blamed-for-Sabotage-Developing-Nations-Suffer-Most/694f33784342f77179d87946</guid><description>The world's two economic superpowers, the United States and China, are accused of 'going rogue,' actively harming the global economy. Their policies of surging US protectionism and resurgent Chinese mercantilism are creating significant economic costs, particularly for developing countries. This "G-Negative-Two" world sees these hegemons inflicting damage rather than providing global public goods, leading to stalled development and reversed globalization.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 01:08:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f33784342f77179d87945_1766798332684.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Hidden Defence Tech Giant: The DeepTech Powerhouse You Need to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Hidden-Defence-Tech-Giant-The-DeepTech-Powerhouse-You-Need-to-Know/694f2d854342f77179d87607</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Hidden-Defence-Tech-Giant-The-DeepTech-Powerhouse-You-Need-to-Know/694f2d854342f77179d87607</guid><description>Astra Microwave, a deeptech firm, quietly supplies critical microwave components for India's advanced defence systems like missiles and radars. Despite its low profile, the company achieved ₹1,051 crore in FY25 revenue, demonstrating robust engineering and consistent growth with a 58% profit CAGR over three years. Its embedded nature in defence platforms ensures future visibility through a significant ₹1,916 crore order book, positioning it as a key player in India's technological self-reliance.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 00:44:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f2d854342f77179d87606_1766796748315.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bank of India Stock Alert: Cheaper Than SBI? Unpacking Value Bet for 2026!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bank-of-India-Stock-Alert-Cheaper-Than-SBI-Unpacking-Value-Bet-for-2026/694f2dce4342f77179d87663</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bank-of-India-Stock-Alert-Cheaper-Than-SBI-Unpacking-Value-Bet-for-2026/694f2dce4342f77179d87663</guid><description>Bank of India is attracting investor attention with its significantly lower valuation compared to State Bank of India, trading at 0.76 times book value versus SBI's 1.57 times. The bank reported strong Q2FY26 results, featuring 15.8% loan growth, improved asset quality with net NPAs at 0.65%, and a 7.6% rise in net profit. Despite a slight dip in Net Interest Margin, its performance and attractive valuation position it as a potential value investment for 2026.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 00:44:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f2dce4342f77179d87662_1766796925237.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Power Demand Surges to 236 GW This Winter: Economic Engine Roaring?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Power-Demand-Surges-to-236-GW-This-Winter-Economic-Engine-Roaring/694f27e44342f77179d87340</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Power-Demand-Surges-to-236-GW-This-Winter-Economic-Engine-Roaring/694f27e44342f77179d87340</guid><description>India's peak power demand surged to approximately 236 gigawatts (GW) in December, marking a strong seasonal rebound after several months of muted consumption. Electricity use increased about 5% year-on-year in early December, driven by winter weather. While overall fiscal year growth is expected to remain modest, capacity additions are accelerating, especially in renewables, and coal stocks are adequate, suggesting readiness to meet demand.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 00:19:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f27e44342f77179d8733f_1766795341256.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Electronics Boom: PLI Scheme Creates 1.33 Million Jobs, Skyrockets Smartphone Exports!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Electronics-Boom-PLI-Scheme-Creates-133-Million-Jobs-Skyrockets-Smartphone-Exports/694f27d84342f77179d87313</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Electronics-Boom-PLI-Scheme-Creates-133-Million-Jobs-Skyrockets-Smartphone-Exports/694f27d84342f77179d87313</guid><description>The "Make in India" electronics sector has become a major success, generating over 1.33 million jobs in the last five years. The Production-Linked Incentive (PLI) scheme has revolutionized smartphone manufacturing and significantly boosted exports, which have surged nearly tenfold. Approximately 70% of these new jobs were filled by women and first-time workers, highlighting inclusivity. The sector contributed an estimated ₹25,000 crore in wages to blue-collar staff in FY25 alone.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 00:19:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f27d84342f77179d87312_1766795297127.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>