<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:53:42 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Srinagar Airport Expansion: ₹1,677 Cr Bet on J&amp;K's Economic Rebound</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Srinagar-Airport-Expansion-1677-Cr-Bet-on-JandKs-Economic-Rebound/699dc43f04a25a58c84f4ab1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Srinagar-Airport-Expansion-1677-Cr-Bet-on-JandKs-Economic-Rebound/699dc43f04a25a58c84f4ab1</guid><description>The Cabinet Committee on Economic Affairs has sanctioned ₹1,677 crore for the Srinagar International Airport civil enclave development. This expansive project aims to significantly enhance aviation infrastructure, boosting the Jammu &amp; Kashmir economy, connectivity, and tourism. With a new terminal designed for 10 million passengers annually and expanded aircraft parking, the initiative targets a modern, culturally integrated, and sustainable facility, reflecting a substantial governmental commitment to regional development.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:31:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699dc43f04a25a58c84f4ab0_1771948355657.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SAMHI Hotels Deepens Marriott Ties, Eyes Navi Mumbai Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/SAMHI-Hotels-Deepens-Marriott-Ties-Eyes-Navi-Mumbai-Expansion/699dc43904a25a58c84f4a99</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/SAMHI-Hotels-Deepens-Marriott-Ties-Eyes-Navi-Mumbai-Expansion/699dc43904a25a58c84f4a99</guid><description>SAMHI Hotels Limited, through its subsidiary Duet India Hotels (Navi Mumbai) Private Limited, has signed operating agreements with Marriott Hotels India for two new hotel projects in Navi Mumbai and Thane. The developments include a 350-room Westin Hotels &amp; Resorts property and a 350-room Fairfield by Marriott hotel. This move deepens SAMHI's collaboration with Marriott, expanding its presence in a key hospitality corridor and strengthening its portfolio for corporate travelers. The expansion aligns with SAMHI's expectation of continued early teens revenue growth over the next 12-18 months.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:31:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699dc43904a25a58c84f4a98_1771947560065.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IRFC OFS Offers Discount, But Analysts See Red</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IRFC-OFS-Offers-Discount-But-Analysts-See-Red/699dc43804a25a58c84f4a82</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IRFC-OFS-Offers-Discount-But-Analysts-See-Red/699dc43804a25a58c84f4a82</guid><description>Indian Railway Finance Corporation (IRFC) is set to undergo a government divestment of 2-4% via an Offer for Sale (OFS), with a floor price of ₹104 per share, presenting a notable discount to its recent trading value of around ₹109-₹111. This move coincides with a starkly bearish sentiment from analysts, who collectively rate the stock a 'Strong Sell' with price targets suggesting significant downside from current levels. Despite IRFC's record quarterly profit and growing assets under management, the upcoming stake sale and analyst consensus indicate potential near-term headwinds for the stock.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:31:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699dc43804a25a58c84f4a81_1771947226851.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kraken Launches Regulated Equity Perps, Blurring Crypto-Finance Lines</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Kraken-Launches-Regulated-Equity-Perps-Blurring-Crypto-Finance-Lines/699dc42704a25a58c84f4a18</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Kraken-Launches-Regulated-Equity-Perps-Blurring-Crypto-Finance-Lines/699dc42704a25a58c84f4a18</guid><description>Crypto exchange Kraken has launched regulated perpetual futures contracts based on tokenized U.S. equities, accessible to eligible non-U.S. users. This move integrates crypto's 24/7 derivatives trading model with traditional assets like stocks, indices, and ETFs. The offering leverages Kraken's acquisition of xStocks infrastructure and taps into the rapidly growing tokenized equities market, projected to reach $1 trillion by 2030. While aiming to enhance accessibility and flexibility, the launch highlights ongoing regulatory evolution and the inherent risks of cross-asset derivatives.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:30:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699dc42704a25a58c84f4a17_1771947209296.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Apple Bets Big on India: Bengaluru Lease Signals Global Strategy Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Apple-Bets-Big-on-India-Bengaluru-Lease-Signals-Global-Strategy-Shift/699dc34c04a25a58c84f4823</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Apple-Bets-Big-on-India-Bengaluru-Lease-Signals-Global-Strategy-Shift/699dc34c04a25a58c84f4823</guid><description>Apple has significantly expanded its office space in Bengaluru, India, by leasing an additional 1.21 lakh sq ft at Embassy Zenith for approximately ₹2.84 crore monthly. This move brings Apple's total leased area in the building to nearly 3.89 lakh sq ft, with a cumulative 10-year rental commitment exceeding ₹1,333 crore. The expansion underscores India's critical role in Apple's global operational strategy and highlights sustained demand for premium Grade A office spaces in the city.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:27:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699dc34c04a25a58c84f4822_1771947054667.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Fertilizer Import Dependence Deepens Amid Production Lags</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indias-Fertilizer-Import-Dependence-Deepens-Amid-Production-Lags/699dc30b04a25a58c84f475a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indias-Fertilizer-Import-Dependence-Deepens-Amid-Production-Lags/699dc30b04a25a58c84f475a</guid><description>India's fertilizer sector faces escalating import dependence, with shipments rising 50% in April-January FY26, largely driven by an 83% surge in urea and 40% in DAP imports. This surge contrasts with declining domestic production of these key nutrients, exacerbating fiscal strain due to the weakening rupee and increasing subsidy burdens. Despite government efforts towards nano-variants, overall fertilizer sales to farmers have seen only a marginal increase.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:26:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699dc30b04a25a58c84f4759_1771946915206.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold-Silver Ratio's Plunge Signals Silver Outperformance, Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Ratios-Plunge-Signals-Silver-Outperformance-Risk/699dc30704a25a58c84f46f1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Ratios-Plunge-Signals-Silver-Outperformance-Risk/699dc30704a25a58c84f46f1</guid><description>The gold-silver ratio has sharply compressed, indicating silver is significantly outperforming gold. This shift is driven by robust industrial demand for silver and persistent supply deficits, contrasting with gold's role as a geopolitical hedge. While this compression signals opportunity, it also highlights silver's inherent volatility and sensitivity to economic cycles, differentiating its market dynamics from gold's more stable monetary function. Investors must navigate these divergent trends, considering the implications for portfolio allocation and risk management.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:25:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699dc30704a25a58c84f46f0_1771948395420.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>3D Printed Homes Debut in India's Dholera Smart City</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/3D-Printed-Homes-Debut-in-Indias-Dholera-Smart-City/699dc2f204a25a58c84f46b1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/3D-Printed-Homes-Debut-in-Indias-Dholera-Smart-City/699dc2f204a25a58c84f46b1</guid><description>Nestoria Group has initiated a large-scale 3D printed housing development in India's Dholera Smart City, leveraging advanced construction technology for faster, sustainable building. While this project marks a significant step in India's infrastructure modernization, it operates within a sector grappling with regulatory gaps, material science limitations, and a shortage of skilled labor, underscoring the complex path to widespread adoption of such innovations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:25:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699dc2f204a25a58c84f46b0_1771947199030.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TRAI Spectrum Push: Competition Boost or Financial Strain for Telcos?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/TRAI-Spectrum-Push-Competition-Boost-or-Financial-Strain-for-Telcos/699dc2ec04a25a58c84f469a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/TRAI-Spectrum-Push-Competition-Boost-or-Financial-Strain-for-Telcos/699dc2ec04a25a58c84f469a</guid><description>The Telecom Regulatory Authority of India (TRAI) has recommended auctioning all available radio wave spectrum, lowering financial entry barriers for new players by halving net worth criteria, and maintaining a uniform 35% spectrum cap. This aggressive stance aims to invigorate competition and expand digital connectivity. However, the move arrives as the sector grapples with high debt levels, particularly affecting Vodafone Idea, raising questions about the practical impact on market dynamics and incumbent financial health.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:25:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699dc2ec04a25a58c84f4699_1771946955897.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Haryana Probe Hits Banks: Governance Glitch or Sector Alert?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Haryana-Probe-Hits-Banks-Governance-Glitch-or-Sector-Alert/699dc27704a25a58c84f45fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Haryana-Probe-Hits-Banks-Governance-Glitch-or-Sector-Alert/699dc27704a25a58c84f45fb</guid><description>Haryana has formed a committee to probe unauthorized fund transfers from IDFC First Bank and AU Small Finance Bank, de-empannelling both. IDFC First Bank disclosed a ₹590 crore fraud, while AU Small Finance Bank faces scrutiny over ₹47 crore in questioned transactions. This has led to significant stock drops and highlighted governance concerns, particularly for smaller banks handling state funds, prompting stricter banking policy reviews.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:23:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699dc27704a25a58c84f45fa_1771947313774.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>State Debt Surge Reshapes India's Bond Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/State-Debt-Surge-Reshapes-Indias-Bond-Market/699dc22704a25a58c84f4572</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/State-Debt-Surge-Reshapes-Indias-Bond-Market/699dc22704a25a58c84f4572</guid><description>Indian states are increasingly turning to market loans to finance deficits, causing State Government Securities (SGS) outstanding to surge five-fold since FY15. This shift approaches parity with central government annual borrowings, fundamentally altering bond market dynamics. States are also extending borrowing maturities, with the weighted-average maturity rising to 16 years. This trend, coupled with fragmented issuances, leads to persistent illiquidity and higher term premiums in the SGS market, necessitating careful investor selection and adequate spreads. Vedartha advocates for standardized yield curves, limited ISIN creation, and mandatory credit ratings to improve market efficiency.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:22:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699dc22704a25a58c84f4571_1771946846583.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-GCC FTA Talks Restart: Strategic Rebalancing Beyond Energy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-GCC-FTA-Talks-Restart-Strategic-Rebalancing-Beyond-Energy/699dc11504a25a58c84f43c2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-GCC-FTA-Talks-Restart-Strategic-Rebalancing-Beyond-Energy/699dc11504a25a58c84f43c2</guid><description>India and the six-nation Gulf Cooperation Council (GCC) have officially launched negotiations for a comprehensive Free Trade Agreement (FTA), marking a significant recalibration after a 15-year pause. This initiative signals a strategic pivot for both regions, moving beyond historical energy dependencies towards diversified trade, investment, and mutual economic transformation. Bilateral trade reached $178.56 billion in FY 2024-25, with a substantial portion comprising India's energy imports and GCC's growing investments in India's development sectors.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:17:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699dc11504a25a58c84f43c1_1771946777169.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aditya Infotech Promoters, Dixon Technologies Plan Block Deal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Aditya-Infotech-Promoters-Dixon-Technologies-Plan-Block-Deal/699dbdae04a25a58c84f40e9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Aditya-Infotech-Promoters-Dixon-Technologies-Plan-Block-Deal/699dbdae04a25a58c84f40e9</guid><description>Aditya Infotech Ltd. (AIL) promoters, along with Dixon Technologies, are preparing to divest up to 5.8% of AIL's equity through a block deal estimated at ₹1,000 crore. This transaction is primarily driven by the need to comply with India's minimum public shareholding (MPS) norms, which mandate at least 25% public ownership. The sale, set at a slight discount to market price, aims to boost AIL's public float and recalibrate promoter holdings. While the regulatory push is clear, the implications for market liquidity and the strategic reasons behind Dixon Technologies' participation warrant close observation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:03:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699dbdae04a25a58c84f40e8_1771945559312.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coinbase Premium Plunge: U.S. Investors Lag Global Crypto Rally</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Coinbase-Premium-Plunge-US-Investors-Lag-Global-Crypto-Rally/699dbd8204a25a58c84f4089</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Coinbase-Premium-Plunge-US-Investors-Lag-Global-Crypto-Rally/699dbd8204a25a58c84f4089</guid><description>Coinbase's Bitcoin premium has registered its longest streak of negative readings at 40 consecutive days, currently at -0.0467%. This indicates U.S. investors are paying less for Bitcoin than the global average, suggesting diminished demand or increased selling pressure from this key demographic. Despite Bitcoin's price recovery, this persistent divergence raises questions about the sustainability of the rally and the underlying health of U.S. institutional and retail participation in the crypto market.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:02:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699dbd8204a25a58c84f4088_1771945633653.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>WisdomTree Unlocks 24/7 Trading for Digital Fund</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/WisdomTree-Unlocks-247-Trading-for-Digital-Fund/699dbd3304a25a58c84f4024</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/WisdomTree-Unlocks-247-Trading-for-Digital-Fund/699dbd3304a25a58c84f4024</guid><description>WisdomTree Investments secured SEC approval to allow its Treasury Money Market Digital Fund (WTGXX) to trade intraday at a fixed $1 NAV with a broker-dealer. This breakthrough, leveraging blockchain, bypasses traditional end-of-day settlement, offering 24/7 liquidity. The move signifies WisdomTree's strategic push to embed tokenized assets into capital markets infrastructure, enhancing investor experience and operational efficiency. The fund offers a 7-day yield of approximately 3.44% and maintains a low 0.25% expense ratio.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 15:01:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699dbd3304a25a58c84f4023_1771946484753.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Meta Bets on Partnerships for Stablecoin Re-entry</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Meta-Bets-on-Partnerships-for-Stablecoin-Re-entry/699dbc7f04a25a58c84f3f18</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Meta-Bets-on-Partnerships-for-Stablecoin-Re-entry/699dbc7f04a25a58c84f3f18</guid><description>Meta Platforms is reportedly planning a cautious re-entry into stablecoin-backed payments, aiming for integration in the second half of 2026. Unlike its prior ambitious Libra/Diem projects, the strategy now centers on partnering with third-party payment providers, with Stripe emerging as a likely pilot candidate following its acquisition of stablecoin specialist Bridge. This shift signifies a direct response to past regulatory challenges and a focus on operational efficiency through established infrastructure. The evolving U.S. regulatory climate, bolstered by the GENIUS Act, provides a more defined path for such initiatives, though inherent risks remain.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:58:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699dbc7f04a25a58c84f3f17_1771945400214.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Private Giants Eye Public Markets With Profit Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-Private-Giants-Eye-Public-Markets-With-Profit-Surge/699dbbcd04a25a58c84f3df1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-Private-Giants-Eye-Public-Markets-With-Profit-Surge/699dbbcd04a25a58c84f3df1</guid><description>India's top 100 unlisted companies nearly tripled net profits to ₹35,900 crore in 2025 from ₹13,000 crore in 2023, driven by efficiency and demand recovery. These firms generated ₹8.9 lakh crore in revenue and ₹1.03 lakh crore in EBITDA. With conservative leverage, 65% below 1x debt-to-equity, they are poised for potential IPOs, representing a new wave of public market entrants.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:55:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699dbbcd04a25a58c84f3df0_1771945521800.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-France Tax Pact Reshapes Investor Flows, Favors Direct Equity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-France-Tax-Pact-Reshapes-Investor-Flows-Favors-Direct-Equity/699dbb7304a25a58c84f3d5b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-France-Tax-Pact-Reshapes-Investor-Flows-Favors-Direct-Equity/699dbb7304a25a58c84f3d5b</guid><description>The revised India-France Double Taxation Avoidance Convention introduces capital gains tax for French portfolio investors, fundamentally altering the appeal of Participatory Notes (P-Notes). While French inflows via P-Notes reached approximately $21 billion as of January 2026, the treaty's clauses on capital gains and dividend taxation are expected to drive a strategic shift towards direct equity investments. This recalibration aims to enhance transparency and align with India's evolving investment framework, despite potential short-term friction for active traders and offshore structures.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:53:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699dbb7304a25a58c84f3d5a_1771945093863.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-GCC FTA Talks Launch: Geopolitics, Deficits, and Strategic Rebalancing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-GCC-FTA-Talks-Launch-Geopolitics-Deficits-and-Strategic-Rebalancing/699db6bc04a25a58c84f391e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-GCC-FTA-Talks-Launch-Geopolitics-Deficits-and-Strategic-Rebalancing/699db6bc04a25a58c84f391e</guid><description>India and the Gulf Cooperation Council (GCC) have officially commenced Free Trade Agreement (FTA) negotiations, aiming to deepen economic ties. This revival follows past stalled talks and occurs amidst India's strategic push for market access and supply chain integration. The agreement seeks to balance a substantial trade deficit, with key sectors like engineering goods, textiles, and energy imports/exports at the forefront. Negotiations face historical hurdles and complex issues like labor mobility and agricultural access.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:33:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699db6bc04a25a58c84f391d_1771943803973.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lupin Gains USFDA Nod for Brivaracetam Amidst Margin Pressures</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupin-Gains-USFDA-Nod-for-Brivaracetam-Amidst-Margin-Pressures/699db6aa04a25a58c84f3900</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Lupin-Gains-USFDA-Nod-for-Brivaracetam-Amidst-Margin-Pressures/699db6aa04a25a58c84f3900</guid><description>Lupin Ltd. has received USFDA approval for Brivaracetam Oral Solution, enabling its launch in the United States where the reference drug had $135 million in annual sales. This positive regulatory development contrasts with the company's third-quarter fiscal year 2026 financial performance, which saw net profit rise 37.5% year-over-year to ₹1,175.6 crore, but was significantly impacted by a ₹449.4 crore provision for antitrust litigations and a ₹134.8 crore settlement charge related to Astellas Pharma. Despite robust revenue growth, these exceptional items dampened sequential profitability, and the stock closed with a minimal gain, signaling investor caution over ongoing legal and competitive challenges.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:33:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699db6aa04a25a58c84f38ff_1771944989047.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coinbase Bets Big on Stocks: A Risky Pivot or Prudent Diversification?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Coinbase-Bets-Big-on-Stocks-A-Risky-Pivot-or-Prudent-Diversification/699db62a04a25a58c84f3840</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Coinbase-Bets-Big-on-Stocks-A-Risky-Pivot-or-Prudent-Diversification/699db62a04a25a58c84f3840</guid><description>Coinbase has expanded its platform to include U.S. stock and ETF trading for all U.S. customers, aiming to become an "everything exchange." This strategic pivot brings it into direct competition with Robinhood and other retail brokerages. While diversification seeks to stabilize its valuation against crypto volatility, it introduces significant margin pressures and risks diluting Coinbase's core crypto appeal in a highly competitive, low-commission market.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:31:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699db62a04a25a58c84f383f_1771943782529.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Goa Court's Cautious Approach Signals Regulatory Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Goa-Courts-Cautious-Approach-Signals-Regulatory-Shift/699db5b304a25a58c84f3780</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Goa-Courts-Cautious-Approach-Signals-Regulatory-Shift/699db5b304a25a58c84f3780</guid><description>The Bombay High Court is adopting a measured approach to addressing alleged illegal commercial operations in Goa following a fatal fire. Justices indicated a reluctance to impose blanket actions, prioritizing systematic resolution over immediate disruption. This judicial posture suggests a complex interplay between public safety mandates and the operational realities of regional businesses, potentially influencing future compliance standards and investor perceptions of the Goa hospitality market.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:29:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699db5b304a25a58c84f377f_1771943666192.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ABB India's Order Surge Masks Persistent Margin Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ABB-Indias-Order-Surge-Masks-Persistent-Margin-Squeeze/699db45404a25a58c84f35c8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ABB-Indias-Order-Surge-Masks-Persistent-Margin-Squeeze/699db45404a25a58c84f35c8</guid><description>ABB India posted a 6% year-over-year revenue increase to ₹3,560 crore in Q4 CY25, fueled by robust order inflows that surged 52% to ₹4,090 crore. However, profitability faced headwinds, with adjusted EBITDA falling 7% and margins contracting 230 basis points to 17.2%. This profit erosion stems from adverse product mix, escalating commodity costs, forex volatility, and increased import content driven by Quality Control (QCO) regulations. Despite a strong order backlog providing future revenue visibility, persistent margin pressure complicates the company's premium valuation, drawing mixed analyst sentiment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:23:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699db45404a25a58c84f35c7_1771943135496.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Xflow Secures $16.6M Series A, Dual License Fuels Cross-Border Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Xflow-Secures-166M-Series-A-Dual-License-Fuels-Cross-Border-Growth/699db44c04a25a58c84f35ae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Xflow-Secures-166M-Series-A-Dual-License-Fuels-Cross-Border-Growth/699db44c04a25a58c84f35ae</guid><description>B2B cross-border payments platform Xflow has closed a $16.6 million Series A funding round at an $85 million valuation, led by General Catalyst. This capital infusion, alongside final Payment Aggregator – Cross Border (PA-CB) authorization for both exports and imports, solidifies Xflow's strategic position. The company reported a tenfold growth in 2025, serving nearly 15,000 businesses across over 100 countries and 25 currencies. This dual licensing is critical for navigating and capitalizing on India's expanding international trade landscape, positioning Xflow as a key infrastructure provider.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:23:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699db44c04a25a58c84f35ad_1771946899337.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Muni Bonds Surge: Budget Boosts Green Debt</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Muni-Bonds-Surge-Budget-Boosts-Green-Debt/699db01304a25a58c84f326d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Muni-Bonds-Surge-Budget-Boosts-Green-Debt/699db01304a25a58c84f326d</guid><description>India's municipal bond market is experiencing unprecedented growth, fueled by the Union Budget 2026-27's incentives for larger issuances and a strong investor appetite for green debt. With nine issuances by December FY26, a significant jump from previous years, urban local bodies are increasingly tapping capital markets. Nashik Municipal Corporation's ₹200 crore green bond issuance exemplifies this trend, highlighting improved credit metrics and a focus on sustainable projects. While this revival signals a maturing market, challenges in liquidity and scale persist.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:05:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699db01304a25a58c84f326c_1771943544553.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Waaree Energies Lands Dual Wins; Stock Jumps Amid Sector Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Waaree-Energies-Lands-Dual-Wins-Stock-Jumps-Amid-Sector-Boom/699dafa304a25a58c84f315e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Waaree-Energies-Lands-Dual-Wins-Stock-Jumps-Amid-Sector-Boom/699dafa304a25a58c84f315e</guid><description>Waaree Energies' subsidiary secured a 300 MW wind power project in Gujarat with a 25-year PPA from SECI. This award, alongside a 500 MW solar module supply contract, underscores the company's strategic expansion. The dual wins propelled Waaree's shares up 4.26% to ₹3,040.00 on February 24, 2026, with a trading volume of 2.29 million shares. The company's recent Q3 FY26 performance showed a 119% YoY revenue surge, reflecting strong operational execution and market positioning.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:03:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699dafa304a25a58c84f315d_1771942117670.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Step-Up SIPs: A Proactive Hedge Against Inflationary Wealth Erosion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Step-Up-SIPs-A-Proactive-Hedge-Against-Inflationary-Wealth-Erosion/699daf8804a25a58c84f3109</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Step-Up-SIPs-A-Proactive-Hedge-Against-Inflationary-Wealth-Erosion/699daf8804a25a58c84f3109</guid><description>Step-up Systematic Investment Plans (SIPs) are emerging as a crucial strategy for investors to counter the insidious impact of inflation on long-term wealth accumulation. Unlike fixed SIPs, which see their real value diminish over time, step-up mechanisms automate annual increases in contributions, typically by 5-10%. This adaptive approach not only accelerates corpus growth through enhanced compounding but also aligns savings with rising incomes, offering a more robust pathway to achieving financial independence and early retirement compared to relying solely on unpredictable market returns.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:02:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699daf8804a25a58c84f3108_1771941879173.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NPS Tier II: Flexible Investing Faces Tax &amp; Return Trade-offs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/NPS-Tier-II-Flexible-Investing-Faces-Tax-and-Return-Trade-offs/699daf3a04a25a58c84f306a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/NPS-Tier-II-Flexible-Investing-Faces-Tax-and-Return-Trade-offs/699daf3a04a25a58c84f306a</guid><description>National Pension System (NPS) Tier II provides investment flexibility with minimal fees, aiming to rival mutual funds. While equity schemes demonstrate strong gross returns, the lack of tax efficiency on withdrawals presents a significant disadvantage compared to equity mutual funds. Furthermore, the emphasis on liquidity may lead to more conservative fund management, potentially capping upside. Investors must weigh these trade-offs against the cost and accessibility benefits.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 14:01:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699daf3a04a25a58c84f3069_1771941816143.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Aviation: Fragile Recovery Ahead Amid Lingering Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indian-Aviation-Fragile-Recovery-Ahead-Amid-Lingering-Risks/699daebd04a25a58c84f2fb2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indian-Aviation-Fragile-Recovery-Ahead-Amid-Lingering-Risks/699daebd04a25a58c84f2fb2</guid><description>The Indian aviation sector anticipates a one-third reduction in net losses for FY2026-27, projecting ₹11,000-12,000 crore compared to an estimated ₹17,000-18,000 crore for FY2025-26. This recovery hinges on 6-8% domestic passenger traffic growth. However, persistent high debt, significant reliance on volatile fuel prices and currency exchange rates, and recent operational disruptions create a narrow, risk-laden path to sustained profitability, despite a 'stable' sector outlook. Key players like IndiGo face scrutiny amid rising leverage and industry-wide vulnerabilities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:59:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699daebd04a25a58c84f2fb1_1771941862956.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Afcons Contract Terminated: Africa Project Dispute Escalates</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Afcons-Contract-Terminated-Africa-Project-Dispute-Escalates/699dae4504a25a58c84f2f09</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Afcons-Contract-Terminated-Africa-Project-Dispute-Escalates/699dae4504a25a58c84f2f09</guid><description>Afcons Infrastructure's Rs 1,200 crore road project in Gabon has been terminated by client SOCIÉTÉ AUTOROUTIÈRE DU GABON (SAG), following the invocation of €17.8 million in bonds. Despite Afcons claiming 93% completion, the dispute has escalated to arbitration proceedings, highlighting significant risks in international infrastructure contracts and adding pressure to the Shapoorji Pallonji group's financial standing.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:57:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699dae4504a25a58c84f2f08_1771941743593.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Asian Paints' Regional Play Faces Fierce Rivalry, Tests Valuation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Asian-Paints-Regional-Play-Faces-Fierce-Rivalry-Tests-Valuation/699dadba04a25a58c84f2e65</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Asian-Paints-Regional-Play-Faces-Fierce-Rivalry-Tests-Valuation/699dadba04a25a58c84f2e65</guid><description>Asian Paints is intensifying a regionalization strategy, focusing on localized color preferences and waterproofing solutions to counter escalating competition from Birla Opus and JSW Paints. This move comes as rivals expand aggressively and JSW consolidates the market via AkzoNobel's acquisition. While Asian Paints aims to defend its dominant market share, concerns linger regarding potential margin compression and the sustainability of its premium valuation amidst tightening competition and subdued demand.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:55:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699dadba04a25a58c84f2e64_1771943235017.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Schaeffler India Posts Strong Q4 Amid Valuation Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Schaeffler-India-Posts-Strong-Q4-Amid-Valuation-Scrutiny/699da90c04a25a58c84f2ac7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Schaeffler-India-Posts-Strong-Q4-Amid-Valuation-Scrutiny/699da90c04a25a58c84f2ac7</guid><description>Schaeffler India Ltd. reported a significant 35.9% net profit increase to ₹322.3 crore for the fourth quarter, driven by a 27.5% revenue surge to ₹2,724 crore. Full-year revenue grew 16.3% to ₹9,395.3 crore. Despite a recommended dividend and strong operational efficiency, the company faces analyst divergence over its elevated valuation metrics and concerns about long-term growth moderation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:35:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699da90c04a25a58c84f2ac6_1771940768002.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hexaware's AWS AI Partnership Faces Scrutiny Amid Financial Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Hexawares-AWS-AI-Partnership-Faces-Scrutiny-Amid-Financial-Headwinds/699da90c04a25a58c84f2ab0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Hexawares-AWS-AI-Partnership-Faces-Scrutiny-Amid-Financial-Headwinds/699da90c04a25a58c84f2ab0</guid><description>Hexaware Technologies has deepened its collaboration with Amazon Web Services (AWS) to integrate AI-enabled Software Development Lifecycle (SDLC) solutions, leveraging platforms like RapidX. This strategic move aims to accelerate client cloud adoption and AI transformation. However, the announcement comes as the company grapples with a recent Q4 earnings miss, sequential revenue decline, and a significant stock price drop, raising concerns about near-term financial performance versus long-term technological ambition. Hexaware's stock has seen sustained pressure, trading near 52-week lows.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:35:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699da90c04a25a58c84f2aaf_1771940283695.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nestoria Group's 3D Housing Push Signals India's Construction Overhaul</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Nestoria-Groups-3D-Housing-Push-Signals-Indias-Construction-Overhaul/699da81b04a25a58c84f296b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Nestoria-Groups-3D-Housing-Push-Signals-Indias-Construction-Overhaul/699da81b04a25a58c84f296b</guid><description>Nestoria Group is spearheading a significant shift in India's construction sector with its large-scale 3D printed housing project in Dholera Smart City. This initiative promises to drastically reduce construction timelines and material waste, aligning with India's Viksit Bharat 2047 vision. However, the success of this disruptive technology hinges on overcoming regulatory hurdles, demonstrating long-term cost-effectiveness for mass adoption, and integrating advanced building practices into India's evolving urban development framework.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:31:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699da81b04a25a58c84f296a_1771940353675.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kissht NBFC Arm Rating Upgraded, But Unsecured Loan Risks Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Kissht-NBFC-Arm-Rating-Upgraded-But-Unsecured-Loan-Risks-Loom/699da73d04a25a58c84f284d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Kissht-NBFC-Arm-Rating-Upgraded-But-Unsecured-Loan-Risks-Loom/699da73d04a25a58c84f284d</guid><description>Kissht's wholly-owned NBFC, Si Creva Capital Services, received a credit rating upgrade from Crisil to A-/Stable, citing strong business momentum and capitalisation. Assets under management grew significantly, driven by unsecured personal loans. However, this expansion occurs amidst increasing regulatory scrutiny on unsecured lending, intense competition, and potential pressures on asset quality and profitability within India's dynamic digital lending sector. The company is also preparing for an IPO.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:27:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699da73d04a25a58c84f284c_1771940124629.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Suzlon Energy Expands with DevCo, Faces Valuation Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Suzlon-Energy-Expands-with-DevCo-Faces-Valuation-Scrutiny/699da6b504a25a58c84f27ec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Suzlon-Energy-Expands-with-DevCo-Faces-Valuation-Scrutiny/699da6b504a25a58c84f27ec</guid><description>Suzlon Energy is launching DevCo, a dedicated project development unit, to broaden its offerings beyond wind into solar and battery storage systems (BESS). This move signifies a strategic shift from an order-driven model to pipeline-led planning, aiming to secure future projects up to five years in advance. While the company projects minimal balance sheet strain, the initiative enters a competitive Indian renewable market grappling with grid integration and storage challenges. Suzlon's valuation metrics are being closely watched against higher-flying peers like Adani Green Energy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:25:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699da6b504a25a58c84f27eb_1771939887509.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dr. Reddy's SEC Probe Ends, But Market Cautious on Disclaimer</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Dr-Reddys-SEC-Probe-Ends-But-Market-Cautious-on-Disclaimer/699da27b04a25a58c84f244e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Dr-Reddys-SEC-Probe-Ends-But-Market-Cautious-on-Disclaimer/699da27b04a25a58c84f244e</guid><description>Dr. Reddy's Laboratories has received notification from the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) that its investigation into allegations of improper payments has concluded without a recommendation for enforcement action at this time. Despite this regulatory reprieve, the company's stock saw a marginal dip, reflecting investor apprehension due to the SEC's cautionary note that the closure does not constitute exoneration and that future action remains possible. This development occurs amidst broader positive trends in the Indian pharmaceutical sector, including sector-wide gains and specific corporate milestones for Dr. Reddy's. The market's muted reaction suggests a focus on lingering uncertainties and the company's history of regulatory scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:07:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699da27b04a25a58c84f244d_1771938586578.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Insurance Advice Gap: Commission Culture Fuels Policy Lapses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Insurance-Advice-Gap-Commission-Culture-Fuels-Policy-Lapses/699da27b04a25a58c84f2437</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/India-Insurance-Advice-Gap-Commission-Culture-Fuels-Policy-Lapses/699da27b04a25a58c84f2437</guid><description>A recent Upstox study highlights a severe advice gap in India's life insurance market, with 63% of customers believing agents prioritize commissions over their needs. This, coupled with low product literacy, results in hurried sales and mismatched policies. Policy persistency is alarmingly low, with only 45-49% of policies surviving past 61 months, severely impacting insurer profitability and customer trust. Regulatory bodies are increasingly scrutinizing commission structures and sales practices to address systemic mis-selling and bolster long-term market stability.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:07:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699da27b04a25a58c84f2436_1771941363225.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tokenized Gilts Repo: Unlocking $300T Collateral or New Infrastructure Bottleneck?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Tokenized-Gilts-Repo-Unlocking-300T-Collateral-or-New-Infrastructure-Bottleneck/699da20604a25a58c84f233f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Tokenized-Gilts-Repo-Unlocking-300T-Collateral-or-New-Infrastructure-Bottleneck/699da20604a25a58c84f233f</guid><description>A consortium, including LSEG and Citadel Securities, executed the first cross-border, intraday repo using tokenized U.K. gilts on the Canton Network. This initiative targets unlocking significant collateral by bypassing traditional market rigidities. However, widespread adoption faces substantial hurdles in regulatory alignment, technological interoperability, and integration into existing financial infrastructure. The global repo market's vast size, estimated at $18 trillion, underscores the potential impact, yet successful scaling remains uncertain.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:05:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699da20604a25a58c84f233e_1771938632018.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bitcoin Plunge: Saylor's Apple Analogy Faces Market Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoin-Plunge-Saylors-Apple-Analogy-Faces-Market-Scrutiny/699da20304a25a58c84f2328</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoin-Plunge-Saylors-Apple-Analogy-Faces-Market-Scrutiny/699da20304a25a58c84f2328</guid><description>MicroStrategy's Michael Saylor drew parallels between Bitcoin's recent 45% drawdown and Apple's 2013 slump, suggesting such volatility is a precursor to success. However, Bitcoin's price now hovers near critical $60,000 support, amid significant realized losses and a broader market sentiment of 'extreme fear.' While Saylor dismisses quantum threats and 'Epstein FUD,' institutional outflows and MicroStrategy's own high leverage present considerable risks that diverge from Apple's mature market position.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 13:05:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699da20304a25a58c84f2327_1771938488635.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>