<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 01:56:20 +0000</pubDate><item><title>AI Spending Fuels Market Hopes Amidst Economic Crosswinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/AI-Spending-Fuels-Market-Hopes-Amidst-Economic-Crosswinds/698bde240c9da38e2e75f1ba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/AI-Spending-Fuels-Market-Hopes-Amidst-Economic-Crosswinds/698bde240c9da38e2e75f1ba</guid><description>Asian shares hover near record peaks as weak U.S. retail sales reinforce expectations of Federal Reserve rate cuts. However, substantial technology sector investment in artificial intelligence may mask underlying margin pressures and unsustainable growth, while central bank officials signal a data-dependent, cautious approach to monetary policy, creating a bifurcated market sentiment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 01:40:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Titan Beats Q3 Estimates; Valuation Scrutiny Mounts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titan-Beats-Q3-Estimates-Valuation-Scrutiny-Mounts/698bdd070c9da38e2e75efba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titan-Beats-Q3-Estimates-Valuation-Scrutiny-Mounts/698bdd070c9da38e2e75efba</guid><description>Titan Company Ltd. posted robust third-quarter earnings, exceeding expectations with a 40% revenue jump and 55% EBITDA growth. Operating margins expanded, driven by the jewellery segment and CaratLane's performance. However, the company's premium valuation, coupled with increasing competition and a slight dip in its high-margin studded ratio, warrants investor caution. Analysts maintain positive ratings but highlight valuation risks amidst sector growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 01:36:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698bdd070c9da38e2e75efb9_1770774119031.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Paramount Bid Sputters as WBD Leans Toward Netflix Amid Regulatory Storm</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Paramount-Bid-Sputters-as-WBD-Leans-Toward-Netflix-Amid-Regulatory-Storm/698bdd050c9da38e2e75efb2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Paramount-Bid-Sputters-as-WBD-Leans-Toward-Netflix-Amid-Regulatory-Storm/698bdd050c9da38e2e75efb2</guid><description>Paramount Global has again sweetened its hostile takeover bid for Warner Bros. Discovery (WBD), introducing a quarterly "ticking fee" and agreeing to cover WBD's $2.8 billion termination payout to Netflix. Despite these concessions, shareholder support has drastically declined, with tendered shares falling from over 168 million to just over 42 million. WBD's board remains committed to its preferred $82.7 billion merger with Netflix, leaving Paramount facing significant hurdles, including intensifying global antitrust reviews that scrutinize both potential transactions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 01:36:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Goldman Sachs Bets Big: India Pivot Aims to Overtake Rivals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Goldman-Sachs-Bets-Big-India-Pivot-Aims-to-Overtake-Rivals/698bdb230c9da38e2e75edff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Goldman-Sachs-Bets-Big-India-Pivot-Aims-to-Overtake-Rivals/698bdb230c9da38e2e75edff</guid><description>Goldman Sachs has injected $500 million into its India operations over three years, abandoning a 'future growth story' approach for a current growth engine strategy. This pivot has improved its deal-making rankings, but faces stiff competition from global giants like JPMorgan and local powerhouses like Kotak Mahindra. The firm is building scale across multiple financial services, accepting narrower margins to gain a foothold in India's rapidly expanding capital markets. This move reflects a broader trend of global banks increasing their focus on India's robust economic growth and dynamic financial sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 01:28:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Fear Triggers Wealth Management Sell-Off: Overreaction?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/AI-Fear-Triggers-Wealth-Management-Sell-Off-Overreaction/698bd7dc0c9da38e2e75ec39</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/AI-Fear-Triggers-Wealth-Management-Sell-Off-Overreaction/698bd7dc0c9da38e2e75ec39</guid><description>A new AI tool from Altruist Corp. sparked a significant sell-off across wealth management stocks on February 10, 2026. Raymond James Financial Inc. dropped 8.8%, Charles Schwab Corp. fell 7.4%, and LPL Financial Holdings Inc. declined 8.3%. This reaction mirrors prior AI-induced market jitters in other sectors, raising questions about whether the market is overestimating the immediate threat of automation and underestimating the enduring value of human advisory services.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 01:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Polaris Smart Metering Bets Big on India's Energy Overhaul</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Polaris-Smart-Metering-Bets-Big-on-Indias-Energy-Overhaul/698bd65a0c9da38e2e75e89f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Polaris-Smart-Metering-Bets-Big-on-Indias-Energy-Overhaul/698bd65a0c9da38e2e75e89f</guid><description>Polaris Smart Metering is injecting Rs 4,500 crore by 2027 to significantly expand its smart meter manufacturing capacity to 10 million units annually and enter the battery energy storage business. Backed by I Squared Capital, the company is also exploring an Initial Public Offering (IPO) to fuel its growth ambitions. This strategic move aims to capture a larger share of India's burgeoning smart metering market, driven by government schemes, while diversifying into the critical energy storage sector. The company targets doubling its current 10% market share within five years.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 01:07:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698bd65a0c9da38e2e75e89e_1770772307026.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BHEL Stake Sale, Titan, Britannia Q3 Surge: Stocks to Watch</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/BHEL-Stake-Sale-Titan-Britannia-Q3-Surge-Stocks-to-Watch/698bd5fd0c9da38e2e75e891</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/BHEL-Stake-Sale-Titan-Britannia-Q3-Surge-Stocks-to-Watch/698bd5fd0c9da38e2e75e891</guid><description>Indian markets are poised for a higher open as GIFT Nifty signals gains. Investors eye Bharat Heavy Electricals (BHEL) as the government plans to divest a 5% stake, potentially raising over ₹4,400 crore. Meanwhile, strong third-quarter earnings are boosting sentiment, with Titan Company reporting a 61% profit jump and Britannia Industries seeing a 17% net profit rise. Eicher Motors and Grasim Industries also posted solid results. Telecom stocks are in focus as Bharti Airtel surpasses Reliance Jio in net subscriber additions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 01:06:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's AI Ambition: DPI Powerhouse Meets Compute Divide</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-DPI-Powerhouse-Meets-Compute-Divide/698bd5840c9da38e2e75e86b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-DPI-Powerhouse-Meets-Compute-Divide/698bd5840c9da38e2e75e86b</guid><description>India's AI development path, distinct through its public-led Digital Public Infrastructure (DPI) playbook, faces critical headwinds. While initiatives like common GPU access, sovereign LLMs (Sarvam AI), and vernacular language integration aim for broad inclusion, the nation grapples with a stark global 'Compute North vs. South' divide. The immense energy demands of AI data centers further strain India's power grid, posing significant scalability and geopolitical risks that could temper its innovation ecosystem's momentum.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 01:04:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Nifty Nears 26K: Auto Strength Meets Retail Valuations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Nifty-Nears-26K-Auto-Strength-Meets-Retail-Valuations/698bd4090c9da38e2e75e6e9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Nifty-Nears-26K-Auto-Strength-Meets-Retail-Valuations/698bd4090c9da38e2e75e6e9</guid><description>The Nifty 50 approaches the significant 26,000 mark, driven by corporate earnings and positive sectorial trends. Eicher Motors demonstrates robust performance, buoyed by strong automotive retail sales and expansion plans. Conversely, Titan Company faces higher valuation scrutiny despite positive revenue outlooks. Investors weigh the index rally against component-specific opportunities and challenges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 00:57:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>JM Financial's 10 Growth Picks: Value or Volatility?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/JM-Financials-10-Growth-Picks-Value-or-Volatility/698bd1c30c9da38e2e75e37d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/JM-Financials-10-Growth-Picks-Value-or-Volatility/698bd1c30c9da38e2e75e37d</guid><description>JM Financial has spotlighted ten Indian companies poised for significant returns through fiscal years 2026-2028, citing robust earnings visibility, balance sheet health, and expansion plans. These selections span diverse sectors from retail to manufacturing. While the brokerage anticipates substantial upside, a deeper look reveals elevated valuations and potential execution hurdles for several names, particularly those undertaking aggressive capacity expansions. Competitor analysis shows many of these firms trade at a premium, suggesting growth is already priced in.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 00:48:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698bd1c30c9da38e2e75e37c_1770771241019.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Solar Push: GIPCL vs. Orient Green Power</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Solar-Push-GIPCL-vs-Orient-Green-Power/698bd1c30c9da38e2e75e375</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Solar-Push-GIPCL-vs-Orient-Green-Power/698bd1c30c9da38e2e75e375</guid><description>India's 2026 budget prioritizes clean energy, creating investment opportunities in renewables. Two small-caps, GIPCL and Orient Green Power, offer distinct plays. GIPCL, a state-backed utility, is pivoting from thermal to solar with significant projects, offering a defensive infrastructure play. Orient Green Power is a speculative turnaround, aggressively cleaning debt for solar expansion but facing promoter risk. Investors must choose between stability and high-risk/high-reward.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 00:48:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698bd1c30c9da38e2e75e374_1770771233204.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mid-Caps Outperform: Hotel Stocks Dazzle Leaders in Q3 FY26.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Mid-Caps-Outperform-Hotel-Stocks-Dazzle-Leaders-in-Q3-FY26/698bd14d0c9da38e2e75e357</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Mid-Caps-Outperform-Hotel-Stocks-Dazzle-Leaders-in-Q3-FY26/698bd14d0c9da38e2e75e357</guid><description>Mid-cap hotel chains are outperforming industry giants like The Indian Hotels Company, fueled by robust Q3 FY26 performance. Strong demand during the peak tourism and wedding season, coupled with higher average daily rates (ADR) and nimbler operations, propelled significant revenue and profit growth for companies such as Leela Palaces Hotels &amp; Resorts, Chalet Hotels, and Ventive Hospitality. Investors are increasingly focusing on these agile players exhibiting impressive financial metrics and expansion plans.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 00:46:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698bd14d0c9da38e2e75e356_1770771136485.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>