<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 01:51:47 +0000</pubDate><item><title>LIC Stock Surges: Analyst Optimism Meets Competitive Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/LIC-Stock-Surges-Analyst-Optimism-Meets-Competitive-Headwinds/698e7f8c119a61fe896eac17</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/LIC-Stock-Surges-Analyst-Optimism-Meets-Competitive-Headwinds/698e7f8c119a61fe896eac17</guid><description>Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC) stock gained nearly 13% last week, reversing prior losses. Despite a broad analyst "Buy" consensus and a lower P/E ratio than competitors, the company faces intensifying competition from agile private insurers and potential margin pressures from new GST policies. Recent Q3 results showed strong profit and premium income growth, yet underlying financial trends are described as flat by some analysts. Current trading price is approximately ₹880.95, with a market capitalization around ₹5.57 lakh crore.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 01:34:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Panic Sell-Off: Is Wall Street Overreacting?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Panic-Sell-Off-Is-Wall-Street-Overreacting/698e7c53119a61fe896eaa32</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Panic-Sell-Off-Is-Wall-Street-Overreacting/698e7c53119a61fe896eaa32</guid><description>Wall Street experienced a sharp sell-off on February 12, 2026, driven by escalating fears over Artificial Intelligence's disruptive potential. Major indices like the Dow Jones, S&amp;P 500, and Nasdaq saw significant declines. Cisco Systems plummeted 12% on disappointing guidance, while software, financial, trucking, and real estate sectors faced heavy losses. Defensive stocks like Walmart and Coca-Cola bucked the trend, offering investors a refuge. This broad market reaction to AI concerns may represent an oversimplification, potentially masking opportunities in fundamentally sound companies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 01:20:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Phoenix Mills Seeks Rs 1,500 Cr From GIC, CPP for Thane Mega Project</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Phoenix-Mills-Seeks-Rs-1500-Cr-From-GIC-CPP-for-Thane-Mega-Project/698e7b1a119a61fe896ea95d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Phoenix-Mills-Seeks-Rs-1500-Cr-From-GIC-CPP-for-Thane-Mega-Project/698e7b1a119a61fe896ea95d</guid><description>India's largest mall operator, Phoenix Mills, is in advanced talks to raise approximately Rs 1,500 crore for its ambitious 3.3 million sq ft mixed-use development in Thane. Discussions involve major global investors like Singapore's GIC and Canada Pension Plan Investment Board (CPP Investments), signaling confidence in the developer's expansion strategy. The project will feature retail, residential, and other commercial components.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 01:15:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Tourism Paradox: A $1 Trillion GDP Engine Stalls</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Indias-Tourism-Paradox-A-1-Trillion-GDP-Engine-Stalls/698e7aa2119a61fe896ea8dd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Indias-Tourism-Paradox-A-1-Trillion-GDP-Engine-Stalls/698e7aa2119a61fe896ea8dd</guid><description>India's tourism sector, a potential $1 trillion GDP engine capable of creating 100 million jobs, is severely underperforming. Despite rich cultural heritage and natural assets, policy drift, regulatory density, and critical infrastructure deficits like hotel capacity result in missed economic opportunities and a net forex outflow. While the sector contributed approximately 6.6% to GDP in 2024, this lags global benchmarks, with only about 196,000 branded hotel rooms available against substantial demand. Proposed reforms focus on deregulation, capacity scaling, and last-mile experience enhancement to unlock this vital sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 01:13:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Panic Overdrives CRE Sell-Off, Fundamentals Under Fire</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/AI-Panic-Overdrives-CRE-Sell-Off-Fundamentals-Under-Fire/698e76a7119a61fe896ea6be</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/AI-Panic-Overdrives-CRE-Sell-Off-Fundamentals-Under-Fire/698e76a7119a61fe896ea6be</guid><description>US-listed commercial real estate stocks experienced a significant downturn for a second consecutive session. Investor apprehension regarding artificial intelligence's disruptive potential has cascaded into the property sector, with shares of major brokers like CBRE and Jones Lang LaSalle falling sharply. Despite widespread fear, some analysts argue the sell-off overstates immediate risks, pointing to robust underlying fundamentals and the potential for AI to enhance productivity, while cautioning that slower adopters face long-term structural challenges.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:56:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India-EU Trade Deal: Tariff Cuts Boost Textiles, But Bangladesh Challenge Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/India-EU-Trade-Deal-Tariff-Cuts-Boost-Textiles-But-Bangladesh-Challenge-Looms/698e7515119a61fe896ea580</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/India-EU-Trade-Deal-Tariff-Cuts-Boost-Textiles-But-Bangladesh-Challenge-Looms/698e7515119a61fe896ea580</guid><description>The recently finalized EU-India Free Trade Agreement (FTA) presents a significant tariff advantage for India's textile sector, potentially doubling exports to the EU within years. However, this optimism is tempered by ongoing competition from Bangladesh in the low-cost segment and the lingering impact of past trade disputes, emphasizing the need for India to focus on value-added production, sustainability, and technological advancement to fully capitalize on this market access.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:49:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Capital Preservation Key as Market Swings Accelerate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Capital-Preservation-Key-as-Market-Swings-Accelerate/698e70cf119a61fe896ea339</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Capital-Preservation-Key-as-Market-Swings-Accelerate/698e70cf119a61fe896ea339</guid><description>A growing market sentiment emphasizes capital preservation, moving focus from 'return on capital' to 'return of capital.' This shift is driven by historical patterns of market cycles, where sustained optimism often precedes sharp downturns. Increased leverage amplifies risks, while a surge in IPOs, many funding debt rather than growth, presents new challenges for investors. Strategic cash holding and a disciplined approach are highlighted as crucial for navigating potential volatility and capitalizing on future opportunities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:31:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bitcoin's Extreme Sentiment Sways Market Amid Capital Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoins-Extreme-Sentiment-Sways-Market-Amid-Capital-Shift/698e70c6119a61fe896ea330</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoins-Extreme-Sentiment-Sways-Market-Amid-Capital-Shift/698e70c6119a61fe896ea330</guid><description>Bitcoin's price action in early 2026 reflects a battle between extreme sentiment and underlying macro pressures. Despite a decline from its October 2025 peak of $126,000, Bitcoin trades around $67,000 amidst widespread "extreme fear". This volatility has triggered significant liquidation events, including a $2.2 billion event on February 1, 2026 and a $1.4 billion event on February 5, 2026. While long-term prospects for Bitcoin remain, the market's susceptibility to leverage, macroeconomic shifts, and a notable migration of speculative capital towards prediction markets highlight its evolving risk profile.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:31:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Gold Lending Rift: Muthoot Soars, Manappuram Trails Amidst Sector Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Gold-Lending-Rift-Muthoot-Soars-Manappuram-Trails-Amidst-Sector-Boom/698e6fa3119a61fe896ea247</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Gold-Lending-Rift-Muthoot-Soars-Manappuram-Trails-Amidst-Sector-Boom/698e6fa3119a61fe896ea247</guid><description>India's gold loan sector is experiencing robust growth, yet a significant performance divergence is evident between leading financiers. Muthoot Finance posted a remarkable 94.9% year-on-year jump in standalone net profit to ₹2,656 crore, driven by a 51% surge in assets under management (AUM) and healthy net interest margins (NIM). In contrast, Manappuram Finance, despite a 56.8% rise in its gold loan book, saw its net profit decline by 15.9%, burdened by increased costs and lower yields. This bifurcation highlights operational strengths and market positioning as key differentiators in a booming market.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:26:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>South Indian Bank: Institutional Influx Meets Valuation Puzzle</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/South-Indian-Bank-Institutional-Influx-Meets-Valuation-Puzzle/698e6f9c119a61fe896ea23f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/South-Indian-Bank-Institutional-Influx-Meets-Valuation-Puzzle/698e6f9c119a61fe896ea23f</guid><description>South Indian Bank (SIB) is attracting significant institutional investment, with Foreign Institutional Investors (FIIs) and Domestic Institutional Investors (DIIs) increasing their stakes during Q3FY26. This is underpinned by robust 45% year-on-year growth in MSME loan disbursements and strong 60% retail advance expansion. Despite improved asset quality (Gross NPA down to 2.7%) and a respectable 13.8% Return on Equity, SIB trades at a stark valuation discount, with a P/E of 7.6x, nearly half the industry median of 15.9x. This divergence highlights a market paradox: sustained fundamental improvements versus persistent valuation skepticism.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:26:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Low-Sugar Boom: Coke Dominates, VBL Soars</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Low-Sugar-Boom-Coke-Dominates-VBL-Soars/698e6b66119a61fe896e9d95</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indias-Low-Sugar-Boom-Coke-Dominates-VBL-Soars/698e6b66119a61fe896e9d95</guid><description>India's zero and low-sugar beverage market has surged to a five-year high, with Coca-Cola reporting its zero-sugar volume sales reaching 30% of total in 2025, and Diet Coke sales doubling. PepsiCo's bottler, Varun Beverages (VBL), saw its no-sugar and mid-sugar drink sales rise to 59% of total volume in Q4 2025, marking a significant year-on-year surge. This trend is fueled by heightened health consciousness among consumers, particularly Gen Z, and a shift towards healthier lifestyle choices. VBL's robust financial performance and strong analyst backing position it as a key player to watch in this evolving market.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:08:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Accel Limited: Revenue Soars, Profits Plummet Amidst Auditor Red Flags</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Accel-Limited-Revenue-Soars-Profits-Plummet-Amidst-Auditor-Red-Flags/698e6af0119a61fe896e9d6c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Accel-Limited-Revenue-Soars-Profits-Plummet-Amidst-Auditor-Red-Flags/698e6af0119a61fe896e9d6c</guid><description>Accel Limited announced Q3 FY26 results showing a substantial 84% YoY revenue jump on a standalone basis, but net profit plunged by 91%. Consolidated results turned into a loss. Recurring qualifications from auditors regarding loan recoverability and investment valuation raise governance concerns for investors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:06:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698e6af0119a61fe896e9d6b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UFLEX Revenue Down 4%, Debt Rises to ₹8,881 Cr, Subsidiary Fraud Alleged</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/UFLEX-Revenue-Down-4percent-Debt-Rises-to-8881-Cr-Subsidiary-Fraud-Alleged/698e6aeb119a61fe896e9d64</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/UFLEX-Revenue-Down-4percent-Debt-Rises-to-8881-Cr-Subsidiary-Fraud-Alleged/698e6aeb119a61fe896e9d64</guid><description>UFLEX Limited reported a challenging Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue falling 3.8% year-on-year to ₹3,632.9 Cr and net profit dropping sharply by 73.6% to ₹36.1 Cr. The company's net debt increased to ₹8,881 Cr, with leverage rising to 4.72x EBITDA. In a significant development, UFLEX also disclosed a fraud case involving a former director of its UK subsidiary.</description><pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:06:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698e6aeb119a61fe896e9d63.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>