<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 01:47:58 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Latent View Revenue Leaps 22%, But Profit Margins Face Pressure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Latent-View-Revenue-Leaps-22percent-But-Profit-Margins-Face-Pressure/697fec5547db7081af6712c7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Latent-View-Revenue-Leaps-22percent-But-Profit-Margins-Face-Pressure/697fec5547db7081af6712c7</guid><description>Latent View Analytics reported strong Q3FY26 results, with revenue up 22.0% YoY to ₹2,780 Mn and Adjusted EBITDA climbing 22.7% to ₹640 Mn. Despite a 19.1% rise in PAT to ₹508 Mn, reported PAT margins compressed 0.4 pp YoY to 17.2%, a trend continuing from FY23. The company is enhancing AI capabilities and data engineering via a Databricks partnership, with Financial Services vertical soaring 105% YoY.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 01:37:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697fec5547db7081af6712c6_1769996220089.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Unveils Massive Infrastructure Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Unveils-Massive-Infrastructure-Push/697ff44d47db7081af671aa7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Unveils-Massive-Infrastructure-Push/697ff44d47db7081af671aa7</guid><description>India's latest Union Budget earmarks substantial investment for national infrastructure, announcing seven high-speed rail corridors and a new trans-continental freight corridor. These ambitious projects, complemented by a strategic focus on critical mineral development, aim to significantly boost connectivity, reduce logistics costs, and stimulate broad-based economic expansion through increased capital expenditure.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 01:36:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ff44d47db7081af671aa6_1769996134129.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BlackBuck: India's Trucking Infrastructure Play</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/BlackBuck-Indias-Trucking-Infrastructure-Play/697ffafc47db7081af67209d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/BlackBuck-Indias-Trucking-Infrastructure-Play/697ffafc47db7081af67209d</guid><description>BlackBuck is strategically positioning itself as the foundational infrastructure for India's vast trucking economy, transcending its initial perception as a logistics technology provider. The company's core strength lies in its near-monopoly in toll and fuel payment processing, augmented by advanced telematics, creating a sticky ecosystem for fleet operators. While operating as a private entity, its reported valuation reflects significant investor confidence in its essential services and expansion plans.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 01:24:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ffafc47db7081af67209c_1769995438807.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Capital Market 'Dark Horses' Compounding Wealth Silently</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Capital-Market-Dark-Horses-Compounding-Wealth-Silently/697ffb1747db7081af67218f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Capital-Market-Dark-Horses-Compounding-Wealth-Silently/697ffb1747db7081af67218f</guid><description>Indian capital markets are frequently misjudged, with value creation occurring away from headline trading volumes. Three companies—Nuvama Wealth Management, IIFL Capital Services, and Computer Age Management Systems (CAMS)—exemplify 'dark horses'. These firms demonstrate sturdy profitability, strong returns, and resilient business models, generating wealth through advisory, asset management, and essential market infrastructure rather than speculative trading. Their market valuations often understate their compounding potential.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 01:20:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ffb1747db7081af67218e_1769995107844.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Bets Record ₹3.16 Trillion Dividend for Fiscal Health</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Bets-Record-316-Trillion-Dividend-for-Fiscal-Health/697ffada47db7081af671fd2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Bets-Record-316-Trillion-Dividend-for-Fiscal-Health/697ffada47db7081af671fd2</guid><description>The Indian government is projecting a record ₹3.16 lakh crore in dividends for fiscal year 2026-27, primarily from the Reserve Bank of India and public sector banks (PSBs). This figure represents a significant increase from the revised estimate of ₹3.04 lakh crore for FY2025-26. The robust inflow is expected to provide a crucial non-tax revenue cushion for managing the fiscal deficit. Key drivers include the RBI's substantial gains from foreign exchange interventions and a surge in profitability among PSBs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 01:16:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Budget 2026 Curbs SGB Tax Exemption for Resale Buyers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Curbs-SGB-Tax-Exemption-for-Resale-Buyers/697ff53e47db7081af671c27</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Curbs-SGB-Tax-Exemption-for-Resale-Buyers/697ff53e47db7081af671c27</guid><description>The Union Budget for 2026-27 has significantly altered capital gains tax rules for Sovereign Gold Bonds (SGBs), effective April 1. Tax exemption at maturity will now exclusively apply to individuals who subscribed at the original issue and held the bonds continuously until redemption. This change eliminates tax-free capital gains for investors acquiring SGBs through the secondary market, even if held until maturity. The move aims to curb speculative trading and reinforce incentives for long-term investment in government debt instruments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 00:56:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697ff53e47db7081af671c26_1769993760798.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Latent View Analytics: Q3 Revenue Surges 22%, Profit Lifts 19% Amidst Cost Pressures</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Latent-View-Analytics-Q3-Revenue-Surges-22percent-Profit-Lifts-19percent-Amidst-Cost-Pressures/697febde47db7081af671193</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Latent-View-Analytics-Q3-Revenue-Surges-22percent-Profit-Lifts-19percent-Amidst-Cost-Pressures/697febde47db7081af671193</guid><description>Latent View Analytics reported a robust Q3 FY26 with revenue leaping 22.06% YoY to ₹2,780 million. Profit After Tax (PAT) grew 19.15% YoY to ₹507.71 million, driven by strong operational performance. However, total expenses climbed 22.75% YoY, with notable jumps in finance costs (+495.91%) and tax expenses (+39.38%), outpacing PBT growth. The company also announced changes to its insider trading code and risk management committee.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 00:48:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697febde47db7081af671192_1769993281014.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Textile Sector Gains Budget Focus on MMF, Cotton</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/India-Textile-Sector-Gains-Budget-Focus-on-MMF-Cotton/697fedc247db7081af67148b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/India-Textile-Sector-Gains-Budget-Focus-on-MMF-Cotton/697fedc247db7081af67148b</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026-27 targets textile sector revitalization through modernization and efficiency incentives. Measures focus on Man-Made Fiber (MMF) and premium cotton apparel, expecting gradual price moderation and quality enhancement. Key initiatives include skill development, mega textile parks, and a national fiber scheme, alongside long-term logistics improvements via the Dankuni-Surat freight corridor.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 00:46:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697fedc247db7081af67148a_1769993161574.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Slashes Import Duty: Overseas Shopping Cost Cut</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Slashes-Import-Duty-Overseas-Shopping-Cost-Cut/697feeac47db7081af671714</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Slashes-Import-Duty-Overseas-Shopping-Cost-Cut/697feeac47db7081af671714</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026-27 proposes a significant reduction in basic customs duty for personal imports, lowering it from 20% to 10% effective April. This move aims to offset the impact of a weakening rupee, making imported goods more accessible for consumers. Experts anticipate a reduction in integrated GST, thereby decreasing overall transaction costs for online shoppers. The policy aligns with the government's objective of alleviating household financial burdens and encouraging compliance with official import procedures.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 00:36:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697feeac47db7081af671713_1769992438543.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Boosts Footwear Exports with Duty-Free Imports</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Boosts-Footwear-Exports-with-Duty-Free-Imports/697fee3347db7081af6715d0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Boosts-Footwear-Exports-with-Duty-Free-Imports/697fee3347db7081af6715d0</guid><description>Government measures, including bringing specific imported inputs for shoe uppers under the Import of Goods on Concessional Rate of Duty (IGCR) scheme, are set to enhance cost competitiveness for India's leather and non-leather footwear exporters. This policy, detailed in the Union Budget 2026-27, extends the re-export obligation period from six months to one year, simplifying business operations. The Council for Leather Exports projects this move could generate two to three lakh additional jobs across the sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 00:26:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697fee3347db7081af6715cf_1769991845167.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Latent View Analytics Surges 22% YoY on Strong Q3 Driven by AI Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Latent-View-Analytics-Surges-22percent-YoY-on-Strong-Q3-Driven-by-AI-Push/697feb6747db7081af671059</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Latent-View-Analytics-Surges-22percent-YoY-on-Strong-Q3-Driven-by-AI-Push/697feb6747db7081af671059</guid><description>Latent View Analytics reported strong Q3FY26 results, with revenue climbing 22.0% year-on-year to ₹2,780 million and adjusted EBITDA rising 22.7% to ₹640 million. The company maintained a healthy 23.0% adjusted EBITDA margin and highlighted significant growth in its Financial Services practice. A key strategic focus is scaling AI and Agentic AI frameworks. A ₹46 million one-time expense due to new labor code implementation was noted.</description><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 00:10:15 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>