<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 12:39:48 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India-UK Trade Pact Ratification Awaits Parliament; Tariff Cuts Spark Sector Debate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-UK-Trade-Pact-Ratification-Awaits-Parliament-Tariff-Cuts-Spark-Sector-Debate/6991bb570caf1c998745dbe9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-UK-Trade-Pact-Ratification-Awaits-Parliament-Tariff-Cuts-Spark-Sector-Debate/6991bb570caf1c998745dbe9</guid><description>The India-UK Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement (CETA), signed in July 2025, is targeting an April 2026 rollout, contingent on UK parliamentary ratification. This pact aims to boost bilateral trade beyond the current estimated $56 billion by 2030, offering Indian exporters 99% duty-free access to the UK while phasing down tariffs on key British goods like Scotch whisky and automobiles. A parallel Double Contributions Convention is also set for implementation. Debates in the UK's House of Commons and House of Lords are underway, representing the critical next phase. Chris Bryant, Minister of State, described the agreement as a "momentous achievement."</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 12:25:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991bb570caf1c998745dbe8_1771158469809.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Manappuram Finance: RBI Nod Comes With Regulatory Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Manappuram-Finance-RBI-Nod-Comes-With-Regulatory-Scrutiny/6991bb280caf1c998745dbd2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Manappuram-Finance-RBI-Nod-Comes-With-Regulatory-Scrutiny/6991bb280caf1c998745dbd2</guid><description>Manappuram Finance shares are under observation following the Reserve Bank of India's conditional approval for Bain Capital affiliates to acquire up to 41.66% stake. This marks the transition to a joint promoter structure, with significant regulatory conditions requiring ongoing compliance and strategic planning. Despite the milestone, the stock saw a slight dip, reflecting investor caution regarding the intricate oversight and future operational adjustments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 12:25:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991bb280caf1c998745dbd1_1771158476851.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Centum Electronics Exits Loss-Making Units, Bets Big on India's Defence &amp; Space Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Centum-Electronics-Exits-Loss-Making-Units-Bets-Big-on-Indias-Defence-and-Space-Boom/6991b3260caf1c998745da3d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Centum-Electronics-Exits-Loss-Making-Units-Bets-Big-on-Indias-Defence-and-Space-Boom/6991b3260caf1c998745da3d</guid><description>Centum Electronics Limited is undergoing a significant strategic overhaul, exiting its loss-making operations in Canada and initiating restructuring for its French subsidiaries. This move, which includes recognizing substantial impairment charges, aims to sharpen the company's focus on the booming high-reliability Electronics System Design and Manufacturing (ESDM) sector in India, particularly in defence, space, and aerospace. The company expects these actions to strengthen its financial foundation and drive value-accretive growth.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 11:51:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Startup Shift: Profitability &amp; Deep Tech Drive New Growth Phase</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-Startup-Shift-Profitability-and-Deep-Tech-Drive-New-Growth-Phase/6991ac9b0caf1c998745d8a3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-Startup-Shift-Profitability-and-Deep-Tech-Drive-New-Growth-Phase/6991ac9b0caf1c998745d8a3</guid><description>India's startup ecosystem, now the world's third largest, is undergoing a significant evolution. While boasting over 2 lakh recognized startups and approximately 125 unicorns by early 2026, the focus is shifting from sheer scale to sustainable profitability and value creation. New government initiatives like the ₹10,000 crore Startup India Fund of Funds 2.0 aim to bridge capital gaps, particularly for deep tech and companies in emerging regions, signalling a more disciplined investment approach driven by fundamentals, ethical practices, and global competitiveness.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 11:23:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991ac9b0caf1c998745d8a2_1771154718106.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Fears Trigger IT Sector Sell-off, Indian Markets Face Valuation Reset</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/AI-Fears-Trigger-IT-Sector-Sell-off-Indian-Markets-Face-Valuation-Reset/6991aa4b0caf1c998745d774</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/AI-Fears-Trigger-IT-Sector-Sell-off-Indian-Markets-Face-Valuation-Reset/6991aa4b0caf1c998745d774</guid><description>Indian equity markets faced sharp volatility, primarily driven by a steep sell-off in technology stocks on rising concerns over artificial intelligence-led disruption. The Nifty IT index plunged over 8% for the week, erasing significant market value. Foreign institutional investors (FIIs) turned net sellers, offloading ₹7,395 crore on February 13 alone, while domestic institutional investors (DIIs) provided crucial support. Analysts warn of structural headwinds and potential long-term impacts on the IT sector's traditional outsourcing model, advocating for a selective investment approach.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 11:13:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991aa4b0caf1c998745d773_1771154141987.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India AI Expo Signals Strategic Pivot to Global Platform Leadership</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-AI-Expo-Signals-Strategic-Pivot-to-Global-Platform-Leadership/6991aa420caf1c998745d75d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-AI-Expo-Signals-Strategic-Pivot-to-Global-Platform-Leadership/6991aa420caf1c998745d75d</guid><description>Prime Minister Modi inaugurated the India AI Impact Expo 2026, underscoring India's ambition to transition from a technology services provider to a global leader in developing and exporting AI platforms. The event showcases over 300 pavilions and 600 startups, emphasizing production-grade AI solutions across critical sectors. This strategic pivot aims to leverage India's growing AI ecosystem, address national challenges, and reshape its position in the global technology landscape, moving beyond its traditional role in the IT sector.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 11:13:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991aa420caf1c998745d75c_1771154143166.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Fears Spark IT Selloff; Indian Market Faces Crucial Levels</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Fears-Spark-IT-Selloff-Indian-Market-Faces-Crucial-Levels/6991a96d0caf1c998745d668</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Fears-Spark-IT-Selloff-Indian-Market-Faces-Crucial-Levels/6991a96d0caf1c998745d668</guid><description>Indian equity markets, led by the Sensex and Nifty, experienced a significant downturn, exceeding 1% losses for the week. The primary driver was a sharp selloff in the Information Technology (IT) sector, fueled by escalating concerns over artificial intelligence (AI) disrupting traditional business models. Foreign institutional investors (FIIs) maintained their selling stance, exacerbating downward pressure. Macroeconomic factors, including anticipated US Federal Reserve policy shifts and persistent geopolitical tensions, further clouded the market outlook. Despite the broader weakness, some IT stocks like Infosys and Wipro saw intraday rebounds from lower levels.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 11:09:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991a96d0caf1c998745d667_1771153897337.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal Focuses on Energy Security, Growth Inputs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Focuses-on-Energy-Security-Growth-Inputs/6991a9550caf1c998745d651</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Focuses-on-Energy-Security-Growth-Inputs/6991a9550caf1c998745d651</guid><description>India and the United States have finalized an interim trade agreement, setting a $500 billion bilateral trade target by 2030. The pact strategically addresses India's rising energy needs, aiming to secure crude oil and other vital resources at competitive prices through diversified sourcing. It also targets growth in sectors like steel, by facilitating coking coal imports, and the IT industry, through access to advanced U.S. technology. Tariff reductions on various goods are designed to invigorate trade flows.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 11:09:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991a9550caf1c998745d650_1771153929734.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fineotex Revenue Surges 46%, But Margins Squeeze Amid US Buyout</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Fineotex-Revenue-Surges-46percent-But-Margins-Squeeze-Amid-US-Buyout/6991a67e0caf1c998745d590</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Fineotex-Revenue-Surges-46percent-But-Margins-Squeeze-Amid-US-Buyout/6991a67e0caf1c998745d590</guid><description>Fineotex Chemical Limited reported a robust 45.90% year-on-year revenue growth in Q3 FY26, reaching ₹183.71 Cr. However, its profit margins faced significant pressure, with EBITDA margins declining to 18.96% from 27.23% YoY. The company also completed a strategic acquisition of US-based CrudeChem Technologies, aiming for global expansion.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 10:57:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Markets Navigate AI Fears Amid FPI Rebound and Sector Strength</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-Navigate-AI-Fears-Amid-FPI-Rebound-and-Sector-Strength/69919b7c0caf1c998745d32f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-Navigate-AI-Fears-Amid-FPI-Rebound-and-Sector-Strength/69919b7c0caf1c998745d32f</guid><description>Indian equity markets are grappling with global economic uncertainties and the profound impact of AI-driven disruptions, particularly on the IT sector. However, a significant rebound in foreign portfolio investor (FPI) inflows in early February, fueled by a new US-India trade agreement, is providing a counter-balance. Analysts point to strong fundamentals in domestically oriented sectors like banking, autos, and consumption, suggesting a potential leadership rotation despite broader market caution. Upcoming economic data and US Federal Reserve policy signals will remain key watchpoints.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 10:10:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69919b7c0caf1c998745d32e_1771150379781.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Religare Enterprises Plans Demerger Amid Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Religare-Enterprises-Plans-Demerger-Amid-Valuation-Concerns/699195270caf1c998745d0e0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Religare-Enterprises-Plans-Demerger-Amid-Valuation-Concerns/699195270caf1c998745d0e0</guid><description>Religare Enterprises (REL) will separate its financial services and insurance businesses into two distinct, listed companies, a strategy initiated post-Burman family takeover in early 2025. The insurance arm, Care Health Insurance, will remain with REL, while the financial services division will be housed under Religare Finvest Ltd. (RFL). RFL is slated for listing on BSE and NSE by Q1 FY28, featuring a 1:1 mirror shareholding. This complex restructuring aims to sharpen strategic focus and streamline operations, though historical demerger outcomes are mixed and Religare faces internal financial and valuation questions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:43:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699195270caf1c998745d0df_1771148737867.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bath &amp; Body Works India Pivot: Localization Over Replication</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Bath-and-Body-Works-India-Pivot-Localization-Over-Replication/699195060caf1c998745d059</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Bath-and-Body-Works-India-Pivot-Localization-Over-Replication/699195060caf1c998745d059</guid><description>Bath &amp; Body Works (BBWI) is undergoing a significant strategic shift in India, prioritizing deep localization over its established US model to capture a massive consumer market. The company plans to introduce ~500 sq ft neighborhood stores, targeting Tier 2 and 3 cities, alongside an aggressive multi-channel digital strategy. This move aims to accelerate growth from doubling the business every five years to potentially every three years. While facing intense competition from players like Nykaa and Myntra, BBWI sees India as a critical global growth engine, with over 50% of its India revenue already coming from online channels.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:42:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699195060caf1c998745d058_1771148676481.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>FPI Inflows Surge, But IT Sector Weakness Clouds Indian Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/FPI-Inflows-Surge-But-IT-Sector-Weakness-Clouds-Indian-Market/699194bb0caf1c998745cff8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/FPI-Inflows-Surge-But-IT-Sector-Weakness-Clouds-Indian-Market/699194bb0caf1c998745cff8</guid><description>Foreign Portfolio Investors (FPIs) injected ₹19,675 crore into Indian equities in the first half of February 2026, reversing months of significant outflows. This surge follows a US-India trade deal and easing global economic concerns. However, a severe sell-off in the Information Technology (IT) sector, triggered by advancements in AI, has introduced a sharp divergence, casting a shadow over the broader market's positive momentum. The Nifty IT index plummeted 8.2% in the week ending February 13, 2026, highlighting significant sector-specific headwinds.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:41:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699194bb0caf1c998745cff7_1771148677309.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nippon India Mid Cap Fund: 30-Year Legend Faces Modern Market Test</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Nippon-India-Mid-Cap-Fund-30-Year-Legend-Faces-Modern-Market-Test/699194b60caf1c998745cfe1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Nippon-India-Mid-Cap-Fund-30-Year-Legend-Faces-Modern-Market-Test/699194b60caf1c998745cfe1</guid><description>The Nippon India Growth Mid Cap Fund, a 30-year industry veteran, has delivered exceptional returns, transforming a ₹10,000 monthly SIP into ₹26 crore and a ₹1 lakh lump sum into ₹4 crore. Despite its stellar historical performance and high-risk adjusted metrics, the fund's significant Assets Under Management (AUM) of ₹41,727 crore and a notable expense ratio of 1.54% warrant close examination against current market conditions and peer performance.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:41:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699194b60caf1c998745cfe0_1771148615520.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NALCO-NLCIL Pact: India PSU Banks on Coal for Power Security Amid Green Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NALCO-NLCIL-Pact-India-PSU-Banks-on-Coal-for-Power-Security-Amid-Green-Push/699194b30caf1c998745cfca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NALCO-NLCIL-Pact-India-PSU-Banks-on-Coal-for-Power-Security-Amid-Green-Push/699194b30caf1c998745cfca</guid><description>National Aluminium Company Ltd (NALCO) has formalized a strategic alliance with NLC India Ltd (NLCIL) via a recent Memorandum of Understanding. This pact centers on developing a 1080-MW thermal captive power project and exploring renewable energy avenues to secure NALCO's long-term energy needs. The collaboration aims to establish a structured framework for power and coal supply, reinforcing NALCO's operational cost stability. This move positions NALCO to leverage established thermal capacity while navigating the industry's accelerating transition towards sustainable energy solutions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:41:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699194b30caf1c998745cfc9_1771148670340.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lodha Developers Buys 80% of Solidrise Realty for ₹294 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Lodha-Developers-Buys-80percent-of-Solidrise-Realty-for-294-Cr/699194af0caf1c998745cfb3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Lodha-Developers-Buys-80percent-of-Solidrise-Realty-for-294-Cr/699194af0caf1c998745cfb3</guid><description>Lodha Developers Ltd. has acquired an 80% stake in Pune-based Solidrise Realty Pvt Ltd (SRPL) for ₹294.07 crore, marking a strategic expansion in the Pune market. This move follows a robust third quarter for Lodha, which reported a consolidated net profit of ₹956.9 crore. The acquisition complements the company's aggressive expansion into new land parcels, aimed at developing projects with an estimated sales value of ₹34,000 crore.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 09:41:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699194af0caf1c998745cfb2_1771148619404.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Tightens NSOP, Airfield Oversight After Fatal LearJet Crash</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Tightens-NSOP-Airfield-Oversight-After-Fatal-LearJet-Crash/699189760caf1c998745ccf0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Tightens-NSOP-Airfield-Oversight-After-Fatal-LearJet-Crash/699189760caf1c998745ccf0</guid><description>Following the fatal January 28 crash of a VSR Ventures LearJet 45 carrying Maharashtra Deputy Chief Minister Ajit Pawar, India's Ministry of Civil Aviation is conducting a comprehensive study of non-scheduled flight operators (NSOPs) and uncontrolled airfields. The Directorate General of Civil Aviation (DGCA) has initiated a special safety audit of major NSOPs and is reviewing over 400 uncontrolled airstrips to implement uniform safety standards. This intensified focus occurs against a backdrop of rapid growth in India's aviation sector, particularly in private aviation, and ongoing concerns over market concentration and systemic risks in commercial air travel.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 08:53:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699189760caf1c998745ccef_1771145714058.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Maharashtra's $1 Trillion Ambition: Growth Drivers Clash with Pace Demands</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Maharashtras-1-Trillion-Ambition-Growth-Drivers-Clash-with-Pace-Demands/699188810caf1c998745cbf6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Maharashtras-1-Trillion-Ambition-Growth-Drivers-Clash-with-Pace-Demands/699188810caf1c998745cbf6</guid><description>Maharashtra aims to become a $1 trillion economy, bolstered by significant foreign direct investment (FDI) and extensive infrastructure development. The state is projected to reach a nominal GSDP near $578 billion in FY26, attracting a substantial portion of India's foreign capital. However, achieving the $1 trillion milestone by 2030 necessitates an unprecedented annual growth rate, potentially requiring 15-17%, a pace significantly higher than current economic expansion. This report analyzes the state's growth engines alongside critical headwinds that could impede its rapid economic ascent.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 08:49:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699188810caf1c998745cbf5_1771145541688.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tech Giants Wilt as Select Banks, Industrials Shine in Market Downturn</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Tech-Giants-Wilt-as-Select-Banks-Industrials-Shine-in-Market-Downturn/699188510caf1c998745cbca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Tech-Giants-Wilt-as-Select-Banks-Industrials-Shine-in-Market-Downturn/699188510caf1c998745cbca</guid><description>A broad market sell-off last week erased over ₹3 lakh crore from the market capitalizations of India's top listed firms. Technology behemoths Tata Consultancy Services and Infosys were the primary casualties, alongside major lenders and telecom operators. In contrast, State Bank of India, Bajaj Finance, Larsen &amp; Toubro, and ICICI Bank demonstrated resilience, posting valuation gains. This divergence highlights a potential investor rotation amid prevailing market caution.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 08:48:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699188510caf1c998745cbc9_1771145435047.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Religare Demerges: Burman Play Faces Execution Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Religare-Demerges-Burman-Play-Faces-Execution-Hurdles/699181780caf1c998745ca40</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Religare-Demerges-Burman-Play-Faces-Execution-Hurdles/699181780caf1c998745ca40</guid><description>Religare Enterprises' board approved a plan to split its financial services and insurance businesses into two listed entities, aiming to unlock shareholder value and sharpen focus. This move, spearheaded by the Burman family following their takeover in February 2025, will see Religare Finvest (RFL) spun off for financial services, while the company retains Care Health Insurance. Despite management optimism, the demerger faces complex regulatory approvals, potential execution challenges, and questions surrounding its high valuation relative to current earnings.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 08:19:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699181780caf1c998745ca3f_1771143679299.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Ambition: Talent Surge Meets Patent Paradox</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-Talent-Surge-Meets-Patent-Paradox/699175750caf1c998745c7c6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-Talent-Surge-Meets-Patent-Paradox/699175750caf1c998745c7c6</guid><description>India's artificial intelligence sector is surging, driven by exceptional talent penetration and high executive optimism, with BCGX projecting a doubling of the AI talent pool by 2027. However, a stark paradox emerges: despite a large volume of AI patent applications, India's grant ratio remains critically low, hindering true 'sovereign by design' capabilities. This, coupled with a significant workforce skills gap, presents a complex dynamic for the nation's AI-driven economic growth, particularly impacting the potential unlocked for MSMEs.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 07:27:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699175750caf1c998745c7c5_1771140583142.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CNH Bets Big on India: Rs 1,800 Cr Boosts Global Strategy Amid US Trade Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/CNH-Bets-Big-on-India-Rs-1800-Cr-Boosts-Global-Strategy-Amid-US-Trade-Shift/6991738f0caf1c998745c6df</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/CNH-Bets-Big-on-India-Rs-1800-Cr-Boosts-Global-Strategy-Amid-US-Trade-Shift/6991738f0caf1c998745c6df</guid><description>CNH India plans a substantial ₹1,800 crore investment over two to three years, focusing on a new greenfield tractor plant to double production capacity to 120,000 units annually. This move capitalizes on a recent India-US trade pact reducing tariffs to 18%, enabling a resumption of full-scale tractor exports to the US. The 'India for Global' strategy positions the country as a key manufacturing hub amid a broader agricultural equipment market growth projection.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 07:19:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991738f0caf1c998745c6de_1771140111013.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Charts AI's Future Amidst Global Power Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Charts-AIs-Future-Amidst-Global-Power-Shifts/69916b3a0caf1c998745c4b3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Charts-AIs-Future-Amidst-Global-Power-Shifts/69916b3a0caf1c998745c4b3</guid><description>UN Secretary-General António Guterres has endorsed India as the ideal host for the AI Impact Summit 2026, stressing artificial intelligence must serve all humanity, not just superpowers. The summit, February 16-20, aims to unite global leaders and tech CEOs on AI's equitable future. Guterres highlighted India's growing economic influence and its central role in shaping a multipolar world order, positioning the nation at the forefront of discussions on AI's potential and risks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 06:44:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69916b3a0caf1c998745c4b2_1771137968989.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-EU FTA: Strategic Gains Amidst Market Caution and Global Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-EU-FTA-Strategic-Gains-Amidst-Market-Caution-and-Global-Headwinds/6991637b0caf1c998745c2bf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-EU-FTA-Strategic-Gains-Amidst-Market-Caution-and-Global-Headwinds/6991637b0caf1c998745c2bf</guid><description>India's Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman's recent diplomatic engagements have yielded a finalized India-EU Free Trade Agreement (FTA) and paved the way for increased European bank presence. While lauded as a long-term strategic win, market reaction remains measured, reflecting lingering global uncertainties and implementation challenges. The economic outlook is buoyed by strong GDP projections, yet external factors like US tariffs and internal fiscal metrics present ongoing concerns.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 06:11:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991637b0caf1c998745c2be_1771135998306.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's SIP Trap: Emergency Fund Crisis Fuels Losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-SIP-Trap-Emergency-Fund-Crisis-Fuels-Losses/69915f4012665ef560f9b61c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-SIP-Trap-Emergency-Fund-Crisis-Fuels-Losses/69915f4012665ef560f9b61c</guid><description>Indian novice investors are falling into a "SIP trap," prioritizing mutual fund investments over essential emergency funds due to low financial literacy and peer pressure. This leads to high SIP breakage rates and financial distress when unexpected expenses arise. Experts stress a foundational approach, advocating for robust emergency savings before or concurrently with initiating investments to ensure long-term financial well-being and prevent wealth destruction.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 05:53:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69915f4012665ef560f9b61b_1771134996187.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Escorts Kubota Eyes US Tractor Exports Amid Trade Deal &amp; Global Strategy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Escorts-Kubota-Eyes-US-Tractor-Exports-Amid-Trade-Deal-and-Global-Strategy/69915e8d12665ef560f9b457</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Escorts-Kubota-Eyes-US-Tractor-Exports-Amid-Trade-Deal-and-Global-Strategy/69915e8d12665ef560f9b457</guid><description>Escorts Kubota sees a significant opportunity to export tractors to the United States following the recent India-US interim trade agreement. This potential expansion aligns with its parent company Kubota Corporation's ambitious 'Mid-Term Business Plan 2030,' which designates India as a critical global hub for R&amp;D, procurement, and production. Despite the promising outlook, the company navigates a competitive landscape, including established players like Mahindra &amp; Mahindra and John Deere, and a domestic market evolving with mechanization trends and affordability challenges. Mixed analyst sentiment and a current P/E ratio of approximately 30.8 suggest a cautious yet opportunistic outlook for the company.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 05:50:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69915e8d12665ef560f9b456_1771134812564.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unilever India Momentum Battles Global Headwinds: Market Share Gains vs. Currency Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Unilever-India-Momentum-Battles-Global-Headwinds-Market-Share-Gains-vs-Currency-Woes/69915dde12665ef560f9b3e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Unilever-India-Momentum-Battles-Global-Headwinds-Market-Share-Gains-vs-Currency-Woes/69915dde12665ef560f9b3e1</guid><description>Hindustan Unilever Limited (HUL) demonstrated robust performance in its Home Care segment, achieving its highest market share in India, a key growth market for parent Unilever. This strength is tempered by global currency depreciation impacting Unilever's overall turnover and ongoing portfolio restructuring. Analysts project sustained demand in India's FMCG sector, yet competitive intensity and currency volatility pose significant challenges.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 05:47:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69915dde12665ef560f9b3e0_1771134807244.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hero MotoCorp Charts Premium &amp; EV Course Amidst Market Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hero-MotoCorp-Charts-Premium-and-EV-Course-Amidst-Market-Headwinds/69915ddd12665ef560f9b3ca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hero-MotoCorp-Charts-Premium-and-EV-Course-Amidst-Market-Headwinds/69915ddd12665ef560f9b3ca</guid><description>Hero MotoCorp is aggressively pivoting to high-potential segments including scooters, premium motorcycles, and electric vehicles to expand its market share beyond commuter dominance. The company reported a 16% surge in Q3 FY25 sales volumes to 16.97 lakh units and achieved a PAT of ₹1,275 crore, even after factoring in a ₹119 crore charge related to new labor laws. Despite optimism for industry growth, the success of its EV and premium ambitions will depend on navigating a highly competitive landscape and ensuring supply chain resilience.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 05:47:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69915ddd12665ef560f9b3c9_1771134699238.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's GST Reforms: Cancer Care Affordable, But Execution Key</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-GST-Reforms-Cancer-Care-Affordable-But-Execution-Key/6991574a12665ef560f9b18c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Indias-GST-Reforms-Cancer-Care-Affordable-But-Execution-Key/6991574a12665ef560f9b18c</guid><description>India's Goods and Services Tax (GST) framework has undergone significant reform, notably removing taxes on life-saving cancer drugs and medical equipment and exempting health insurance premiums. This aims to drastically reduce patient out-of-pocket expenditure. Concurrently, a higher GST slab on tobacco products is intended to fund cancer care initiatives. However, the actual impact hinges on manufacturers passing benefits, effective implementation, and whether tobacco revenues adequately support healthcare, presenting a complex outlook for the sector.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 05:19:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991574a12665ef560f9b18b_1771132982054.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Reliance's Acquisitions: Midas Touch Fades on Many Bets</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Reliances-Acquisitions-Midas-Touch-Fades-on-Many-Bets/6991565c12665ef560f9b0a6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Reliances-Acquisitions-Midas-Touch-Fades-on-Many-Bets/6991565c12665ef560f9b0a6</guid><description>Reliance Industries' expansive acquisition strategy presents a bifurcated performance narrative. While strategic investments in Asian Paints and EIH Hotels have yielded significant returns, many other acquisitions such as Just Dial, Alok Industries, Den Networks, Hathway Cable &amp; Datacom, Balaji Telefilms, and HFCL have struggled to impress investors. This divergence highlights how sector-specific headwinds, competitive pressures, and operational challenges can overshadow the conglomerate's backing, leading to underperformance and testing investor patience across its varied portfolio.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 05:15:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991565c12665ef560f9b0a5_1771132695191.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Curbs Broker Lending, Shifting Focus from Speculation to Stability</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Curbs-Broker-Lending-Shifting-Focus-from-Speculation-to-Stability/6991345212665ef560f9a9a3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Curbs-Broker-Lending-Shifting-Focus-from-Speculation-to-Stability/6991345212665ef560f9a9a3</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has enforced stringent regulations on credit facilities for securities firms, effective April 1, 2026. All loans to capital market intermediaries must now be fully secured, with proprietary trading by brokers prohibited. These measures follow recent tax hikes on derivatives and aim to curb speculative market activity, potentially impacting trading volumes but strengthening financial system resilience. The banking sector's average P/E ratio hovers around 12.6x, positioning it to adapt to these shifts.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 02:49:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991345212665ef560f9a9a2_1771123953646.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Budget Survey Stance Risks Economic Resilience, Investor Confidence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-Survey-Stance-Risks-Economic-Resilience-Investor-Confidence/699133e112665ef560f9a96c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-Survey-Stance-Risks-Economic-Resilience-Investor-Confidence/699133e112665ef560f9a96c</guid><description>The 2025-2026 Indian Economic Survey suggests development needs should precede climate mitigation, framing growth as adaptation. This approach, however, risks overlooking the immediate, quantifiable economic costs of climate disasters, which already inflict billions in damages annually. Critics argue this prioritization may deter crucial foreign investment, particularly from ESG-focused funds, and create long-term economic vulnerabilities despite stated sustainability goals.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 02:48:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699133e112665ef560f9a96b_1771123869626.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mixed Signals: Brokerages Cheer, but Valuations Raise Eyebrows</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Mixed-Signals-Brokerages-Cheer-but-Valuations-Raise-Eyebrows/6991315712665ef560f9a7f7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Mixed-Signals-Brokerages-Cheer-but-Valuations-Raise-Eyebrows/6991315712665ef560f9a7f7</guid><description>Leading brokerages Motilal Oswal and Nomura maintain 'Buy' recommendations across Tech Mahindra, SBI Life Insurance, Indian Hotels, Britannia Industries, and Max Financial Services, citing earnings potential. However, divergent price targets and elevated P/E multiples, particularly for SBI Life and Britannia, suggest varying analyst confidence and potential valuation risks amidst sector-specific challenges like IT slowdowns and high FMCG valuations.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 02:37:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991315712665ef560f9a7f6_1771123227411.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Retail Investing Boom Masks Behavioral Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-Retail-Investing-Boom-Masks-Behavioral-Risk/699129f412665ef560f98ff9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-Retail-Investing-Boom-Masks-Behavioral-Risk/699129f412665ef560f98ff9</guid><description>India's burgeoning retail investment sector, marked by 25 crore trading accounts and consistent ₹31,000 crore monthly SIP inflows, is increasingly susceptible to a systemic behavioral risk. Many investors, despite professing long-term goals, are trapped in a cycle of frequent portfolio monitoring and reactive decision-making driven by loss aversion and emotional responses to market volatility. This disconnect between stated strategy and behavioral execution necessitates a structural overhaul in investor decision-making processes to safeguard wealth creation.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 02:05:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699129f412665ef560f98ff8_1771121293491.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India EV Two-Wheeler Market: Incumbents Gain Share Amidst Startup Strife</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-EV-Two-Wheeler-Market-Incumbents-Gain-Share-Amidst-Startup-Strife/6991178b12665ef560f98c79</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-EV-Two-Wheeler-Market-Incumbents-Gain-Share-Amidst-Startup-Strife/6991178b12665ef560f98c79</guid><description>India's electric two-wheeler market has seen a dramatic consolidation, with established players TVS Motor, Bajaj Auto, and Hero MotoCorp capturing 60% of the segment by January 2026, a substantial increase from 34% in 2023. This shift moves the market from startup-led disruption to incumbent dominance driven by scale and distribution networks. While TVS and Bajaj have leveraged their strengths for significant sales growth, startups like Ola Electric are facing severe market share erosion and execution challenges, contrasted by Ather Energy's strategic product positioning and steady growth. The evolving consumer priorities now favor reliability and after-sales support, reshaping the competitive dynamics.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:47:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991178b12665ef560f98c78_1771116608519.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Digital Surge: From Data Costs to 6G Ambitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Digital-Surge-From-Data-Costs-to-6G-Ambitions/699111ee12665ef560f989de</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Digital-Surge-From-Data-Costs-to-6G-Ambitions/699111ee12665ef560f989de</guid><description>India's economic momentum is propelled by a robust digital highway. Broadband subscribers have surpassed 970 million, fueled by data costs plummeting to approximately ₹9 per GB, democratizing access nationwide. The nation now leads global digital transactions, with UPI processing immense volumes. A strategic shift towards indigenous telecom technology, including BSNL's 4G network and ambitious 6G goals, aims for global standardization and patent leadership.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:23:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699111ee12665ef560f989dd_1771115169736.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Copper Stocks Correct Amidst Inventory Glut, Demand Slowdown</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Copper-Stocks-Correct-Amidst-Inventory-Glut-Demand-Slowdown/6991117612665ef560f988fa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Copper-Stocks-Correct-Amidst-Inventory-Glut-Demand-Slowdown/6991117612665ef560f988fa</guid><description>Copper's narrative of impending scarcity and price rallies is fraying at the edges. While long-term demand drivers like AI and electrification remain robust, recent weeks have seen significant copper stock corrections for key Indian players like Hindustan Copper and Hindalco Industries. This divergence from the bullish macro outlook stems from a confluence of factors: surging global inventories, particularly in the U.S., a more pronounced demand slowdown in China than anticipated, and evolving smelter economics. For investors, the current market disconnect presents a complex picture, moving beyond simple supply-demand equations to consider specific company challenges and escalating geopolitical trade implications.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:21:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991117612665ef560f988f9_1771115046588.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Restaurant Brands Asia: Scale Emerging, But Profitability Path Uncertain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Restaurant-Brands-Asia-Scale-Emerging-But-Profitability-Path-Uncertain/6991117112665ef560f988e3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Restaurant-Brands-Asia-Scale-Emerging-But-Profitability-Path-Uncertain/6991117112665ef560f988e3</guid><description>Restaurant Brands Asia (RBA) posted a 16.5% revenue increase to ₹5,773 million in Q3 FY26, fueled by 577 stores and 4.5% same-store sales growth. Gross margins improved to 69.9%, and EBITDA margins expanded, indicating early operational leverage. However, net losses persist, the Indonesian segment remains a significant drag, and the company carries a high debt-to-equity ratio. A recent strategic shift sees Inspira Global acquiring a controlling stake, injecting capital and aiming for value creation.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:21:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6991117112665ef560f988e2_1771115127345.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Domestic Institutions Lead as Investors Favor Growth Over Profitability</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Domestic-Institutions-Lead-as-Investors-Favor-Growth-Over-Profitability/699110fb12665ef560f98886</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Domestic-Institutions-Lead-as-Investors-Favor-Growth-Over-Profitability/699110fb12665ef560f98886</guid><description>Domestic Institutional Investors (DIIs) have overtaken Foreign Institutional Investors (FIIs) in Nifty 50 equity stakes, injecting significant capital into the market in 2025. Despite a broader market downturn in February 2026, particularly impacting IT stocks due to AI disruption fears, DIIs and FIIs converged on five key stocks. This includes banking and IT players like Mphasis and RBL Bank, exhibiting strong growth and strategic initiatives, but also Utkarsh Small Finance Bank and Swiggy, which currently report widening losses and asset quality concerns. Institutional conviction appears increasingly focused on long-term strategic growth narratives rather than immediate profitability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:19:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699110fb12665ef560f98885_1771115009100.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>