<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 21:19:28 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India Vital for Trials Amidst Global Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Vital-for-Trials-Amidst-Global-Volatility/6990d31a632d3e861c625364</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Vital-for-Trials-Amidst-Global-Volatility/6990d31a632d3e861c625364</guid><description>India serves as a crucial hub for global clinical trials, bolstering business continuity for organizations like Parexel despite escalating geopolitical tensions and regulatory fragmentation. CEO Peyton Howell emphasized India's expanding capacity and skilled talent pool, noting that AI integration enhances operational speed and accuracy. However, this strategic reliance on India is framed by Parexel as a necessary measure to counter global uncertainties and ensure the scientific integrity and representativeness of clinical research worldwide, with a focus on elevating human expertise rather than job displacement.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 19:55:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6990d31a632d3e861c625363_1771099018828.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Brands Eye Global Scale: Brnd.me's Data-Driven Expansion Strategy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indian-Brands-Eye-Global-Scale-Brndmes-Data-Driven-Expansion-Strategy/6990cbfd632d3e861c61f4a2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indian-Brands-Eye-Global-Scale-Brndmes-Data-Driven-Expansion-Strategy/6990cbfd632d3e861c61f4a2</guid><description>Brnd.me, formerly Mensa Brands, is capitalizing on a 20-year opportunity for Indian consumer brands to expand globally, fueled by trade agreements and accessible data. The company, under CEO Ananth Narayanan, focuses on a tech-first, data-driven approach and capital efficiency to build defensible brands. Despite a challenging roll-up market, Brnd.me aims for ₹1,600-1,700 Cr revenue by FY26, preparing for an IPO by strategically focusing on its core brands and expanding internationally.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 19:24:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6990cbfd632d3e861c61f4a1_1771097214377.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IOC Pivots to Anti-Fragility: Bolstering Energy Security Amidst Global Flux</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/IOC-Pivots-to-Anti-Fragility-Bolstering-Energy-Security-Amidst-Global-Flux/6990cbe1632d3e861c61f316</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/IOC-Pivots-to-Anti-Fragility-Bolstering-Energy-Security-Amidst-Global-Flux/6990cbe1632d3e861c61f316</guid><description>Indian Oil Corporation (IOC) is strategically enhancing its resilience by prioritizing 'anti-fragility' over pure efficiency. This involves diversifying energy sources, securing supply chains, and fostering optionality to navigate global disruptions. The company is aggressively pursuing energy transition initiatives, including compressed biogas and green hydrogen, to reduce India's substantial oil import bill. Supported by a leading market share, strong fundamentals, and a favorable 'Strong Buy' analyst consensus, IOC is positioned to manage geopolitical volatility and evolving energy demands.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 19:24:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6990cbe1632d3e861c61f315_1771097250872.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Stocks: Index Up, Individual Shares Down - The Divergence Deepens</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Stocks-Index-Up-Individual-Shares-Down-The-Divergence-Deepens/6990c1c92c7cdffb0a9ff637</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/India-Stocks-Index-Up-Individual-Shares-Down-The-Divergence-Deepens/6990c1c92c7cdffb0a9ff637</guid><description>India's benchmark Nifty 500 TRI rose 12.57% in the year ending Feb 13, 2026, yet only 26% of stocks beat the index, with average returns turning negative. Large caps held up better, but small caps suffered, with only 20.5% outperforming. This stark divergence, driven by tighter liquidity and AI anxieties, signals a challenging environment where stock picking requires deep analysis, unlike the euphoric 2021 period. Investors must distinguish between index performance and individual stock realities.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 18:41:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6990c1c92c7cdffb0a9ff636_1771094581361.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Weighs FDI Flexibility for Strategic Sector Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Weighs-FDI-Flexibility-for-Strategic-Sector-Gains/6990c17a2c7cdffb0a9ff1d0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Weighs-FDI-Flexibility-for-Strategic-Sector-Gains/6990c17a2c7cdffb0a9ff1d0</guid><description>India's government is proposing significant rationalizations to its Foreign Direct Investment (FDI) framework, including allowing graded investment limits within sectoral caps and harmonizing FDI definitions for listed and unlisted companies. These measures aim to enhance the competitive edge of Indian firms in strategic sectors like telecom, defense, and pharmaceuticals, while simultaneously clarifying downstream investment and pricing guidelines. Public consultations are slated to refine these non-debt instrument rules, balancing ease of business with national objectives. Recent trends show India attracting robust FDI, with inflows reaching approximately $80.5 billion in FY24-25, signaling continued investor confidence despite global economic shifts. The proposed changes reflect a strategic approach to capital inflow management, prioritizing both domestic fortification and international attractiveness.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 18:39:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6990c17a2c7cdffb0a9ff1cf_1771094453215.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Navigates US Oil Pressure Amidst Russian Supply Reliance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/India-Navigates-US-Oil-Pressure-Amidst-Russian-Supply-Reliance/6990c0e32c7cdffb0a9feba9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/India-Navigates-US-Oil-Pressure-Amidst-Russian-Supply-Reliance/6990c0e32c7cdffb0a9feba9</guid><description>US Secretary of State Marco Rubio stated Washington secured India's commitment to cease additional Russian oil purchases, a claim contested by Russia. India simultaneously reaffirmed its dedication to 'strategic autonomy' in energy sourcing, prioritizing national interest and market dynamics. This diplomatic exchange occurs against a backdrop of global oil market oversupply and bearish sentiment, complicating India's efforts to balance energy security with geopolitical alignment and its substantial reliance on discounted Russian crude.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 18:37:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6990c0e32c7cdffb0a9feba8_1771094345973.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Manappuram Finance: RBI Seals Bain Capital's Joint Control</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Manappuram-Finance-RBI-Seals-Bain-Capitals-Joint-Control/6990b90d2c7cdffb0a9f866d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Manappuram-Finance-RBI-Seals-Bain-Capitals-Joint-Control/6990b90d2c7cdffb0a9f866d</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India has granted final approval for Bain Capital's affiliates to acquire up to 41.66% of Manappuram Finance, signifying a substantial shift to joint control. The investment of approximately ₹4,385 crore at ₹236 per share triggers a mandatory open offer for an additional 26% stake. This move is poised to integrate Bain Capital's strategic vision to accelerate growth, bolster technology, and expand the company's nationwide branch network.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 18:03:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6990a59ce2b1df5863091208_1771090842946.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI Funds: Long-Term Bets vs. Short-Term Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/SBI-Funds-Long-Term-Bets-vs-Short-Term-Gains/6990b0f52c7cdffb0a9ee7ed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/SBI-Funds-Long-Term-Bets-vs-Short-Term-Gains/6990b0f52c7cdffb0a9ee7ed</guid><description>SBI Mutual Fund's equity offerings present a performance dichotomy: the SBI Contra Fund consistently leads over three, five, and ten-year horizons, signaling long-term wealth creation. However, the SBI Focused Fund captured recent market momentum, outperforming over the last year. The SBI Large &amp; Midcap Fund offers a blend. All funds carry 'Very High Risk'. Investors must weigh consistent long-term value against tactical short-term gains, aligning choices with their risk tolerance and investment timelines. Past performance does not guarantee future results, and market conditions remain dynamic.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 17:29:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6990b0f52c7cdffb0a9ee7ec_1771090265234.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Doubles Down on Climate Spending: Self-Funded Push Faces Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/India-Doubles-Down-on-Climate-Spending-Self-Funded-Push-Faces-Scrutiny/6990a45a2c7cdffb0a9e2a5a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/India-Doubles-Down-on-Climate-Spending-Self-Funded-Push-Faces-Scrutiny/6990a45a2c7cdffb0a9e2a5a</guid><description>Union Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman announced India's climate action spending has surged to 5.6% of GDP, more than doubling from six years prior. This substantial domestic investment signals a strategic pivot away from reliance on external aid, emphasizing self-sufficiency in meeting environmental commitments. The minister also advocated for equitable global climate finance, calling for adherence to the "polluter pays" principle, and highlighted the need for balancing emission control with adaptation strategies. Budget 2026-27 allocates significant funds for carbon capture technologies and renewable energy initiatives, underscoring a multi-pronged approach to a greener economy.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:35:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6990a45a2c7cdffb0a9e2a59.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Railways Pursues Rs 30k Cr GCT Revenue Amidst Sweeping Reforms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indian-Railways-Pursues-Rs-30k-Cr-GCT-Revenue-Amidst-Sweeping-Reforms/69909e722c7cdffb0a9dd440</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indian-Railways-Pursues-Rs-30k-Cr-GCT-Revenue-Amidst-Sweeping-Reforms/69909e722c7cdffb0a9dd440</guid><description>Indian Railways is targeting an additional Rs 30,000 crore in revenue over three years from its Gati Shakti Cargo Terminals (GCTs), planning to expand the network from 124 to over 500 terminals within five years. This initiative, alongside a comprehensive overhaul of passenger hygiene standards in general class coaches, forms part of the '52 reforms in 52 weeks' drive. The strategy aims to bolster freight capacity for sectors like automotive and cement while significantly improving the travel experience, signaling a broad modernization effort to enhance operational efficiency and service delivery.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:10:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69909e722c7cdffb0a9dd43f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Climate Spending Surge Signals Economic Ambition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Indias-Climate-Spending-Surge-Signals-Economic-Ambition/69909da22c7cdffb0a9dc7e2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Indias-Climate-Spending-Surge-Signals-Economic-Ambition/69909da22c7cdffb0a9dc7e2</guid><description>India has dramatically increased its investment in climate action, now allocating 5.6% of its GDP compared to 3.7% six years prior. This enhanced fiscal commitment, announced by Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman at the Munich Security Conference, underpins the nation's early achievement of two-thirds of its renewable energy goals, four years ahead of schedule. The strategy includes substantial funding for carbon capture and incentivization for renewable energy expansion, signaling a proactive approach to national environmental objectives and global climate finance discussions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 16:06:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69909da22c7cdffb0a9dc7e1_1771085341334.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Court Mandates Food Warning Labels: Industry Faces Major Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/India-Court-Mandates-Food-Warning-Labels-Industry-Faces-Major-Shift/699095822c7cdffb0a9d2bd9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/India-Court-Mandates-Food-Warning-Labels-Industry-Faces-Major-Shift/699095822c7cdffb0a9d2bd9</guid><description>The Supreme Court of India has directed the Food Safety and Standards Authority of India (FSSAI) to consider implementing prominent front-of-pack warning labels on packaged foods containing high levels of sugar, salt, and saturated fat. This move follows dissatisfaction with FSSAI's slow progress on nutrition labeling and emphasizes a critical public health objective. Leading companies like ITC, Nestle India, Britannia, and Hindustan Unilever may face substantial challenges in product reformulation and managing potential shifts in consumer demand.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:32:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699095822c7cdffb0a9d2bd8_1771083304197.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Namo Bharat Corridor Opens: A Catalyst for NCR's Economic Rebalancing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Namo-Bharat-Corridor-Opens-A-Catalyst-for-NCRs-Economic-Rebalancing/699094e02c7cdffb0a9d245a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Namo-Bharat-Corridor-Opens-A-Catalyst-for-NCRs-Economic-Rebalancing/699094e02c7cdffb0a9d245a</guid><description>The complete inauguration of the 82-km Delhi-Ghaziabad-Meerut Namo Bharat corridor, alongside the Meerut Metro, marks a critical juncture for regional development. This infrastructure milestone is projected to unlock significant socio-economic shifts, foster polycentric growth, and catalyze substantial real estate value appreciation in secondary urban centers like Meerut and Ghaziabad. The corridor aims to reduce travel times drastically, boost economic productivity, and integrate Transit-Oriented Development principles to promote sustainable, high-density urban expansion around transit hubs, potentially influencing migration patterns and creating new employment accessible within an hour.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:29:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699094e02c7cdffb0a9d2459_1771083086074.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Namo Bharat: Corridor Inauguration Sparks Real Estate Surge Amidst Funding Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Namo-Bharat-Corridor-Inauguration-Sparks-Real-Estate-Surge-Amidst-Funding-Scrutiny/699094402c7cdffb0a9d1b15</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Namo-Bharat-Corridor-Inauguration-Sparks-Real-Estate-Surge-Amidst-Funding-Scrutiny/699094402c7cdffb0a9d1b15</guid><description>The Delhi-Ghaziabad-Meerut Namo Bharat corridor is set to be fully inaugurated on February 22, marking a significant infrastructure milestone. This development has already fueled a substantial surge in real estate values along its alignment, with some areas seeing price jumps of up to 67% in two years. However, questions linger regarding the long-term financial health and funding trajectory of the National Capital Region Transport Corporation (NCRTC) as budgetary allocations show a downward trend.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:26:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699094402c7cdffb0a9d1b14_1771082956020.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Airbnb Stock: Market Chasing AI Acceleration Over Stability</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Airbnb-Stock-Market-Chasing-AI-Acceleration-Over-Stability/699092d02c7cdffb0a9d0c39</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Airbnb-Stock-Market-Chasing-AI-Acceleration-Over-Stability/699092d02c7cdffb0a9d0c39</guid><description>Despite a strong fiscal year 2025 with $12.2 billion in revenue and $4.6 billion in free cash flow, Airbnb shares have struggled, delivering negative returns over the past year. The market's current appetite for AI-fueled acceleration and hyper-growth narratives is eclipsing the company's steady, profitable compounding growth. This disconnect is evident in Airbnb's valuation relative to peers and its steady single to low double-digit growth trajectory, which fails to excite investors seeking explosive expansion.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 15:20:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699092d02c7cdffb0a9d0c38_1771082572737.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian IPO Market Cools Amidst Valuation Concerns and FPI Outflows</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-IPO-Market-Cools-Amidst-Valuation-Concerns-and-FPI-Outflows/699088992c7cdffb0a9c7747</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-IPO-Market-Cools-Amidst-Valuation-Concerns-and-FPI-Outflows/699088992c7cdffb0a9c7747</guid><description>The Indian primary market experienced a significant downturn in January 2026, with fundraising plummeting to ₹4,765 crore from ₹21,858 crore in December. This slowdown is attributed to subdued post-listing performance of recent IPOs, heightened investor caution, particularly in mid- and small-cap segments, and sustained selling by foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) driven by global growth prospects and India's valuation premium.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 14:37:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699088992c7cdffb0a9c7746_1771079931816.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GRSE Expands Research Vessel Fleet, Diversifies Order Book</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GRSE-Expands-Research-Vessel-Fleet-Diversifies-Order-Book/6990714f2c7cdffb0a9b3ce6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/GRSE-Expands-Research-Vessel-Fleet-Diversifies-Order-Book/6990714f2c7cdffb0a9b3ce6</guid><description>Garden Reach Shipbuilders and Engineers (GRSE) Ltd. has commenced construction of two coastal research vessels (CRVs) for the Geological Survey of India (GSI). These 64-meter vessels are designed for advanced geological mapping and mineral exploration. This project signifies GRSE's expanding capabilities in specialized maritime platforms, complementing its extensive order book which includes warships for the Indian Navy, multi-purpose vessels for a German company, and hybrid ferries for the West Bengal government. The diversified portfolio highlights GRSE's strategic importance beyond core defense manufacturing.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:57:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6990714f2c7cdffb0a9b3ce5_1771073952745.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 'Debt Shift': Rapid Rise in Household Credit Fuels Stability Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Debt-Shift-Rapid-Rise-in-Household-Credit-Fuels-Stability-Concerns/699070e72c7cdffb0a9b3816</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Debt-Shift-Rapid-Rise-in-Household-Credit-Fuels-Stability-Concerns/699070e72c7cdffb0a9b3816</guid><description>India's household debt has climbed to 41.3% of GDP by March 2025, exceeding its five-year average. This surge is primarily fueled by non-housing retail loans, which now constitute over 55% of borrowings, growing at a blistering 16.21% CAGR compared to a mere 4.10% for industry credit. Professor Dirk Bezemer highlights this "debt shift" phenomenon, drawing parallels to Western economies where lending migrated from productive businesses to households. While India's overall debt-to-GDP remains lower than many emerging market economies, the accelerating pace of consumption-driven borrowing and increasing leverage in the mortgage market present distinct risks to financial stability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:56:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699070e72c7cdffb0a9b3815_1771073988572.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Asian Energy Services: Profit Surge Masks Merger Risks &amp; Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Asian-Energy-Services-Profit-Surge-Masks-Merger-Risks-and-Valuation-Concerns/699070a32c7cdffb0a9b3477</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Asian-Energy-Services-Profit-Surge-Masks-Merger-Risks-and-Valuation-Concerns/699070a32c7cdffb0a9b3477</guid><description>Asian Energy Services declared a robust net profit of ₹18 crore for the December quarter, more than double the previous year's ₹8 crore, alongside a revenue leap to ₹235 crore from ₹92 crore. This surge was attributed to strong project execution and O&amp;M contracts. However, the company is navigating significant complexities, including an impending merger with Oilmax Energy, which could lead to substantial equity dilution and has previously caused stock price volatility. Furthermore, historical financial performance shows weaknesses, with negative cash flow from operations and a below-average quality track record. Competitively, while the company's P/E ratio aligns with some sector averages, it appears elevated compared to industry leaders, raising valuation concerns.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:54:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699070a32c7cdffb0a9b3476.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NSIL Partners GalaxEye: A New Era for India's Space Data</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/NSIL-Partners-GalaxEye-A-New-Era-for-Indias-Space-Data/699070812c7cdffb0a9b3322</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/NSIL-Partners-GalaxEye-A-New-Era-for-Indias-Space-Data/699070812c7cdffb0a9b3322</guid><description>NewSpace India Limited (NSIL), the commercial arm of India's Department of Space, has formalized an agreement to resell satellite data and solutions from Bengaluru-based GalaxEye Space. This partnership marks GalaxEye as the first private Indian satellite operator to secure such a formal reseller agreement with NSIL. The collaboration will leverage GalaxEye's advanced Earth observation capabilities, including its proprietary SyncFused OptoSAR technology, to broaden market access and drive innovation within India's rapidly expanding space economy. With NSIL acting as an extended sales arm, the deal aims to bolster India's position in the global satellite data market.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:54:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699070812c7cdffb0a9b3321.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Fiscal Shift: Performance Over Protection in Tax Transfers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Fiscal-Shift-Performance-Over-Protection-in-Tax-Transfers/6990701d2c7cdffb0a9b2e6a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Fiscal-Shift-Performance-Over-Protection-in-Tax-Transfers/6990701d2c7cdffb0a9b2e6a</guid><description>India's 16th Finance Commission has subtly reshaped fiscal federalism, maintaining states' 41% share of central taxes but fundamentally altering how funds are distributed. A new 10% weight for GDP contribution signals a strong push for economic output and efficiency, while the elimination of revenue deficit grants and the introduction of performance benchmarks for local bodies and disaster funding mark a decisive move away from unconditional support. This recalibration aims to incentivize growth and fiscal prudence, potentially creating winners and losers among states based on their economic performance.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:52:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6990701d2c7cdffb0a9b2e69.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ixigo Expands to Europe: Spain Acquisitions Fuel AI, Rail Ambitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/ixigo-Expands-to-Europe-Spain-Acquisitions-Fuel-AI-Rail-Ambitions/69906f652c7cdffb0a9b23fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/ixigo-Expands-to-Europe-Spain-Acquisitions-Fuel-AI-Rail-Ambitions/69906f652c7cdffb0a9b23fb</guid><description>Le Travenues Technology Limited, operating as ixigo, has approved two strategic acquisitions in Spain via its subsidiary IXIGO PTE. LTD. The company will acquire a 60% stake in Spain's second-largest train OTA, Trenes, for €11.7 million, and a 45.02% stake in AI technology firm Sqaas for €0.45 million. These moves signal ixigo's aggressive push into the European travel market, aiming to leverage its AI capabilities and expand its rail booking infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:49:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69906f652c7cdffb0a9b23fa_1771073467269.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cautious Capital Inflow: FPIs Reallocate Amid Trade Deal Clarity and Tech Sector Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Cautious-Capital-Inflow-FPIs-Reallocate-Amid-Trade-Deal-Clarity-and-Tech-Sector-Woes/69906f2b2c7cdffb0a9b211a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Cautious-Capital-Inflow-FPIs-Reallocate-Amid-Trade-Deal-Clarity-and-Tech-Sector-Woes/69906f2b2c7cdffb0a9b211a</guid><description>Foreign Portfolio Investors (FPIs) injected ₹14,160 crore into Indian markets for the week ending February 13, 2026, marking five consecutive sessions of net buying. This inflow was primarily fueled by increased clarity surrounding the India-US trade deal. However, the overall sentiment remains cautious, with significant outflows from hybrid instruments and a mixed monthly picture for February. The sustainability of these inflows is contingent on the finer points of trade negotiations and a broader recovery from recent tech sector disruptions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 12:48:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69906f2b2c7cdffb0a9b2119_1771073465852.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Rs 1 Lakh Cr Urban Fund: Market Shift Faces Reform Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Rs-1-Lakh-Cr-Urban-Fund-Market-Shift-Faces-Reform-Hurdles/699046ba7e6478cdfc279f0a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Rs-1-Lakh-Cr-Urban-Fund-Market-Shift-Faces-Reform-Hurdles/699046ba7e6478cdfc279f0a</guid><description>India's Union Cabinet greenlit the Rs 1 lakh crore Urban Challenge Fund, shifting urban development from grants to market-linked, reform-driven infrastructure. Central aid will fund 25%, requiring 50%+ from markets via bonds or PPPs. A ₹5,000 crore corpus targets Tier-II/III cities' market access, while a credit guarantee supports smaller municipalities. The fund's success hinges on local governments' ability to implement reforms and deliver outcomes, a historical challenge.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:56:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699046ba7e6478cdfc279f09.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tiger Logistics: Volume Surge Masks Profit Squeeze Amid Market Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Tiger-Logistics-Volume-Surge-Masks-Profit-Squeeze-Amid-Market-Headwinds/6990445a7e6478cdfc279ea1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Tiger-Logistics-Volume-Surge-Masks-Profit-Squeeze-Amid-Market-Headwinds/6990445a7e6478cdfc279ea1</guid><description>Tiger Logistics reported a sharp 29.5% drop in Q3 FY26 net profit and revenue contraction, contrasting with a 52% surge in TEU volumes. This volume-profit disconnect highlights margin pressures from normalizing freight rates and increased finance costs. Despite a growing Indian logistics market, the company's stock has lagged significantly over the past year, testing its asset-light model's ability to translate operational gains into shareholder value.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:46:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6990445a7e6478cdfc279ea0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's ETF Surge: Gold &amp; Silver Outshine Equities Amidst Allocation Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-ETF-Surge-Gold-and-Silver-Outshine-Equities-Amidst-Allocation-Shift/69903bf27e6478cdfc279d43</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-ETF-Surge-Gold-and-Silver-Outshine-Equities-Amidst-Allocation-Shift/69903bf27e6478cdfc279d43</guid><description>January 2026 saw Indian investors channel a record ₹33,503 crore into gold and silver ETFs, eclipsing equity fund inflows. This surge reflects a maturing asset allocation culture, propelled by robust precious metal performance and a search for diversification amidst equity market softness. While silver ETFs have significantly outperformed gold over recent years, experts caution against chasing momentum without disciplined portfolio construction, highlighting inherent volatility and the risk of over-allocation.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:10:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69903bf27e6478cdfc279d42.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Changi Eyes India's Skies, Seeks Partners for Airport Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Changi-Eyes-Indias-Skies-Seeks-Partners-for-Airport-Growth/69903afd7e6478cdfc279cf2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Changi-Eyes-Indias-Skies-Seeks-Partners-for-Airport-Growth/69903afd7e6478cdfc279cf2</guid><description>Changi Airport Group (CAG) is actively monitoring India's burgeoning airport development, signaling strategic intent to partner with local entities for expansion. Chairman Lim Ming Yan highlighted CAG's technical management strengths, aiming for 'win-win situations' to navigate the growth potential and inherent complexities of the Indian aviation market. This approach contrasts with aggressive domestic expansion models and reflects a calculated strategy to de-risk investment.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:06:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69903afd7e6478cdfc279cf1.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget Boosts Infra, STT Hike Dampens Market Sentiment</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-Boosts-Infra-STT-Hike-Dampens-Market-Sentiment/69903a117e6478cdfc279caf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-Boosts-Infra-STT-Hike-Dampens-Market-Sentiment/69903a117e6478cdfc279caf</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 unveiled a substantial ₹12.21 lakh crore infrastructure outlay, aiming for a developed India by 2047 through self-reliance and export-led growth. However, the market reacted negatively, primarily due to a significant increase in Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on derivatives, which heightened trading costs and dampened sentiment. Maharashtra is positioned to be a major beneficiary of enhanced infrastructure allocations. While the budget champions long-term growth, underlying risks such as fiscal sustainability, execution challenges for large projects, and global economic headwinds present considerable concerns for the nation's ambitious agenda.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 09:02:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69903a117e6478cdfc279cae.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Africa's Mineral Wealth Trapped by Infrastructure Gaps, AFC Warns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Africas-Mineral-Wealth-Trapped-by-Infrastructure-Gaps-AFC-Warns/699033b57e6478cdfc279bbe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Africas-Mineral-Wealth-Trapped-by-Infrastructure-Gaps-AFC-Warns/699033b57e6478cdfc279bbe</guid><description>Africa holds $29.5 trillion in mine-site mineral wealth, strategically vital due to global supply chain realignments. However, the continent captures minimal value due to a profound 'conversion deficit' stemming from critical infrastructure, governance, and data gaps. These systemic challenges constitute the primary bear case, hindering Africa from capitalizing on its resource endowment despite opportunities in processing key materials like graphite, rare earths, and manganese.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 08:35:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699033b57e6478cdfc279bbd.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tech Giants Form Trust Alliance Amid Geopolitical Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tech-Giants-Form-Trust-Alliance-Amid-Geopolitical-Headwinds/699032967e6478cdfc279b69</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tech-Giants-Form-Trust-Alliance-Amid-Geopolitical-Headwinds/699032967e6478cdfc279b69</guid><description>Fifteen global technology leaders, including Amazon Web Services, Microsoft, and Google Cloud, have established the Trusted Tech Alliance (TTA). This initiative aims to create unified standards for transparency, security, and governance across semiconductors, cloud, AI, and connectivity, directly addressing escalating geopolitical fragmentation and technological change. The TTA proposes a framework for trust independent of a technology provider's country of origin, seeking to foster resilience and reliability in a complex global landscape.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 08:30:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699032967e6478cdfc279b68.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Railways: Kavach Safety Push Faces Cost, Staffing Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indian-Railways-Kavach-Safety-Push-Faces-Cost-Staffing-Hurdles/699031297e6478cdfc279ae9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Indian-Railways-Kavach-Safety-Push-Faces-Cost-Staffing-Hurdles/699031297e6478cdfc279ae9</guid><description>Indian Railways has nearly tripled its safety expenditure over the past decade to ₹1.17 lakh crore, driven by the Kavach train protection system and expanded CCTV surveillance. While this has contributed to a significant reported decline in accidents, the rollout faces substantial execution challenges, a persistent high operating ratio, and a critical deficit of over 1.5 lakh safety personnel. These factors raise questions about the long-term efficacy and financial sustainability of the modernization drive, despite significant capital outlays.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 08:24:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699031297e6478cdfc279ae8.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Assam's Brahmaputra Tunnel: Rs 18,662 Cr Infra Gambit Faces Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Assams-Brahmaputra-Tunnel-Rs-18662-Cr-Infra-Gambit-Faces-Scrutiny/69902c007e6478cdfc279a18</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Assams-Brahmaputra-Tunnel-Rs-18662-Cr-Infra-Gambit-Faces-Scrutiny/69902c007e6478cdfc279a18</guid><description>India's Union Cabinet approved the Rs 18,662 crore underwater twin-tube railway and road tunnel project beneath the Brahmaputra River, connecting Gohpur and Numaligarh. This 33.7 km corridor, a first for the nation, aims to bolster Northeast connectivity and economic development. However, the project's considerable cost, demanding engineering in a seismically active and flood-prone region, coupled with its strategic timing before state elections, prompts critical examination of its feasibility and ultimate benefits.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 08:02:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69902c007e6478cdfc279a17.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Signature Global Eyes Commercial Pivot; High Valuation Raises Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Signature-Global-Eyes-Commercial-Pivot-High-Valuation-Raises-Risk/69902bfd7e6478cdfc279a10</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Signature-Global-Eyes-Commercial-Pivot-High-Valuation-Raises-Risk/69902bfd7e6478cdfc279a10</guid><description>Signature Global has formed a 50:50 joint venture with RMZ to develop a significant mixed-use project in Gurugram, backed by RMZ's Rs 1,283 crore investment. This venture marks Signature Global's ambitious expansion into large-scale commercial real estate, a departure from its core housing business. However, the company's already stretched valuation and the capital-intensive nature of this new segment raise questions about execution and profitability, especially given market volatility.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 08:02:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69902bfd7e6478cdfc279a0f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's MF Tax Tool: MF Central's Limits in Evolving Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-MF-Tax-Tool-MF-Centrals-Limits-in-Evolving-Market/69902b8a7e6478cdfc2799d8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-MF-Tax-Tool-MF-Centrals-Limits-in-Evolving-Market/69902b8a7e6478cdfc2799d8</guid><description>MF Central offers essential data consolidation for Indian mutual fund investors during tax season. Backed by CAMS and KFintech under SEBI's guidance, it simplifies tracking across multiple AMCs. However, its passive role and the increasing complexity of tax regulations, particularly post-Budget 2024 changes, highlight its limitations in providing strategic tax optimization and proactive financial planning.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 08:00:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69902b8a7e6478cdfc2799d7.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Softens India Trade Deal Claims Amid Political Realities</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Softens-India-Trade-Deal-Claims-Amid-Political-Realities/69902b127e6478cdfc27999c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Softens-India-Trade-Deal-Claims-Amid-Political-Realities/69902b127e6478cdfc27999c</guid><description>The United States has significantly revised its public statements on the interim trade agreement with India, replacing definitive language with softer phrasing. Key changes include the transition from 'committed to' purchasing over $500 billion in U.S. goods to 'intends to', removal of references to tariff reductions on 'pulses', and dropping explicit mentions of India eliminating digital services taxes. These recalibrations underscore the influence of domestic political sensitivities, particularly within India's agricultural sector, and the non-binding nature of preliminary trade frameworks. The modifications reflect a pragmatic adjustment to manage political backlash while signaling a continued path toward deeper economic engagement.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 07:58:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69902b127e6478cdfc27999b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Delhi P2P Energy Trading: Regulatory Leap Faces Grid, Economic Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Delhi-P2P-Energy-Trading-Regulatory-Leap-Faces-Grid-Economic-Hurdles/699029aa7e6478cdfc27993e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Delhi-P2P-Energy-Trading-Regulatory-Leap-Faces-Grid-Economic-Hurdles/699029aa7e6478cdfc27993e</guid><description>The Delhi Electricity Regulatory Commission (DERC) has greenlit a pilot for peer-to-peer (P2P) electricity trading, allowing consumers with solar generation to sell surplus power directly. While this initiative promises greater consumer participation and potential cost savings, its successful implementation hinges on overcoming complex grid integration issues, long-term economic sustainability beyond initial waivers, and the scalability of its blockchain-enabled framework.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 07:52:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699029aa7e6478cdfc27993d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian IT Stocks Plunge: AI Fears Spark Valuation Reset, Stock Picking Dominates 2026 Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Indian-IT-Stocks-Plunge-AI-Fears-Spark-Valuation-Reset-Stock-Picking-Dominates-2026-Outlook/699026d97e6478cdfc2798ca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Indian-IT-Stocks-Plunge-AI-Fears-Spark-Valuation-Reset-Stock-Picking-Dominates-2026-Outlook/699026d97e6478cdfc2798ca</guid><description>The Nifty IT index experienced its worst weekly decline in over a year, plummeting more than 8%, driven by escalating AI disruption fears. Anand Shah, CIO at ICICI Prudential AMC, views this as a valuation reset rather than imminent earnings damage. He anticipates 2026 will be a year for selective stock picking, favoring sectors like metals and precious metals due to global reflationary trends, while maintaining a cautious stance on IT due to uncertain growth visibility and elevated valuations. The sector faces structural risks from AI automation, potentially eroding traditional revenue streams.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 07:40:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699026d97e6478cdfc2798c9.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's ₹1.60L Cr Infra Push: Strategic Growth Bet or Fiscal Strain?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-160L-Cr-Infra-Push-Strategic-Growth-Bet-or-Fiscal-Strain/6990254c7e6478cdfc2793ed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-160L-Cr-Infra-Push-Strategic-Growth-Bet-or-Fiscal-Strain/6990254c7e6478cdfc2793ed</guid><description>The Union Cabinet has greenlit ₹1.60 lakh crore in infrastructure and startup funding projects, marking a significant development push from the historic South Block before its relocation. The package targets railways, urban development, and innovation ecosystems, signalling a strategic growth agenda. However, it arrives amidst ongoing fiscal consolidation efforts and persistent challenges in project execution and climate resilience, testing India's capacity for sustained, efficient capital deployment.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 07:33:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6990254c7e6478cdfc2793ec.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-Brazil Pact: Pharma, Minerals, Aviation Synergy Ignites Strategic Trade</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-Brazil-Pact-Pharma-Minerals-Aviation-Synergy-Ignites-Strategic-Trade/69901b967e6478cdfc278de7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/India-Brazil-Pact-Pharma-Minerals-Aviation-Synergy-Ignites-Strategic-Trade/69901b967e6478cdfc278de7</guid><description>India and Brazil are finalizing a suite of agreements to significantly enhance pharmaceutical exports, strengthen critical mineral supply chains, and bolster the civil aviation sector. These pacts, set to be signed during Brazilian President Lula da Silva's visit, include a 10-year multiple-entry visa for Indian tourists and eased business visa norms, aiming to deepen bilateral trade and investment flows beyond $15 billion. The collaboration targets India's strategic resource security and manufacturing ambitions.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:52:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69901b967e6478cdfc278de6.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Anupam Rasayan: Revenue Surge Masks Margin Erosion Amid Sector Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Anupam-Rasayan-Revenue-Surge-Masks-Margin-Erosion-Amid-Sector-Headwinds/699017d57e6478cdfc278d3c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Anupam-Rasayan-Revenue-Surge-Masks-Margin-Erosion-Amid-Sector-Headwinds/699017d57e6478cdfc278d3c</guid><description>Anupam Rasayan India Ltd. reported a 31.4% revenue jump to ₹512.4 crore in Q3 FY26, but EBITDA margins contracted significantly to 24.9% from 31.8%, limiting net profit growth to 11.6%. This performance highlights escalating costs and puts pressure on the company's valuation, which trades at a high P/E ratio, while sector peers navigate similar margin challenges. The company also announced a strategic acquisition in the US.</description><pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:36:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699017d57e6478cdfc278d3b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>