<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:35:55 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India Finsec Promoters Un-Pledge 49.3 Lakh Shares, Easing Promoter Overhang</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Finsec-Promoters-Un-Pledge-493-Lakh-Shares-Easing-Promoter-Overhang/69994f4b730b6847a5174663</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Finsec-Promoters-Un-Pledge-493-Lakh-Shares-Easing-Promoter-Overhang/69994f4b730b6847a5174663</guid><description>India Finsec Limited's promoters, Gopal Bansal HUF and Gopal Bansal LLP, have officially reported the release of a substantial 49,32,050 equity shares on February 20, 2026. This action represents 16.89% of the company's total share capital, significantly reducing the pledged promoter holdings and potentially easing overhang concerns for the stock. The total promoter shareholding remains at 55.98%.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:23:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69994f4b730b6847a5174662_1771655128951.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NCL Industries Promoters Boost Holdings via Open Market Buys</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCL-Industries-Promoters-Boost-Holdings-via-Open-Market-Buys/69994f47730b6847a517464d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCL-Industries-Promoters-Boost-Holdings-via-Open-Market-Buys/69994f47730b6847a517464d</guid><description>NCL Industries announced that key promoter group entities, Kalidindi Ravi and Kakatiya Industries Private Ltd, have acquired shares through open market transactions on February 19, 2026. While the acquisitions are marginal, they represent an increase in their respective shareholdings, signaling continued confidence from the promoter group in the company's future prospects.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:23:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69994f47730b6847a517464c_1771655098286.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Treadmill: Big Tech's Spending Spree Risks Bubble</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Treadmill-Big-Techs-Spending-Spree-Risks-Bubble/69994c93730b6847a51744fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Treadmill-Big-Techs-Spending-Spree-Risks-Bubble/69994c93730b6847a51744fb</guid><description>The global push for Artificial Intelligence has companies locked onto an expensive 'treadmill,' compelling massive, non-negotiable capital expenditures for fear of obsolescence. While projections show AI driving significant economic growth and massive industry spending reaching trillions by 2026, a growing concern is the sustainability of these valuations and the concentration of power. The technology sector, particularly US mega-caps, showcases elevated P/E ratios, albeit with increasing investor selectivity. Meanwhile, sectors like India's IT services are already facing steep corrections due to AI's disruptive potential on traditional revenue streams. The accelerating pace and immense cost of AI development present significant systemic, geopolitical, and labor market risks, hinting at potential market corrections if tangible, profitable outcomes do not materialize at pace.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:11:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69994c93730b6847a51744fa_1771654468029.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Central Bank of India Partners SBI Funds Management; ₹12.41 Lakh Crore AUM Access for Customers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Central-Bank-of-India-Partners-SBI-Funds-Management-1241-Lakh-Crore-AUM-Access-for-Customers/69994c04730b6847a5174478</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Central-Bank-of-India-Partners-SBI-Funds-Management-1241-Lakh-Crore-AUM-Access-for-Customers/69994c04730b6847a5174478</guid><description>Central Bank of India (CBI) has partnered with SBI Funds Management Limited (SBIFML) to offer its extensive range of mutual fund products to CBI's customer base. This strategic alliance will provide CBI customers access to SBIFML's substantial ₹12.41 lakh crore AUM and aims to diversify revenue streams for the public sector bank.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:09:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69994c04730b6847a5174477_1771654252632.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBL Bank Appoints Jaideep Iyer as Executive Director, Rajeev Ahuja Retires</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBL-Bank-Appoints-Jaideep-Iyer-as-Executive-Director-Rajeev-Ahuja-Retires/699948bc730b6847a517431d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBL-Bank-Appoints-Jaideep-Iyer-as-Executive-Director-Rajeev-Ahuja-Retires/699948bc730b6847a517431d</guid><description>RBL Bank has announced a significant change in its Key Managerial Personnel (KMP). Rajeev Ahuja retired as Executive Director on February 20, 2026, after a decade with the bank. Jaideep Iyer has been appointed as the new Whole-time Director, designated as Executive Director, for a three-year term beginning February 21, 2026. The bank also updated its fair disclosure code.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:55:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699948bc730b6847a517431c_1771653437889.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pashupati Cotspin Board Meets Feb 26 For Stock Split Proposal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Pashupati-Cotspin-Board-Meets-Feb-26-For-Stock-Split-Proposal/699947c7730b6847a5174283</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Pashupati-Cotspin-Board-Meets-Feb-26-For-Stock-Split-Proposal/699947c7730b6847a5174283</guid><description>Pashupati Cotspin Limited has announced a Board Meeting scheduled for February 26, 2026, to discuss and approve a proposed sub-division of its equity shares. This move, which requires shareholder and regulatory approvals, aims to increase share liquidity and affordability. An amendment to the company's Memorandum of Association is also on the agenda.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:51:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699947c7730b6847a5174282_1771653181024.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RPP Infra Secures Mega Orders, But Profit Margins Falter</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/RPP-Infra-Secures-Mega-Orders-But-Profit-Margins-Falter/699946e1730b6847a51741de</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/RPP-Infra-Secures-Mega-Orders-But-Profit-Margins-Falter/699946e1730b6847a51741de</guid><description>RPP Infra Projects Limited announced substantial new work orders, boosting its total order book to ₹3,964 crore. The company secured a ₹205.89 crore contract for Chennai's Global Sports City and a ₹52.17 crore flood mitigation project. Despite this influx, recent Q3 FY26 results revealed a dramatic 95.15% year-on-year profit decline and an eight-quarter low operating margin of 1.00%, signaling execution and cost management challenges within a cautious infrastructure sector.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:47:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699946e1730b6847a51741dd_1771652952892.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hi-Tech Gears: NCLAT Hearing Postponed, CIRP Stay Extended to April 20</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hi-Tech-Gears-NCLAT-Hearing-Postponed-CIRP-Stay-Extended-to-April-20/69994660730b6847a517416d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hi-Tech-Gears-NCLAT-Hearing-Postponed-CIRP-Stay-Extended-to-April-20/69994660730b6847a517416d</guid><description>Hi-Tech Gears Ltd has received a temporary reprieve as the National Company Law Appellate Tribunal (NCLAT) postponed its hearing scheduled for February 18, 2026. The tribunal has extended the interim stay on the Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP) until the next hearing, now slated for April 20, 2026. This continuation of the legal proceedings means the status quo is maintained, offering the company a further period of operational continuity amidst its insolvency resolution.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:45:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69994660730b6847a517416c_1771652814208.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Surges Amid Geopolitics, But Dollar &amp; Fed Cloud Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Surges-Amid-Geopolitics-But-Dollar-and-Fed-Cloud-Outlook/69994507730b6847a5174071</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Surges-Amid-Geopolitics-But-Dollar-and-Fed-Cloud-Outlook/69994507730b6847a5174071</guid><description>Silver prices jumped nearly 9% on February 21, driven by escalating geopolitical tensions and a retreat in the US dollar. However, underlying macroeconomic pressures, including a strong dollar and a divided Federal Reserve outlook, introduce substantial volatility. Analysts forecast a wide trading range, emphasizing tactical trading strategies amid conflicting market signals. Gold also shows strength, nearing $5,100 per ounce, indicating broader precious metal appeal.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:39:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69994507730b6847a5174070_1771652473950.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Emversity Secures $30M Series A for Skilling Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Emversity-Secures-30M-Series-A-for-Skilling-Expansion/699944fa730b6847a5174057</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Emversity-Secures-30M-Series-A-for-Skilling-Expansion/699944fa730b6847a5174057</guid><description>Emversity, an employability-focused EdTech platform, has secured $30 million in Series A funding led by Premji Invest, with participation from Lightspeed and Z47. This capital injection is earmarked for aggressive expansion across over 200 campuses and the introduction of new upskilling courses. The funding underscores investor confidence in Emversity's model of bridging the gap between higher education and industry demands, aiming to deliver job-ready graduates in a rapidly evolving skill-centric job market.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:39:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699944fa730b6847a5174056_1771652476283.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Embraer's India Ambition: 200-Jet Orders Key to FAL</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Embraers-India-Ambition-200-Jet-Orders-Key-to-FAL/69993d2c730b6847a5173dbc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Embraers-India-Ambition-200-Jet-Orders-Key-to-FAL/69993d2c730b6847a5173dbc</guid><description>Embraer aims to establish a Final Assembly Line (FAL) in India, contingent on firm orders exceeding 200 regional jets. President and CEO Francisco Gomes Neto has indicated this threshold is critical for the venture's viability, with a potential 2028 rollout if orders materialize soon. In parallel, the company plans a 'completion centre' as an initial step if the primary target isn't met immediately. This strategic push leverages India's burgeoning aviation sector, projected to need at least 500 regional jets, positioning Embraer to serve both domestic and potentially regional markets.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:05:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69993d2c730b6847a5173dbb_1771650433280.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Microsoft Gaming Pivots to AI Under New CEO Asha Sharma</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Microsoft-Gaming-Pivots-to-AI-Under-New-CEO-Asha-Sharma/69993d24730b6847a5173da3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Microsoft-Gaming-Pivots-to-AI-Under-New-CEO-Asha-Sharma/69993d24730b6847a5173da3</guid><description>Microsoft Gaming has appointed Asha Sharma, formerly head of CoreAI, as its new CEO, replacing veteran Phil Spencer. This transition signals a strategic pivot towards leveraging artificial intelligence for operational efficiency and platform innovation, departing from Spencer's legacy focused on studio acquisitions and content expansion. Sharma aims to balance AI integration with creative integrity, emphasizing games as 'art crafted by humans' while navigating an increasingly competitive and saturated gaming market. Microsoft Gaming reported over 500 million monthly active users, but faces headwinds including revenue declines in its gaming division.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:05:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69993d24730b6847a5173da2_1771650444747.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IPO Surge Meets Market Caution: 2026 IPO Wave Faces Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/IPO-Surge-Meets-Market-Caution-2026-IPO-Wave-Faces-Headwinds/69993c99730b6847a5173cf5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/IPO-Surge-Meets-Market-Caution-2026-IPO-Wave-Faces-Headwinds/69993c99730b6847a5173cf5</guid><description>India's primary market is set for a robust IPO week, with eight new issues launching between February 23-27. However, this surge occurs against a backdrop of a cooling IPO market in early 2026, marked by lower listing gains and heightened investor selectivity due to volatile secondary markets and global economic uncertainties. Companies must now navigate stricter SEBI regulations and focus on realistic valuations to attract capital.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:03:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69993c99730b6847a5173cf4_1771650331956.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BMW Eyes India EV Assembly: Cost Cuts vs. Luxury Rivals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/BMW-Eyes-India-EV-Assembly-Cost-Cuts-vs-Luxury-Rivals/69993c12730b6847a5173c5e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/BMW-Eyes-India-EV-Assembly-Cost-Cuts-vs-Luxury-Rivals/69993c12730b6847a5173c5e</guid><description>BMW Group is contemplating full local assembly for its Battery Electric Vehicles (BEVs) in India. This strategic pivot aims to leverage cost efficiencies and tariff advantages, accelerating electrification in a key growth market. The move follows the successful initial localization of the iX1 and seeks to enhance competitiveness against Mercedes-Benz and Audi, while navigating the rapidly evolving Indian luxury EV segment. Success will depend on scaling operations and managing component sourcing.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 05:01:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69993c12730b6847a5173c5d_1771650197258.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UPI's Invisible Security Upgrade: Trust Boost for Digital Payments</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/UPIs-Invisible-Security-Upgrade-Trust-Boost-for-Digital-Payments/69993712730b6847a5173b05</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/UPIs-Invisible-Security-Upgrade-Trust-Boost-for-Digital-Payments/69993712730b6847a5173b05</guid><description>India's Unified Payments Interface (UPI) is set for a significant security overhaul, aiming to make user sign-ups largely invisible by phasing out SMS-based verification. This strategic shift towards tokenized, back-end processes by the National Payments Corporation of India (NPCI) prioritizes enhanced fraud prevention and a smoother onboarding experience. The move is poised to further cement UPI's dominance in India's rapidly expanding digital payments market, projected to reach $10 trillion by 2026.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:39:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69993712730b6847a5173b04_1771648876024.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Digital Trade Pivot: Bilateral Gains vs. Global South Voice</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Indias-Digital-Trade-Pivot-Bilateral-Gains-vs-Global-South-Voice/69993473730b6847a5173a1a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Indias-Digital-Trade-Pivot-Bilateral-Gains-vs-Global-South-Voice/69993473730b6847a5173a1a</guid><description>India faces a critical juncture in digital trade negotiations ahead of the WTO's MC14. Emerging details from interim FTAs with the US and EU suggest a potential departure from its long-held opposition to customs duties on e-transmissions and participation in WTO's Electronic Commerce Joint Statement Initiative (JSI). This strategic pivot aims to secure bilateral advantages but raises questions about its influence and commitment to developing nations' interests on the global stage.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:28:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69993473730b6847a5173a19_1771648225143.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-Brazil Pact: Securing Critical Minerals Beyond China</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Brazil-Pact-Securing-Critical-Minerals-Beyond-China/6999332c730b6847a5173923</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Brazil-Pact-Securing-Critical-Minerals-Beyond-China/6999332c730b6847a5173923</guid><description>Prime Minister Modi and President Lula finalized a memorandum of understanding on critical minerals, aiming to bolster India's supply chain diversification away from China. The agreement seeks to strengthen resource cooperation and advance strategic partnerships, targeting a significant increase in bilateral trade. This move is crucial for India's energy transition and manufacturing ambitions, leveraging Brazil's substantial mineral wealth.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:23:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999332c730b6847a5173922_1771647922704.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Trade Tensions Persist Post-Court Ruling</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Trade-Tensions-Persist-Post-Court-Ruling/699932ef730b6847a51738f5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Trade-Tensions-Persist-Post-Court-Ruling/699932ef730b6847a51738f5</guid><description>Following a significant Supreme Court decision invalidating certain import tariffs, the US administration has swiftly implemented a new 10% global tariff under Section 122 of the Trade Act of 1974. This move maintains trade friction with partners like India, which is expected to bear the new levy, despite existing bilateral agreements and ongoing market volatility. The administration also confirmed that existing national security and unfair trade practice tariffs remain in effect, contributing to a complex and uncertain global trade environment.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:22:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699932ef730b6847a51738f4_1771647914968.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Rent vs. Buy Debate: Wealth Shift Amidst Rising Prices</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-Rent-vs-Buy-Debate-Wealth-Shift-Amidst-Rising-Prices/69992e21730b6847a51737ad</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-Rent-vs-Buy-Debate-Wealth-Shift-Amidst-Rising-Prices/69992e21730b6847a51737ad</guid><description>In India's 2026 property market, soaring home prices are increasingly outpacing salary growth, intensifying the rent versus buy dilemma. Changes in tax laws and robust returns from alternative investments are compelling a pragmatic re-evaluation, positioning renting not just as a lifestyle choice but a financially astute strategy for many. While property values climb, compressed rental yields and affordability concerns are reshaping wealth-building narratives beyond traditional homeownership.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 04:01:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69992e21730b6847a51737ac_1771646598000.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Industrial Giants Secure Major Global Orders</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indian-Industrial-Giants-Secure-Major-Global-Orders/699925a0730b6847a51735c9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indian-Industrial-Giants-Secure-Major-Global-Orders/699925a0730b6847a51735c9</guid><description>Indian companies across energy, infrastructure, and engineering sectors have secured substantial orders this week. Cochin Shipyard's ₹3,267 crore deal with CMA CGM for LNG vessels marks a turning point in global shipbuilding sourcing. BHEL secured a ₹1,200-1,500 crore power project from SAIL, while Power Mech Projects won ₹1,000 crore from Adani Power. These wins underscore India's growing industrial prowess and its increasing role in international projects, driven by government support and evolving global dynamics.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 03:25:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699925a0730b6847a51735c8_1771644493716.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Banks Monitor West Asia Risk Amid Resilience Drive</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Banks-Monitor-West-Asia-Risk-Amid-Resilience-Drive/69992481730b6847a51734fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Banks-Monitor-West-Asia-Risk-Amid-Resilience-Drive/69992481730b6847a51734fb</guid><description>Finance Secretary M. Nagaraju stated that the Indian government is closely monitoring geopolitical developments in West Asia and assessing the nation's financial exposure to the region. Despite rising global uncertainties, including potential conflict stemming from US-Iran tensions, the Indian banking system and economy are deemed resilient. The government is also focused on the long-term evolution of banking, emphasizing credit provision remaining bank-dominated and guiding the sector's transformation over the next two to three decades.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 03:20:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69992481730b6847a51734fa_1771644187019.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>OpenAI's $850B Valuation Bets on $280B Revenue Amid Spending Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/OpenAIs-850B-Valuation-Bets-on-280B-Revenue-Amid-Spending-Shift/69991bbb730b6847a517325c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/OpenAIs-850B-Valuation-Bets-on-280B-Revenue-Amid-Spending-Shift/69991bbb730b6847a517325c</guid><description>OpenAI is projecting revenues to exceed $280 billion by 2030, buoyed by a potential $100 billion+ funding round that could push its valuation past $850 billion. This ambitious outlook is tempered by a significant recalibration of its infrastructure spending, now targeting $600 billion by 2030, down from a previous $1.4 trillion projection. This adjustment reflects growing investor scrutiny on the immense capital required to fuel AI advancements, even as competitors like Anthropic also secure substantial funding.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 02:43:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69991bbb730b6847a517325b_1771641912690.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Embraer's India FAL Gambit: 200 Orders as High Bar</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Embraers-India-FAL-Gambit-200-Orders-as-High-Bar/69991529730b6847a5171850</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Embraers-India-FAL-Gambit-200-Orders-as-High-Bar/69991529730b6847a5171850</guid><description>Embraer is pushing for a commercial fixed-wing aircraft final assembly line (FAL) in India, contingent on firm orders exceeding 200 jets. President and CEO Francisco Gomes Neto indicated this threshold is crucial for viability, with a potential 2028 rollout if orders materialize this year. This move comes as India's aviation market is projected to require at least 500 regional jets, driven by rapid growth and government initiatives like UDAN. Embraer also eyes a 'completion center' as an interim step, while facing competition and a cautious stance from global giants like Boeing and Airbus on establishing similar manufacturing hubs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 02:15:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69991529730b6847a517184f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Brokerage Bets: AI, Silver Drive 10 Stocks Amid Mixed Valuations</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Brokerage-Bets-AI-Silver-Drive-10-Stocks-Amid-Mixed-Valuations/69990fa3730b6847a5171674</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Brokerage-Bets-AI-Silver-Drive-10-Stocks-Amid-Mixed-Valuations/69990fa3730b6847a5171674</guid><description>Indian equities saw a wave of positive brokerage recommendations this week, spotlighting ten stocks across diverse sectors. Analysts are betting on AI-driven growth for IT giants like Infosys, sustained demand for metals from Tata Steel, and a persistent silver deficit supporting Hindustan Zinc. Pharmaceutical firms such as Lupin are favored for their complex generics, while packaging solutions from EPL Limited and paint demand for Indigo Paints also feature. Go Digit's unique underwriting model and IHCL's hospitality strength draw 'Buy' ratings, alongside LG Electronics India and Lenskart for their market positions. Despite optimism, several counters face scrutiny over elevated valuations and past performance.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 01:51:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69990fa3730b6847a5171673.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LTI Mindtree Navigates AI Shift: Diamond Workforce &amp; Brownfield Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/LTI-Mindtree-Navigates-AI-Shift-Diamond-Workforce-and-Brownfield-Hurdles/69990fa2730b6847a517165d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/LTI-Mindtree-Navigates-AI-Shift-Diamond-Workforce-and-Brownfield-Hurdles/69990fa2730b6847a517165d</guid><description>LTI Mindtree's Chief Delivery Officer Gururaj Deshpande predicts a 'diamond' workforce, with fewer entry-level roles due to AI automation. The firm focuses on simplifying AI for enterprises overwhelmed by options, acting as a structure and governance enabler rather than a foundational model builder. This strategy addresses the significant challenges of scaling AI in complex, legacy brownfield environments, where operating models must be rethought for consistency and scalability, not just tool deployment. Amidst broader sector concerns over AI disruption and recent stock declines, LTI Mindtree's approach positions it to manage margin pressures and talent evolution.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 01:51:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69990fa2730b6847a517165c.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Defense Electronics Boom: Valuation Premiums Face Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defense-Electronics-Boom-Valuation-Premiums-Face-Scrutiny/69990f28730b6847a5171598</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defense-Electronics-Boom-Valuation-Premiums-Face-Scrutiny/69990f28730b6847a5171598</guid><description>India's defense sector is pivoting from traditional hardware to sophisticated electronics, with Kaynes Technology and Avalon Technologies leading the charge as key component suppliers. While revenue and order books show strong growth, the companies trade at substantial valuation premiums. This report analyzes their market position, competitive landscape, and the critical risks that could challenge their sky-high valuations, contrasting them with sector peers and broader industry trends.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 01:49:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69990f28730b6847a5171597_1771638683872.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Smart Meter Boom: Genus, Techno, HPL Face Execution Test</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Smart-Meter-Boom-Genus-Techno-HPL-Face-Execution-Test/69990f11730b6847a5171581</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Smart-Meter-Boom-Genus-Techno-HPL-Face-Execution-Test/69990f11730b6847a5171581</guid><description>India's ambitious smart meter program, targeting 250-300 million installations, presents a substantial ₹60,000-90,000 crore market opportunity. Genus Power leads in scale and market share, Techno Electric excels in high-speed execution and annuity revenue, and HPL Electric diversifies into water metering. However, sustained growth hinges on operational efficiency, balance sheet strength, and navigating competitive pressures as the sector matures.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 01:49:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69990f11730b6847a5171580.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI: IMF Flags Tsunami Risk, Growth Duality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-IMF-Flags-Tsunami-Risk-Growth-Duality/69990df9730b6847a51714c3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-IMF-Flags-Tsunami-Risk-Growth-Duality/69990df9730b6847a51714c3</guid><description>The IMF warns AI's labor market impact is a "tsunami," potentially displacing 40% of jobs globally and widening inequality. While projecting a 0.8% global growth boost, the fund highlights severe financial stability risks, including market volatility and increased systemic vulnerabilities. Investors and policymakers face the critical challenge of managing these dualities.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 01:44:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69990df9730b6847a51714c2_1771638369220.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kyndryl's India AI Push Faces Scrutiny Amid Reporting Issues</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Kyndryls-India-AI-Push-Faces-Scrutiny-Amid-Reporting-Issues/6999062a730b6847a51712aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Kyndryls-India-AI-Push-Faces-Scrutiny-Amid-Reporting-Issues/6999062a730b6847a51712aa</guid><description>Kyndryl is aggressively expanding its AI and digital transformation services in India, with a new AI Innovation Lab in Bengaluru and plans to train 50,000 students in AI literacy. This strategic push aims to bolster governance and cybersecurity initiatives. However, the company is currently under heightened investor scrutiny following a significant stock price drop in early February 2026, triggered by a delayed Q4 fiscal 2025 earnings report, disclosures of material internal control weaknesses, and the departure of key finance executives. A securities class-action lawsuit is also pending, compounding concerns about financial transparency and reporting integrity.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 01:11:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999062a730b6847a51712a9_1771636386396.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Muni Bonds Gain Scale, Eye Institutional Capital</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Muni-Bonds-Gain-Scale-Eye-Institutional-Capital/699900ad730b6847a5171146</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Muni-Bonds-Gain-Scale-Eye-Institutional-Capital/699900ad730b6847a5171146</guid><description>India's municipal bond market is undergoing a structural transformation. The Union Budget 2026-27 introduced a ₹100 crore incentive for issuances exceeding ₹1,000 crore, aiming to attract institutional capital by promoting scale, corporate-like financial discipline, and advanced credit mechanisms such as escrow accounts. This initiative moves the market beyond its historically fragmented and illiquid state, potentially enhancing its depth and tradability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:47:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699900ad730b6847a5171145_1771634960446.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nitin Castings Proposes BSE Voluntary Delisting at ₹273.36 Floor Price</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nitin-Castings-Proposes-BSE-Voluntary-Delisting-at-27336-Floor-Price/6998f6b0730b6847a5170f6e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nitin-Castings-Proposes-BSE-Voluntary-Delisting-at-27336-Floor-Price/6998f6b0730b6847a5170f6e</guid><description>Nitin Castings Limited's Board has approved a proposal to voluntarily delist its equity shares from the BSE. The offer, initiated by promoters, sets a floor price of ₹273.36 per share and requires shareholder approval. This move aims to acquire all publicly held shares.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:05:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6998f6b0730b6847a5170f6d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>