<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 01:25:20 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Hidden Indian Gems: 2 Debt-Free Smallcaps Poised for 2026 Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hidden-Indian-Gems-2-Debt-Free-Smallcaps-Poised-for-2026-Growth/695086784342f77179da2525</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hidden-Indian-Gems-2-Debt-Free-Smallcaps-Poised-for-2026-Growth/695086784342f77179da2525</guid><description>Two smallcap companies, Jyoti Resins and Adhesives Ltd. and Garuda Construction and Engineering Ltd., are gaining investor attention for their robust financial health and growth potential. Both operate with virtually no debt, boasting high Return on Capital Employed (ROCE) significantly above industry medians. Jyoti Resins, known for its EURO 7000 adhesive brand, has seen over 800% stock growth since 2020. Garuda Construction, a civil engineering specialist, has demonstrated impressive EBITDA and profit growth. With ambitious expansion plans, these firms are recommended for investor watchlists targeting 2026.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 01:14:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695086784342f77179da2524_1766885054989.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Rally Cools! 3 Indian Micro-Cap Stocks Poised for Explosive 2026 Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Gold-Rally-Cools-3-Indian-Micro-Cap-Stocks-Poised-for-Explosive-2026-Growth/695086274342f77179da24bc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Gold-Rally-Cools-3-Indian-Micro-Cap-Stocks-Poised-for-Explosive-2026-Growth/695086274342f77179da24bc</guid><description>While gold and silver saw massive rallies in 2025, India's major stock indices like Nifty 50 and BSE Sensex delivered modest returns. Amidst this, three micro-cap stocks—Strides Pharma Science Ltd, Cemindia Projects Ltd, and Sandur Manganese and Iron Ores Ltd—have been identified using key technical indicators as potential outperformers for 2026. These selections, based on signals like RSI, MACD, and ADX, suggest significant long-term potential, especially after notable price breakouts and consolidation phases.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 01:14:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695086274342f77179da24bb_1766885006222.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Wines Conquer Global Markets: Fruit-Based Brews Spark Export Boom!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indian-Wines-Conquer-Global-Markets-Fruit-Based-Brews-Spark-Export-Boom/695079e74342f77179da1ff9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Indian-Wines-Conquer-Global-Markets-Fruit-Based-Brews-Spark-Export-Boom/695079e74342f77179da1ff9</guid><description>India's non-grape wines, made from fruits like jamun, mango, and apple, are achieving significant export success, reaching markets like the US, UAE, and UK. Exports surged to a record $6.7 million in the first seven months of the fiscal year, more than doubling the previous year's performance. This growth is driven by companies like Sula Vineyards and newer players, as they focus on international markets due to tepid domestic sales.</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 00:21:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695079e74342f77179da1ff8_1766881855363.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>