<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 01:18:37 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India's AI Future Ignites: 2026 Poised for Massive BOOM as Govt &amp; Big Tech Pour Billions into Tech Revolution!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Future-Ignites-2026-Poised-for-Massive-BOOM-as-Govt-and-Big-Tech-Pour-Billions-into-Tech-Revolution/695477e64342f77179ecca5d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Future-Ignites-2026-Poised-for-Massive-BOOM-as-Govt-and-Big-Tech-Pour-Billions-into-Tech-Revolution/695477e64342f77179ecca5d</guid><description>India is set for a significant AI surge in 2026, driven by government-backed startups building foundational models and Big Tech's massive investment in data centers. The nation will host the global AI summit, aiming to showcase 'sovereign' AI trained on non-English data. Expect growth in local datasets, regulatory clarity, and a boom in data centers, potentially mirroring the IT services revolution of the past, with generative AI projected to reach $438 billion by 2030.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:55:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695477e64342f77179ecca5c_1767143527131.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India IPOs: PE/VC Cashes Out ₹20,643 Cr, But Market Share Plummets to Decade Low!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-IPOs-PEVC-Cashes-Out-20643-Cr-But-Market-Share-Plummets-to-Decade-Low/6954773c4342f77179ecc893</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-IPOs-PEVC-Cashes-Out-20643-Cr-But-Market-Share-Plummets-to-Decade-Low/6954773c4342f77179ecc893</guid><description>In 2025, private equity and venture capital firms achieved their highest cash extraction from Indian IPOs in four years, totaling ₹20,643 crore. However, their participation in the primary market dropped to an 18.45% share, the lowest in a decade. This trend reflects a strong broader economy and increased promoter exits, rather than a slowdown in PE/VC strategy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:55:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6954773c4342f77179ecc892_1767143296418.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Raja Venkatraman's Top Stock Picks Revealed! Buy HINDALCO, UPL? Sell GODREJPROP? Find Out Now!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Raja-Venkatramans-Top-Stock-Picks-Revealed-Buy-HINDALCO-UPL-Sell-GODREJPROP-Find-Out-Now/695477464342f77179ecc8de</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Raja-Venkatramans-Top-Stock-Picks-Revealed-Buy-HINDALCO-UPL-Sell-GODREJPROP-Find-Out-Now/695477464342f77179ecc8de</guid><description>Indian markets ended flat on Dec 30th amid cautious investor sentiment and mixed global cues. Raja Venkatraman of NeoTrader shared his top stock recommendations: Buy Hindalco Industries above ₹885, UPL above ₹789, and Sell Godrej Properties below ₹1975. Investors are watching upcoming earnings and geopolitical events.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:55:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695477464342f77179ecc8dd_1767143371651.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sensex's Stoic Calm: How India's Stock Market Beat Global Storms in 2025 – shocking insights!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Sensexs-Stoic-Calm-How-Indias-Stock-Market-Beat-Global-Storms-in-2025-shocking-insights/695476fa4342f77179ecc824</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Sensexs-Stoic-Calm-How-Indias-Stock-Market-Beat-Global-Storms-in-2025-shocking-insights/695476fa4342f77179ecc824</guid><description>In 2025, India's Sensex index showed remarkable resilience, achieving an 8% year-end return with a minimal 9% maximum drawdown despite global tariff wars and geopolitical tensions. This stability is attributed to a structural shift towards stronger domestic capital, steady Systematic Investment Plan (SIP) inflows, and a market microstructure that balances supply from IPOs and QIPs with consistent domestic demand, effectively insulating it from external shocks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:55:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695476fa4342f77179ecc823_1767143528696.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Market Tumbles! MarketSmith India Picks Nykaa, Choice International for Big Gains - Buy Now?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Market-Tumbles-MarketSmith-India-Picks-Nykaa-Choice-International-for-Big-Gains-Buy-Now/695476c54342f77179ecc78b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Market-Tumbles-MarketSmith-India-Picks-Nykaa-Choice-International-for-Big-Gains-Buy-Now/695476c54342f77179ecc78b</guid><description>Indian markets closed subdued on December 31st. MarketSmith India has recommended buying FSN E-Commerce Ventures (Nykaa) for its strong brand and Choice International Ltd for its financial platform. Learn why these stocks are highlighted amidst cautious trading and technical signals.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:55:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695476c54342f77179ecc78a_1767143227536.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Why FPIs Are STILL Investing Billions in India, Even as They Sell Stocks!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Why-FPIs-Are-STILL-Investing-Billions-in-India-Even-as-They-Sell-Stocks/695476104342f77179ecc6ad</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Why-FPIs-Are-STILL-Investing-Billions-in-India-Even-as-They-Sell-Stocks/695476104342f77179ecc6ad</guid><description>Foreign Portfolio Investors (FPIs) have offloaded a record ₹ 2.34 trillion in Indian stocks in 2025 but invested ₹ 73,749 crore in primary markets (IPOs), the second-highest on record. This shift signals long-term growth conviction despite India's underperformance versus peers like China and South Korea, and concerns over valuations and earnings growth. Historically, FPIs have shown a net buying trend in India via primary markets, offsetting secondary market sales.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:55:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695476104342f77179ecc6ac_1767143008495.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Trump's Trade Bombshell: Global Chaos Erupts as America First Policy Rewrites World Order!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Trumps-Trade-Bombshell-Global-Chaos-Erupts-as-America-First-Policy-Rewrites-World-Order/695475594342f77179ecc5d7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Trumps-Trade-Bombshell-Global-Chaos-Erupts-as-America-First-Policy-Rewrites-World-Order/695475594342f77179ecc5d7</guid><description>Former US President Donald Trump's 'America First' trade policy, implemented through widespread tariffs on 57 countries, significantly disrupted global trade and alliances. This protectionist approach weakened the World Trade Organization and altered global value chains. Unexpectedly, it fostered a thaw in India-China relations, leading to improved trade ties and normalized diplomatic exchanges, despite failed US concession demands from both nations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:49:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695475594342f77179ecc5d6_1767142806479.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vodafone Idea Lifeline? Government Cabinet Decides Crucial AGR Relief Wednesday - Will It Survive?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vodafone-Idea-Lifeline-Government-Cabinet-Decides-Crucial-AGR-Relief-Wednesday-Will-It-Survive/695474164342f77179ecc442</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vodafone-Idea-Lifeline-Government-Cabinet-Decides-Crucial-AGR-Relief-Wednesday-Will-It-Survive/695474164342f77179ecc442</guid><description>The Union Cabinet is set to discuss a significant relief package for Vodafone Idea on Wednesday. This measure is seen as a critical lifeline for the struggling telecom operator, which faces Adjusted Gross Revenue (AGR) dues of approximately ₹83,000 crore and a total debt exceeding ₹2 lakh crore. The potential relief could involve concessions on interest and penalties related to these dues, aiming to ease the company's severe financial challenges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:45:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695474164342f77179ecc441_1767142495732.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Massive ₹458 Crore GST Hit: IndiGo Slapped With Huge Penalty, Vows Fierce Appeal!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Massive-458-Crore-GST-Hit-IndiGo-Slapped-With-Huge-Penalty-Vows-Fierce-Appeal/695473bf4342f77179ecc3dd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Massive-458-Crore-GST-Hit-IndiGo-Slapped-With-Huge-Penalty-Vows-Fierce-Appeal/695473bf4342f77179ecc3dd</guid><description>IndiGo faces a substantial Goods and Services Tax (GST) penalty of ₹458.3 crore imposed by the CGST Delhi South Commissionerate. The airline stated on Tuesday that it strongly believes the order is erroneous and not in accordance with the law. IndiGo plans to contest the penalty vigorously and pursue appropriate legal remedies.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:45:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695473bf4342f77179ecc3dc_1767142411565.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coforge's Bold $2.35 Billion Bet: Is India's Top IT Acquisition Set for Explosive Growth?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Coforges-Bold-235-Billion-Bet-Is-Indias-Top-IT-Acquisition-Set-for-Explosive-Growth/695471064342f77179ecc167</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Coforges-Bold-235-Billion-Bet-Is-Indias-Top-IT-Acquisition-Set-for-Explosive-Growth/695471064342f77179ecc167</guid><description>Coforge Ltd. is defying the IT sector's slowdown, achieving the fastest sequential growth among top peers in 2025 and reaching the 7th position by revenue. Under CEO Sudhir Singh, the company secured its largest client win ($1.56 billion with Sabre) and announced India's biggest IT acquisition ever: the $2.35 billion purchase of California-based Encora. This aggressive expansion occurs while peers face declining demand, showcasing Coforge's robust deal execution, strategic client focus, and AI-driven roadmap.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:29:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695471064342f77179ecc166_1767141710379.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Adani Eyes Global Hub: Demands More Flights Amidst Airline Battle!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Adani-Eyes-Global-Hub-Demands-More-Flights-Amidst-Airline-Battle/695469bc4342f77179ecbc88</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Adani-Eyes-Global-Hub-Demands-More-Flights-Amidst-Airline-Battle/695469bc4342f77179ecbc88</guid><description>Adani Group is pushing the Indian government to grant more international flying rights to boost traffic at its airports, investing billions. This clashes with Air India and IndiGo, who fear unfair competition. Adani argues more capacity is crucial for India's financial capital to become a global aviation hub, warning of higher ticket prices and wasted investments if restricted.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:02:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695469bc4342f77179ecbc87_1767139846895.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gen Z's Mutual Fund Mania: Fintech Fuels Explosive Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Gen-Zs-Mutual-Fund-Mania-Fintech-Fuels-Explosive-Growth/695469474342f77179ecbbef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Gen-Zs-Mutual-Fund-Mania-Fintech-Fuels-Explosive-Growth/695469474342f77179ecbbef</guid><description>Young investors, or Gen Z, are increasingly flocking to mutual funds, especially equity-oriented ones, via fintech platforms. Fintech distributors are leading in new SIP registrations and collections, indicating a significant shift in investment habits among the youth. Data shows a growing percentage of investors under 30 on platforms like PhonePe Wealth, NSE, and CAMS-managed funds.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:00:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695469474342f77179ecbbee_1767139732684.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gen Z's Digital Domination: Banks Race to Capture Mobile-First Generation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Gen-Zs-Digital-Domination-Banks-Race-to-Capture-Mobile-First-Generation/695469174342f77179ecbbb7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Gen-Zs-Digital-Domination-Banks-Race-to-Capture-Mobile-First-Generation/695469174342f77179ecbbb7</guid><description>India's Gen Z is redefining banking, prioritizing mobile apps and UPI over traditional bank visits. Financial institutions like DBS Bank India and Bank of Baroda are seeing significant Gen Z adoption on their digital platforms, prompting a strategic push towards enhanced, user-friendly digital experiences to attract and retain this influential demographic.</description><pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:00:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695469174342f77179ecbbb6_1767139684044.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>