<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 01:16:14 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India's Economic Surge: RBI Deputy Governor Predicts Stronger Growth Driven by Reforms!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economic-Surge-RBI-Deputy-Governor-Predicts-Stronger-Growth-Driven-by-Reforms/694b3d52e10c98d0787a32a8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economic-Surge-RBI-Deputy-Governor-Predicts-Stronger-Growth-Driven-by-Reforms/694b3d52e10c98d0787a32a8</guid><description>Reserve Bank of India Deputy Governor Poonam Gupta is optimistic about India's economic future, citing rapid reforms that are expected to fuel stronger growth, potentially reaching 7-7.5% annually with limited downside. She also noted benign inflation trends, forecasting it to remain low and stable. Gupta expressed confidence in the rupee's resilience and the economy's ability to withstand global uncertainties, emphasizing the positive impact of Free Trade Agreements (FTAs).</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 01:02:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b3d52e10c98d0787a32a7_1766538649364.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dalal Street Buzz: Nifty Bulls Eyeing Santa Rally as Christmas Nears! 🎅🎁</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Dalal-Street-Buzz-Nifty-Bulls-Eyeing-Santa-Rally-as-Christmas-Nears/694b3b61e10c98d0787a31be</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Dalal-Street-Buzz-Nifty-Bulls-Eyeing-Santa-Rally-as-Christmas-Nears/694b3b61e10c98d0787a31be</guid><description>Indian stock markets, including the Sensex and Nifty, are showing signs of anticipation for a 'Santa rally' as the Christmas holiday approaches. Investors are looking for a year-end boost on Dalal Street, seeking positive momentum before the festive season concludes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 00:52:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Indian Markets Flat: Analyst Raja Venkatraman Reveals 3 Must-Buy Stocks for Big Gains!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Markets-Flat-Analyst-Raja-Venkatraman-Reveals-3-Must-Buy-Stocks-for-Big-Gains/694b3af8e10c98d0787a3143</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Markets-Flat-Analyst-Raja-Venkatraman-Reveals-3-Must-Buy-Stocks-for-Big-Gains/694b3af8e10c98d0787a3143</guid><description>Indian stock markets, Sensex and Nifty 50, closed nearly flat on December 23rd due to profit booking, while mid and small-cap stocks saw modest gains. Amidst mixed global cues, analyst Raja Venkatraman of NeoTrader recommended three stocks for potential upside: Ashok Leyland, HDFC AMC, and Dalmia Bharat, detailing buy levels, stop losses, and target prices based on technical analysis.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 00:46:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b3af8e10c98d0787a3142_1766538044926.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Market Flat, But 2 Stocks Could Soar: MarketSmith India's Bold Buy Picks Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Market-Flat-But-2-Stocks-Could-Soar-MarketSmith-Indias-Bold-Buy-Picks-Revealed/694b3a65e10c98d0787a3064</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Market-Flat-But-2-Stocks-Could-Soar-MarketSmith-Indias-Bold-Buy-Picks-Revealed/694b3a65e10c98d0787a3064</guid><description>Indian stock markets closed flat on Tuesday with the Sensex and Nifty 50 showing minimal changes, despite modest gains in mid and small-cap segments. MarketSmith India has issued buy recommendations for Bajaj Auto Ltd and S.J.S. Enterprises Ltd, citing strong fundamentals, brand leadership, and growth potential. The advisory service also provided specific target prices and risk factors for both stocks, alongside a technical analysis of the broader market.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 00:46:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b3a65e10c98d0787a3063_1766537976006.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Post Postmen to Sell Mutual Funds: Can Their Trust Overcome Market Risks?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/India-Post-Postmen-to-Sell-Mutual-Funds-Can-Their-Trust-Overcome-Market-Risks/694b3a2ce10c98d0787a302a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/India-Post-Postmen-to-Sell-Mutual-Funds-Can-Their-Trust-Overcome-Market-Risks/694b3a2ce10c98d0787a302a</guid><description>The Association of Mutual Funds in India (Amfi) plans to train one lakh postmen to sell mutual funds, leveraging India Post's vast network of 1.6 lakh branches. However, experts express skepticism due to challenges in training for complex products, potential mis-selling risks, and the need for robust digital KYC. The initiative is starting with simpler funds in a pilot phase.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 00:46:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b3a2ce10c98d0787a3029_1766538548576.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Rare Earth Powerhouse: Attero Plans Massive ₹2,000 Crore Expansion to Secure Critical Minerals!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Rare-Earth-Powerhouse-Attero-Plans-Massive-2000-Crore-Expansion-to-Secure-Critical-Minerals/694b397be10c98d0787a2f3a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Rare-Earth-Powerhouse-Attero-Plans-Massive-2000-Crore-Expansion-to-Secure-Critical-Minerals/694b397be10c98d0787a2f3a</guid><description>E-waste recycler Attero plans a significant ₹2,000 crore expansion over three years to boost battery recycling and critical minerals refining capacity. The move aims to enhance India's self-reliance in rare earths and support government missions, with the company also eyeing a public listing in two to three years.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 00:46:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b397be10c98d0787a2f39_1766538418811.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bajaj Auto's Bold KTM Rescue Plan: Can It Save the Premium Bike Giant Amidst Domestic Woes?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bajaj-Autos-Bold-KTM-Rescue-Plan-Can-It-Save-the-Premium-Bike-Giant-Amidst-Domestic-Woes/694b397be10c98d0787a2f65</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bajaj-Autos-Bold-KTM-Rescue-Plan-Can-It-Save-the-Premium-Bike-Giant-Amidst-Domestic-Woes/694b397be10c98d0787a2f65</guid><description>Bajaj Auto is launching a comprehensive revival plan for its major acquisition, KTM, which is undergoing judicial restructuring. The strategy includes discontinuing smaller brands, optimizing operations, and leveraging supply chain synergies to boost profitability. This comes as Bajaj Auto faces declining domestic market share, making KTM's turnaround crucial for its premium offerings and overall financial health. Efforts will ramp up in early 2026.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 00:46:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b397be10c98d0787a2f64_1766537665830.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Silver Skyrockets Past Apple's Value: Is This The Ultimate Safe Haven?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Skyrockets-Past-Apples-Value-Is-This-The-Ultimate-Safe-Haven/694b353ce10c98d0787a2d62</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Silver-Skyrockets-Past-Apples-Value-Is-This-The-Ultimate-Safe-Haven/694b353ce10c98d0787a2d62</guid><description>Silver prices have surged dramatically, pushing its market capitalization to $4.04 trillion, now exceeding tech giant Apple Inc.'s $4.02 trillion. This unprecedented rally makes silver the third most valuable asset globally, trailing only gold and Nvidia, signaling a significant shift in investor preferences towards precious metals.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 00:25:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b353ce10c98d0787a2d61_1766536861794.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coca-Cola India's Big Shake-Up: Hundreds of Jobs Cut as Bottler Targets Profit Boost!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Coca-Cola-Indias-Big-Shake-Up-Hundreds-of-Jobs-Cut-as-Bottler-Targets-Profit-Boost/694b3317e10c98d0787a2c6e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Coca-Cola-Indias-Big-Shake-Up-Hundreds-of-Jobs-Cut-as-Bottler-Targets-Profit-Boost/694b3317e10c98d0787a2c6e</guid><description>Hindustan Coca-Cola Beverages (HCCB), Coca-Cola's bottling arm in India, is laying off approximately 300 employees across various functions like sales, supply chain, and plant operations. This move, affecting about 4-6% of its 5,000-strong workforce, aims to enhance profitability and streamline operations under its new CEO, Hemant Rupani. The company reported a significant 73% drop in net profit for FY25 to ₹756.64 crore and a 9% decline in revenue, partly due to selling bottling operations and muted demand.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 00:17:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b3317e10c98d0787a2c6d_1766536174973.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>