<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 01:30:09 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Kyndryl's India AI Push Faces Scrutiny Amid Reporting Issues</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Kyndryls-India-AI-Push-Faces-Scrutiny-Amid-Reporting-Issues/6999062a730b6847a51712aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Kyndryls-India-AI-Push-Faces-Scrutiny-Amid-Reporting-Issues/6999062a730b6847a51712aa</guid><description>Kyndryl is aggressively expanding its AI and digital transformation services in India, with a new AI Innovation Lab in Bengaluru and plans to train 50,000 students in AI literacy. This strategic push aims to bolster governance and cybersecurity initiatives. However, the company is currently under heightened investor scrutiny following a significant stock price drop in early February 2026, triggered by a delayed Q4 fiscal 2025 earnings report, disclosures of material internal control weaknesses, and the departure of key finance executives. A securities class-action lawsuit is also pending, compounding concerns about financial transparency and reporting integrity.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 01:11:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6999062a730b6847a51712a9_1771636386396.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Muni Bonds Gain Scale, Eye Institutional Capital</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Muni-Bonds-Gain-Scale-Eye-Institutional-Capital/699900ad730b6847a5171146</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Muni-Bonds-Gain-Scale-Eye-Institutional-Capital/699900ad730b6847a5171146</guid><description>India's municipal bond market is undergoing a structural transformation. The Union Budget 2026-27 introduced a ₹100 crore incentive for issuances exceeding ₹1,000 crore, aiming to attract institutional capital by promoting scale, corporate-like financial discipline, and advanced credit mechanisms such as escrow accounts. This initiative moves the market beyond its historically fragmented and illiquid state, potentially enhancing its depth and tradability.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:47:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699900ad730b6847a5171145_1771634960446.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nitin Castings Proposes BSE Voluntary Delisting at ₹273.36 Floor Price</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nitin-Castings-Proposes-BSE-Voluntary-Delisting-at-27336-Floor-Price/6998f6b0730b6847a5170f6e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Nitin-Castings-Proposes-BSE-Voluntary-Delisting-at-27336-Floor-Price/6998f6b0730b6847a5170f6e</guid><description>Nitin Castings Limited's Board has approved a proposal to voluntarily delist its equity shares from the BSE. The offer, initiated by promoters, sets a floor price of ₹273.36 per share and requires shareholder approval. This move aims to acquire all publicly held shares.</description><pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:05:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6998f6b0730b6847a5170f6d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>