<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 01:46:16 +0000</pubDate><item><title>US Tech Giants' AI Bets Face Strain Amid China Challenge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/US-Tech-Giants-AI-Bets-Face-Strain-Amid-China-Challenge/6993c50ecffb93b3e92769a2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/US-Tech-Giants-AI-Bets-Face-Strain-Amid-China-Challenge/6993c50ecffb93b3e92769a2</guid><description>The narrative of US technological exceptionalism in AI faces a significant challenge as China's rapid advancements, bolstered by state funding and a cost-competitive ecosystem, erode American dominance. US tech titans are committing unprecedented capital to AI infrastructure, prompting investor scrutiny over return on investment and signaling a potential shift in global tech leadership. This escalating competition is forcing a re-evaluation of market dynamics and investment strategies.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 01:31:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6993c50ecffb93b3e92769a1_1771291996287.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Clean Max IPO: Debt Paydown Dominates Amidst Sector Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Clean-Max-IPO-Debt-Paydown-Dominates-Amidst-Sector-Valuation-Concerns/6993c4d9cffb93b3e9276988</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Clean-Max-IPO-Debt-Paydown-Dominates-Amidst-Sector-Valuation-Concerns/6993c4d9cffb93b3e9276988</guid><description>Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions is launching an IPO to raise ₹3,100 crore, with a significant portion earmarked for debt repayment. The reduced IPO size reflects a strategic shift towards strengthening its balance sheet amidst the capital-intensive renewable energy sector. This move occurs as peers like Adani Green Energy and NTPC Green Energy operate with higher valuations, while ACME Solar Holdings shows a diverse valuation range. The company, a leader in the C&amp;I renewable segment, faces sector-wide valuation reassessments and potential cost pressures, making financial prudence a key aspect of its public debut.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 01:31:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6993c4d9cffb93b3e9276987_1771292061826.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Capital Efficiency vs. Market Ruthlessness: Ajax, Kirloskar at Crossroads</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Capital-Efficiency-vs-Market-Ruthlessness-Ajax-Kirloskar-at-Crossroads/6993be54cffb93b3e927678a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Capital-Efficiency-vs-Market-Ruthlessness-Ajax-Kirloskar-at-Crossroads/6993be54cffb93b3e927678a</guid><description>Despite near-zero debt and robust operational metrics, Ajax Engineering and Kirloskar Pneumatic Company Ltd. have seen their market valuations plummet, with share prices falling over 35% from all-time highs. This divergence between fundamental strength and market sentiment has drawn institutional investor interest, raising questions about whether this represents a mispricing opportunity or a precursor to deeper sectoral revaluation. While Kirloskar Pneumatic reported strong year-on-year Q3 results, Ajax Engineering faces margin pressures and revenue contraction, highlighting distinct challenges within the sector.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 01:03:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6993be54cffb93b3e9276789.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Banks Shed Bad Loans, But Recovery Rates Tumble</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banks-Shed-Bad-Loans-But-Recovery-Rates-Tumble/6993be4dcffb93b3e9276773</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Banks-Shed-Bad-Loans-But-Recovery-Rates-Tumble/6993be4dcffb93b3e9276773</guid><description>Banks significantly accelerated the sale of retail non-performing assets (NPAs) in the December quarter, offloading Rs 24,814 crore, a sharp increase from the prior quarter. However, this surge in sales has been accompanied by a drastic decline in recovery values. Asset reconstruction companies issued security receipts equivalent to just 15% of the sold retail NPAs, a steep drop from over 34% in the September quarter, highlighting a widening gap between asset acquisition and realizable value.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 01:03:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6993be4dcffb93b3e9276772.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Budget 2026: DPI's Hidden Value &amp; Fragmentation Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Budget-2026-DPIs-Hidden-Value-and-Fragmentation-Risk/6993bd25cffb93b3e9276653</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Budget-2026-DPIs-Hidden-Value-and-Fragmentation-Risk/6993bd25cffb93b3e9276653</guid><description>While Budget 2026-27 allocates substantial capital expenditure, it overlooks Digital Public Infrastructure (DPI), the proven multiplier behind India's digital economy. Despite enabling financial inclusion akin to 47 years of progress in nine, and driving significant savings via DBT, DPI's fragmented funding and misclassification as operational expenditure risk undermining its strategic role. The Economic Survey 2025-26 flagged DPI as 'strategic national infrastructure,' yet current budgeting practices fail to reflect this, potentially hindering future AI and tech-led growth.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 00:58:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6993bd25cffb93b3e9276652_1771290045341.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Coconut Sector Pivots: Agro-Industrial Ambitions Face Global Competition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indias-Coconut-Sector-Pivots-Agro-Industrial-Ambitions-Face-Global-Competition/6993bce4cffb93b3e9276612</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Indias-Coconut-Sector-Pivots-Agro-Industrial-Ambitions-Face-Global-Competition/6993bce4cffb93b3e9276612</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 signals a significant policy elevation for India's coconut sector, reframing it as a priority agro-industrial ecosystem rather than a mere agricultural crop. Initiatives aim to boost productivity, farmer incomes, and value-added processing, leveraging schemes like the Coconut Promotion Scheme and Mahila Coir Yojana. However, the sector faces a formidable challenge in translating domestic strengths into global competitiveness, with established players like the Philippines and Indonesia dominating export markets for value-added products. The success hinges on robust execution and strategic market penetration beyond existing support mechanisms.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 00:57:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6993bce4cffb93b3e9276611.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Inflation Cools, AI Fears Simmer Amid Market Caution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Inflation-Cools-AI-Fears-Simmer-Amid-Market-Caution/6993ba55cffb93b3e92764a3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Inflation-Cools-AI-Fears-Simmer-Amid-Market-Caution/6993ba55cffb93b3e92764a3</guid><description>U.S. stock futures traded with little change on February 16, 2026, as investors prepared for the week ahead following a subdued performance last week. Softer-than-expected January inflation data bolstered expectations for Federal Reserve rate cuts later this year, pushing yields lower. However, apprehension over Artificial Intelligence's disruptive potential continues to cast a shadow over sectors like real estate, trucking, and financial services, contributing to a challenging market environment. Investors now await the Federal Reserve's January meeting minutes and the Personal Consumption Expenditures (PCE) inflation report for further policy direction.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 00:46:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6993ba55cffb93b3e92764a2.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Passkey Push: Visa &amp; Mastercard Bypass OTPs, Sparking New Security Era</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Passkey-Push-Visa-and-Mastercard-Bypass-OTPs-Sparking-New-Security-Era/6993ba14cffb93b3e9276478</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Passkey-Push-Visa-and-Mastercard-Bypass-OTPs-Sparking-New-Security-Era/6993ba14cffb93b3e9276478</guid><description>Mastercard and Visa are introducing passkeys in India, enabling biometric authentication for card transactions and phasing out traditional One-Time Passwords (OTPs). This move aligns with Reserve Bank of India (RBI) directives mandating advanced, dynamic authentication factors. Initial consumer uptake shows 30% opting for passkeys, signaling a shift towards faster, more secure payments and an expected 2-3% increase in transaction success rates. The initiative aims to combat rising card fraud, estimated at over ₹1,800 crore between FY22 and September 2025, particularly social engineering scams exploiting OTP vulnerabilities. While banks avoid major API changes, policy adjustments are key. This transition marks a significant step in India's rapidly growing digital payments market, projected for substantial growth through 2034, as the nation embraces a digitally-first payment culture.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 00:45:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6993ba14cffb93b3e9276477_1771289238715.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 5th-Gen AMCA Fighter: DRDO Shortlists New Defense Powerhouses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-5th-Gen-AMCA-Fighter-DRDO-Shortlists-New-Defense-Powerhouses/6993b167cffb93b3e927620b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-5th-Gen-AMCA-Fighter-DRDO-Shortlists-New-Defense-Powerhouses/6993b167cffb93b3e927620b</guid><description>The Defence Research and Development Organisation (DRDO) has shortlisted three key entities for the development of India's Advanced Medium Combat Aircraft (AMCA). Tata Advanced Systems Ltd will compete independently, while Larsen &amp; Toubro will partner with Bharat Electronics Ltd, and a third consortium comprises Bharat Forge, BEML Ltd, and Data Patterns. This selection process emphasizes a competitive approach to developing India's homegrown fifth-generation stealth fighter, with the government expected to provide crucial funding for prototype development. The move signals a significant evolution in India's defense industrial strategy, potentially sidelining traditional players like HAL due to procedural missteps.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 00:08:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6993b167cffb93b3e927620a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-US Trade Deal: Tariffs Cut, But Concessions Spark Debate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Tariffs-Cut-But-Concessions-Spark-Debate/6993b131cffb93b3e92761d6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-US-Trade-Deal-Tariffs-Cut-But-Concessions-Spark-Debate/6993b131cffb93b3e92761d6</guid><description>An interim trade agreement framework between India and the United States is set for finalization by March 2026, involving significant US tariff reductions on Indian goods from 50% to 18%. India has offered agricultural quotas and concessions, notably on animal feed inputs like cotton for its textile sector, while maintaining protections for sensitive farm products. The deal is partly conditioned on India halting Russian oil purchases. Indian markets reacted positively to the news on February 16, 2026, though analysts caution that the reduced tariffs still represent a substantial levy.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 00:07:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6993b131cffb93b3e92761d5_1771286965788.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Centennial Surgical Alerts BSE on Alleged Stock Price Manipulation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Centennial-Surgical-Alerts-BSE-on-Alleged-Stock-Price-Manipulation/6993b038cffb93b3e9276137</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Centennial-Surgical-Alerts-BSE-on-Alleged-Stock-Price-Manipulation/6993b038cffb93b3e9276137</guid><description>Centennial Surgical Suture Ltd. has formally alerted the BSE about suspected stock price manipulation between February 6-13, 2026. The company alleges an artificial price surge, unsupported by business fundamentals, is harming investors and requests an urgent investigation into potential violations of SEBI's anti-fraud regulations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 00:03:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6993b038cffb93b3e9276136_1771286697206.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>