<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:51:45 +0000</pubDate><item><title>ADAG Faces ₹40K Crore Fraud Probe; SC Mandates 'Fair' Investigation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/ADAG-Faces-40K-Crore-Fraud-Probe-SC-Mandates-Fair-Investigation/6989ffffb81b2b81dc00f163</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/ADAG-Faces-40K-Crore-Fraud-Probe-SC-Mandates-Fair-Investigation/6989ffffb81b2b81dc00f163</guid><description>A Supreme Court-directed Special Investigation Team (SIT) has been formed by the Enforcement Directorate (ED) to probe alleged banking and corporate fraud totaling ₹40,000 crore involving the Anil Dhirubhai Ambani Group (ADAG) and associated entities. This escalation follows the Supreme Court's directive for a "fair, independent, prompt and dispassionate" investigation, signaling a significant tightening of regulatory scrutiny on the conglomerate. The ED has previously attached assets worth ₹12,000 crore in connection with its ongoing probes.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:40:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Affle 3i Posts Record Q3 Revenue, EBITDA, PAT; Eyes 10x Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Affle-3i-Posts-Record-Q3-Revenue-EBITDA-PAT-Eyes-10x-Growth/6989ffdab81b2b81dc00f053</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Affle-3i-Posts-Record-Q3-Revenue-EBITDA-PAT-Eyes-10x-Growth/6989ffdab81b2b81dc00f053</guid><description>Affle 3i Limited (formerly Affle (India) Limited) reported its best-ever quarterly performance in Q3 FY2026, with revenue surging 19.2% YoY to INR 7.17 billion and EBITDA growing 24.1% YoY to INR 1.63 billion, reaching a record PAT of INR 1.19 billion. The company reiterated its '10x growth vision', driven by AI, verticalization, and international expansion, while actively evaluating acquisitions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:40:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989ffdab81b2b81dc00f052_1770651692003.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>EPFO Revamps Rs 31 Trillion Fund Management, Seeks New Custodian</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/EPFO-Revamps-Rs-31-Trillion-Fund-Management-Seeks-New-Custodian/6989ff60b81b2b81dc00eee9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/EPFO-Revamps-Rs-31-Trillion-Fund-Management-Seeks-New-Custodian/6989ff60b81b2b81dc00eee9</guid><description>The Employees' Provident Fund Organisation is undertaking a major overhaul of its investment and audit partnerships. After nearly 15 years, the retirement fund body is set to appoint a new custodian to manage its ₹31 trillion corpus. This comes as EPFO also finalizes new asset management companies for equity investments and seeks an external auditor.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:38:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6989ff60b81b2b81dc00eee8.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jubilant Agri-Consumer Q3 Mixed; Agri Demerger Boosts Growth Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Jubilant-Agri-Consumer-Q3-Mixed-Agri-Demerger-Boosts-Growth-Outlook/6989ff15b81b2b81dc00ed8d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Jubilant-Agri-Consumer-Q3-Mixed-Agri-Demerger-Boosts-Growth-Outlook/6989ff15b81b2b81dc00ed8d</guid><description>Jubilant Agri &amp; Consumer Products reported mixed Q3 FY26 results with a 13% YoY sales rise to ₹4,510m, but a 49% QoQ drop. However, 9M FY26 showcased robust growth: sales up 21% to ₹14,059m, EBITDA up 41%, and PAT up 50% to ₹1,079m, with margins expanding significantly. The Agri Products segment was a strong performer, while Performance Polymers &amp; Chemicals faced demand softness and input cost pressures. Key announcements include the approved demerger of the Agri division into Jubilant Agri Solutions Ltd and a ₹50 crore capacity expansion for Performance Polymers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:36:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Pfizer India's Margin Leap Fuels Q3 Profit Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Pfizer-Indias-Margin-Leap-Fuels-Q3-Profit-Surge/6989feecb81b2b81dc00ec99</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Pfizer-Indias-Margin-Leap-Fuels-Q3-Profit-Surge/6989feecb81b2b81dc00ec99</guid><description>Pfizer India demonstrated a strong third quarter with net profit up 11.1% to ₹141.8 crore, propelled by 19.9% revenue growth to ₹645 crore. The company's operational performance saw a substantial improvement, with EBITDA rising 55.8% to ₹228.3 crore, leading to operating margins widening to 35.4% from 27.2%. This enhanced efficiency and robust demand across key therapy areas contributed to a 3.91% rise in its share price leading up to the earnings announcement.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:36:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Chalet Hotels Surges 27% Revenue, Expands Luxury Segment Amid Project Updates</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Chalet-Hotels-Surges-27percent-Revenue-Expands-Luxury-Segment-Amid-Project-Updates/6989fe74b81b2b81dc00eaf2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Chalet-Hotels-Surges-27percent-Revenue-Expands-Luxury-Segment-Amid-Project-Updates/6989fe74b81b2b81dc00eaf2</guid><description>Chalet Hotels reported a strong Q3 FY26, with consolidated revenue soaring 27% YoY to ₹5,892 million and EBITDA climbing 29% to ₹2,726 million. Margins improved, driven by robust performance in hospitality and commercial real estate. Management highlighted industry tailwinds, planned capex of ₹25 billion, and expansion into luxury and leisure segments. Key projects like Athiva, Khandala launched successfully, while the Delhi Airport and Goa projects face revised timelines and pending clearances respectively.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:34:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Swadeshi Industries Revenue Surges 500% But Q3 Profit Plummets 30%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Swadeshi-Industries-Revenue-Surges-500percent-But-Q3-Profit-Plummets-30percent/6989fda5b81b2b81dc00e8ec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Swadeshi-Industries-Revenue-Surges-500percent-But-Q3-Profit-Plummets-30percent/6989fda5b81b2b81dc00e8ec</guid><description>Swadeshi Industries &amp; Leasing Ltd. reported a colossal 519.47% YoY jump in standalone revenue to ₹1,578.63 Cr for Q3 FY26, driven by its Trading and Food Processing segments. However, this revenue surge came at the cost of profitability, with standalone net profit declining 31.03% YoY to ₹43.51 Cr. Basic EPS also fell to ₹0.40 from ₹0.58. The company's balance sheet shows significant expansion, with total assets growing to ₹1,361.62 Cr, fueled by a substantial increase in loans.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Tax Overhaul: PAN Hikes, Crypto Scrutiny, and Perks Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Tax-Overhaul-PAN-Hikes-Crypto-Scrutiny-and-Perks-Shift/6989fd87b81b2b81dc00e841</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Tax-Overhaul-PAN-Hikes-Crypto-Scrutiny-and-Perks-Shift/6989fd87b81b2b81dc00e841</guid><description>India's proposed Income Tax Rules 2026, effective April 1, signal a dual approach of simplification and intensified regulatory oversight. Key changes include significantly higher Permanent Account Number (PAN) thresholds for transactions like cash deposits, property, and vehicle purchases, alongside mandatory information sharing for crypto exchanges. While perquisite values for salaried employees are updated, reflecting market realities, the overall impact points to a more data-driven and transparent tax regime.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:30:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Navigates Energy Diversification Amid US Trade Deal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Navigates-Energy-Diversification-Amid-US-Trade-Deal/6989fd0db81b2b81dc00466c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Navigates-Energy-Diversification-Amid-US-Trade-Deal/6989fd0db81b2b81dc00466c</guid><description>India is strategically recalibrating its energy sourcing and deepening economic ties with the United States. Foreign Secretary Vikram Misri reiterated the nation's commitment to stable, affordable energy through diversified imports, influenced by market conditions and national interests. Simultaneously, a landmark interim trade agreement with the U.S. promises reduced tariffs on a broad range of American industrial and agricultural goods in exchange for tariff cuts on Indian exports. This dual approach signals India's intent to enhance energy security while leveraging trade for economic growth, navigating complex geopolitical pressures.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:28:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6989fd0db81b2b81dc00466b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rapido's Delhi Surge Faces Fierce Competition, Driver Grievances</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Rapidos-Delhi-Surge-Faces-Fierce-Competition-Driver-Grievances/6989fc94b81b2b81dc00452d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Rapidos-Delhi-Surge-Faces-Fierce-Competition-Driver-Grievances/6989fc94b81b2b81dc00452d</guid><description>Rapido has solidified its position in Delhi, clocking nearly 3 crore rides monthly and expanding its driver base. However, this growth is increasingly tested by intense competition, including new cooperative models, and mounting regulatory and driver-related challenges that threaten sustainable expansion. The company's strategy of high-volume, multi-modal transport faces headwinds from driver welfare concerns and a rapidly evolving market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:26:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Gulf Oil Lubricants Posts Record Revenue, EBITDA; PAT Dips on Exceptional Item</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Gulf-Oil-Lubricants-Posts-Record-Revenue-EBITDA-PAT-Dips-on-Exceptional-Item/6989fc1cb81b2b81dc0043e2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Gulf-Oil-Lubricants-Posts-Record-Revenue-EBITDA-PAT-Dips-on-Exceptional-Item/6989fc1cb81b2b81dc0043e2</guid><description>Gulf Oil Lubricants India Limited (GOLIL) achieved record Q3 FY26 performance, with revenue up 10.56% YoY to ₹1,017.55 Cr and EBITDA up 7.80% YoY to ₹132.46 Cr. Lubricants volumes grew 8% YoY, outperforming the industry. However, PAT declined 21.77% YoY to ₹76.13 Cr due to an exceptional item. Management remains optimistic, citing demand momentum, GST rationalization, and strong growth from its EV subsidiary, Tirex. An interim dividend of ₹21 per share was declared.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:24:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6989fc1cb81b2b81dc0043e1.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndoStar Capital Finance PAT Drops 28% Despite Revenue Jump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IndoStar-Capital-Finance-PAT-Drops-28percent-Despite-Revenue-Jump/6989fb33b81b2b81dc00420f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IndoStar-Capital-Finance-PAT-Drops-28percent-Despite-Revenue-Jump/6989fb33b81b2b81dc00420f</guid><description>IndoStar Capital Finance reported a 27.7% year-on-year decline in Profit After Tax (PAT) to INR 8.3 crore for Q3 FY26, impacted by a one-time INR 4.8 crore employee benefit expense. Despite this, net revenue from operations surged 15.9% YoY to INR 209.3 crore, with Pre-Provision Operating Profit (PPOP) jumping 43.5% YoY to INR 85.2 crore. The company is focused on its Vehicle Finance and Micro Loans Against Property segments, demonstrating improved leverage at 1.2x and a robust Capital Adequacy Ratio of 41.4%.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:20:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989fb33b81b2b81dc00420e_1770650664689.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BSE's Profit Surge Driven by Diversification and Efficiency</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/BSEs-Profit-Surge-Driven-by-Diversification-and-Efficiency/6989f9c5b81b2b81dc003f83</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/BSEs-Profit-Surge-Driven-by-Diversification-and-Efficiency/6989f9c5b81b2b81dc003f83</guid><description>BSE Ltd posted a significant 174% year-on-year net profit increase to ₹602 crore in Q3 FY26, with margins widening to 45%. Revenue climbed 62% to ₹1,244 crore. This performance is underpinned by strong growth in equity listings, derivatives trading, the BSE StAR MF platform, and expanding index services, showcasing diversified revenue streams and enhanced operational efficiency.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:14:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6989f9c5b81b2b81dc003f82.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SC Examines State Police Limits in ₹1000 Cr Scam Probe</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/SC-Examines-State-Police-Limits-in-1000-Cr-Scam-Probe/6989f8d7b81b2b81dc003d85</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/SC-Examines-State-Police-Limits-in-1000-Cr-Scam-Probe/6989f8d7b81b2b81dc003d85</guid><description>Depositors in a ₹1,000 crore alleged financial fraud are petitioning the Supreme Court to transfer the investigation of Coimbatore-based Universal Trading Solution Private Limited to the CBI. They cite the Tamil Nadu Police's Economic Offences Wing (EOW) and subsequent court-appointed committees for failing to recover assets. The apex court is now examining the jurisdictional boundaries and effectiveness of state police versus central agencies in handling inter-state financial scams.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:10:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6989f8d7b81b2b81dc003d84.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NHAI InvIT Opens Highway Assets to Retail Investors</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/NHAI-InvIT-Opens-Highway-Assets-to-Retail-Investors/6989f88bb81b2b81dc003be8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/NHAI-InvIT-Opens-Highway-Assets-to-Retail-Investors/6989f88bb81b2b81dc003be8</guid><description>The National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) has transferred Rs 9,500 crore worth of national highway sections, spanning 260 km across four states, to its inaugural public Infrastructure Investment Trust (InvIT), Raajmarg Infra Investment Trust (RIIT). This move aims to unlock value from operational assets and provide retail investors direct access to income-generating infrastructure. NHAI plans to inject an additional 1,500 km of assets into RIIT over the next three to five years, signaling a sustained strategy to broaden public participation and capital recycling within the sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:08:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's 74-Day Oil Buffer: Strategic Gains vs. Global Norms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-74-Day-Oil-Buffer-Strategic-Gains-vs-Global-Norms/6989f862b81b2b81dc003b0a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-74-Day-Oil-Buffer-Strategic-Gains-vs-Global-Norms/6989f862b81b2b81dc003b0a</guid><description>India maintains a 74-day strategic petroleum reserve (SPR), falling short of the International Energy Agency's 90-day benchmark. While the Oil Minister deems this level adequate, it highlights a potential vulnerability in prolonged global turbulence. The nation's energy security strategy leverages strategic procurement, notably filling reserves during the April-May 2020 price slump which yielded significant notional savings. This approach underscores India's positioning as a major energy consumer navigating complex geopolitical supply chains.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:08:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Eyes 7 New Bullet Train Routes Amid Cost Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Eyes-7-New-Bullet-Train-Routes-Amid-Cost-Concerns/6989f811b81b2b81dc00395b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Eyes-7-New-Bullet-Train-Routes-Amid-Cost-Concerns/6989f811b81b2b81dc00395b</guid><description>India is advancing plans for seven new high-speed rail corridors totaling 4,000 km, backed by an estimated ₹16 lakh crore investment. The initiative prioritizes updated Detailed Project Reports (DPRs) for accurate financial viability assessments, a direct response to the Mumbai-Ahmedabad corridor's significant cost escalations driven by land acquisition delays. This strategic shift signals a focus on de-risking large-scale infrastructure execution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:06:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6989f811b81b2b81dc00395a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NHAI InvIT IPO: Retail Access to Highways</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/NHAI-InvIT-IPO-Retail-Access-to-Highways/6989f7eab81b2b81dc0038ae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/NHAI-InvIT-IPO-Retail-Access-to-Highways/6989f7eab81b2b81dc0038ae</guid><description>The National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) is set to launch the Raajmarg Infra Investment Trust (RIIT) IPO, aiming to raise ₹9500 crore by monetizing five operational highway stretches totaling over 260 km. This public InvIT will offer retail investors a minimum investment opportunity starting at ₹10,000, providing access to stable, income-generating infrastructure assets. Funds will be raised through a 60% equity and 40% debt mix, with NHAI retaining a 15% stake. The move aligns with NHAI's strategy to aggressively reduce its outstanding debt and fund future infrastructure development.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:06:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Navigates Oil Sourcing: Diversification Amidst Geopolitical Flux</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Navigates-Oil-Sourcing-Diversification-Amidst-Geopolitical-Flux/6989f710b81b2b81dc0036cb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Navigates-Oil-Sourcing-Diversification-Amidst-Geopolitical-Flux/6989f710b81b2b81dc0036cb</guid><description>India's foreign secretary emphasized a national interest approach to crude oil procurement, driven by market dynamics and supply security, not singular geographies. This strategy aims for diversification across numerous global sources, a pivot from previous heavy reliance, notably on Russian oil, influenced by evolving geopolitical conditions and a recent US-India trade framework. While acknowledging the economic advantages of Russian crude, India is strategically recalibrating its import mix, a move supported by trade concessions from the United States and aimed at enhancing energy security and mitigating inflation risks.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:02:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6989f710b81b2b81dc0036ca.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gulf Oil Lubricants Q3 Profit Dips 22% Despite Revenue Growth; Declares Dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Gulf-Oil-Lubricants-Q3-Profit-Dips-22percent-Despite-Revenue-Growth-Declares-Dividend/6989f6f8b81b2b81dc0035ce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Gulf-Oil-Lubricants-Q3-Profit-Dips-22percent-Despite-Revenue-Growth-Declares-Dividend/6989f6f8b81b2b81dc0035ce</guid><description>Gulf Oil Lubricants India reported a 21.93% YoY decline in consolidated net profit to ₹7,643.64 lakhs for Q3 FY26, even as revenue rose 10.55% to ₹1,01,755.31 lakhs. The drop was largely due to an exceptional item of ₹2,278.21 lakhs related to new labor codes. Despite the profit dip, the company declared an interim dividend of ₹21 per share.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:02:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Nykaa Posts Record 8% EBITDA Margin, 156% PAT Surge in Q3 FY26</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nykaa-Posts-Record-8percent-EBITDA-Margin-156percent-PAT-Surge-in-Q3-FY26/6989f6a6b81b2b81dc003496</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nykaa-Posts-Record-8percent-EBITDA-Margin-156percent-PAT-Surge-in-Q3-FY26/6989f6a6b81b2b81dc003496</guid><description>FSN E-Commerce Ventures (Nykaa) reported a stellar Q3 FY26, with Gross Merchandise Value (GMV) up 28% YoY to ₹5,795 crore and Net Revenue (NSV) up 27% YoY to ₹2,873 crore. The company achieved a record 8.0% EBITDA margin (₹230 crore, +63% YoY) and 156% YoY PAT growth to ₹68 crore. Gross margins hit a 13-quarter high at 45.2%. Strategic partnerships and strong brand performance drive confidence in continued growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ceigall India Secures ₹1700 Cr, 220 MW Solar-BESS Project in MP</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Ceigall-India-Secures-1700-Cr-220-MW-Solar-BESS-Project-in-MP/6989f67bb81b2b81dc00339c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Ceigall-India-Secures-1700-Cr-220-MW-Solar-BESS-Project-in-MP/6989f67bb81b2b81dc00339c</guid><description>Ceigall India Limited has secured a significant Letter of Award (LOA) worth approximately ₹1,700 Crores from Rewa Ultra Mega Solar Limited. The project involves developing a 220 MW solar power plant integrated with Battery Energy Storage Systems (BESS) at Morena Solar Park in Madhya Pradesh. This award enhances the company's future revenue visibility and solidifies its presence in the renewable energy infrastructure sector, with a tariff of ₹2.70/kWh.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 15:00:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6989f67bb81b2b81dc00339b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aarti Pharmalabs Declares Dividend Amidst Mixed Results and Margin Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aarti-Pharmalabs-Declares-Dividend-Amidst-Mixed-Results-and-Margin-Squeeze/6989f637b81b2b81dc0031e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aarti-Pharmalabs-Declares-Dividend-Amidst-Mixed-Results-and-Margin-Squeeze/6989f637b81b2b81dc0031e1</guid><description>Aarti Pharmalabs announced a mixed financial performance for Q3 FY26, with standalone revenue leaping 261% YoY to ₹255.28 Cr, but net profit margins compressing to 17.17% from 43.72%. Consolidated revenue grew 19.86% YoY to ₹205.57 Cr. The company declared an interim dividend of ₹1.50 per share. However, nine-month periods show declines in EPS, with consolidated EPS falling 29.9% YoY to ₹13.84, despite a 50.8% surge in consolidated net profit.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:59:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>SMC Global Q3 Revenue Surges 12.4% QoQ; NBFC Segment Faces Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SMC-Global-Q3-Revenue-Surges-124percent-QoQ-NBFC-Segment-Faces-Headwinds/6989f625b81b2b81dc003124</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/SMC-Global-Q3-Revenue-Surges-124percent-QoQ-NBFC-Segment-Faces-Headwinds/6989f625b81b2b81dc003124</guid><description>SMC Global Securities posted a strong Q3 FY'26 with consolidated revenue up 12.4% QoQ to ₹494.8 Cr. EBITDA rose to ₹102.1 Cr (20.6% margin) and PAT surged 46.8% QoQ to ₹30.8 Cr. Fee-based segments like Broking and Insurance Broking showed robust YoY growth. However, the NBFC financing segment's revenue and AUM declined due to strategic portfolio churn. Management forecasts 10-14% broking growth and 20-25% annual MF AUM growth.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:58:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>NRB Bearings Posts Strong Q3, Approves Capacity Expansion and New JV</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NRB-Bearings-Posts-Strong-Q3-Approves-Capacity-Expansion-and-New-JV/6989f600b81b2b81dc003008</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NRB-Bearings-Posts-Strong-Q3-Approves-Capacity-Expansion-and-New-JV/6989f600b81b2b81dc003008</guid><description>NRB Bearings announced strong Q3 FY26 financial results, showcasing a 15.26% YoY standalone revenue growth to ₹29,632 lakh and a 31.63% PAT increase to ₹2,397 lakh. Consolidated figures also saw robust gains. The company's Board approved a significant ₹70 Crore capital investment for capacity enhancement, targeting a 17-25% volume increase, and sanctioned a new Joint Venture with Italy's Unitec Group to manufacture Cylindrical Roller Bearings. A second interim dividend of ₹3.20 per share was also declared.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:58:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6989f600b81b2b81dc003007.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Muthoot Microfin PAT Soars 1544%, Eyes ₹2000 Cr Debt Raise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Muthoot-Microfin-PAT-Soars-1544percent-Eyes-2000-Cr-Debt-Raise/6989f559b81b2b81dc002e52</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Muthoot-Microfin-PAT-Soars-1544percent-Eyes-2000-Cr-Debt-Raise/6989f559b81b2b81dc002e52</guid><description>Muthoot Microfin Limited posted a phenomenal 1544.0% year-on-year growth in net profit for Q3 FY26, reaching ₹62.4 crore from ₹3.8 crore in Q3 FY25. Despite a 14.5% YoY decline in Net Interest Income (NII) and a 30.5% drop in Pre-Provisioning Operating Profit (PPOP), the company's Assets Under Management (AUM) grew 5.4% YoY. Asset quality improved with GNPA at 4.40%, and the company announced plans to raise up to ₹2000 crore via NCDs.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:55:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IndoStar Capital Finance Pivots to Retail, NIM Surges Amidst PAT Decline</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IndoStar-Capital-Finance-Pivots-to-Retail-NIM-Surges-Amidst-PAT-Decline/6989f521b81b2b81dc002d18</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IndoStar-Capital-Finance-Pivots-to-Retail-NIM-Surges-Amidst-PAT-Decline/6989f521b81b2b81dc002d18</guid><description>IndoStar Capital Finance Limited is strategically transforming into a retail-centric, tech-driven NBFC, exiting affordable housing finance to focus on Vehicle Finance and Micro LAP. Q3 FY26 saw Net Interest Income rise 16.1% YoY to ₹209.3 cr and Net Interest Margins climb to 8.6%. However, Profit After Tax dipped 20.9% YoY to ₹8.3 cr, attributed to a one-off gain in the previous year's discontinued operations. Total assets reduced to ₹9,791 cr due to the business sale.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:54:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6989f521b81b2b81dc002d17.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Muthoot Microfin PAT Surges 1544% on Revenue Growth, Funding Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Muthoot-Microfin-PAT-Surges-1544percent-on-Revenue-Growth-Funding-Boost/6989f49bb81b2b81dc002b98</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Muthoot-Microfin-PAT-Surges-1544percent-on-Revenue-Growth-Funding-Boost/6989f49bb81b2b81dc002b98</guid><description>Muthoot Microfin reported stellar Q3 FY26 results, with Profit After Tax (PAT) soaring 1544.0% year-on-year to ₹62.4 crore. Total income grew 44.1% YoY to ₹605.4 crore, driven by a 4.1% sequential increase in Assets Under Management (AUM) to ₹13,078.6 crore. The company also improved its Net Interest Margin (NIM) to 12.0% and saw a significant QoQ reduction in its Cost/Income ratio to 54.8%. Key approvals included the issuance of Non-Convertible Debentures (NCDs) up to ₹2000 crore. Despite a YoY decline in Net Interest Income and Pre-Provisioning Operating Profit, and a YoY increase in Gross NPA, the sharp PAT growth and positive outlook signal strong recovery momentum.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:52:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Leverages Oil Sourcing for Trade Gains Amidst Geopolitics</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Leverages-Oil-Sourcing-for-Trade-Gains-Amidst-Geopolitics/6989f427b81b2b81dc002a12</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Leverages-Oil-Sourcing-for-Trade-Gains-Amidst-Geopolitics/6989f427b81b2b81dc002a12</guid><description>India is prioritizing energy security through a diversified crude oil procurement strategy, emphasizing national interests as the guiding principle. This approach, highlighted by Foreign Secretary Vikram Misri, aims to mitigate supply risks and ensure economic stability amidst evolving global trade relations. The policy shift comes as India navigates complex geopolitical currents, using its significant import demand as leverage in international trade negotiations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:50:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bata India Q3 PAT Surges 375% QoQ, YoY Hit by One-Offs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Bata-India-Q3-PAT-Surges-375percent-QoQ-YoY-Hit-by-One-Offs/6989f3d6b81b2b81dc002893</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Bata-India-Q3-PAT-Surges-375percent-QoQ-YoY-Hit-by-One-Offs/6989f3d6b81b2b81dc002893</guid><description>Bata India posted a strong quarter-on-quarter performance in Q3 FY26, with consolidated revenue climbing 17.89% to ₹944.68 Crores and Profit After Tax (PAT) surging 375.57% to ₹66.10 Crores. However, year-on-year comparisons for PAT are heavily distorted by exceptional items: Q3 FY25 benefited from a ₹133.95 Crore land sale gain, while Q3 FY26 incurred ₹7.93 Crores in exceptional expenses. Consequently, nine-month consolidated PAT fell 53.7% YoY. No future guidance was provided.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:48:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6989f3d6b81b2b81dc002892.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aurobindo Pharma Surges 8.4% Revenue, Europe Leads Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Aurobindo-Pharma-Surges-84percent-Revenue-Europe-Leads-Growth/6989f3aab81b2b81dc002786</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Aurobindo-Pharma-Surges-84percent-Revenue-Europe-Leads-Growth/6989f3aab81b2b81dc002786</guid><description>Aurobindo Pharma reported an 8.4% YoY revenue increase to ₹8,646 crores for Q3 FY26, fueled by a robust 27.4% surge in Europe and stable US performance. EBITDA grew 9.0% to ₹1,773 crores, with margins holding steady at 20.5%. The company highlighted progress in its biosimilars pipeline and secured product approvals in the US, while maintaining a healthy net cash position.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:48:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6989f3aab81b2b81dc002785_1770648617047.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Data Center Boom: Tax Breaks Fuel Growth, Power &amp; AI Strain Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Data-Center-Boom-Tax-Breaks-Fuel-Growth-Power-and-AI-Strain-Loom/6989f335b81b2b81dc00263e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Data-Center-Boom-Tax-Breaks-Fuel-Growth-Power-and-AI-Strain-Loom/6989f335b81b2b81dc00263e</guid><description>India's burgeoning data center sector is experiencing an unprecedented surge in investment, propelled by a proposed 20-year tax holiday aimed at attracting global cloud hyperscalers. While this influx promises significant economic activity and job creation, the rapid expansion, particularly for AI-driven workloads, is placing immense pressure on the nation's power grid and water resources. Critical infrastructure readiness, regulatory complexities, and environmental sustainability present substantial hurdles that could temper the sector's long-term viability despite its impressive growth projections.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:46:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Banks: NPA Trough Marks Economic Tailwind</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Banks-NPA-Trough-Marks-Economic-Tailwind/6989f2e2b81b2b81dc002472</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Banks-NPA-Trough-Marks-Economic-Tailwind/6989f2e2b81b2b81dc002472</guid><description>India's banking sector has achieved its healthiest position in over a decade, with gross non-performing assets (NPAs) falling to a historic 2.15% by September 2025. This significant turnaround, driven by regulatory reforms and structural interventions, is bolstering banks' capacity to expand credit, laying a stronger foundation for sustained economic growth. Public sector banks have demonstrated a particularly sharp reduction in NPAs since 2018. However, emerging challenges in retail lending and rising write-offs warrant close observation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:44:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6989f2e2b81b2b81dc002471.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Marico Bets Big on Vietnam: Skinetiq Acquisition at Premium Valuation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Marico-Bets-Big-on-Vietnam-Skinetiq-Acquisition-at-Premium-Valuation/6989f2c0b81b2b81dc002397</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Marico-Bets-Big-on-Vietnam-Skinetiq-Acquisition-at-Premium-Valuation/6989f2c0b81b2b81dc002397</guid><description>Marico Limited has acquired a 75% stake in Vietnamese direct-to-consumer skincare company Skinetiq Joint Stock Company for approximately ₹350 crore. This move, intended to bolster Marico's premium beauty presence in Vietnam, values Skinetiq at a P/S multiple of roughly 2.3x its projected 2025 revenue of ₹152 crore. The acquisition leverages Skinetiq's digital-first 'Candid' brand and exclusive distribution for 'Murad' in a market where e-commerce drives half of all beauty sales.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:44:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Tata Steel Bets on India Prices Amidst CCI Probe &amp; Global Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-Bets-on-India-Prices-Amidst-CCI-Probe-and-Global-Woes/6989f1f4b81b2b81dc0021e4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Steel-Bets-on-India-Prices-Amidst-CCI-Probe-and-Global-Woes/6989f1f4b81b2b81dc0021e4</guid><description>Tata Steel anticipates improved steel price realizations in India for the March quarter, projecting an increase exceeding ₹2,200 per tonne. This optimism follows a robust December quarter performance, with consolidated revenue up 6% year-on-year to ₹57,002 crore and net profit reaching ₹2,689 crore. However, the company is concurrently navigating a critical Competition Commission of India investigation into alleged cartelization, alongside persistent global steel oversupply and volatile iron ore prices. Management maintains the company adheres to regulations, refuting cartelization claims.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:40:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Growth-Climate Tug-of-War: Material Costs &amp; Moonshot Needs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-Climate-Tug-of-War-Material-Costs-and-Moonshot-Needs/6989f1cfb81b2b81dc0020d5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-Climate-Tug-of-War-Material-Costs-and-Moonshot-Needs/6989f1cfb81b2b81dc0020d5</guid><description>India's pursuit of manufacturing expansion alongside net-zero commitments presents a significant structural challenge, as highlighted by Chief Economic Advisor Anantha Nageswaran. The nation must contend with the inherent material and energy intensity of renewable technologies, potential critical mineral supply gaps, and the imperative for domestic innovation in areas like Carbon Capture, Utilisation, and Storage (CCUS). Amidst geopolitical uncertainties and a focus on domestic resource mobilization, substantial budget allocations are being directed towards these complex solutions, underscoring a strategic shift to balance industrial growth with climate objectives.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:40:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Sanchay Finvest Posts Loss as Auditors Flag Serious Financial Compliance Issues</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Sanchay-Finvest-Posts-Loss-as-Auditors-Flag-Serious-Financial-Compliance-Issues/6989f066b81b2b81dc001ed2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Sanchay-Finvest-Posts-Loss-as-Auditors-Flag-Serious-Financial-Compliance-Issues/6989f066b81b2b81dc001ed2</guid><description>Sanchay Finvest Limited announced a net loss of ₹511 Lakhs for the quarter ended December 31, 2025. Compounding the financial setback, the independent auditor's limited review report highlighted significant qualifications concerning the company's failure to provision for expected credit losses, non-compliance with preference share terms, absence of reconciliation systems, and disputed trade payables classifications. An NSE penalty of ₹20.43 Lakhs was also recognized as an extraordinary expense.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:34:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6989f066b81b2b81dc001ed1.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AXISCADES Technologies Posts Stellar Q3 Results, Eyes Manufacturing Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/AXISCADES-Technologies-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Results-Eyes-Manufacturing-Growth/6989efeeb81b2b81dc001d77</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/AXISCADES-Technologies-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Results-Eyes-Manufacturing-Growth/6989efeeb81b2b81dc001d77</guid><description>AXISCADES Technologies has delivered a strong Q3 FY26, with revenue climbing 25.0% YoY to ₹343 crore and EBITDA soaring 55.3% to ₹63 crore, marking an 18.3% margin. Profit After Tax (PAT) surged 87.2% YoY to ₹28 crore. The company is executing a strategic shift towards a product, solutions, and manufacturing-centric business model, aiming for over 80% of revenues from manufacturing by FY28, supported by significant investments in new facilities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:32:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6989efeeb81b2b81dc001d76.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indus Infra Trust Buys 3 GRIL Projects, Eyes 70% Debt Limit Hike</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indus-Infra-Trust-Buys-3-GRIL-Projects-Eyes-70percent-Debt-Limit-Hike/6989ef8db81b2b81dc001bd7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indus-Infra-Trust-Buys-3-GRIL-Projects-Eyes-70percent-Debt-Limit-Hike/6989ef8db81b2b81dc001bd7</guid><description>Indus Infra Trust has greenlit the acquisition of three Hybrid Annuity Mode (HAM) highway projects from its sponsor, G R Infraprojects Limited, for a combined enterprise value up to Rs. 24,312 million. Concurrently, the Trust proposes a substantial increase in its borrowing limit to 70% from 49%, pending unitholder approval. This move aims to be yield accretive and enhance distribution stability, though it signifies a higher financial leverage.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:30:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Latent View Analytics: Q3 Revenue Climbs, FY28 Target Set Amidst Margin Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Latent-View-Analytics-Q3-Revenue-Climbs-FY28-Target-Set-Amidst-Margin-Concerns/6989ef75b81b2b81dc001af3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Latent-View-Analytics-Q3-Revenue-Climbs-FY28-Target-Set-Amidst-Margin-Concerns/6989ef75b81b2b81dc001af3</guid><description>Latent View Analytics reported its 12th consecutive quarter of sequential revenue growth in Q3 FY26, driven by BFSI and Technology segments. The company reaffirmed its FY26 revenue guidance and set an ambitious $200 million target for FY28. However, management flagged potential FY27 margin compression due to strategic investments in AI and M&amp;A, alongside a significant client-specific revenue risk in the Technology vertical.</description><pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 14:30:13 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>