<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 06:27:52 +0000</pubDate><item><title>JTEKT India Stock Poised for 33% Surge? Brokerage Initiates 'Buy' Rating with Bold Price Target!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/JTEKT-India-Stock-Poised-for-33percent-Surge-Brokerage-Initiates-Buy-Rating-with-Bold-Price-Target/694b8799e10c98d0787ab0f4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/JTEKT-India-Stock-Poised-for-33percent-Surge-Brokerage-Initiates-Buy-Rating-with-Bold-Price-Target/694b8799e10c98d0787ab0f4</guid><description>Systematix Institutional Equities has initiated coverage on JTEKT India with a 'Buy' rating and a target price of ₹192, suggesting a 33% upside potential. The brokerage cites the company's strong 35% market share in steering systems, planned capacity expansion, and growth in its driveline business, particularly CVJs. Analysts expect significant margin expansion and robust sales, Ebitda, and PAT CAGRs over FY25-28E.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 06:01:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bank of Baroda Stock Soars! Emkay Global Hikes Target to ₹350 – Is This Your Next Big Win?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bank-of-Baroda-Stock-Soars-Emkay-Global-Hikes-Target-to-350-Is-This-Your-Next-Big-Win/694b8786e10c98d0787ab0c0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Bank-of-Baroda-Stock-Soars-Emkay-Global-Hikes-Target-to-350-Is-This-Your-Next-Big-Win/694b8786e10c98d0787ab0c0</guid><description>Emkay Global Financial Services has raised its price target for Bank of Baroda shares to ₹350, maintaining a 'Buy' rating. The upgrade stems from an optimistic outlook on the bank's credit growth, which is projected at 11-13% for FY26. Analysts also highlighted stable net interest margins around 2.8% and strong asset quality, with a Gross Non-Performing Asset ratio of 2.2%, reinforcing confidence in the bank's future performance and investor returns.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 06:01:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Belrise Industries Defence Deal Sparks 5% Surge: Is This India's Next Big Defense Stock?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Belrise-Industries-Defence-Deal-Sparks-5percent-Surge-Is-This-Indias-Next-Big-Defense-Stock/694b8741e10c98d0787ab04d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Belrise-Industries-Defence-Deal-Sparks-5percent-Surge-Is-This-Indias-Next-Big-Defense-Stock/694b8741e10c98d0787ab04d</guid><description>Belrise Industries shares jumped over 5 per cent on Wednesday after announcing a strategic agreement with Israel's Plasan Sasa. The collaboration aims to explore and pursue defense business opportunities in India, including tenders from the Ministry of Defence and paramilitary forces. Plasan Sasa is a global leader in military vehicle survivability and armor solutions. This partnership aligns with India's 'Make in India' and 'Atmanirbhar Bharat' initiatives, potentially boosting Belrise's long-term strategic goals and expanding its global supply chain role.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 06:01:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Gold Loan Stars MUTHOOT &amp; MANAPPURAM EXPLODE: Are They Your Next Big Investment? See Gains Up To 82%!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Gold-Loan-Stars-MUTHOOT-and-MANAPPURAM-EXPLODE-Are-They-Your-Next-Big-Investment-See-Gains-Up-To-82percent/694b8676e10c98d0787aaf3c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Gold-Loan-Stars-MUTHOOT-and-MANAPPURAM-EXPLODE-Are-They-Your-Next-Big-Investment-See-Gains-Up-To-82percent/694b8676e10c98d0787aaf3c</guid><description>Gold finance companies Muthoot Finance and Manappuram Finance have reached record highs in 2025, significantly outperforming the BSE Sensex. Muthoot Finance shares have surged 82% and Manappuram Finance 65% year-to-date, driven by surging gold prices and increased demand for gold loans amid a crunch in unsecured credit. Analysts remain optimistic about their future growth prospects.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 06:01:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b8676e10c98d0787aaf3b_1766557362907.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ACME Solar Soars! New Subsidiary &amp; Mega Project Win Boost Share Price – Investors Buzzing!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/ACME-Solar-Soars-New-Subsidiary-and-Mega-Project-Win-Boost-Share-Price-Investors-Buzzing/694b8649e10c98d0787aaef3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/ACME-Solar-Soars-New-Subsidiary-and-Mega-Project-Win-Boost-Share-Price-Investors-Buzzing/694b8649e10c98d0787aaef3</guid><description>ACME Solar Holdings shares jumped nearly 3% after announcing the incorporation of its wholly owned subsidiary, ACME Greentech Sixteen Private Limited, aimed at developing renewable energy projects. The company also secured a Letter of Award for a significant 130 MW Round-the-Clock renewable power project from REMC Limited, with a fixed tariff of ₹4.35 per unit for 25 years, driving investor interest.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 06:01:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Belrise Industries Surges 6% as Mutual Fund Giants SBI MF &amp; BlackRock Buy Major Stake!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Belrise-Industries-Surges-6percent-as-Mutual-Fund-Giants-SBI-MF-and-BlackRock-Buy-Major-Stake/694b8549e10c98d0787aad14</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Belrise-Industries-Surges-6percent-as-Mutual-Fund-Giants-SBI-MF-and-BlackRock-Buy-Major-Stake/694b8549e10c98d0787aad14</guid><description>Belrise Industries shares jumped nearly 6% on December 24th after SBI Mutual Fund and BlackRock acquired a combined 6.56% stake for approximately ₹897 crore in open market transactions. SBI Mutual Fund purchased 5.76%, while BlackRock's arm bought 0.79%. The stock opened at ₹170.99 and reached a high of ₹177.28 following the significant investment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 06:00:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b8549e10c98d0787aad13_1766557624866.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Caught by Taxman? Why Indian Companies Face GST &amp; Income Tax Notices</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Caught-by-Taxman-Why-Indian-Companies-Face-GST-and-Income-Tax-Notices/694b84d3e10c98d0787aac54</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Caught-by-Taxman-Why-Indian-Companies-Face-GST-and-Income-Tax-Notices/694b84d3e10c98d0787aac54</guid><description>Indian tax authorities issue income tax and GST notices to companies primarily due to discrepancies found through system-generated checks. Common triggers include mismatches between reported transactions and third-party data like Annual Information Statements (AIS), issues with GST input tax credit (ITC) claims compared to vendor filings (GSTR-2A/2B), non-compliance with e-invoicing mandates, incorrect application of GST Rule 86B, and inconsistencies in Tax Deducted at Source (TDS) or payroll filings. Many notices are for clarification, with penalties arising only from unresolved discrepancies.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 06:00:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b84d3e10c98d0787aac53_1766557081870.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Solar Power Poised for Explosive Growth: 50GW Target Looms as Saatvik Green Energy Charts Aggressive Expansion!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Indias-Solar-Power-Poised-for-Explosive-Growth-50GW-Target-Looms-as-Saatvik-Green-Energy-Charts-Aggressive-Expansion/694b8532e10c98d0787aace8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Indias-Solar-Power-Poised-for-Explosive-Growth-50GW-Target-Looms-as-Saatvik-Green-Energy-Charts-Aggressive-Expansion/694b8532e10c98d0787aace8</guid><description>India's solar market is projected to surpass 50 gigawatts (GW) of installations this year, fueled by consistent domestic demand and strong execution. Prashant Mathur, CEO of Saatvik Green Energy, expects his company to achieve over 80% top-line growth in FY26, bolstered by ₹400 crore in new orders and the commissioning of a 2 GW EPE film manufacturing facility. The company is also expanding module capacity and plans further backward integration into cell, ingot, and wafer manufacturing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 06:00:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b8532e10c98d0787aace7_1766557111713.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ICICI Securities' Bold Bet: Shyam Metalics Price Target SKYROCKETS to ₹1000! Is This India's Next Big Stock?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/ICICI-Securities-Bold-Bet-Shyam-Metalics-Price-Target-SKYROCKETS-to-1000-Is-This-Indias-Next-Big-Stock/694b8414e10c98d0787aab30</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/ICICI-Securities-Bold-Bet-Shyam-Metalics-Price-Target-SKYROCKETS-to-1000-Is-This-Indias-Next-Big-Stock/694b8414e10c98d0787aab30</guid><description>ICICI Securities has issued a strong 'BUY' recommendation for Shyam Metalics and Energy (SMEL), setting an ambitious target price of ₹1,000. The brokerage report highlights SMEL's successful revenue tripling over the past five years, driven by significant capacity expansion. With its INR 95 billion capital expenditure nearing completion, the company plans to further boost revenue and EBITDA by 2.5 times in the next five years through expanded crude steel capacity, a four-fold increase in its stainless steel portfolio, and doubling capacities in downstream segments like cold rolling mills and aluminum FRP.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 05:56:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b8414e10c98d0787aab2f_1766556764392.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hero MotoCorp Stock Surge? Motilal Oswal Unveils Massive Rs 6,782 Target – Analyst's BUY Signal!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hero-MotoCorp-Stock-Surge-Motilal-Oswal-Unveils-Massive-Rs-6782-Target-Analysts-BUY-Signal/694b83b7e10c98d0787aaa60</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hero-MotoCorp-Stock-Surge-Motilal-Oswal-Unveils-Massive-Rs-6782-Target-Analysts-BUY-Signal/694b83b7e10c98d0787aaa60</guid><description>Motilal Oswal has reiterated a strong BUY rating for Hero MotoCorp, setting an ambitious target price of ₹6,782. The brokerage cites improving domestic two-wheeler demand, positive rural sentiment, and the company's strategic efforts to regain market share in the 125cc segment and boost its scooter business. Revived export momentum and projected healthy revenue and profit growth through FY28 underpin this optimistic outlook.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 05:56:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b83b7e10c98d0787aaa5f_1766556664251.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fino Payments Bank's SFB Ambition: CEO Gupta Unveils Unique Profit Strategy to Conquer Market Doubts!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Fino-Payments-Banks-SFB-Ambition-CEO-Gupta-Unveils-Unique-Profit-Strategy-to-Conquer-Market-Doubts/694b83b6e10c98d0787aaa35</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Fino-Payments-Banks-SFB-Ambition-CEO-Gupta-Unveils-Unique-Profit-Strategy-to-Conquer-Market-Doubts/694b83b6e10c98d0787aaa35</guid><description>Fino Payments Bank received in-principle approval to become a Small Finance Bank (SFB), but its stock dipped due to investor concerns about profitability. CEO Rishi Gupta assures that Fino will maintain its profit-centric approach, differentiating itself from other SFBs through its strong payment ecosystem, low-cost liabilities, advanced technology, and focus on secured lending. The bank aims for an Rs 8,000-10,000 crore loan book within three years while targeting robust return ratios, all without compromising its core profitability agenda.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 05:56:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b83b6e10c98d0787aaa34_1766556690663.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Office Market Hits Record High in 2025: Rentals Soar, Vacancies Plummet!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Office-Market-Hits-Record-High-in-2025-Rentals-Soar-Vacancies-Plummet/694b8385e10c98d0787aa9c4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Indias-Office-Market-Hits-Record-High-in-2025-Rentals-Soar-Vacancies-Plummet/694b8385e10c98d0787aa9c4</guid><description>India's Grade A office market reached a new peak in 2025, leasing 71.5 million sq ft, a 6% increase year-on-year. Bengaluru led with 22.1 million sq ft leased. Rentals rose up to 15%, while overall vacancies tightened significantly by 49 basis points. Strong demand from Global Capability Centers (GCCs), technology firms, BFSI, and flex space operators, coupled with a preference for high-quality spaces, fueled this growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 05:53:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b8385e10c98d0787aa9c3_1766557502771.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Russia Sanctions Cripple India's Nayara Energy: Major Refinery Maintenance DELAYED Amid Contractor Exodus!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Russia-Sanctions-Cripple-Indias-Nayara-Energy-Major-Refinery-Maintenance-DELAYED-Amid-Contractor-Exodus/694b82b5e10c98d0787aa7dd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Russia-Sanctions-Cripple-Indias-Nayara-Energy-Major-Refinery-Maintenance-DELAYED-Amid-Contractor-Exodus/694b82b5e10c98d0787aa7dd</guid><description>India's Nayara Energy Ltd. has postponed essential maintenance work at its 400,000 barrel-a-day Vadinar oil refinery. The closure, initially planned for early next year, is now delayed until April 2026. This decision stems from European contractors' reluctance to work with the company due to sanctions linked to its Russian owner, Rosneft PJSC. The situation has also stalled a planned petrochemical project, highlighting significant operational challenges for the refiner.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 05:53:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b82b5e10c98d0787aa7dc_1766556904494.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Stocks Plummet: 3 Penny Gems Crushed 55% From Peaks - Are They Buy Now?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Stocks-Plummet-3-Penny-Gems-Crushed-55percent-From-Peaks-Are-They-Buy-Now/694b82efe10c98d0787aa887</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Stocks-Plummet-3-Penny-Gems-Crushed-55percent-From-Peaks-Are-They-Buy-Now/694b82efe10c98d0787aa887</guid><description>India's stock market faces headwinds in 2025, underperforming regional peers. Amid this, penny stocks have seen sharp drops. This analysis examines three fundamentally strong penny stocks—Delta Corp, HCC, and NTPC Green Energy—that have fallen significantly from their 52-week highs, exploring their potential for investors despite market volatility and sector-specific challenges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 05:51:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b82efe10c98d0787aa886_1766556559791.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BSE Shocker! Groww &amp; Lenskart Surge into Large Cap Index - What It Means For Your Portfolio!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/BSE-Shocker-Groww-and-Lenskart-Surge-into-Large-Cap-Index-What-It-Means-For-Your-Portfolio/694b82e4e10c98d0787aa858</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/BSE-Shocker-Groww-and-Lenskart-Surge-into-Large-Cap-Index-What-It-Means-For-Your-Portfolio/694b82e4e10c98d0787aa858</guid><description>Groww and Lenskart Solutions, along with Tata Motors, are set to be included in key Bombay Stock Exchange indices, including the BSE Large Cap, effective January 6, 2026. This move follows their recent listings, with Groww's IPO raising over ₹6,600 crore and Lenskart Solutions' IPO raising over ₹7,278 crore. The inclusion is expected to impact stock liquidity and investor interest.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 05:51:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b82e4e10c98d0787aa857_1766557035415.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Next Boom! Motilal Oswal Unveils Top Large-Cap Stocks Poised for Massive Wealth Creation by 2026!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-Next-Boom-Motilal-Oswal-Unveils-Top-Large-Cap-Stocks-Poised-for-Massive-Wealth-Creation-by-2026/694b819ce10c98d0787aa5a5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indias-Next-Boom-Motilal-Oswal-Unveils-Top-Large-Cap-Stocks-Poised-for-Massive-Wealth-Creation-by-2026/694b819ce10c98d0787aa5a5</guid><description>Motilal Oswal Financial Services' latest study forecasts a strong Indian economic expansion, projecting ₹148 lakh crore wealth creation from 2020-2025. The report highlights BSE, Rail Vikas Nigam, and Jindal Stainless as top wealth creators driven by valuation and earnings growth. Looking ahead to 2026, the focus shifts to large-cap companies supported by rising incomes and consumption.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 05:51:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b819ce10c98d0787aa5a4_1766556549451.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coal India Board's Bold Move: IPOs for MCL &amp; SECL Approved, Stock Surges 3%!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Coal-India-Boards-Bold-Move-IPOs-for-MCL-and-SECL-Approved-Stock-Surges-3percent/694b8159e10c98d0787aa537</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Coal-India-Boards-Bold-Move-IPOs-for-MCL-and-SECL-Approved-Stock-Surges-3percent/694b8159e10c98d0787aa537</guid><description>Coal India Limited's board has given in-principle approval for the Initial Public Offering (IPO) of its two major subsidiaries, Mahanadi Coalfields Limited (MCL) and South Eastern Coalfields Limited (SECL). This development propelled Coal India's shares up by 3% to ₹412.40 on the BSE, extending a six-session rally. The move aligns with directives from the Ministry of Coal for listings in FY2026-27, aiming to unlock subsidiary value and meet regulatory requirements.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 05:50:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b8159e10c98d0787aa536_1766556438386.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Groww's Secret Weapon: Trade During Outages with New 'Lite' Portal!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Growws-Secret-Weapon-Trade-During-Outages-with-New-Lite-Portal/694b807ee10c98d0787aa38a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Growws-Secret-Weapon-Trade-During-Outages-with-New-Lite-Portal/694b807ee10c98d0787aa38a</guid><description>Indian stock broking platform Groww has launched Groww Lite, a web-based emergency portal. It allows users to exit existing trades during app outages or technical glitches, addressing issues seen during recent internet disruptions. This 'safety layer' operates independently, ensuring traders can manage positions during critical market hours even if the main platform is down.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 05:46:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b807ee10c98d0787aa389_1766555976747.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Rate Cut Shocks Investors: Top Banks Slash FD Rates! What It Means For Your Savings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Rate-Cut-Shocks-Investors-Top-Banks-Slash-FD-Rates-What-It-Means-For-Your-Savings/694b7ee0e10c98d0787aa192</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Rate-Cut-Shocks-Investors-Top-Banks-Slash-FD-Rates-What-It-Means-For-Your-Savings/694b7ee0e10c98d0787aa192</guid><description>Following the Reserve Bank of India's December 2025 decision to cut the repo rate by 25 basis points to 5.25%, major Indian banks including HDFC Bank, State Bank of India, and Axis Bank have announced reductions in their Fixed Deposit (FD) interest rates. This move aims to stimulate economic growth by making borrowing cheaper for banks, but it results in lower returns for FD investors, impacting long-term financial planning.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 05:41:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b7ee0e10c98d0787aa191_1766555708360.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian IT Stocks SHOCKED! US Court Upholds $100k H-1B Fee – Are Your Investments Safe?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Stocks-SHOCKED-US-Court-Upholds-100k-H-1B-Fee-Are-Your-Investments-Safe/694b7cb4e10c98d0787a9f32</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Stocks-SHOCKED-US-Court-Upholds-100k-H-1B-Fee-Are-Your-Investments-Safe/694b7cb4e10c98d0787a9f32</guid><description>Indian IT stocks fell significantly after a US federal judge upheld the Trump administration's plan to impose a $100,000 fee on new H-1B visa applications. Coforge, Wipro, Infosys, HCL Technologies, and Tech Mahindra experienced declines. The Nifty IT index dropped, reflecting investor concerns. While the fee applies only to initial applications, analysts suggest mid-tier firms might face greater challenges than larger ones.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 05:27:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b7cb4e10c98d0787a9f31_1766555465968.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Will Hindusthan Urban Split Its Stock? Shares Jump 12% Ahead of Crucial Board Meet!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Will-Hindusthan-Urban-Split-Its-Stock-Shares-Jump-12percent-Ahead-of-Crucial-Board-Meet/694b7ca1e10c98d0787a9ef1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Will-Hindusthan-Urban-Split-Its-Stock-Shares-Jump-12percent-Ahead-of-Crucial-Board-Meet/694b7ca1e10c98d0787a9ef1</guid><description>Hindusthan Urban Infrastructure shares surged approximately 12% on the BSE, reaching an intra-day high of ₹2,199. This significant price movement follows the company's announcement that its board will convene on December 29, 2025, to discuss a potential stock split and an increase in its authorized share capital. The market is reacting positively to the prospect of these corporate actions.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 05:27:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b7ca1e10c98d0787a9ef0_1766554878570.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Private Equity's Big Bet on Indian Education? K-12 Techno Eyes $200M Funding Boom!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Private-Equitys-Big-Bet-on-Indian-Education-K-12-Techno-Eyes-200M-Funding-Boom/694b7a3ce10c98d0787a9706</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Private-Equitys-Big-Bet-on-Indian-Education-K-12-Techno-Eyes-200M-Funding-Boom/694b7a3ce10c98d0787a9706</guid><description>Kedaara Capital-backed K-12 Techno Services, operator of Orchids The International School, is in talks to raise $150-200 million. European PE firm Vitruvian Partners is considering a lead role, with ChrysCapital, Warburg Pincus, and Permira showing interest. The deal, largely secondary, could value the company at $800-900 million, reflecting renewed PE interest in India's K-12 education sector, particularly in aggregator platforms.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 05:21:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b7a3ce10c98d0787a9705_1766554544312.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>China Greenlights Major Haier India Stake Sale to Bharti-Warburg: What This Means for Your Investments!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/China-Greenlights-Major-Haier-India-Stake-Sale-to-Bharti-Warburg-What-This-Means-for-Your-Investments/694b795be10c98d0787a9584</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/China-Greenlights-Major-Haier-India-Stake-Sale-to-Bharti-Warburg-What-This-Means-for-Your-Investments/694b795be10c98d0787a9584</guid><description>Haier has received approval from the Chinese government to sell a 49% stake in its wholly-owned Indian arm, Haier Appliances India, to a combine of Bharti Enterprises and Warburg Pincus. Haier will retain 49%, employees will get 2%, and the deal is valued between $1.3-1.5 billion. This strategic move aims to secure capital for Haier India's expansion and bypass regulatory hurdles like Press Note 3. Haier India is now the third-largest consumer electronics company in India.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 05:18:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b795be10c98d0787a9583_1766554008466.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ISRO's 'Bahubali' Makes History: Lifts Heaviest US Satellite, Showcasing India's Global Space Prowess!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/ISROs-Bahubali-Makes-History-Lifts-Heaviest-US-Satellite-Showcasing-Indias-Global-Space-Prowess/694b7957e10c98d0787a9555</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/ISROs-Bahubali-Makes-History-Lifts-Heaviest-US-Satellite-Showcasing-Indias-Global-Space-Prowess/694b7957e10c98d0787a9555</guid><description>Indian Space Research Organisation (ISRO) successfully launched the next-generation US communication satellite BlueBird Block-2 using its LVM3-M6 'Bahubali' rocket from Sriharikota. This mission marks the deployment of the largest commercial satellite ever launched from Indian soil, carrying the heaviest payload for a commercial venture. The successful launch underscores India's growing capabilities and its significant role in the global commercial space launch market. Prime Minister Narendra Modi congratulated ISRO scientists, highlighting this achievement as a milestone for India's space journey and self-reliance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 05:16:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b7957e10c98d0787a9554_1766554383330.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coal India Stock Soars Near 52-Week High After HUGE Board Decision: Is This Your Next Multibagger?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Coal-India-Stock-Soars-Near-52-Week-High-After-HUGE-Board-Decision-Is-This-Your-Next-Multibagger/694b74e5e10c98d0787a90cb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Coal-India-Stock-Soars-Near-52-Week-High-After-HUGE-Board-Decision-Is-This-Your-Next-Multibagger/694b74e5e10c98d0787a90cb</guid><description>Coal India's stock price surged 7% in two days, nearing its 52-week high. This rally follows the company's board granting in-principle approval for the public listing of its subsidiaries, South Eastern Coalfields Limited (SECL) and Mahanadi Coalfields Limited (MCL). The move is subject to regulatory approvals and aims to unlock value and potentially boost investor confidence in the state-owned enterprise.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 04:53:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b74e5e10c98d0787a90ca_1766552864447.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Markets Today: Bajaj Finance Soars, Infosys Dips – See Top Gainers &amp; Losers for Dec 24!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Markets-Today-Bajaj-Finance-Soars-Infosys-Dips-See-Top-Gainers-and-Losers-for-Dec-24/694b7428e10c98d0787a8ffd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Markets-Today-Bajaj-Finance-Soars-Infosys-Dips-See-Top-Gainers-and-Losers-for-Dec-24/694b7428e10c98d0787a8ffd</guid><description>On December 24, 2025, the Indian stock market saw Bajaj Finance Ltd and Coal India Ltd leading the gains, while Dr Reddys Laboratories Ltd and Infosys Ltd were among the top losers. The benchmark indices, Sensex and Nifty 50, traded with modest gains, reflecting a mixed but largely stable trading session. Investors tracked these movements for insights into market sentiment and sector performance.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 04:52:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b7428e10c98d0787a8ffc_1766553071734.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>VA Tech Wabag Bags Mega Saudi Water Project: Shares Surge – What Investors Need to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/VA-Tech-Wabag-Bags-Mega-Saudi-Water-Project-Shares-Surge-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/694b7346e10c98d0787a8ec8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/VA-Tech-Wabag-Bags-Mega-Saudi-Water-Project-Shares-Surge-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/694b7346e10c98d0787a8ec8</guid><description>VA Tech Wabag has been named the preferred bidder for Saudi Arabia's Hadda Independent Sewage Treatment Plant (ISTP) project. As the engineering, procurement, and construction (EPC) partner in a consortium led by Metito Utilities, the company will design and build advanced wastewater treatment facilities under a 25-year build, operate, and transfer (BOT) model. This significant win reinforces VA Tech Wabag's Middle East presence and future revenue prospects, despite a recent year-to-date decline in its stock value.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 04:52:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b7346e10c98d0787a8ec7_1766552457719.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Approves Landmark Risk-Based Deposit Insurance: Banks to Pay Premiums Based on Risk!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Approves-Landmark-Risk-Based-Deposit-Insurance-Banks-to-Pay-Premiums-Based-on-Risk/694b7320e10c98d0787a8e85</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Approves-Landmark-Risk-Based-Deposit-Insurance-Banks-to-Pay-Premiums-Based-on-Risk/694b7320e10c98d0787a8e85</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's central board has approved a risk-based deposit insurance framework. Under this new system, banks with stronger risk management and sound financial health will pay lower insurance premiums, while weaker banks will face higher costs, though with a defined ceiling. This move aims to enhance systemic resilience and encourage better governance within the Indian banking sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 04:48:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b7320e10c98d0787a8e84_1766552947014.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Yes Bank's SMBC Deal: Why Is The Stock Stuck Despite Stake Hike?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Yes-Banks-SMBC-Deal-Why-Is-The-Stock-Stuck-Despite-Stake-Hike/694b6e36e10c98d0787a8945</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Yes-Banks-SMBC-Deal-Why-Is-The-Stock-Stuck-Despite-Stake-Hike/694b6e36e10c98d0787a8945</guid><description>Despite Sumitomo Mitsui Banking Corporation (SMBC) increasing its stake in Yes Bank to 24.2%, the bank's stock price remains near the deal value of ₹21.5. Investors are cautious due to slow profitability improvement and a long path to achieving the 1% Return on Assets (RoA) target. Key positives include an improving deposit mix, with higher low-cost CASA deposits, and steady asset quality. The bank aims to leverage the SMBC partnership, but stock re-rating hinges on faster RoA growth and effective use of the SMBC stake.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 04:29:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b6e36e10c98d0787a8944_1766551384445.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NIBE Stock Skyrockets 6% After Board Approves Massive ₹250 Crore Fundraising Plan!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NIBE-Stock-Skyrockets-6percent-After-Board-Approves-Massive-250-Crore-Fundraising-Plan/694b6d0ce10c98d0787a84da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NIBE-Stock-Skyrockets-6percent-After-Board-Approves-Massive-250-Crore-Fundraising-Plan/694b6d0ce10c98d0787a84da</guid><description>NIBE's share price surged by up to 5.69% to ₹1,186.75 after its Board of Directors approved a proposal to raise up to ₹249.85 crore. The funds will be raised through the issuance of equity shares and warrants at ₹1,248 per share/warrant. This announcement comes amid other recent developments, including land acquisition and a change in CFO, and follows a period of net loss and revenue drop in Q2FY26.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 04:19:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b6d0ce10c98d0787a84d9_1766551157556.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Earnings Surge: Motilal Oswal Spots Turnaround, Profit Upgrades Lead Stocks!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Indian-Earnings-Surge-Motilal-Oswal-Spots-Turnaround-Profit-Upgrades-Lead-Stocks/694b6d39e10c98d0787a8534</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Indian-Earnings-Surge-Motilal-Oswal-Spots-Turnaround-Profit-Upgrades-Lead-Stocks/694b6d39e10c98d0787a8534</guid><description>Motilal Oswal Financial Services reports a significant turnaround in Indian corporate earnings, with profit upgrades recorded for the first time in five quarters during the September quarter. FY26 PAT estimates rose 2%, led by mid-cap stocks. The brokerage maintains a positive outlook, forecasting 12-15% earnings growth for FY26/27 and sees reasonable valuations.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 04:19:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b6d39e10c98d0787a8533_1766551268881.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Websol Energy Skyrockets 14% After Winning Crucial ₹73 Crore Tax Dispute!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Websol-Energy-Skyrockets-14percent-After-Winning-Crucial-73-Crore-Tax-Dispute/694b6c30e10c98d0787a8099</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Websol-Energy-Skyrockets-14percent-After-Winning-Crucial-73-Crore-Tax-Dispute/694b6c30e10c98d0787a8099</guid><description>Websol Energy System shares surged 14% to a high of ₹97.55 after the company won a significant income-tax appeal for Assessment Year 2017-18. This victory nullifies a previously disclosed ₹73.04 crore tax demand, removing a substantial contingent liability and boosting investor confidence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 04:19:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b6c30e10c98d0787a8098_1766550651640.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sensex Surges 115 Points! Indian Markets Kick Off Strong - What It Means For Your Investments</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Sensex-Surges-115-Points-Indian-Markets-Kick-Off-Strong-What-It-Means-For-Your-Investments/694b6c5fe10c98d0787a8117</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Sensex-Surges-115-Points-Indian-Markets-Kick-Off-Strong-What-It-Means-For-Your-Investments/694b6c5fe10c98d0787a8117</guid><description>Indian stock markets opened on a positive note today, with the benchmark Sensex climbing 115.8 points to reach 85,640.64 in early trading. The Nifty also saw gains, rising 40.7 points to trade at 26,217.85, indicating a bullish sentiment among investors at the start of the session.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 04:18:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b6c5fe10c98d0787a8116_1766550786111.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>VIP Industries Skyrockets 7% on Massive 26% Stake Block Deal - What Investors Need to Know NOW!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/VIP-Industries-Skyrockets-7percent-on-Massive-26percent-Stake-Block-Deal-What-Investors-Need-to-Know-NOW/694b6adfe10c98d0787a7f68</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/VIP-Industries-Skyrockets-7percent-on-Massive-26percent-Stake-Block-Deal-What-Investors-Need-to-Know-NOW/694b6adfe10c98d0787a7f68</guid><description>VIP Industries shares jumped over 7% after a significant block deal saw approximately 3.7 crore shares, or 26% of the company's equity, change hands. While buyers and sellers remain undisclosed, the transaction size aligns with the residual open-offer quantum previously announced by a consortium led by Multiples Private Equity. This major ownership development follows a series of stake transactions involving promoters and the private equity firm in recent months.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 04:14:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b6adfe10c98d0787a7f67_1766550425472.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Flexi-Cap Showdown: Parag Parikh vs HDFC Fund - Who Wins Over 3, 5 &amp; 10 Years?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Flexi-Cap-Showdown-Parag-Parikh-vs-HDFC-Fund-Who-Wins-Over-3-5-and-10-Years/694b69ade10c98d0787a7da2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Flexi-Cap-Showdown-Parag-Parikh-vs-HDFC-Fund-Who-Wins-Over-3-5-and-10-Years/694b69ade10c98d0787a7da2</guid><description>A detailed comparison between Parag Parikh Flexi Cap Fund and HDFC Flexi Cap Fund reveals their performance over 3, 5, and 10-year horizons for both lump sum investments and Systematic Investment Plans (SIPs). While Parag Parikh leads in 3 and 10-year lump sum returns, HDFC Flexi Cap Fund dominates the 5-year period. For SIPs, HDFC Flexi Cap Fund shows stronger short to medium-term results, whereas Parag Parikh Flexi Cap Fund excels in the long run, highlighting varied leadership across market cycles.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 04:09:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b69ade10c98d0787a7da1_1766550186485.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ServiceNow Shocker: $7.75 Billion Cybersecurity Heist to Supercharge AI Future!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ServiceNow-Shocker-775-Billion-Cybersecurity-Heist-to-Supercharge-AI-Future/694b68f8e10c98d0787a7c60</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ServiceNow-Shocker-775-Billion-Cybersecurity-Heist-to-Supercharge-AI-Future/694b68f8e10c98d0787a7c60</guid><description>AI-first tech giant ServiceNow is set to acquire cybersecurity firm Armis for a massive $7.75 billion, marking its largest acquisition yet. This strategic move aims to significantly expand ServiceNow's security offerings across IT, operational technology, and critical infrastructure, bolstering its defenses in the rapidly evolving AI era. The deal, expected to close in late 2026, brings Armis's substantial revenue and Fortune 100 client base into ServiceNow's fold, reinforcing its position in the booming cybersecurity market.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 04:08:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b68f8e10c98d0787a7c5f_1766550065308.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Economic Shield: Falling Oil &amp; Booming Services Exports Keep CAD in Safe Zone!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economic-Shield-Falling-Oil-and-Booming-Services-Exports-Keep-CAD-in-Safe-Zone/694b686be10c98d0787a7ba9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economic-Shield-Falling-Oil-and-Booming-Services-Exports-Keep-CAD-in-Safe-Zone/694b686be10c98d0787a7ba9</guid><description>India's Current Account Deficit (CAD) is projected to remain stable around 1% of GDP in fiscal year 2026, according to Crisil. This stability is attributed to declining crude oil prices, a strong surplus in services exports, and consistent remittance inflows, which are expected to counterbalance pressures on goods exports due to global economic headwinds. The deficit narrowed significantly in Q2 FY26, signaling resilience.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 04:06:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b686be10c98d0787a7ba8_1766549828254.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jyoti CNC Automation Stock Set for Explosive Growth? Rs 4,546 Cr Order Book Fuels Massive Expansion!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jyoti-CNC-Automation-Stock-Set-for-Explosive-Growth-Rs-4546-Cr-Order-Book-Fuels-Massive-Expansion/694b6750e10c98d0787a7a1d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jyoti-CNC-Automation-Stock-Set-for-Explosive-Growth-Rs-4546-Cr-Order-Book-Fuels-Massive-Expansion/694b6750e10c98d0787a7a1d</guid><description>Jyoti CNC Automation, India's third-largest metal-cutting CNC machine player, is poised for significant growth. The company reported 18% YoY revenue increase in Q2 FY26, driven by the aerospace and defence sector. With a robust order book of ₹4,546 crore offering 24-30 months visibility and a Rs 450 crore capacity expansion plan underway, Jyoti CNC is strategically shifting towards high-margin semiconductor manufacturing. Valued at 32x FY28 earnings, the stock is approaching a potential inflection point as capacity expansion and delivery momentum are key growth catalysts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 03:55:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b6750e10c98d0787a7a1c_1766549710865.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jefferies Unleashes FIRST 'Buy' Rating on Pine Labs! Target ₹300 – Massive Surge Ahead?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Jefferies-Unleashes-FIRST-Buy-Rating-on-Pine-Labs-Target-300-Massive-Surge-Ahead/694b63cbe10c98d0787a774e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Jefferies-Unleashes-FIRST-Buy-Rating-on-Pine-Labs-Target-300-Massive-Surge-Ahead/694b63cbe10c98d0787a774e</guid><description>Brokerage firm Jefferies has initiated coverage on Pine Labs shares with a 'buy' rating and a price target of ₹300, projecting a 28.5% upside. Jefferies highlights Pine Labs' leadership in digital payments, strong revenue growth potential (23% CAGR FY25-28), and expected margin expansion from 15% to 27% by FY28. The report notes current valuations are a discount to peers, suggesting potential for re-rating with consistent growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 03:44:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b63cbe10c98d0787a774d_1766548505533.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>8th Pay Commission Takes Shape: Millions of Govt Employees &amp; Pensioners Eye Salary, Pension Hikes Soon!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/8th-Pay-Commission-Takes-Shape-Millions-of-Govt-Employees-and-Pensioners-Eye-Salary-Pension-Hikes-Soon/694b63ace10c98d0787a771e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/8th-Pay-Commission-Takes-Shape-Millions-of-Govt-Employees-and-Pensioners-Eye-Salary-Pension-Hikes-Soon/694b63ace10c98d0787a771e</guid><description>The 8th Central Pay Commission has been officially constituted, set to revise pay and pensions for over 50 lakh central government employees and 69 lakh pensioners. Recommendations are expected within 18 months, with potential payouts effective January 1, 2026. The 'fitment factor' will guide salary increases, while Dearness Allowance (DA) will remain separate. Estimated fiscal implications are substantial, potentially exceeding ₹4 lakh crore.</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 03:44:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694b63ace10c98d0787a771d_1766548463792.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>