<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:21:05 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India Textiles Sector: Budget Fuels Fiber Push, RSWM Navigates Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/India-Textiles-Sector-Budget-Fuels-Fiber-Push-RSWM-Navigates-Market/697f6cdc47db7081af63d38a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/India-Textiles-Sector-Budget-Fuels-Fiber-Push-RSWM-Navigates-Market/697f6cdc47db7081af63d38a</guid><description>The 2025-26 Union Budget unveils ambitious plans for India's textile sector, focusing on a National Fibre Scheme and Mission for Cotton Productivity to enhance self-reliance. Initiatives like Mega Textile Parks and employment schemes target modernization and rural livelihoods. These measures come as RSWM Limited, a key player, navigates a challenging market with a high P/E ratio, despite reporting Q2 FY26 profits.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:10:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Budget 2026: Roadmap, Not Sops; Market Falls on STT Hike</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Roadmap-Not-Sops-Market-Falls-on-STT-Hike/697f674647db7081af63bd9a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Roadmap-Not-Sops-Market-Falls-on-STT-Hike/697f674647db7081af63bd9a</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 has been unveiled, emphasizing a long-term strategic roadmap for India's future rather than immediate market sops. A hike in Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on futures and options, alongside new taxation on buybacks, led to a dip in market sentiment. However, the Budget prioritizes building economic resilience and self-reliance, aiming to position India against global volatility.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:08:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f674647db7081af63bd99_1769958516239.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UAE E-Invoicing Mandate: Business Overhaul Starts July 2026</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/UAE-E-Invoicing-Mandate-Business-Overhaul-Starts-July-2026/697f6c6047db7081af63d221</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/UAE-E-Invoicing-Mandate-Business-Overhaul-Starts-July-2026/697f6c6047db7081af63d221</guid><description>The United Arab Emirates is implementing a national e-invoicing system, transitioning businesses from paper to structured digital data. A pilot phase begins July 1, 2026, followed by mandatory compliance for large businesses (revenue over AED 50 million) by January 1, 2027, and all VAT-registered entities by July 1, 2027. This mandate, driven by the Ministry of Finance and Federal Tax Authority, requires appointing Accredited Service Providers and will fundamentally alter VAT reporting, operational workflows, and compliance risks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:08:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Budget: Agriculture, Rural Sectors Face Funding Wait Amid Infra Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/India-Budget-Agriculture-Rural-Sectors-Face-Funding-Wait-Amid-Infra-Push/697f673747db7081af63bc6a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/India-Budget-Agriculture-Rural-Sectors-Face-Funding-Wait-Amid-Infra-Push/697f673747db7081af63bc6a</guid><description>India's budget allocates a substantial ₹12.2 trillion for capital expenditure, driving infrastructure development with a 9% increase. However, agriculture and rural sectors appear sidelined. While allied sectors like dairy and fisheries gained, crop farming and critical agricultural research funding saw cuts or stagnation. This prioritization raises questions about future productivity and sector growth.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:06:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f673747db7081af63bc69_1769958408312.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Budget 2026: STT Hike Sparks Market Sell-off</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-2026-STT-Hike-Sparks-Market-Sell-off/697f6be947db7081af63d0a8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-2026-STT-Hike-Sparks-Market-Sell-off/697f6be947db7081af63d0a8</guid><description>Indian equity markets experienced a sharp sell-off following the Union Budget 2026 announcement of increased Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on futures and options. Effective April 1, 2026, the revised rates aim to curb speculative trading and bolster government revenue, mirroring a 'sin tax' approach on financial speculation.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:06:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Budget 2026: India Eyes Critical Mineral Dominance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Budget-2026-India-Eyes-Critical-Mineral-Dominance/697f66ca47db7081af63bb48</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Budget-2026-India-Eyes-Critical-Mineral-Dominance/697f66ca47db7081af63bb48</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 introduces significant fiscal incentives for India's critical minerals sector, including exemptions on basic customs duty for imported capital goods used in mineral processing. This move addresses a key bottleneck, seeking to bolster domestic capabilities and reduce India's substantial reliance on refined minerals and components. The budget also boosts exploration incentives, reinforcing a national strategy to secure supply chains for minerals essential to green energy and advanced manufacturing.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:04:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f66ca47db7081af63bb47_1769958255929.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Pivots to Digital: AI &amp; Chips Fuel 2025 Budget</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Pivots-to-Digital-AI-and-Chips-Fuel-2025-Budget/697f6b6e47db7081af63cf3c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Pivots-to-Digital-AI-and-Chips-Fuel-2025-Budget/697f6b6e47db7081af63cf3c</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2025-26 marks a decisive move away from traditional steel and cement infrastructure, prioritizing the digital economy. Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman announced significant allocations towards the India AI Mission, semiconductor manufacturing, and data center development. This strategic redirection aims to bolster economic growth by fostering technological self-reliance and innovation, projecting AI's substantial contribution to the nation's GDP.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:04:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Budget 2026: Manufacturing &amp; Digital Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-2026-Manufacturing-and-Digital-Shift/697f6b2c47db7081af63ce03</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-2026-Manufacturing-and-Digital-Shift/697f6b2c47db7081af63ce03</guid><description>Budget 2026 marks a significant policy recalibration in India, prioritizing manufacturing, services, and digital infrastructure over traditional rural-centric growth drivers. This strategic shift aims to boost long-term economic competitiveness, supported by substantial public capital expenditure in sectors like defense, railways, and roads. While the focus is on structural economic transformation, an increase in Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on futures and options introduced near-term market volatility.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:03:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Budget 2026: Strategic Allocations Mask Political Discontent</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Strategic-Allocations-Mask-Political-Discontent/697f6b1147db7081af63cd65</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Strategic-Allocations-Mask-Political-Discontent/697f6b1147db7081af63cd65</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27, presented on February 1, 2026, demonstrates a strategic allocation of resources, particularly favoring Tamil Nadu and West Bengal, despite vocal dissent from their state governments. Key announcements include initiatives for rare earth mineral corridors, high-speed rail networks, and agricultural development, signaling a push for self-reliance and economic integration. While the budget aims to bolster domestic manufacturing and critical supply chains, the immediate market reaction saw a notable dip in equity indices. Political leaders, including West Bengal Chief Minister Mamata Banerjee and Tamil Nadu Chief Minister MK Stalin, have decried the budget for its perceived neglect of their states, terming it 'directionless' and 'disappointing'.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:02:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Budget Tightens Fertilizer Subsidies, Eyes Reform</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-Tightens-Fertilizer-Subsidies-Eyes-Reform/697f66c147db7081af63bab4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-Tightens-Fertilizer-Subsidies-Eyes-Reform/697f66c147db7081af63bab4</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 introduces a calibrated tightening of fertilizer subsidies, projecting an overall allocation of ₹1.70 lakh crore, a decrease from the previous fiscal year's revised estimate. Policymakers are increasingly considering structural reforms in nutrient pricing, spurred by concerns over unbalanced fertilizer use and soil degradation. The budget reflects a strategic shift, cutting allocations for imported inputs while noting the rise in domestic urea production and India's near 87% self-sufficiency. This fiscal recalibration aligns with discussions from the Economic Survey 2025-26, which advocates for potential urea price adjustments coupled with direct income transfers to farmers.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:02:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f66c147db7081af63bab3_1769958147928.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Union Budget 2026: India Launches Second Mental Health Institute, Trauma Care Boosted</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Union-Budget-2026-India-Launches-Second-Mental-Health-Institute-Trauma-Care-Boosted/697f6af947db7081af63cc64</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Union-Budget-2026-India-Launches-Second-Mental-Health-Institute-Trauma-Care-Boosted/697f6af947db7081af63cc64</guid><description>Union Budget 2026 prioritizes public health infrastructure, with Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman announcing the creation of a second National Institute of Mental Health and Neuro Sciences (NIMHANS-2). The budget also mandates a 50% expansion of trauma care services in district hospitals, aiming to fortify support for vulnerable populations and address critical gaps in mental health and emergency services across India.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:02:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Boosts I&amp;B Ministry Funds to ₹4,551 Cr, Prioritizing Prasar Bharati &amp; AVGC Sector</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/India-Boosts-IandB-Ministry-Funds-to-4551-Cr-Prioritizing-Prasar-Bharati-and-AVGC-Sector/697f66c047db7081af63baa0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/India-Boosts-IandB-Ministry-Funds-to-4551-Cr-Prioritizing-Prasar-Bharati-and-AVGC-Sector/697f66c047db7081af63baa0</guid><description>The Information and Broadcasting Ministry secured ₹4,551.94 crore in the Union Budget 2026-27, a decrease from the previous fiscal's revised estimates. Key allocations target Prasar Bharati, public service broadcasting, and significant investment in the Animation, Visual Effects, Gaming, and Comics (AVGC) sector. Funds will also support community radio and government media units.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:00:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f66c047db7081af63ba9f_1769958015229.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: Tax Slabs Unchanged, Focus Shifts to Compliance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Tax-Slabs-Unchanged-Focus-Shifts-to-Compliance/697f648547db7081af63b603</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Tax-Slabs-Unchanged-Focus-Shifts-to-Compliance/697f648547db7081af63b603</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026, presented by Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman, has maintained existing income tax slabs for salaried taxpayers, disappointing widespread expectations for immediate relief. Instead, the government is intensifying its strategic push towards the new tax regime, emphasizing administrative simplification and compliance enhancements over direct rate cuts. Key measures include streamlined tax proceedings, reduced litigation, and a new Income Tax Act effective April 1, 2026, signaling a long-term focus on tax system efficiency. The budget also introduced targeted reductions in Tax Collected at Source (TCS) for overseas remittances and travel, alongside other administrative easing measures.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:59:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f648547db7081af63b602_1769957972948.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Budget Prioritizes Minerals, Nuclear Energy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-Prioritizes-Minerals-Nuclear-Energy/697f69d747db7081af63ca52</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-Prioritizes-Minerals-Nuclear-Energy/697f69d747db7081af63ca52</guid><description>Presented February 1, 2026, India's Union Budget 2026-27 targets strategic self-reliance, introducing dedicated Rare Earth Corridors to integrate mining to manufacturing and reduce import dependence. The budget also offers significant long-term support for nuclear energy infrastructure and duty exemptions for processing capital goods. While ambitious, experts note the need for coordinated policy and administrative reforms for full operationalization, alongside concerns about support for specific renewable energy segments.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:57:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Budget 2026 Sparks Market Sell-off on STT Hike; IT, Tourism Shine</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Sparks-Market-Sell-off-on-STT-Hike-IT-Tourism-Shine/697f646547db7081af63b569</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Sparks-Market-Sell-off-on-STT-Hike-IT-Tourism-Shine/697f646547db7081af63b569</guid><description>Indian equity markets registered a sharp decline on February 1, 2026, following Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman's Budget 2026 presentation. The benchmark Sensex plummeted by 1,547 points and the Nifty 50 dropped by 495 points. A substantial increase in Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on futures and options was identified as the primary catalyst for the sell-off, escalating trading costs. Conversely, the budget's provisions provided tailwinds for the IT sector, driven by revised buyback taxation, alongside gains in tourism, jewellery, and electronics manufacturing stocks.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:56:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f646547db7081af63b568_1769957801241.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget Slashes LPG, Internship Funds: Poor Families, Youth Feel Pinch</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-Slashes-LPG-Internship-Funds-Poor-Families-Youth-Feel-Pinch/697f698f47db7081af63c91c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-Slashes-LPG-Internship-Funds-Poor-Families-Youth-Feel-Pinch/697f698f47db7081af63c91c</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 presents deep cuts to crucial welfare programs. Funding for providing LPG connections to impoverished families has been slashed by nearly 28%. Additionally, the PM Internship Scheme faces a significant reduction, with its allocation dropping from a revised Rs 526.39 crore to Rs 4,799.96 crore, signaling potential implementation hurdles. Meanwhile, allocations for women and child development schemes see increases.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:56:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Budget 2026 Fuels Mahindra's Growth Amid Manufacturing Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Budget-2026-Fuels-Mahindras-Growth-Amid-Manufacturing-Push/697f639d47db7081af63b376</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Budget-2026-Fuels-Mahindras-Growth-Amid-Manufacturing-Push/697f639d47db7081af63b376</guid><description>Mahindra Group CEO Anish Shah praised Union Budget 2026, calling it an "excellent" fiscal plan that will accelerate India's economic expansion by bolstering manufacturing. The budget's emphasis on 'Viksit Bharat,' 'Atma Nirbharata,' and specific sector support, including a ₹10,000 crore MSME fund and rare earth corridors, is expected to significantly boost the automotive, hospitality, and logistics sectors where Mahindra operates. This policy alignment is set to support the group's rapid growth trajectory and 'Make in India for the world' strategy.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:55:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f639d47db7081af63b375_1769957706687.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Realty Stocks Tumble on Budget's Affordable Housing Gap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Realty-Stocks-Tumble-on-Budgets-Affordable-Housing-Gap/697f692f47db7081af63c78f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Realty-Stocks-Tumble-on-Budgets-Affordable-Housing-Gap/697f692f47db7081af63c78f</guid><description>The Indian real estate sector experienced significant profit booking following the Union Budget 2026, with the Nifty Realty index shedding 2% on January 31, 2026. Major developers like Lodha, Sobha, Godrej Properties, DLF, Oberoi Realty, and Signatureglobal (India) saw declines of up to 5%. The downturn was attributed to the Budget's perceived lack of concrete measures for the affordable housing segment, a concern voiced strongly by industry body CREDAI. While long-term infrastructure development plans offer some optimism, immediate investor sentiment soured due to the absence of targeted support for affordable housing.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:54:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Stricter Crypto Reporting Penalties</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Stricter-Crypto-Reporting-Penalties/697f691c47db7081af63c6b7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Stricter-Crypto-Reporting-Penalties/697f691c47db7081af63c6b7</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026, presented on February 1, 2026, introduces significant penalties for crypto reporting entities, including exchanges and investment platforms. Effective April 1, 2026, these measures aim to enforce stricter compliance with transaction reporting under the Income Tax Act, 2025. While the existing tax framework remains unchanged, the government is implementing a daily fine of Rs. 200 for non-furnishing of statements and Rs. 50,000 for providing inaccurate information. This move is seen by industry stakeholders as a step towards greater transparency and accountability in the digital asset sector.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:54:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Edelweiss MF: Budget 2026 Prioritizes Long-Term Growth Over Quick Wins</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Edelweiss-MF-Budget-2026-Prioritizes-Long-Term-Growth-Over-Quick-Wins/697f68b847db7081af63c588</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Edelweiss-MF-Budget-2026-Prioritizes-Long-Term-Growth-Over-Quick-Wins/697f68b847db7081af63c588</guid><description>Budget 2026-27 favors long-term capability-building and fiscal discipline over immediate welfare spending, signaling sustained growth for disciplined investors. Edelweiss MF's Radhika Gupta notes this continuity enhances capital markets and sector stability.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:52:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Payment Firms Blast 'Paltry' UPI Subsidy, Warn Digital Growth Hit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Payment-Firms-Blast-Paltry-UPI-Subsidy-Warn-Digital-Growth-Hit/697f62ca47db7081af63b168</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Payment-Firms-Blast-Paltry-UPI-Subsidy-Warn-Digital-Growth-Hit/697f62ca47db7081af63b168</guid><description>The payment industry expressed sharp disappointment with the government's ₹2,000 crore subsidy allocation for Unified Payments Interface (UPI) and RuPay debit cards. Industry leaders warn this meager incentive will severely stunt digital payment expansion, particularly in rural areas. They are urging the government to permit a controlled Merchant Discount Rate (MDR) for merchants exceeding Rs 20 lakh in turnover to ensure ecosystem sustainability and further adoption.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:52:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f62ca47db7081af63b167_1769957543407.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: Lithium Battery Duty Cut to Fuel EV Infrastructure Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Budget-2026-Lithium-Battery-Duty-Cut-to-Fuel-EV-Infrastructure-Boom/697f68a047db7081af63c4e7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Budget-2026-Lithium-Battery-Duty-Cut-to-Fuel-EV-Infrastructure-Boom/697f68a047db7081af63c4e7</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 proposes extending customs duty exemptions on capital goods for lithium-ion battery manufacturing. This move, coupled with concessional duty benefits for cells and parts until March 2028, aims to foster a robust electric vehicle ecosystem in India. Industry bodies welcomed the policy continuity, anticipating boosts to domestic production, affordability, and green mobility.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:52:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Healthcare Elevated to Economic Engine</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Budget-2026-Healthcare-Elevated-to-Economic-Engine/697f629d47db7081af63b03f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/India-Budget-2026-Healthcare-Elevated-to-Economic-Engine/697f629d47db7081af63b03f</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 positions India's healthcare sector as a key economic growth engine, shifting focus from social service to productive infrastructure. Key initiatives include the Biopharma Shakti program to boost domestic biopharmaceutical manufacturing, development of five regional medical tourism hubs, and strategic integration of Artificial Intelligence. These measures aim to enhance India's global competitiveness and resilience while attracting sustained investment. Initial market reactions saw hospital stocks gain momentum.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:51:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f629d47db7081af63b03e_1769957478763.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Navigates Global Headwinds: Budget Prioritizes Resilience</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Navigates-Global-Headwinds-Budget-Prioritizes-Resilience/697f628347db7081af63af8c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Navigates-Global-Headwinds-Budget-Prioritizes-Resilience/697f628347db7081af63af8c</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman stated on February 1, 2026, that India's policymaking continuously factors in global uncertainty, assuring that domestic macroeconomic fundamentals remain robust. The Union Budget 2026 was presented against a backdrop of international volatility, with the government prioritizing sustained growth and economic resilience. External factors are acknowledged as primary drivers of currency pressures, rather than domestic issues.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:48:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f628347db7081af63af8b_1769957322676.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Bets Big on Private Sector for Semiconductor Future 2.0</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Bets-Big-on-Private-Sector-for-Semiconductor-Future-20/697f673a47db7081af63bd07</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Bets-Big-on-Private-Sector-for-Semiconductor-Future-20/697f673a47db7081af63bd07</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman unveiled India Semiconductor Mission (ISM) 2.0, handing over future development to the private sector. The initiative targets equipment, materials, and Indian IP. Despite ₹1.6 lakh crore invested and major projects underway by Tata and Micron, India faces talent shortages, import reliance, and fierce global competition.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:46:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Budget 2026 Streamlines Investor Tax Compliance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Streamlines-Investor-Tax-Compliance/697f622547db7081af63ad8c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Streamlines-Investor-Tax-Compliance/697f622547db7081af63ad8c</guid><description>Union Budget 2026 introduces a significant simplification for retail investors by enabling depositories like NSDL and CDSL to accept Form 15G and Form 15H. This centralized process aims to reduce paperwork and TDS errors by allowing investors to submit these tax exemption declarations once, with depositories then distributing them to relevant companies. The move is expected to enhance tax administration efficiency and ease compliance burdens, particularly for senior citizens and small taxpayers.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:46:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f622547db7081af63ad8b_1769957170979.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>16th FC: Stable Tax Share, Efficiency Push Stirs Debate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/16th-FC-Stable-Tax-Share-Efficiency-Push-Stirs-Debate/697f621647db7081af63ad22</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/16th-FC-Stable-Tax-Share-Efficiency-Push-Stirs-Debate/697f621647db7081af63ad22</guid><description>The Sixteenth Finance Commission's report proposes maintaining states' share of central divisible taxes at 41%, prioritizing fiscal consolidation and introducing a new efficiency metric in horizontal distribution. This approach, which ends revenue deficit grants, aims to incentivize economic growth but raises concerns about widening inter-state disparities and the impact on poorer regions.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:44:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f621647db7081af63ad21_1769957034013.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tobacco Tax Surge Sparks Stock Sell-off, Profit Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Tobacco-Tax-Surge-Sparks-Stock-Sell-off-Profit-Fears/697f61b847db7081af63ab9d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Tobacco-Tax-Surge-Sparks-Stock-Sell-off-Profit-Fears/697f61b847db7081af63ab9d</guid><description>The Indian tobacco sector faces a severe tax shock following the Union Budget 2026. A sharp increase in GST to 40% and new excise duties, effective February 1, 2026, alongside higher NCCD on certain products, has triggered a sell-off in major cigarette stocks. ITC and Godfrey Phillips have seen substantial drops, with analysts projecting significant price hikes, potential volume contractions, and increased risks of illicit trade.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:42:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f61b847db7081af63ab9c_1769956858475.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: Biogas Duty Cut May Boost Gas Retailer Margins</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Budget-2026-Biogas-Duty-Cut-May-Boost-Gas-Retailer-Margins/697f615647db7081af63a98b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Budget-2026-Biogas-Duty-Cut-May-Boost-Gas-Retailer-Margins/697f615647db7081af63a98b</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 has introduced an excise duty exemption for the biogas component within compressed natural gas (CNG). This move, effective from fiscal year 2026-27, aims to reduce costs for CNG retailers by effectively zeroing out the excise duty on the biogas portion. While this offers a fiscal incentive, industry executives note the average national blend of compressed biogas (CBG) in CNG remains low at approximately 1%, suggesting a marginal immediate impact on overall costs. However, companies may defer passing on savings to consumers, potentially leading to short-term margin enhancements.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:38:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f615647db7081af63a98a_1769956703207.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ashok Leyland Surges as Budget Fuels Infra &amp; CV Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ashok-Leyland-Surges-as-Budget-Fuels-Infra-and-CV-Demand/697f612b47db7081af63a8d4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ashok-Leyland-Surges-as-Budget-Fuels-Infra-and-CV-Demand/697f612b47db7081af63a8d4</guid><description>Ashok Leyland stands to benefit significantly from the Union Budget 2026's emphasis on infrastructure development, logistics, and manufacturing. Chairman Dheeraj Hinduja highlighted how increased capital expenditure in these areas is expected to drive substantial demand for commercial vehicles, bolstering the company's sales. The budget's broader focus on economic growth and industrial resilience further strengthens the positive outlook for the sector.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:36:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f612b47db7081af63a8d3_1769956612969.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: Infra Fuels Realty, Affordable Housing Lags</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Budget-2026-Infra-Fuels-Realty-Affordable-Housing-Lags/697f603147db7081af63a6af</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Budget-2026-Infra-Fuels-Realty-Affordable-Housing-Lags/697f603147db7081af63a6af</guid><description>The Union Budget for FY2026-27 prioritizes infrastructure-led growth, injecting ₹12.2 lakh crore in public capital expenditure and launching initiatives like an Infrastructure Risk Guarantee Fund and dedicated REITs for CPSE asset monetization. Seven high-speed rail corridors are slated for development. While these measures are expected to stimulate housing demand and commercial development, particularly in Tier-2 and Tier-3 cities, the budget omits direct fiscal incentives for residential buyers or developers, leaving affordable housing concerns unresolved. Industry experts view the budget as a catalyst for stability and medium-term demand rather than an immediate stimulus.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:35:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f603147db7081af63a6ae_1769956536701.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Capital Markets Gain Depth from Wider Investor Base</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Capital-Markets-Gain-Depth-from-Wider-Investor-Base/697f5f3d47db7081af63a4c0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Capital-Markets-Gain-Depth-from-Wider-Investor-Base/697f5f3d47db7081af63a4c0</guid><description>India's capital markets are demonstrating increased depth and resilience, driven by a significantly broadened investor base since the pandemic. Pankaj Murarka of Renaissance Investment Managers points to a structural expansion fueled by first-time participants, while acknowledging the need to curb speculative trading. Robust growth is expected across asset management, wealth management, and investment banking segments, with India maintaining a strong global standing in IPOs. The recent Union Budget 2026-27 is viewed as detail-oriented, supporting infrastructure and credit markets.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:32:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f5f3d47db7081af63a4bf_1769956356280.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Banks Face 'Viksit Bharat' Reform Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Banks-Face-Viksit-Bharat-Reform-Push/697f5ecb47db7081af63a38c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Indias-Banks-Face-Viksit-Bharat-Reform-Push/697f5ecb47db7081af63a38c</guid><description>Union Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman has announced the formation of a "High Level Committee on Banking for Viksit Bharat" and proposed restructuring Public Sector NBFCs like PFC and REC as part of Budget 2026. These initiatives aim to comprehensively review and align India's financial sector with future growth trajectories, bolstering financial stability, inclusion, and consumer protection. The sector is currently characterized by robust balance sheets and record profitability, positioning it to embrace future reforms.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f5ecb47db7081af63a38b_1769956193140.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026 Fuels Adventure Tourism Sector</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/India-Budget-2026-Fuels-Adventure-Tourism-Sector/697f5e5647db7081af63a228</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/India-Budget-2026-Fuels-Adventure-Tourism-Sector/697f5e5647db7081af63a228</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 signals a substantial push for India's adventure tourism sector, announcing comprehensive plans to develop diverse trails including mountain, coastal, and wildlife paths across key regions. This strategic allocation aims to tap into the growing demand for ecological adventure experiences, bolster local economies through employment generation, and diversify India's tourism offerings towards sustainable, low-impact travel. Initial market reactions show a positive trend, with tourism and hospitality stocks experiencing notable gains following the budget's announcement.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:27:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f5e5647db7081af63a227_1769956053889.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Healthcare Stocks Rally on Budget Boost Amid Market Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Healthcare-Stocks-Rally-on-Budget-Boost-Amid-Market-Slump/697f5d9b47db7081af63a04f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Healthcare-Stocks-Rally-on-Budget-Boost-Amid-Market-Slump/697f5d9b47db7081af63a04f</guid><description>Despite a market-wide downturn triggered by increased Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on futures and options, leading hospital chains like Max Healthcare Institute and Aster DM Healthcare saw significant gains on February 1, 2026. The Union Budget 2026-27 announced a substantial ₹1.05 trillion allocation for the healthcare sector and unveiled plans for five medical tourism hubs, alongside initiatives to train 1.5 lakh caregivers and expand allied health professional institutions. While Narayana Hrudayalaya also posted gains, Apollo Hospitals Enterprises saw its intraday gains erased by the market's close.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:25:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f5d9b47db7081af63a04e_1769955951928.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Consumer Costs Shift Dramatically</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Consumer-Costs-Shift-Dramatically/697f5d7747db7081af639f30</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Consumer-Costs-Shift-Dramatically/697f5d7747db7081af639f30</guid><description>Union Budget 2026 has recalibrated India's consumer cost landscape, easing taxes on essential medicines, smartphones, and foreign travel while increasing levies on luxury imports, tobacco, and derivatives trading. Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman's proposals aim to stimulate domestic manufacturing and boost government revenue through targeted fiscal measures.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:22:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f5d7747db7081af639f2f_1769955700616.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Budget 2026: Data Center Tax Holiday Fuels AI Ambitions, STT Hike Sparks Concern</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Budget-2026-Data-Center-Tax-Holiday-Fuels-AI-Ambitions-STT-Hike-Sparks-Concern/697f5d6447db7081af639e4e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Budget-2026-Data-Center-Tax-Holiday-Fuels-AI-Ambitions-STT-Hike-Sparks-Concern/697f5d6447db7081af639e4e</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 has unveiled a significant tax holiday for foreign companies operating data centers in India, extending until 2047. Raamdeo Agrawal of Motilal Oswal Financial Services described this measure as the budget's most consequential, overshadowing other proposals and aiming to transform India into a global AI manufacturing hub. This initiative targets substantial foreign investment, projecting a build-out potentially worth $70-80 billion by 2030. Conversely, the budget's proposed increase in the Securities Transaction Tax (STT) signals potential headwinds for market liquidity, as higher trading costs may deter speculative and arbitrage strategies.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:20:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f5d6447db7081af639e4d_1769955565232.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: India Shifts Focus to Startup Scale</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Budget-2026-India-Shifts-Focus-to-Startup-Scale/697f5d2847db7081af639cdf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Budget-2026-India-Shifts-Focus-to-Startup-Scale/697f5d2847db7081af639cdf</guid><description>Union Budget 2026 marks a definitive shift from nurturing startup creation to fostering global scale. Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman announced significant capital infusions and policy support, targeting deep tech, advanced manufacturing, and MSMEs. Key initiatives include India Semiconductor Mission 2.0 with ₹40,000 crore for electronics components, a ₹10,000 crore SME Growth Fund, and increased allocations for AI capacity-building missions, aiming to build globally competitive Indian enterprises.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:17:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f5d2847db7081af639cde_1769955440465.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: STT Hike to Curb F&amp;O Speculation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Budget-2026-STT-Hike-to-Curb-FandO-Speculation/697f5d1747db7081af639c9d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Budget-2026-STT-Hike-to-Curb-FandO-Speculation/697f5d1747db7081af639c9d</guid><description>The Indian Budget 2026 has significantly increased Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on futures and options trading. Rates for futures rose to 0.05% (from 0.02%), and options now face 0.15% (from 0.1% and 0.125%). This move, aimed at curbing excessive speculation and systemic risk, has increased trading costs for all participants, particularly frequent traders. While causing an immediate dip in market sentiment and impacting brokerage stocks, experts are divided on its long-term effects, with some noting other budget positives like clarified buyback taxation.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:15:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f5d1747db7081af639c9c_1769955309138.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Green Tech Surge, Adaptation Gap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/India-Budget-2026-Green-Tech-Surge-Adaptation-Gap/697f5ce747db7081af639bae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/India-Budget-2026-Green-Tech-Surge-Adaptation-Gap/697f5ce747db7081af639bae</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 prioritizes renewable energy, critical minerals, and green manufacturing with targeted incentives and infrastructure development. However, it notably omits specific measures for climate change adaptation, drawing criticism from experts who highlight the vulnerability of communities to extreme weather events. While mitigation efforts are strong, the focus on protecting lives and livelihoods from climate impacts remains underdeveloped.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:12:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f5ce747db7081af639bad_1769955161737.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>