<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 06:27:51 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Fertiliser Stocks to Shine? Elara Capital Reveals Top Agri Bets Over Troubled Agrochemicals!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Fertiliser-Stocks-to-Shine-Elara-Capital-Reveals-Top-Agri-Bets-Over-Troubled-Agrochemicals/6957617b4342f77179fa5121</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Fertiliser-Stocks-to-Shine-Elara-Capital-Reveals-Top-Agri-Bets-Over-Troubled-Agrochemicals/6957617b4342f77179fa5121</guid><description>Brokerage firm Elara Capital is favoring fertiliser stocks over agrochemicals, citing muted performance expectations for the latter due to stressed demand drivers like pest issues and weather. While fertilisers face raw material cost pressures, their volumes are more stable. Elara highlights Coromandel International and Paradeep Phosphates as top 'Buy' picks in fertilisers, with Chambal Fertilisers rated 'Accumulate'. In agrochemicals, UPL and Sumitomo Chemical India are listed as preferred stocks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 05:58:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957617b4342f77179fa5120_1767334384703.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Market Buzz: Indian Stocks See Mixed Action Jan 2! Hindalco Soars, ITC Dives – See Full Gainers &amp; Losers List!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Buzz-Indian-Stocks-See-Mixed-Action-Jan-2-Hindalco-Soars-ITC-Dives-See-Full-Gainers-and-Losers-List/695760ff4342f77179fa4efb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Market-Buzz-Indian-Stocks-See-Mixed-Action-Jan-2-Hindalco-Soars-ITC-Dives-See-Full-Gainers-and-Losers-List/695760ff4342f77179fa4efb</guid><description>On January 2, 2026, Indian stock markets showed mixed performance. Hindalco Industries Ltd and Coal India Ltd led the gains, while ITC Ltd and Bajaj Auto Ltd were among the top losers. The Sensex closed up 0.40% at 85532.64, and the Nifty 50 rose 0.41% to 26253.50, indicating a generally positive but selective trading session.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 05:58:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695760ff4342f77179fa4efa_1767334405946.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI Unleashes Fury: 26 Banned, Rs 1.87 Crore Penalty in DU Digital Stock Manipulation Shockwave!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Unleashes-Fury-26-Banned-Rs-187-Crore-Penalty-in-DU-Digital-Stock-Manipulation-Shockwave/695761484342f77179fa5040</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Unleashes-Fury-26-Banned-Rs-187-Crore-Penalty-in-DU-Digital-Stock-Manipulation-Shockwave/695761484342f77179fa5040</guid><description>India's market watchdog, SEBI, has banned at least 26 individuals from trading for up to 30 months and levied a Rs 1.87 crore penalty. The action targets their involvement in manipulating the stock of DU Digital Technologies Limited, an SME listed on the NSE Emerge platform. SEBI also ordered 21 individuals to return Rs 98.78 lakh in unlawful gains, plus interest.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 05:57:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695761484342f77179fa503f_1767334405429.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Power Stocks Skyrocket! REC &amp; PFC Stage Massive Comeback - Best Week in Months!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Power-Stocks-Skyrocket-REC-and-PFC-Stage-Massive-Comeback-Best-Week-in-Months/695760904342f77179fa4ce8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Power-Stocks-Skyrocket-REC-and-PFC-Stage-Massive-Comeback-Best-Week-in-Months/695760904342f77179fa4ce8</guid><description>State-run power financiers REC Ltd. and Power Finance Corporation Ltd. (PFC) are experiencing a significant rally, with shares up nearly 4% on Friday, marking their third consecutive day of gains. REC shares have surged 7% this week, their best performance since March 2024, while PFC shares are up over 6%, their strongest week since May 2024. This follows a challenging 2024 for both companies. Despite past declines from record highs, analysts remain overwhelmingly positive, with 12 out of 13 tracking analysts recommending a 'buy' for both stocks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 05:57:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695760904342f77179fa4ce7_1767334133859.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Reliance Industries Nears Record Highs: Morgan Stanley Unlocks 2026's Massive Growth Potential!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Reliance-Industries-Nears-Record-Highs-Morgan-Stanley-Unlocks-2026s-Massive-Growth-Potential/695760334342f77179fa4adb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Reliance-Industries-Nears-Record-Highs-Morgan-Stanley-Unlocks-2026s-Massive-Growth-Potential/695760334342f77179fa4adb</guid><description>Reliance Industries shares are trading near record highs after Morgan Stanley reiterated its 'Overweight' rating and set a price target of ₹1,847, implying an 18% upside. The brokerage identifies 2026 as a pivotal year with catalysts in every quarter, including refining up-cycles, ARPU hikes, new energy initiatives, and potential digital IPO, expecting significant multiple and return expansion.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 05:57:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695760334342f77179fa4ada_1767334005741.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>L&amp;T Lands Massive Orders! ₹10,000 Crore Boost Fuels Stock Surge to New Highs!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/LandT-Lands-Massive-Orders-10000-Crore-Boost-Fuels-Stock-Surge-to-New-Highs/695760424342f77179fa4b3a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/LandT-Lands-Massive-Orders-10000-Crore-Boost-Fuels-Stock-Surge-to-New-Highs/695760424342f77179fa4b3a</guid><description>Larsen &amp; Toubro's minerals and metals division secured "major" engineering, procurement, and construction (EPC) orders worth up to ₹10,000 crore from Steel Authority of India Ltd. (SAIL) and other domestic clients. These contracts involve critical process plants for SAIL's plant expansions in West Bengal and Jharkhand, alongside specialized material handling equipment, driving L&amp;T's stock to a 52-week intraday high.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 05:57:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695760424342f77179fa4b39_1767334037808.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vodafone Idea Shares Skyrocket 4% as Report Hints at Dues Halved – Government Exit on the Horizon?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vodafone-Idea-Shares-Skyrocket-4percent-as-Report-Hints-at-Dues-Halved-Government-Exit-on-the-Horizon/69575f9d4342f77179fa485e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vodafone-Idea-Shares-Skyrocket-4percent-as-Report-Hints-at-Dues-Halved-Government-Exit-on-the-Horizon/69575f9d4342f77179fa485e</guid><description>Vodafone Idea shares surged 4% following reports that the Department of Telecommunications (DoT) committee may significantly reduce the company's Adjusted Gross Revenue (AGR) dues, potentially by over 50% after reassessment. This relief package also reportedly sets the stage for the Indian government to exit its substantial stake in the debt-ridden telecom operator, provided a profitable sale is possible.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 05:53:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69575f9d4342f77179fa485d_1767333888169.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Defence Deal Alert! Rs 79,000 Crore Approval Ignites Indian Stock Surge - 7 Companies to Watch!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defence-Deal-Alert-Rs-79000-Crore-Approval-Ignites-Indian-Stock-Surge-7-Companies-to-Watch/69575e9b4342f77179fa431f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defence-Deal-Alert-Rs-79000-Crore-Approval-Ignites-Indian-Stock-Surge-7-Companies-to-Watch/69575e9b4342f77179fa431f</guid><description>India's Defence Acquisition Council (DAC) has approved defence goods worth approximately ₹79,000 crore, prioritizing domestic procurement for the Army, Navy, and Air Force. This significant move is expected to boost the stock performance of key defense manufacturers like Solar Industries, Bharat Electronics, Hindustan Aeronautics, and others, signaling robust growth prospects for the indigenous defense sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 05:48:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69575e9b4342f77179fa431e_1767333617636.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kia India Unveils 2026 Seltos: Price Shock, Futuristic Tech, and Massive Upgrades Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Kia-India-Unveils-2026-Seltos-Price-Shock-Futuristic-Tech-and-Massive-Upgrades-Revealed/69575e964342f77179fa42ec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Kia-India-Unveils-2026-Seltos-Price-Shock-Futuristic-Tech-and-Massive-Upgrades-Revealed/69575e964342f77179fa42ec</guid><description>Kia India has launched the 2026 Seltos with prices ranging from ₹10.99 lakh to ₹19.99 lakh. This facelifted SUV boasts increased dimensions, a striking new design with a Digital Tiger Face and connected LED tail lamps, and a premium interior featuring a massive 75.18cm three-screen display. It offers advanced safety with ADAS Level 2 and enhanced connectivity, aiming to redefine the mid-SUV segment and boost Kia India's market position with multiple petrol and diesel powertrain options.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 05:48:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69575e964342f77179fa42eb_1767333705337.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Manufacturing Engine Slows: PMI Hits 38-Month Low, Economy Faces Headwinds!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Manufacturing-Engine-Slows-PMI-Hits-38-Month-Low-Economy-Faces-Headwinds/69575dda4342f77179fa3f67</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Manufacturing-Engine-Slows-PMI-Hits-38-Month-Low-Economy-Faces-Headwinds/69575dda4342f77179fa3f67</guid><description>India's manufacturing sector experienced its slowest growth in 38 months, with the S&amp;P Global PMI dipping to 55 in December from 56.6 in November. This signals the weakest improvement in the sector's health in two years. Employment growth also slowed to its lowest pace in 22 months. Despite the easing momentum, analysts remain cautiously optimistic due to stable demand and low inflationary pressures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 05:46:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69575dda4342f77179fa3f66_1767333405367.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Drunk Pilot Scare: Air India Flight Delayed After Vancouver Alcohol Incident!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Drunk-Pilot-Scare-Air-India-Flight-Delayed-After-Vancouver-Alcohol-Incident/69575cf44342f77179fa3b3f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Drunk-Pilot-Scare-Air-India-Flight-Delayed-After-Vancouver-Alcohol-Incident/69575cf44342f77179fa3b3f</guid><description>Air India is investigating after one of its pilots was found under the influence of alcohol by Canadian authorities before operating a Vancouver-Delhi flight (AI186) on December 23. The pilot was offloaded, causing a flight delay, and is now off flying duties pending an inquiry. Air India expressed regret and is cooperating with local authorities, promising strict action if violations are confirmed.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 05:43:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69575cf44342f77179fa3b3e_1767333181216.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Health Insurance Boom: GST Cut Fuels 31% Cover Jump, Bigger Policies Now Rule!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indias-Health-Insurance-Boom-GST-Cut-Fuels-31percent-Cover-Jump-Bigger-Policies-Now-Rule/69575c6d4342f77179fa38bf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indias-Health-Insurance-Boom-GST-Cut-Fuels-31percent-Cover-Jump-Bigger-Policies-Now-Rule/69575c6d4342f77179fa38bf</guid><description>Data from Policybazaar reveals a significant shift in India's health insurance market. Following the removal of GST on premiums, the average health cover has surged by 31%, rising from ₹14.5 lakh to nearly ₹19 lakh. This trend indicates a move towards more comprehensive and longer-term policies, with substantial growth in mid-to-high value and unlimited coverage plans, signalling a crucial behavioral change among Indian consumers towards protection-led financial planning.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 05:39:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69575c6d4342f77179fa38be_1767333186420.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bansal Wire Stock Surges 10%! Highest-Ever Sales Volume in Q3 Ignites Investor Frenzy!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Bansal-Wire-Stock-Surges-10percent-Highest-Ever-Sales-Volume-in-Q3-Ignites-Investor-Frenzy/69575a234342f77179fa2f82</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Bansal-Wire-Stock-Surges-10percent-Highest-Ever-Sales-Volume-in-Q3-Ignites-Investor-Frenzy/69575a234342f77179fa2f82</guid><description>Bansal Wire Industries shares rallied nearly 10% on January 2, 2026, hitting an intraday high of ₹335. The surge was driven by the company's announcement of its highest-ever quarterly sales volume of 121,702 metric tonnes in Q3 FY26, surpassing its previous record. This strong performance highlights the company's dominant position as India's largest stainless steel wire manufacturer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 05:26:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69575a234342f77179fa2f81_1767332458703.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Biman Bangladesh Shocks Rivals, Picks Boeing for Massive 14-Aircraft Order! See the Dreamliners &amp; 737 MAX Deal!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Biman-Bangladesh-Shocks-Rivals-Picks-Boeing-for-Massive-14-Aircraft-Order-See-the-Dreamliners-and-737-MAX-Deal/695758ac4342f77179fa26dc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Biman-Bangladesh-Shocks-Rivals-Picks-Boeing-for-Massive-14-Aircraft-Order-See-the-Dreamliners-and-737-MAX-Deal/695758ac4342f77179fa26dc</guid><description>Biman Bangladesh Airlines has decided to purchase 14 aircraft from US manufacturer Boeing, ending a bidding contest with European rival Airbus. The state-run airline's board approved the acquisition of eight Boeing 787-10 Dreamliners, two Boeing 787-9 Dreamliners, and four Boeing 737-8 MAX planes. This fleet expansion and modernization plan aims to boost Bangladesh's aviation capacity and international connectivity. The deal awaits final price negotiations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 05:25:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695758ac4342f77179fa26db_1767332264542.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cardano's ADA Skyrockets 7%, Bitcoin &amp; Ether Steady: Crypto Kicks Off 2026 With Cautious Optimism!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Cardanos-ADA-Skyrockets-7percent-Bitcoin-and-Ether-Steady-Crypto-Kicks-Off-2026-With-Cautious-Optimism/695758d64342f77179fa27a9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Cardanos-ADA-Skyrockets-7percent-Bitcoin-and-Ether-Steady-Crypto-Kicks-Off-2026-With-Cautious-Optimism/695758d64342f77179fa27a9</guid><description>Cardano's ADA surged 7% as major cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ether began 2026 with steady gains, trading near $88,700 and $3,010 respectively. This uptick occurred amidst a global risk-on sentiment, with Asian equities and precious metals also advancing. Analysts suggest selective positioning and a focus on capital preservation, indicating continued Bitcoin dominance rather than a widespread altcoin rally, as investors return from the holiday break.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 05:22:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695758d64342f77179fa27a8_1767332243062.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bitcoin Price EXPLOSION Coming? Bollinger Band Squeeze Hints at Massive Swing!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoin-Price-EXPLOSION-Coming-Bollinger-Band-Squeeze-Hints-at-Massive-Swing/695757ce4342f77179fa20da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Bitcoin-Price-EXPLOSION-Coming-Bollinger-Band-Squeeze-Hints-at-Massive-Swing/695757ce4342f77179fa20da</guid><description>Bitcoin's price is unusually calm, trapped in a tight $85,000-$90,000 range for two weeks. This 'Bollinger Bands squeeze,' where volatility bands narrow, historically precedes significant price swings. Traders are advised to be vigilant as a major move appears imminent, with historical patterns suggesting sharp uptrends or downtrends can follow such periods of low volatility.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 05:21:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695757ce4342f77179fa20d9_1767331856228.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>E to E Transportation IPO Skyrockets 90% on Debut, Hits Upper Circuit!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/E-to-E-Transportation-IPO-Skyrockets-90percent-on-Debut-Hits-Upper-Circuit/695750eb4342f77179fa0476</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/E-to-E-Transportation-IPO-Skyrockets-90percent-on-Debut-Hits-Upper-Circuit/695750eb4342f77179fa0476</guid><description>E to E Transportation, a railway system integration specialist, achieved a spectacular debut on the NSE SME platform, listing at ₹330.5 per share, a 90% premium over its issue price of ₹174. The stock quickly surged to hit the 5% upper circuit at ₹347.10. The company's IPO, which raised ₹84.22 crore through a fresh issue, was vastly oversubscribed, attracting bids over 526 times the shares on offer.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:52:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695750eb4342f77179fa0475_1767330107813.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's First! Time Technoplast Wins Crucial Approval, Stock Jumps 5% - What's Next?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-First-Time-Technoplast-Wins-Crucial-Approval-Stock-Jumps-5percent-Whats-Next/695750aa4342f77179fa032f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-First-Time-Technoplast-Wins-Crucial-Approval-Stock-Jumps-5percent-Whats-Next/695750aa4342f77179fa032f</guid><description>Time Technoplast shares surged over 5% to ₹197.80 after receiving crucial approvals from PESO and TUV Rheinland for manufacturing High-Pressure Type-3 Composite Cylinders. This makes the company the first in India to secure such approval for compressed gas applications, expanding its market reach in hydrogen, oxygen, medical, and industrial sectors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:52:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695750aa4342f77179fa032e_1767330068939.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ITC Stock Faces Downgrade Amidst Tax Hike Fears; Devyani-Sapphire Merger Sparks Optimism!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ITC-Stock-Faces-Downgrade-Amidst-Tax-Hike-Fears-Devyani-Sapphire-Merger-Sparks-Optimism/6957511a4342f77179fa059b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ITC-Stock-Faces-Downgrade-Amidst-Tax-Hike-Fears-Devyani-Sapphire-Merger-Sparks-Optimism/6957511a4342f77179fa059b</guid><description>Motilal Oswal has downgraded ITC to neutral due to a sharp excise duty hike on cigarettes, warning of potential price increases, volume declines, and earnings pressure. Conversely, the brokerage views the proposed merger between Devyani International and Sapphire Foods positively, anticipating significant synergies, improved scale, and enhanced profitability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:52:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957511a4342f77179fa059a_1767330231111.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>E TO E Transportation Infra IPO Skyrockets: 90% Listing Gain on Stellar Debut!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/E-TO-E-Transportation-Infra-IPO-Skyrockets-90percent-Listing-Gain-on-Stellar-Debut/695750074342f77179fa0044</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/E-TO-E-Transportation-Infra-IPO-Skyrockets-90percent-Listing-Gain-on-Stellar-Debut/695750074342f77179fa0044</guid><description>E TO E Transportation Infrastructure made a spectacular market debut on the NSE Emerge platform, listing at a 90% premium over its IPO price. The ₹84 crore issue, which saw a massive 527 times subscription, opened at ₹330.60 per share. The railway signalling and telecom infrastructure solutions provider now has a market capitalization of ₹599 crore.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:47:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695750074342f77179fa0043_1767330068936.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Budget 2026-27: Is Solar Energy Set to Eclipse Fossil Fuels? Investors Watch for Crucial Moves!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Budget-2026-27-Is-Solar-Energy-Set-to-Eclipse-Fossil-Fuels-Investors-Watch-for-Crucial-Moves/695750044342f77179fa0009</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Budget-2026-27-Is-Solar-Energy-Set-to-Eclipse-Fossil-Fuels-Investors-Watch-for-Crucial-Moves/695750044342f77179fa0009</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026-27 is expected to be a game-changer for solar energy, aiming to boost its competitiveness against fossil fuels. The budget is anticipated to focus on enhancing domestic solar manufacturing via Production-Linked Incentives (PLI), expanding renewable capacity, optimizing schemes like PM Surya Ghar Muft Bijli Yojana, and introducing new green finance tools. This strategic push could solidify solar as a cornerstone of India's energy future and drive significant investment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:47:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695750044342f77179fa0008_1767329928714.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Defence Stock EXPLODES: Multibagger Returns, Massive New Orders Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defence-Stock-EXPLODES-Multibagger-Returns-Massive-New-Orders-Revealed/69574aa64342f77179f9e753</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Defence-Stock-EXPLODES-Multibagger-Returns-Massive-New-Orders-Revealed/69574aa64342f77179f9e753</guid><description>Apollo Micro Systems Limited has been declared the lowest bidder for a defense order worth ₹25.78 crore, to be executed in 18 months. This adds to recent wins totaling approximately ₹5,708.96 crore through its subsidiaries, including contracts for Coal India Limited and defense projects. The company reported strong Q2FY26 results with revenue up 40% to ₹225.26 crore and PAT soaring 91% to ₹30.03 crore. The stock has delivered exceptional multibagger returns of 800% in 3 years and 2,100% in 5 years.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:22:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69574aa64342f77179f9e752_1767328507234.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Equities Poised for CY26 Rebound: Earnings Revival &amp; Top MOFSL Picks Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Equities-Poised-for-CY26-Rebound-Earnings-Revival-and-Top-MOFSL-Picks-Revealed/69574ba14342f77179f9ed22</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Equities-Poised-for-CY26-Rebound-Earnings-Revival-and-Top-MOFSL-Picks-Revealed/69574ba14342f77179f9ed22</guid><description>Motilal Oswal predicts Indian equities will rebound in calendar year 2026, driven by improving earnings, stable macro conditions, and reasonable valuations near long-period averages. The brokerage favors diversified financials, IT services, automobiles, telecom, and capital goods, highlighting key large-cap and mid/small-cap stock picks. This outlook follows Indian equities' tenth consecutive year of gains in CY25, despite a volatile December and divergence in market segment performance. Domestic investors dominated inflows while foreign investors exited.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:17:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69574ba14342f77179f9ed21_1767328749414.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hyundai India Shares Tumble! December Sales Miss; New Indian CEO Takes Charge Amidst Stock Dip</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-India-Shares-Tumble-December-Sales-Miss-New-Indian-CEO-Takes-Charge-Amidst-Stock-Dip/6957497e4342f77179f9df63</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Hyundai-India-Shares-Tumble-December-Sales-Miss-New-Indian-CEO-Takes-Charge-Amidst-Stock-Dip/6957497e4342f77179f9df63</guid><description>Hyundai Motor India's stock dropped nearly 2% after its December sales figures missed analyst expectations. While total sales rose 6.6% year-over-year, this was below the projected 13% increase. Domestic sales saw minimal growth, though exports performed strongly. The company also announced Tarun Garg will become its first Indian MD and CEO from January 1, 2026.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:16:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957497e4342f77179f9df62_1767328383826.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kotak Bullish on PVR Inox: Correction Overdone, Buy Signal Issued!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Kotak-Bullish-on-PVR-Inox-Correction-Overdone-Buy-Signal-Issued/695748b44342f77179f9db18</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Kotak-Bullish-on-PVR-Inox-Correction-Overdone-Buy-Signal-Issued/695748b44342f77179f9db18</guid><description>Kotak Institutional Equities has reiterated its 'Buy' rating on PVR Inox, setting a INR1,380 price target. The firm expects strong Q3 occupancy and mid-teen EBITDA margins, noting that the Q4 movie slate could boost FY26 estimates. Kotak considers the recent stock correction unjustified, given improving cinema trends and consistent free cash flow generation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:16:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695748b44342f77179f9db17_1767327980842.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tax Deadline Dread Vanishes! ICICI Bank Unveils Game-Changing Scheme to Save Your Capital Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Tax-Deadline-Dread-Vanishes-ICICI-Bank-Unveils-Game-Changing-Scheme-to-Save-Your-Capital-Gains/695748f14342f77179f9dcc1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Tax-Deadline-Dread-Vanishes-ICICI-Bank-Unveils-Game-Changing-Scheme-to-Save-Your-Capital-Gains/695748f14342f77179f9dcc1</guid><description>ICICI Bank has launched the Capital Gains Account Scheme (CGAS) following government approval. This facility allows resident individuals and HUFs to deposit un-invested long-term capital gains, earning interest while remaining tax-exempt until reinvestment. The scheme, effective January 1, 2026, offers flexible savings or term deposit options for parking funds up to three years for reinvestment in assets like property or agricultural land.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:16:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695748f14342f77179f9dcc0_1767328100328.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold &amp; Silver Skyrocket: 2026 Kicks Off with Record-Breaking Gains After Stellar 2025!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-Skyrocket-2026-Kicks-Off-with-Record-Breaking-Gains-After-Stellar-2025/695748b94342f77179f9db5d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-Skyrocket-2026-Kicks-Off-with-Record-Breaking-Gains-After-Stellar-2025/695748b94342f77179f9db5d</guid><description>Precious metals, gold and silver, started 2026 with a strong upward trend, recouping recent losses. Following a record-shattering 2025 where gold surged 64% and silver achieved its best year ever, investor confidence remains high. Expectations of U.S. Federal Reserve interest rate cuts and safe-haven demand continue to support gold prices, while silver's 'critical mineral' status and industrial demand fuel its rally.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:14:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695748b94342f77179f9db5c_1767328031022.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unlocking Hidden Gems: This Chemical Stock's Massive Correction Creates a Rare Entry Point for Investors!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Unlocking-Hidden-Gems-This-Chemical-Stocks-Massive-Correction-Creates-a-Rare-Entry-Point-for-Investors/6957481c4342f77179f9d7df</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Unlocking-Hidden-Gems-This-Chemical-Stocks-Massive-Correction-Creates-a-Rare-Entry-Point-for-Investors/6957481c4342f77179f9d7df</guid><description>PCBL, a key carbon black manufacturer, is attracting attention after a significant 36% stock correction. The company is expanding its core carbon black capacity and diversifying into high-growth areas like water treatment chemicals (via Aquapharm) and battery chemicals (via Nonvance). Despite an elevated debt ratio, its valuation is seen as reasonable, offering a potential entry opportunity for investors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:12:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957481c4342f77179f9d7de_1767327950970.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Gold Rush: Indian IT Giants Splurge Billions on Mega-Deals! Will Profits Soar or Sink?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Gold-Rush-Indian-IT-Giants-Splurge-Billions-on-Mega-Deals-Will-Profits-Soar-or-Sink/695748284342f77179f9d838</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Gold-Rush-Indian-IT-Giants-Splurge-Billions-on-Mega-Deals-Will-Profits-Soar-or-Sink/695748284342f77179f9d838</guid><description>Indian IT leaders TCS and Coforge are making their largest-ever acquisitions to boost AI capabilities, part of an estimated $4 billion industry investment in 2025. While crucial for staying competitive in the AI era, companies face investor scrutiny over balancing massive spending with profitability, especially as clients cautiously evaluate AI's real-world financial impact. Integration challenges and demonstrating ROI remain key.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:12:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695748284342f77179f9d837_1767328015688.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Prices Tumble! Is This Safe Haven Now a Risky Bet? Experts Reveal What's Next</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Prices-Tumble-Is-This-Safe-Haven-Now-a-Risky-Bet-Experts-Reveal-Whats-Next/695747564342f77179f9d464</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Prices-Tumble-Is-This-Safe-Haven-Now-a-Risky-Bet-Experts-Reveal-Whats-Next/695747564342f77179f9d464</guid><description>Gold spot prices dipped to $4,365/oz, marking a 3.68% weekly decline and a 1.27% daily gain. MCX futures for 24-carat gold closed lower at Rs 1,35,690 per 10g. Despite a historic 65% surge in 2025, analysts predict consolidation between $4,320 and $4,420 amid geopolitical tensions and shifting US interest rate expectations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 04:12:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695747564342f77179f9d463_1767327635639.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bumper Year Ahead for Indian Real Estate? Nomura Names Top Developers Defying Market Woes!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Bumper-Year-Ahead-for-Indian-Real-Estate-Nomura-Names-Top-Developers-Defying-Market-Woes/695740c34342f77179f9bbec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Bumper-Year-Ahead-for-Indian-Real-Estate-Nomura-Names-Top-Developers-Defying-Market-Woes/695740c34342f77179f9bbec</guid><description>Nomura forecasts a strong performance for India's listed real estate developers, expecting a third consecutive quarter of resilient pre-sales in Q3FY26. Despite broader market pressures, demand for branded residential projects remains healthy, with supply and regulatory approvals cited as key bottlenecks rather than buyer appetite. Nomura reiterates Prestige Estates as its top pick and also favors Lodha Developers and Aditya Birla Real Estate, anticipating many leading developers will meet their FY26 sales targets.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 03:43:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695740c34342f77179f9bbeb_1767325993953.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LAST CHANCE: Modern Diagnostic IPO Closes Today with Massive 28x Subscription &amp; ₹14 GMP!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/LAST-CHANCE-Modern-Diagnostic-IPO-Closes-Today-with-Massive-28x-Subscription-and-14-GMP/695740b74342f77179f9bb9b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/LAST-CHANCE-Modern-Diagnostic-IPO-Closes-Today-with-Massive-28x-Subscription-and-14-GMP/695740b74342f77179f9bb9b</guid><description>Modern Diagnostic IPO is closing today, January 2, 2026, after opening on December 31, 2025. The public issue has seen overwhelming investor demand, reaching over 28.77 times subscription, largely driven by Non-Institutional Investors and retail investors. The Grey Market Premium (GMP) stands strong at ₹14 (15.56%) over the upper price band of ₹90. The ₹36.89 crore IPO aims to fund medical equipment, working capital, and debt repayment. Listing is expected on BSE SME on January 7, 2026.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 03:43:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695740b74342f77179f9bb9a_1767325953532.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Government's Rs 3.84 Lakh Crore T-Bill Plan: Your Guide to Safe Investing!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Governments-Rs-384-Lakh-Crore-T-Bill-Plan-Your-Guide-to-Safe-Investing/69573fe34342f77179f9b8b7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Governments-Rs-384-Lakh-Crore-T-Bill-Plan-Your-Guide-to-Safe-Investing/69573fe34342f77179f9b8b7</guid><description>The Finance Ministry has announced the auction calendar for Government of India Treasury Bills, aiming to raise Rs 3.84 lakh crore by March 2026. These T-bills, available in 91, 182, and 364-day terms with a minimum investment of Rs 25,000, offer assured returns and are suitable for risk-averse investors. Profits are taxed as short-term capital gains.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 03:38:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69573fe34342f77179f9b8b6_1767325739027.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Smartworks Stock Set for 19% Surge? Analysts Say BUY as Vikhroli Campus Nears World Record!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Smartworks-Stock-Set-for-19percent-Surge-Analysts-Say-BUY-as-Vikhroli-Campus-Nears-World-Record/695739634342f77179f99948</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Smartworks-Stock-Set-for-19percent-Surge-Analysts-Say-BUY-as-Vikhroli-Campus-Nears-World-Record/695739634342f77179f99948</guid><description>Kotak Institutional Equities initiated coverage on Smartworks Coworking Spaces Ltd. with a 'Buy' rating and ₹600 price target, expecting a 19% upside. The firm cited Smartworks' leading position in India's flexible workspace market, projecting 38% EBITDA CAGR and significant area expansion. All five analysts tracking the stock have a 'Buy' rating. The company is also developing the world's largest managed office campus in Vikhroli.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 03:09:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695739634342f77179f99947_1767324176826.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Fed's Shocking Concern: December Minutes Reveal Hidden Risk of Short-Term Funding Seizing Up!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Feds-Shocking-Concern-December-Minutes-Reveal-Hidden-Risk-of-Short-Term-Funding-Seizing-Up/695737a54342f77179f99133</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Feds-Shocking-Concern-December-Minutes-Reveal-Hidden-Risk-of-Short-Term-Funding-Seizing-Up/695737a54342f77179f99133</guid><description>Minutes from the Federal Reserve's December 2025 policy meeting reveal officials are closely monitoring a significant risk: the potential for short-term funding markets to experience a cash shortage. Despite comfort with the economic outlook and expected rate cuts, signs indicate tighter conditions in overnight borrowing markets. The Fed is considering purchasing approximately $220 billion in short-term Treasury securities to maintain adequate bank reserves and ensure smooth market functioning.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 03:05:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695737a54342f77179f99132_1767323620353.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Chemical Stocks in Freefall: 4 Giants Down Nearly 50%! China's Shadow or Market Glitch?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Chemical-Stocks-in-Freefall-4-Giants-Down-Nearly-50percent-Chinas-Shadow-or-Market-Glitch/6957374a4342f77179f98f00</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Chemical-Stocks-in-Freefall-4-Giants-Down-Nearly-50percent-Chinas-Shadow-or-Market-Glitch/6957374a4342f77179f98f00</guid><description>Four prominent Indian chemical companies — Neogen Chemicals, Clean Science and Technology, Balaji Amines, and Sudarshan Chemical Industries — have seen their stock prices fall by up to 49% from their 52-week highs. This decline is attributed to factors including intensified competition from Chinese manufacturers flooding the market with cheaper alternatives, a global demand slowdown, rising input costs, and company-specific challenges like plant incidents and inventory pressures. Investors are advised to exercise caution and conduct thorough research.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 03:04:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957374a4342f77179f98eff_1767323530444.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>DRDO Unveils Rs 1.30 Lakh Crore Defence Arsenal: India's Self-Reliance Takes 'Quantum Leap'!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DRDO-Unveils-Rs-130-Lakh-Crore-Defence-Arsenal-Indias-Self-Reliance-Takes-Quantum-Leap/695736294342f77179f98937</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/DRDO-Unveils-Rs-130-Lakh-Crore-Defence-Arsenal-Indias-Self-Reliance-Takes-Quantum-Leap/695736294342f77179f98937</guid><description>India's defence self-reliance has achieved a 'quantum jump' with the government approving 22 Acceptance of Necessity (AoN) for defence systems worth approximately Rs 1.30 lakh crore. DRDO Chairman Samir V Kamat stated these systems will be manufactured by Indian industries, marking the highest value of AoNs in history and significantly boosting the 'Aatmanirbhar Bharat' vision. Key approvals include advanced missile systems and drone interdiction technology.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 02:57:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695736294342f77179f98936_1767323338262.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>2026 Indian Startups: Profit Surge or Bust? AI, Fintech IPOs &amp; Gaming Shake-up!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/2026-Indian-Startups-Profit-Surge-or-Bust-AI-Fintech-IPOs-and-Gaming-Shake-up/695735994342f77179f9863b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/2026-Indian-Startups-Profit-Surge-or-Bust-AI-Fintech-IPOs-and-Gaming-Shake-up/695735994342f77179f9863b</guid><description>Indian startups in 2026 will prioritize discipline, profitability, and sustainable unit economics over rapid expansion. Expect a shift towards AI integration, heightened scrutiny of the EV sector, and a surge in lending tech IPOs from companies like Kreditbee, Fibe, and Moneyview. The real money gaming sector is rebuilding post-ban, while e-commerce focuses on owned channels and quick commerce intensifies competition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 02:56:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695735994342f77179f9863a_1767323103092.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global Markets Soar: Tech Stocks Hit New Highs, Gold &amp; Silver Rebound as New Year Begins!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Global-Markets-Soar-Tech-Stocks-Hit-New-Highs-Gold-and-Silver-Rebound-as-New-Year-Begins/6957340c4342f77179f97f4d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Global-Markets-Soar-Tech-Stocks-Hit-New-Highs-Gold-and-Silver-Rebound-as-New-Year-Begins/6957340c4342f77179f97f4d</guid><description>Global stocks and US equity futures climbed at the start of the new year, led by technology shares like Samsung Electronics. Precious metals, including gold and silver, also rebounded. Despite optimism around artificial intelligence and strong 2025 performance, risks from US monetary policy and high tech valuations persist.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 02:49:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6957340c4342f77179f97f4c_1767322701122.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Supreme Court Declares: Corporate Duty Extends to Nature, Profit Not Paramount!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Supreme-Court-Declares-Corporate-Duty-Extends-to-Nature-Profit-Not-Paramount/695731dc4342f77179f975a0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Environment/Supreme-Court-Declares-Corporate-Duty-Extends-to-Nature-Profit-Not-Paramount/695731dc4342f77179f975a0</guid><description>India's Supreme Court has ruled that corporations must prioritize environmental and wildlife protection, expanding Corporate Social Responsibility beyond shareholder interests. The court invoked the 'polluter pays' principle, mandating companies to fund conservation efforts if their operations threaten endangered species' habitats. This landmark observation calls for a critical reevaluation of development policies and judicial intervention against state actions that harm ecosystems.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 02:34:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695731dc4342f77179f9759f_1767322383282.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>