<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 21:14:16 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India's Car Buyers Crave Tech: Connected Features Double Sales Share, Driving Next-Gen Auto Boom!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Car-Buyers-Crave-Tech-Connected-Features-Double-Sales-Share-Driving-Next-Gen-Auto-Boom/695020c74342f77179d97f0e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Indias-Car-Buyers-Crave-Tech-Connected-Features-Double-Sales-Share-Driving-Next-Gen-Auto-Boom/695020c74342f77179d97f0e</guid><description>Digital and connected features are now a major draw for Indian car buyers, especially young and Gen Z consumers. Sales of connected cars have doubled in five years, reaching 27.4% of new vehicle sales (Jan-Oct 2025). Carmakers are integrating advanced features like geofencing, remote monitoring, and driver safety tech even into compact models such as the Hyundai Venue and Tata Altroz, driven by demand for convenience and safety on modern expressways. This trend is reshaping automotive sales and product development in India.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 17:59:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695020c74342f77179d97f0d_1766859243582.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata's Air India Express Lands First Brand-New Boeing MAX Jet: A Game Changer Arrives!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Tatas-Air-India-Express-Lands-First-Brand-New-Boeing-MAX-Jet-A-Game-Changer-Arrives/69501f354342f77179d97d3d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Tatas-Air-India-Express-Lands-First-Brand-New-Boeing-MAX-Jet-A-Game-Changer-Arrives/69501f354342f77179d97d3d</guid><description>Air India Express receives its first brand-new Boeing 737-8 MAX aircraft, registered VT-RNT, featuring a special Ratan Tata tribute livery. This marks a significant milestone as the first new plane acquired since Tata Group took over. It's part of a massive order of over 570 aircraft, signaling a major fleet expansion and modernization effort aimed at enhancing the airline's operational capabilities and market presence.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 17:52:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69501f354342f77179d97d3c_1766858757382.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SILVER EXPLODES! Prices Skyrocket to Record Highs - Is Your Investment Portfolio Ready for This Shine?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/SILVER-EXPLODES-Prices-Skyrocket-to-Record-Highs-Is-Your-Investment-Portfolio-Ready-for-This-Shine/69500bcd4342f77179d96ff0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/SILVER-EXPLODES-Prices-Skyrocket-to-Record-Highs-Is-Your-Investment-Portfolio-Ready-for-This-Shine/69500bcd4342f77179d96ff0</guid><description>Silver prices have surged to a fresh lifetime high of ₹2.42 lakh per kg on MCX and $79.70 per ounce globally. This rally is driven by robust industrial demand, anticipation of US interest rate cuts, and concerns over supply disruptions, particularly due to potential export restrictions from China. Experts see silver as a better investment than gold for 2026, with prices expected to climb further.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:30:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69500bcd4342f77179d96fef_1766853719921.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Stocks Shock: 79% Fail to Beat SBI FD in 2025! Is Your Portfolio Missing Out?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Stocks-Shock-79percent-Fail-to-Beat-SBI-FD-in-2025-Is-Your-Portfolio-Missing-Out/695009ac4342f77179d96d9e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Stocks-Shock-79percent-Fail-to-Beat-SBI-FD-in-2025-Is-Your-Portfolio-Missing-Out/695009ac4342f77179d96d9e</guid><description>In 2025, nearly 79% of actively traded BSE stocks underperformed the State Bank of India's fixed deposit rate of 6.25%. This occurred despite the benchmark Sensex rising 8.8%. Gains were concentrated among large-cap stocks, with only 18.5% of companies ranked 251 and below by market capitalization beating the FD hurdle. This marks a shift from previous years where a majority of stocks outperformed fixed deposits, highlighting a selective and potentially unforgiving market environment.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:19:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695009ac4342f77179d96d9d_1766853332158.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nilesh Shah's 2026 Market Secrets REVEALED! Gold &amp; Midcaps Poised for Massive Gains? Investor Alert!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Nilesh-Shahs-2026-Market-Secrets-REVEALED-Gold-and-Midcaps-Poised-for-Massive-Gains-Investor-Alert/694ffc944342f77179d96324</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Nilesh-Shahs-2026-Market-Secrets-REVEALED-Gold-and-Midcaps-Poised-for-Massive-Gains-Investor-Alert/694ffc944342f77179d96324</guid><description>Kotak AMC MD Nilesh Shah advocates for a balanced investment portfolio, including equities and precious metals. He predicts a positive outlook for gold and silver, supported by central bank purchases and industrial demand. Shah expects midcap stocks to outperform large caps in 2026-2027, fueled by robust earnings growth, while small caps might lag due to high valuations. He also highlights the need for capital and profitability in new-age sectors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 15:25:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ffc944342f77179d96323_1766850205976.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ceigall India's Bold Move: Exceeds FY26 Order Target, Signals Major Growth Ahead!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ceigall-Indias-Bold-Move-Exceeds-FY26-Order-Target-Signals-Major-Growth-Ahead/694ffd7a4342f77179d96420</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ceigall-Indias-Bold-Move-Exceeds-FY26-Order-Target-Signals-Major-Growth-Ahead/694ffd7a4342f77179d96420</guid><description>Ceigall India, an infrastructure construction firm, has surpassed its fiscal year 2025-26 (FY26) order inflow target by securing ₹5,386 crore in new orders, bringing its total order book to ₹14,237 crore. Despite initial execution challenges, the company maintains its 10-15% revenue growth forecast for the year, expecting stronger performance in the second half. A recent renewable energy order under the PM-KUSUM scheme in Madhya Pradesh highlights its growing presence in solar projects.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 15:25:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ffd7a4342f77179d9641f_1766850111827.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Growth At Risk? Ex-RBI Governor Warns of US Tariffs, Calls for Urgent Diplomacy!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-At-Risk-Ex-RBI-Governor-Warns-of-US-Tariffs-Calls-for-Urgent-Diplomacy/694ffa064342f77179d96114</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-At-Risk-Ex-RBI-Governor-Warns-of-US-Tariffs-Calls-for-Urgent-Diplomacy/694ffa064342f77179d96114</guid><description>Former Reserve Bank of India Governor C. Rangarajan warned that India's economic growth is vulnerable due to challenges like 50% US tariffs and the need for stronger economic diplomacy. He linked the Indian Rupee's fall to tense India-US relations causing capital outflows. Rangarajan emphasized that achieving development targets requires sustained GDP growth, private investment revival, and effective technology adoption, including AI.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 15:13:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ffa064342f77179d96113_1766849129165.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>China's Bold Trade Law Overhaul: National Security, IP Rights, and Global Supply Chains Face Major Shift!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Chinas-Bold-Trade-Law-Overhaul-National-Security-IP-Rights-and-Global-Supply-Chains-Face-Major-Shift/694ff7a74342f77179d95eef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Chinas-Bold-Trade-Law-Overhaul-National-Security-IP-Rights-and-Global-Supply-Chains-Face-Major-Shift/694ff7a74342f77179d95eef</guid><description>China's legislature has approved significant revisions to its foreign trade law, set to take effect on March 1, 2026. The updated law aims to safeguard national sovereignty, security, and development interests amidst escalating global tensions. Key changes include strengthening intellectual property rights protection and establishing a trade adjustment assistance system to enhance supply chain stability and overall competitiveness.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 15:06:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694ff7a74342f77179d95eee_1766848498549.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Boom &amp; Visa Shake-up: Why Mid-Cap Indian IT Stocks Could Be Your Next Big Win!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Boom-and-Visa-Shake-up-Why-Mid-Cap-Indian-IT-Stocks-Could-Be-Your-Next-Big-Win/694fed1b4342f77179d9564d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Boom-and-Visa-Shake-up-Why-Mid-Cap-Indian-IT-Stocks-Could-Be-Your-Next-Big-Win/694fed1b4342f77179d9564d</guid><description>Mid-cap Indian IT firms are better positioned than large caps due to improving enterprise demand and accelerating AI upskilling, according to Equirus Capital. Changes to the US H-1B visa framework are expected to drive more local hiring and offshoring, with minimal margin impact. Analysts predict mid- to high-single-digit growth for the sector in FY27, with specialized, nimble mid-cap players potentially benefiting most from AI adoption and BFSI spending.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 14:19:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fed1b4342f77179d9564c_1766845891528.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aadhar Housing Finance Surges Ahead: 20% AUM Growth on Track! Investor Bullish Signals?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Aadhar-Housing-Finance-Surges-Ahead-20percent-AUM-Growth-on-Track-Investor-Bullish-Signals/694fed404342f77179d95685</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Aadhar-Housing-Finance-Surges-Ahead-20percent-AUM-Growth-on-Track-Investor-Bullish-Signals/694fed404342f77179d95685</guid><description>Aadhar Housing Finance is poised for strong growth, targeting 20-22% Asset Under Management (AUM) expansion this fiscal year. Managing Director Rishi Anand confirmed that second-half disbursements are on track for an 18% rise, with incremental Q3 figures exceeding 20%. Funding costs are gradually decreasing, and the company anticipates maintaining stable spreads while remaining adequately capitalized for near-term growth, expecting AUM to double in 3.5 years. Gross NPAs are projected to stay within 1.10-1.15%.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 14:19:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fed404342f77179d95684_1766845848972.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tech Stocks Wild Ride! Meesho, Aequs Dive as ideaForge, DroneAcharya Soar in Mixed Week</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tech-Stocks-Wild-Ride-Meesho-Aequs-Dive-as-ideaForge-DroneAcharya-Soar-in-Mixed-Week/694fea994342f77179d9534e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tech-Stocks-Wild-Ride-Meesho-Aequs-Dive-as-ideaForge-DroneAcharya-Soar-in-Mixed-Week/694fea994342f77179d9534e</guid><description>India's new-age tech stocks experienced a mixed trading week from December 22-26. While ideaForge and DroneAcharya saw significant gains, companies like Meesho and Aequs declined amid profit booking. Broader market sentiment remained cautious due to continued Foreign Institutional Investor (FII) selling, impacting the overall market cap of new-age tech firms.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 14:06:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fea994342f77179d9534d_1766845426640.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global Trade WARNING: 2026 Faces Tariff BACKLASH! Will Your Portfolio Feel the Pinch?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Trade-WARNING-2026-Faces-Tariff-BACKLASH-Will-Your-Portfolio-Feel-the-Pinch/694fe9664342f77179d95193</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Global-Trade-WARNING-2026-Faces-Tariff-BACKLASH-Will-Your-Portfolio-Feel-the-Pinch/694fe9664342f77179d95193</guid><description>Global merchandise trade proved resilient in 2025 despite US tariffs, but 2026 is anticipated to bring significant "tariff consequences." Trade patterns are rebalancing, with India showing strong import growth, but challenges like the USMCA review and supply chain risks loom. Experts anticipate a turbulent year ahead for global commerce.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 14:04:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fe9664342f77179d95192_1766844937842.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Economic Secret: Why Sanjeev Sanyal Says Bankruptcy is Crucial for Riches!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economic-Secret-Why-Sanjeev-Sanyal-Says-Bankruptcy-is-Crucial-for-Riches/694fe8dd4342f77179d950b0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Economic-Secret-Why-Sanjeev-Sanyal-Says-Bankruptcy-is-Crucial-for-Riches/694fe8dd4342f77179d950b0</guid><description>Sanjeev Sanyal, a member of the Prime Minister's Economic Advisory Council, asserts that India must embrace bankruptcy to build a dynamic, risk-taking economy. He emphasizes continuous churn, where old companies exit and new ones emerge, as vital for long-term strength. Sanyal cited historical examples and highlighted Mumbai's growing financial prominence as indicators of this necessary evolution for innovation.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 14:02:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fe8dd4342f77179d950af_1766844937300.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Gem Exports Hold Steady: US Trade Talk Clarity Expected in January, Fueling Hope!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/India-Gem-Exports-Hold-Steady-US-Trade-Talk-Clarity-Expected-in-January-Fueling-Hope/694fe4d54342f77179d94cb1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/India-Gem-Exports-Hold-Steady-US-Trade-Talk-Clarity-Expected-in-January-Fueling-Hope/694fe4d54342f77179d94cb1</guid><description>India's gem and jewellery exports have remained steady at $19 billion until November, buoyed by Free Trade Agreements (FTAs) despite US tariff pressures and a slowdown in China. The Gem &amp; Jewellery Export Promotion Council (GJEPC) chairman Kirit Bhansali anticipates clarity on US trade talks in early January, potentially bringing good news. New markets in the Middle East, Europe, and Africa, especially Oman, are offsetting China's demand dip, with plain gold jewellery demand surging 80% in the region. High gold prices are making buyers cautious, though the wedding season may offer some domestic support.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 13:44:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fe4d54342f77179d94cb0_1766843715987.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SHOCKER: Hikal Admits Employee Fraud! Revenue Reversed, Millions at Stake – What Investors MUST Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/SHOCKER-Hikal-Admits-Employee-Fraud-Revenue-Reversed-Millions-at-Stake-What-Investors-MUST-Know/694fe02c4342f77179d947fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/SHOCKER-Hikal-Admits-Employee-Fraud-Revenue-Reversed-Millions-at-Stake-What-Investors-MUST-Know/694fe02c4342f77179d947fb</guid><description>Hikal Ltd. has discovered revenue recognition irregularities impacting Q4FY25, Q1FY26, and Q2FY26, suspecting employee misconduct. The company has reversed ₹80.7 crore in Q2FY26 revenue and stated sales were overstated by approximately 2% in prior quarters. Hikal assures that underlying sales are genuine and no funds were misappropriated, while evaluating necessary reporting to authorities.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 13:26:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fe02c4342f77179d947fa_1766842509411.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Trade Power Unleashed: 7 Mega Deals Signed – Massive Gains Ahead for Investors!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Trade-Power-Unleashed-7-Mega-Deals-Signed-Massive-Gains-Ahead-for-Investors/694fe08a4342f77179d9487b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Trade-Power-Unleashed-7-Mega-Deals-Signed-Massive-Gains-Ahead-for-Investors/694fe08a4342f77179d9487b</guid><description>India has rapidly expanded its trade network, signing seven Free Trade Agreements (FTAs) and Comprehensive Economic Partnership Agreements (CEPAs) since 2021. Recent deals with New Zealand and Oman, alongside agreements with the UK, EFTA, UAE, Australia, and Mauritius, offer Indian exporters significant duty-free access to new markets. These pacts aim to boost trade, attract foreign investment, create jobs, and open doors for Indian professionals and services, strengthening India's global economic position.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 13:26:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fe08a4342f77179d9487a_1766842874316.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CAMS Dividend Alert! Record Date Set for Cash Reward; Q3 Results &amp; Payout on Jan 22!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/CAMS-Dividend-Alert-Record-Date-Set-for-Cash-Reward-Q3-Results-and-Payout-on-Jan-22/694fde3e4342f77179d945fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/CAMS-Dividend-Alert-Record-Date-Set-for-Cash-Reward-Q3-Results-and-Payout-on-Jan-22/694fde3e4342f77179d945fb</guid><description>Computer Age Management Services (CAMS) will hold a board meeting on January 22, 2026, to approve its Q3 FY26 financial results and consider an interim dividend. The company has fixed January 30, 2026, as the record date to determine eligible shareholders for any approved dividend payout. CAMS previously announced a stock split in October and has a history of providing interim and final dividends to its investors. The company reported a 5.4% year-on-year rise in net profit to ₹115 crore for Q2 FY26.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 13:11:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fde3e4342f77179d945fa_1766841996700.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's PMLA Law: Supreme Court Review Sparks Storm Over Past Crimes!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Indias-PMLA-Law-Supreme-Court-Review-Sparks-Storm-Over-Past-Crimes/694fd48b4342f77179d93e22</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Indias-PMLA-Law-Supreme-Court-Review-Sparks-Storm-Over-Past-Crimes/694fd48b4342f77179d93e22</guid><description>India's Prevention of Money Laundering Act (PMLA), 2002, is under intense legal scrutiny as the Supreme Court reviews its application to past actions. The core debate questions whether the PMLA's provisions, particularly concerning "proceeds of crime" and "predicate offences," can be applied retrospectively, potentially clashing with constitutional protections against ex post facto laws. This ongoing review, stemming from the 2022 Vijay Madanlal Choudhary judgment, has significant implications for financial crime investigations and the broader legal framework.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 12:32:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fd48b4342f77179d93e21_1766839654777.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Legal Showdown: NCLAT Rejects Equitas Bank's Insolvency Bid Against Jumbo Finvest!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Legal-Showdown-NCLAT-Rejects-Equitas-Banks-Insolvency-Bid-Against-Jumbo-Finvest/694fd3a64342f77179d93cd5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Law-Court/Legal-Showdown-NCLAT-Rejects-Equitas-Banks-Insolvency-Bid-Against-Jumbo-Finvest/694fd3a64342f77179d93cd5</guid><description>The National Company Law Appellate Tribunal (NCLAT) has dismissed Equitas Small Finance Bank's plea to start insolvency proceedings against Jumbo Finvest. Upholding a National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT) order, NCLAT ruled that Jumbo Finvest, as a registered Financial Service Provider, is not subject to standard insolvency applications initiated by creditors under the Insolvency and Bankruptcy Code.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 12:29:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fd3a64342f77179d93cd4_1766839475076.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kavach Countdown Extended! Railways Misses Another Deadline – Will 2026 Deliver Safety on Mumbai-Delhi Routes?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Kavach-Countdown-Extended-Railways-Misses-Another-Deadline-Will-2026-Deliver-Safety-on-Mumbai-Delhi-Routes/694fcbfe4342f77179d936ac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Kavach-Countdown-Extended-Railways-Misses-Another-Deadline-Will-2026-Deliver-Safety-on-Mumbai-Delhi-Routes/694fcbfe4342f77179d936ac</guid><description>Indian Railways has missed its second deadline for installing the Kavach automatic train protection system on the crucial New Delhi-Mumbai and New Delhi-Howrah routes. While 25% of the work is commissioned, officials now aim for operationalization by 2026. The system, designed to enhance safety by automatically applying brakes, faces challenges including an insufficient number of approved manufacturers to expedite deployment across the vast railway network.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 11:58:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fcbfe4342f77179d936ab_1766837357723.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Laxmi Organic Denies Hazardous Waste Claims: Here's How They Ensure Safety!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Laxmi-Organic-Denies-Hazardous-Waste-Claims-Heres-How-They-Ensure-Safety/694fcb3a4342f77179d935fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Laxmi-Organic-Denies-Hazardous-Waste-Claims-Heres-How-They-Ensure-Safety/694fcb3a4342f77179d935fb</guid><description>Laxmi Organic Industries Ltd denies allegations of hazardous effluent discharge from its Lote, Maharashtra facility. The company asserts full compliance with Indian environmental regulations, stating all emissions are treated and disposed of at government-approved facilities, utilizing closed-loop systems. LOIL distinguishes its practices from the Miteni incident in Italy, which involved direct river contamination. The company emphasizes its commitment to transparency and responsible manufacturing of essential products.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 11:55:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fcb3a4342f77179d935fa_1766837329528.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Ethanol Floodgates Open for India: Record Exports in 2025 Signal Massive Energy Trade Boom!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/US-Ethanol-Floodgates-Open-for-India-Record-Exports-in-2025-Signal-Massive-Energy-Trade-Boom/694fca764342f77179d9350d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/US-Ethanol-Floodgates-Open-for-India-Record-Exports-in-2025-Signal-Massive-Energy-Trade-Boom/694fca764342f77179d9350d</guid><description>United States ethanol exports to India are poised for a record year in 2025. Volumes shipped from January to September 2025 have already exceeded total shipments for 2022 and 2023, nearing 2020 levels. India imports this fuel ethanol for its industrial sector, which allows its domestic ethanol production to meet ambitious fuel blending targets. This trend is a significant part of India's increasing energy import bill from the US.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 11:53:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fca764342f77179d9350c_1766836927291.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's M&amp;A Market Set For Strategic Shake-Up: Will 2026 Spark a New Era of Smart Deals?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-MandA-Market-Set-For-Strategic-Shake-Up-Will-2026-Spark-a-New-Era-of-Smart-Deals/694fc2bb4342f77179d92b59</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Indias-MandA-Market-Set-For-Strategic-Shake-Up-Will-2026-Spark-a-New-Era-of-Smart-Deals/694fc2bb4342f77179d92b59</guid><description>India's mergers and acquisitions activity is unlikely to see a volume rebound in 2026, shifting instead towards fewer, more strategic transactions. Following a sharp correction after the 2021-22 bull run, dealmaking has become cautious, with a focus on profitability-anchored growth. Key sectors like consumer brands, healthcare, and SaaS are expected to lead, driven by disciplined execution rather than sheer scale. Equity is also set to play a larger role as an acquisition currency.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 11:19:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fc2bb4342f77179d92b58_1766835009630.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zepto Files for $1.3 Billion IPO: India's Youngest Startup Gears Up for Stock Market Debut!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Zepto-Files-for-13-Billion-IPO-Indias-Youngest-Startup-Gears-Up-for-Stock-Market-Debut/694fc1ff4342f77179d92a3f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/Zepto-Files-for-13-Billion-IPO-Indias-Youngest-Startup-Gears-Up-for-Stock-Market-Debut/694fc1ff4342f77179d92a3f</guid><description>Quick commerce leader Zepto has reportedly filed confidential draft papers with India's SEBI for an Initial Public Offering (IPO) aiming to raise approximately $1.3 billion (around ₹11,600 crore). This move, expected in July-September 2026, would make Zepto the youngest VC-funded startup in India to go public, navigating a competitive landscape against rivals like Blinkit and Swiggy Instamart.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 11:18:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fc1ff4342f77179d92a3e_1766834960631.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GCL Aims for 5X Revenue Growth to ₹5,000 Cr by 2030, Eyes Breakfast &amp; Kids Markets!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/GCL-Aims-for-5X-Revenue-Growth-to-5000-Cr-by-2030-Eyes-Breakfast-and-Kids-Markets/694fbaf94342f77179d92499</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/GCL-Aims-for-5X-Revenue-Growth-to-5000-Cr-by-2030-Eyes-Breakfast-and-Kids-Markets/694fbaf94342f77179d92499</guid><description>Ghodawat Consumer Limited (GCL) targets a massive fivefold revenue increase to ₹5,000 crore by 2030, up from ₹1,200 crore. The FMCG firm plans aggressive expansion into the breakfast and kids' product segments, including launching 'Lunch Bites' beetroot chips for children. GCL is also shifting towards an asset-light manufacturing model, aiming for 60% outsourcing by 2030. The company is exploring a potential Initial Public Offering (IPO) within the next five years and expanding its premium product range.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 10:48:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fbaf94342f77179d92498_1766832995433.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Taiwanese Tech Giant Teema Set to Launch Massive Tech Park in India – Huge Investment Incoming?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Taiwanese-Tech-Giant-Teema-Set-to-Launch-Massive-Tech-Park-in-India-Huge-Investment-Incoming/694fba654342f77179d923bb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Taiwanese-Tech-Giant-Teema-Set-to-Launch-Massive-Tech-Park-in-India-Huge-Investment-Incoming/694fba654342f77179d923bb</guid><description>Taiwanese electronics association Teema, led by Foxconn chairman Young Liu, is considering Uttar Pradesh's Yamuna Expressway Industrial Development Authority (Yeida) region for a major technology park. This initiative aims to create advanced, AI-integrated, and ESG-focused manufacturing hubs, mirroring Taiwan's successful model. The park would be located near a proposed Foxconn outsourced semiconductor assembly and test (OSAT) facility, boosting Taiwan's global competitiveness and supply chain expansion in India, particularly in northern states.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 10:42:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fba654342f77179d923ba_1766833043623.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Startup Cities 2025: Bengaluru Leads, Mumbai &amp; Gurugram Surge!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Startup-Cities-2025-Bengaluru-Leads-Mumbai-and-Gurugram-Surge/694fb2a74342f77179d91c4c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Startup-Cities-2025-Bengaluru-Leads-Mumbai-and-Gurugram-Surge/694fb2a74342f77179d91c4c</guid><description>Bengaluru remains India's top startup hub in 2025, anchoring the ecosystem according to a new report by IDFC FIRST Private Banking and Hurun India. While Bengaluru leads with 88 founders and 52 company headquarters, a slight decline indicates a diffusion of entrepreneurial activity. Mumbai and Gurugram are rapidly gaining ground, with Mumbai hosting 83 founders and 41 companies, and Gurugram featuring 32 founders and 36 companies. The report highlights a diversifying landscape and the significant role of educational institutions in nurturing entrepreneurs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 10:10:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fb2a74342f77179d91c4b_1766830996111.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>China's Shocking AI Overhaul: New Rules Could Reshape Global Tech!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Chinas-Shocking-AI-Overhaul-New-Rules-Could-Reshape-Global-Tech/694fb1784342f77179d91abb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Chinas-Shocking-AI-Overhaul-New-Rules-Could-Reshape-Global-Tech/694fb1784342f77179d91abb</guid><description>China has released draft regulations for human-like AI systems, mandating that providers ensure their services are ethical, secure, and transparent. Users will need to be informed when interacting with AI, with notifications required at login, every two hours, or upon detecting overdependence. The rules also stipulate security assessments and adherence to 'core socialist values,' with proposals open for public comment until January 25.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 10:05:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fb1784342f77179d91aba_1766830657442.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Diamond Power Infrastructure Secures ₹66 Crore Power Cable Deal, Boosting Infrastructure Sector</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Diamond-Power-Infrastructure-Secures-66-Crore-Power-Cable-Deal-Boosting-Infrastructure-Sector/694fada24342f77179d91757</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Diamond-Power-Infrastructure-Secures-66-Crore-Power-Cable-Deal-Boosting-Infrastructure-Sector/694fada24342f77179d91757</guid><description>Diamond Power Infrastructure Ltd has received a letter of intent from Hild Projects Private Limited for a ₹66.18 crore power cable supply order. The contract is scheduled for execution between January 1, 2026, and June 30, 2026. This order win highlights the company's continued success in securing business linked to ongoing investments in India's power transmission and infrastructure projects.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 09:50:51 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fada24342f77179d91756_1766829530289.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Consumer Payout Bonanza! ₹45 Crore Refunds Disbursed Across India – Are You Covered?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Consumer-Payout-Bonanza-45-Crore-Refunds-Disbursed-Across-India-Are-You-Covered/694fad544342f77179d916f8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Consumer-Payout-Bonanza-45-Crore-Refunds-Disbursed-Across-India-Are-You-Covered/694fad544342f77179d916f8</guid><description>The Department of Consumer Affairs has facilitated ₹45 crore in refunds across 31 sectors over eight months (April 25 to December 26, 2025), handling 67,265 grievances via the National Consumer Helpline. E-commerce led with ₹32 crore, followed by travel and tourism, agency services, electronics, and airlines, demonstrating robust consumer redressal efforts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 09:50:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fad544342f77179d916f7_1766829457533.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>₹10 Lakh Crore &amp; Doubling! India's ETF Boom You Can't Ignore - Zerodha Reveals Shocking Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/10-Lakh-Crore-and-Doubling-Indias-ETF-Boom-You-Cant-Ignore-Zerodha-Reveals-Shocking-Growth/694fab304342f77179d914c0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/10-Lakh-Crore-and-Doubling-Indias-ETF-Boom-You-Cant-Ignore-Zerodha-Reveals-Shocking-Growth/694fab304342f77179d914c0</guid><description>India's Exchange Traded Fund (ETF) industry has surged past a landmark ₹10 lakh crore in Assets Under Management (AUM) by October 2025, doubling its size in just three years. Zerodha Fund House reports a seven-fold increase in ETF trading volumes since 2019-20, reaching ₹3.83 lakh crore in FY 2024-25. Retail investor accounts have grown eight-fold in five years, exceeding three crore folios, driven by a preference for low-cost, transparent investments and easier digital access. Diversification into gold and silver ETFs is also accelerating.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 09:40:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fab304342f77179d914bf_1766828947102.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Smallcaps Skyrocket! 50+ Stocks Jump 10-34% As Indian Markets Outperform!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Smallcaps-Skyrocket-50-Stocks-Jump-10-34percent-As-Indian-Markets-Outperform/694fa5344342f77179d90fc3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Smallcaps-Skyrocket-50-Stocks-Jump-10-34percent-As-Indian-Markets-Outperform/694fa5344342f77179d90fc3</guid><description>Indian equity markets ended a shortened week positively, with the BSE Smallcap index outperforming, rising 1 percent. Over 50 small-cap stocks surged between 10% and 34%. Sectoral performance was mixed, with Defence and Metals leading gains. Foreign Institutional Investors continued selling, but Domestic Institutional Investors provided strong support with significant buying. The market outlook remains cautious due to the upcoming earnings season and global factors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 09:12:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fa5344342f77179d90fc2_1766827394006.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>DMart's Bold Expansion: Will Store Growth Boost Long-Term Cash Flow Amid Digital Rivals' Surge?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/DMarts-Bold-Expansion-Will-Store-Growth-Boost-Long-Term-Cash-Flow-Amid-Digital-Rivals-Surge/694fa4b54342f77179d90f3b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/DMarts-Bold-Expansion-Will-Store-Growth-Boost-Long-Term-Cash-Flow-Amid-Digital-Rivals-Surge/694fa4b54342f77179d90f3b</guid><description>Indian retailer DMart is prioritizing long-term cash flow through aggressive store expansion, adding 15-20% annually. CLSA reports this strategy will lead to negative near-term free cash flow. While quick commerce apps like JioMart and Blinkit see user growth, CLSA expects physical stores to remain crucial, as DMart expands its lower-priced private-label brands.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 09:10:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fa4b54342f77179d90f3a_1766827285446.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Oracle's $300 Billion AI Dream Shattered? Stock Plummets 40% - What Investors MUST Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Oracles-300-Billion-AI-Dream-Shattered-Stock-Plummets-40percent-What-Investors-MUST-Know/694fa3bd4342f77179d90dae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Oracles-300-Billion-AI-Dream-Shattered-Stock-Plummets-40percent-What-Investors-MUST-Know/694fa3bd4342f77179d90dae</guid><description>Oracle's stock surged on AI optimism and a massive OpenAI deal, but has since fallen nearly 40%. Investors are reassessing profitability due to lower margins in AI infrastructure compared to legacy software, soaring capital expenditure leading to negative free cash flow, significant reliance on a few large customers like OpenAI, and increased debt. The dream run revealed the capital-intensive economics of AI infrastructure, a stark contrast to Oracle's traditional software business.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 09:08:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fa3bd4342f77179d90dad_1766827008299.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Green Hydrogen Dream Stalls: Billions Pledged, But Projects Remain Stuck!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Green-Hydrogen-Dream-Stalls-Billions-Pledged-But-Projects-Remain-Stuck/694fa3d24342f77179d90dff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Green-Hydrogen-Dream-Stalls-Billions-Pledged-But-Projects-Remain-Stuck/694fa3d24342f77179d90dff</guid><description>India's ambitious plan to become a global green hydrogen hub is facing significant delays. Nearly two years after launching the National Green Hydrogen Mission, most announced projects are still on paper. Data shows only 2.8% of planned capacity is operational, with 94% at the announcement stage due to unresolved issues like uncertain demand, high costs, and lack of infrastructure. Experts express concern that many announced capacities may not materialize, hindering India's export and domestic production targets.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 09:07:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fa3d24342f77179d90dfe_1766827143065.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Zepto's $1.3 Billion IPO Ambition Unveiled! Quick Commerce Giant Files Secret Draft Papers with SEBI – Is This India's Next Big Listing?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Zeptos-13-Billion-IPO-Ambition-Unveiled-Quick-Commerce-Giant-Files-Secret-Draft-Papers-with-SEBI-Is-This-Indias-Next-Big-Listing/694fa2de4342f77179d90cb1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Zeptos-13-Billion-IPO-Ambition-Unveiled-Quick-Commerce-Giant-Files-Secret-Draft-Papers-with-SEBI-Is-This-Indias-Next-Big-Listing/694fa2de4342f77179d90cb1</guid><description>Quick commerce leader Zepto has submitted draft IPO papers to India's market regulator SEBI for a potential $1.3 billion (approximately ₹11,682 Cr) public offering. Led by Aadit Palicha, the company aims to raise around ₹11,000 Cr via a fresh issuance of shares, with early investors also expected to participate in an offer for sale. Shareholder approval for the IPO was secured in December.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 09:04:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fa2de4342f77179d90cb0_1766826778369.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>No Big Jump? Indian Railways Budget 2026: Funding Unchanged, But Vande Bharat &amp; Bullet Trains STILL Ahead!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/No-Big-Jump-Indian-Railways-Budget-2026-Funding-Unchanged-But-Vande-Bharat-and-Bullet-Trains-STILL-Ahead/694fa24d4342f77179d90bb1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/No-Big-Jump-Indian-Railways-Budget-2026-Funding-Unchanged-But-Vande-Bharat-and-Bullet-Trains-STILL-Ahead/694fa24d4342f77179d90bb1</guid><description>The Gross Budgetary Support (GBS) for Indian Railways in the 2026-27 Union Budget is expected to remain largely the same as the current Rs 2.52 lakh crore, as infrastructure upgrades are progressing well. While overall funding may be steady, allocations will be adjusted to prioritize the bullet train project, track safety, and decongestion. Funding for new Vande Bharat and Amrit Bharat trains will also increase, focusing on passenger experience and punctuality. Railway electrification is nearing 99.2% completion, reducing diesel costs.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 09:00:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694fa24d4342f77179d90bb0_1766826668372.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HDFC AMC vs ICICI Prudential AMC: Which Fund House Wins? Experts Break Down Stock Picks!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/HDFC-AMC-vs-ICICI-Prudential-AMC-Which-Fund-House-Wins-Experts-Break-Down-Stock-Picks/694f9dc14342f77179d9070e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/HDFC-AMC-vs-ICICI-Prudential-AMC-Which-Fund-House-Wins-Experts-Break-Down-Stock-Picks/694f9dc14342f77179d9070e</guid><description>Analysts compare HDFC Asset Management Company and ICICI Prudential Asset Management Company, two leading Indian AMCs. The analysis covers fundamental strengths, including revenue, net profit, and assets under management (AUM), alongside technical views. ICICI Prudential AMC shows higher revenue and AUM, while HDFC AMC leads in net profit margin due to operational efficiency. Both are key players in India's growing mutual fund sector, offering distinct investment profiles for investors.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 08:42:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f9dc14342f77179d9070d_1766825587851.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mangaluru Set to Dominate Data Centres? Study Reveals Shocking Cost Savings!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mangaluru-Set-to-Dominate-Data-Centres-Study-Reveals-Shocking-Cost-Savings/694f9a794342f77179d903c1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Mangaluru-Set-to-Dominate-Data-Centres-Study-Reveals-Shocking-Cost-Savings/694f9a794342f77179d903c1</guid><description>A new study by Karnataka Digital Economy Mission (KDEM) and Deloitte India identifies Mangaluru as India's next cost-efficient data centre hub. Leveraging its strategic coastal location, robust power infrastructure, and lower land leasing rates (approx. ₹7.69/sq ft), Mangaluru offers a significant cost advantage over cities like Mumbai and Chennai. This positioning is crucial for supporting India's projected 10-12 GW data centre capacity by 2030, catering to cloud computing and AI demands.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 08:28:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f9a794342f77179d903c0_1766824783713.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unlock Your Child's Future: The Simple Way to Invest with Direct Mutual Funds!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Unlock-Your-Childs-Future-The-Simple-Way-to-Invest-with-Direct-Mutual-Funds/694f956a4342f77179d8fe9d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Unlock-Your-Childs-Future-The-Simple-Way-to-Invest-with-Direct-Mutual-Funds/694f956a4342f77179d8fe9d</guid><description>Forget special 'child plans.' Low-cost direct mutual funds offer a simpler, more effective way to invest for your child. An adult guardian manages the investment until the child turns 18, ensuring disciplined long-term growth with lower expenses and greater transparency than traditional insurance-linked schemes.</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 08:04:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694f956a4342f77179d8fe9c_1766823427041.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>