<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:46:52 +0000</pubDate><item><title>IndiGrid Logs Strong Q3 Growth, Fuels Expansion with ₹1500 Cr Equity Raise</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/IndiGrid-Logs-Strong-Q3-Growth-Fuels-Expansion-with-1500-Cr-Equity-Raise/698df387e8013a522e77b819</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/IndiGrid-Logs-Strong-Q3-Growth-Fuels-Expansion-with-1500-Cr-Equity-Raise/698df387e8013a522e77b819</guid><description>IndiGrid Infrastructure Trust reported a strong Q3 FY26, with revenue up 11.7% YoY to ₹8,622 million and EBITDA rising 13.0% to ₹7,843 million. The InvIT successfully raised ₹1,500 crore via a 2x oversubscribed placement to fund strategic acquisitions in transmission and BESS totaling over ₹3,000 crore, bolstering its AUM growth targets. DPU increased 6.7% YoY to ₹4.00.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:36:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698df387e8013a522e77b818_1770910879968.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Technojet Consultants Reports Zero Revenue, Deepens Losses on Other Income</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Technojet-Consultants-Reports-Zero-Revenue-Deepens-Losses-on-Other-Income/698df370e8013a522e77b747</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Research-Reports/Technojet-Consultants-Reports-Zero-Revenue-Deepens-Losses-on-Other-Income/698df370e8013a522e77b747</guid><description>Technojet Consultants Limited has announced its third-quarter and nine-month results for FY26, revealing a critical absence of revenue from operations. Total income, derived solely from 'other income,' stood at ₹0.53 Lakhs for Q3 FY26, against expenses of ₹3.00 Lakhs, leading to a net loss of ₹2.47 Lakhs and an EPS of (₹1.24). The nine-month period saw similar trends with a net loss of ₹6.75 Lakhs. While the company reported a profit of ₹3.73 Lakhs for the full fiscal year 2025, this was also solely from other income, as operational revenue remained nil. Management offered no financial guidance.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:36:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698df370e8013a522e77b746_1770910950334.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NITCO Revenue Soars 56%, But ₹17,000 Lakh Penalty Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NITCO-Revenue-Soars-56percent-But-17000-Lakh-Penalty-Looms/698df33be8013a522e77b6ef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NITCO-Revenue-Soars-56percent-But-17000-Lakh-Penalty-Looms/698df33be8013a522e77b6ef</guid><description>NITCO Limited reported a strong Q3 FY26 with consolidated revenue surging 55.70% YoY to ₹13,175.62 Lakhs. The company also showed a significant reduction in losses, with the nine-month period swinging to a profit of ₹3,643.34 Lakhs. However, a major red flag emerged as auditors noted a ₹17,000 Lakh penalty levied by ADGFT, for which no provision has been made, citing legal opinion. This unprovided contingent liability casts a significant risk over the otherwise positive operational improvements.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:35:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698df33be8013a522e77b6ee.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Physicswallah Posts 34% Revenue Growth, Eyes K-12 Domination with AI Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Physicswallah-Posts-34percent-Revenue-Growth-Eyes-K-12-Domination-with-AI-Boost/698df301e8013a522e77b5be</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Physicswallah-Posts-34percent-Revenue-Growth-Eyes-K-12-Domination-with-AI-Boost/698df301e8013a522e77b5be</guid><description>Physicswallah Limited reported a robust Q3 FY'26, with revenue soaring 34% year-over-year to ₹1,082 Cr. The edtech giant surpassed its FY'25 full-year revenue in just nine months of FY'26. Management highlighted aggressive expansion into the K-12 segment, significant AI investments, and the successful integration of recent acquisitions. The company also plans to introduce separate EBITDA reporting for its online and offline businesses.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:34:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698df301e8013a522e77b5bd.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mahindra Bets Big on EV Future: R&amp;D Boost Meets UDO Launch</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Mahindra-Bets-Big-on-EV-Future-RandD-Boost-Meets-UDO-Launch/698df2a7e8013a522e77b4ba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Mahindra-Bets-Big-on-EV-Future-RandD-Boost-Meets-UDO-Launch/698df2a7e8013a522e77b4ba</guid><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra is significantly expanding its Chennai R&amp;D hub with a ₹196 crore investment to bolster future vehicle development, aiming to create 2,000 jobs. Concurrently, its subsidiary launched the Mahindra UDO electric three-wheeler, entering the growing last-mile EV segment. This dual strategy aims to leverage advanced engineering for next-generation platforms while capturing immediate market share, though the UDO faces competitive pricing and range pressures in India's cost-sensitive commercial EV sector.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:32:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698df2a7e8013a522e77b4b9.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Thomas Cook India Sees 5% Income Jump, Forex &amp; Sterling Lead Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Thomas-Cook-India-Sees-5percent-Income-Jump-Forex-and-Sterling-Lead-Growth/698df266e8013a522e77b48a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Thomas-Cook-India-Sees-5percent-Income-Jump-Forex-and-Sterling-Lead-Growth/698df266e8013a522e77b48a</guid><description>Thomas Cook India reported a robust 5% YoY increase in Q3 FY26 consolidated total income to INR 21,866 million, with Profit Before Tax (PBT) surging 20% YoY (excluding one-offs). The Forex segment delivered strong EBIT growth (+10%) and margin expansion, while Sterling Holidays achieved record revenue. These gains partially offset B2C declines and challenges in specific international markets. Management is optimistic for double-digit earnings growth in FY27, supported by technology investments and the positive impact of reduced TCS on outbound travel.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:31:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698df266e8013a522e77b489.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's CPI Overhaul: New Data Sparks Policy Debate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-CPI-Overhaul-New-Data-Sparks-Policy-Debate/698df216e8013a522e77b3f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-CPI-Overhaul-New-Data-Sparks-Policy-Debate/698df216e8013a522e77b3f9</guid><description>India has launched its Consumer Price Index (CPI) 2024 series, significantly revising its inflation measurement framework. The new series incorporates data from e-commerce, OTT platforms, and rail fares, utilizing Computer Assisted Personal Interviewing (CAPI) for enhanced data collection quality and timeliness. Based on the Household Consumption Expenditure Survey (HCES) 2023-24, the revised basket features recalibrated weights, notably reducing the influence of food items and expanding coverage of services. This recalibration aims to provide more accurate inflation signals crucial for monetary and fiscal policy decisions, although it presents new challenges for interpretation and historical comparability.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:30:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698df216e8013a522e77b3f8_1770910537484.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hindware Home Innovation Posts Profit Turnaround, Exits Key Product Lines</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Hindware-Home-Innovation-Posts-Profit-Turnaround-Exits-Key-Product-Lines/698df154e8013a522e77b08a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Hindware-Home-Innovation-Posts-Profit-Turnaround-Exits-Key-Product-Lines/698df154e8013a522e77b08a</guid><description>Hindware Home Innovation reported a robust turnaround in Q3 FY26, posting a net profit of ₹4.81 Cr against a loss last year, driven by operational efficiencies and a significant decrease in exceptional charges. Revenue grew 7.7% YoY to ₹640 Cr. However, sequential performance showed a 5.4% dip in revenue and a 42% drop in net profit. The company also announced the strategic exit from several loss-making product categories, including fans and air coolers, to focus on core kitchen appliances, alongside ongoing corporate restructuring.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:27:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698df153e8013a522e77b089.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Stanley Lifestyles Suffers Steep Revenue Fall, Q3 PAT Plummets 98%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Stanley-Lifestyles-Suffers-Steep-Revenue-Fall-Q3-PAT-Plummets-98percent/698df0d9e8013a522e77af31</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Stanley-Lifestyles-Suffers-Steep-Revenue-Fall-Q3-PAT-Plummets-98percent/698df0d9e8013a522e77af31</guid><description>Stanley Lifestyles posted disastrous Q3 FY26 results, with standalone revenue plummeting 88.57% YoY to ₹63 Mn and consolidated revenue falling 92.54% to ₹10 Mn. Standalone Profit After Tax (PAT) cratered 98% YoY to ₹2 Mn, leading to a negative standalone Basic EPS of ₹-0.20. Consolidated operations swung to a loss of ₹7 Mn from a profit last year. The company also approved ESOP grants and made its subsidiary wholly owned.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:25:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698df0d9e8013a522e77af30.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LKP Finance to become Gyftr Limited, exits NBFC; auditors flag litigation risk.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/LKP-Finance-to-become-Gyftr-Limited-exits-NBFC-auditors-flag-litigation-risk/698df0a8e8013a522e77ae38</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/LKP-Finance-to-become-Gyftr-Limited-exits-NBFC-auditors-flag-litigation-risk/698df0a8e8013a522e77ae38</guid><description>LKP Finance Limited approved its Q3 FY26 results, announcing a significant strategic pivot. The company plans to change its name to Gyftr Limited, discontinue NBFC operations, and focus on the digital gifting sector. Despite a substantial write-back boosting income, auditors issued a qualified conclusion due to ongoing litigation related to borrowings, impacting financial result disclosures.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:24:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698df0a8e8013a522e77ae37_1770910188496.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coffee Day Enterprises: Auditor's Disclaimer Triggers Major Going Concern Doubts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Coffee-Day-Enterprises-Auditors-Disclaimer-Triggers-Major-Going-Concern-Doubts/698df08be8013a522e77adf7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Coffee-Day-Enterprises-Auditors-Disclaimer-Triggers-Major-Going-Concern-Doubts/698df08be8013a522e77adf7</guid><description>Coffee Day Enterprises (CDEL) reported a consolidated net profit of ₹55.30 Cr for Q3 FY26, a turnaround from a loss last year, driven by significant other income and exceptional items. However, the company's statutory auditors issued a disclaimer of conclusion, citing inability to obtain sufficient evidence on the recoverability of ₹3,357 Cr in dues from group companies, debt covenant breaches, and defaults on loan repayments. These issues cast severe doubt on CDEL's ability to continue as a going concern.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:23:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698df08be8013a522e77adf6_1770910025898.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Everest Kanto Cylinders posts strong profit jump, approves expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Everest-Kanto-Cylinders-posts-strong-profit-jump-approves-expansion/698df00be8013a522e77acf5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Everest-Kanto-Cylinders-posts-strong-profit-jump-approves-expansion/698df00be8013a522e77acf5</guid><description>Everest Kanto Cylinder Limited (EKC) reported a robust Q3FY26, with consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) soaring by 98.9% year-on-year to ₹35.73 Cr, driven by improved margins despite flat revenues. Standalone PAT also jumped 57.6% YoY to ₹35.98 Cr. The company's board has approved significant capital expenditure for its Indian and US operations, signaling a strong growth outlook.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:21:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698df00be8013a522e77acf4.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Puravankara Posts Huge Profit Jump, But Tax Woes Loom Large</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Puravankara-Posts-Huge-Profit-Jump-But-Tax-Woes-Loom-Large/698defe5e8013a522e77abde</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Puravankara-Posts-Huge-Profit-Jump-But-Tax-Woes-Loom-Large/698defe5e8013a522e77abde</guid><description>Puravankara Limited reported a dramatic turnaround in Q3 FY26, with consolidated revenue soaring 236% YoY to ₹1,069 crore and net profit swinging to ₹58 crore from a loss. Standalone performance also surged. However, the company faces substantial legal challenges from income tax authorities and Benami property probes, with potential liabilities adding a significant overhang.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:21:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698defe5e8013a522e77abdd_1770909984805.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Golden Legend: Revenue Soars 3000% but Q3 Loss Widens Amid Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Golden-Legend-Revenue-Soars-3000percent-but-Q3-Loss-Widens-Amid-Volatility/698def4ee8013a522e77a96b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Golden-Legend-Revenue-Soars-3000percent-but-Q3-Loss-Widens-Amid-Volatility/698def4ee8013a522e77a96b</guid><description>Golden Legend Leasing and Finance reported a volatile Q3 FY26. While nine-month revenues surged 2077% YoY turning a loss into profit, the latest quarter saw revenue drop 25.2% sequentially. This led to a widened net loss of ₹562.15 Lakhs YoY, a stark swing from a ₹837.26 Lakhs profit QoQ. Significant expenses, including write-offs of irrecoverable loan balances, contributed to the performance dip.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:18:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698def4ee8013a522e77a96a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Golkunda Diamonds to Raise Rs 27.6 Cr, Eyes Indian Jewellery Market Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Golkunda-Diamonds-to-Raise-Rs-276-Cr-Eyes-Indian-Jewellery-Market-Expansion/698def16e8013a522e77a821</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Golkunda-Diamonds-to-Raise-Rs-276-Cr-Eyes-Indian-Jewellery-Market-Expansion/698def16e8013a522e77a821</guid><description>Golkunda Diamonds &amp; Jewellery Ltd's board greenlit a Rs 27.61 crore preferential issue of convertible warrants and a strategic expansion into the Indian domestic jewellery market. The company plans to invest Rs 5 crore to add 75-100 Kg annual capacity, leveraging its 40-year international expertise to reduce export dependence and capture rising demand for fine jewellery, including lab-grown diamonds. Shareholder approval is pending via an EOGM on March 9, 2026.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:17:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698def16e8013a522e77a820_1770909970917.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Neogen Chemicals Gets Rs 60 Cr Insurance Payout Amid Dahej Plant Fire Recovery</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Neogen-Chemicals-Gets-Rs-60-Cr-Insurance-Payout-Amid-Dahej-Plant-Fire-Recovery/698deecde8013a522e77a77c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Neogen-Chemicals-Gets-Rs-60-Cr-Insurance-Payout-Amid-Dahej-Plant-Fire-Recovery/698deecde8013a522e77a77c</guid><description>Neogen Chemicals reported an update on its Dahej plant fire. The company received an additional Rs. 60 Crore on-account insurance payment, totaling Rs. 140 Crore. While the total loss is Rs. 362.90 Crore, the net impact after recognized claims is Rs. 14.08 Crore. Production shifts and a new plant (Q1 FY27 commissioning) aim to mitigate disruption.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:16:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698deecde8013a522e77a77b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IGL Surges on Strong Q3 Profit, Declares 162.5% Interim Dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/IGL-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Profit-Declares-1625percent-Interim-Dividend/698dee66e8013a522e77a53b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/IGL-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Profit-Declares-1625percent-Interim-Dividend/698dee66e8013a522e77a53b</guid><description>Indraprastha Gas Limited (IGL) reported a robust Q3 FY26 with standalone revenue up 7.87% YoY to ₹4,488.71 Cr and net profit surging 25.45% YoY to ₹358.57 Cr. EBITDA also climbed 31.34% YoY. The company declared a 162.5% interim dividend (₹3.25/share). However, the nine-month performance saw a decline in standalone net profit and EBITDA. Volumes grew 3% YoY in Q3.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:14:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698dee66e8013a522e77a53a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hitachi Energy India Surges on Record Orders, Profit Leap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hitachi-Energy-India-Surges-on-Record-Orders-Profit-Leap/698dee35e8013a522e77a3a6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hitachi-Energy-India-Surges-on-Record-Orders-Profit-Leap/698dee35e8013a522e77a3a6</guid><description>Hitachi Energy India posted a stellar Q3 FY26, with revenue climbing 29.6% YoY to ₹2,168 crores. Profit Before Tax (PBT) before exceptional items surged 118.4% YoY to ₹402 crores, driving PBT margin to 18.5%. Operational EBITDA doubled YoY to ₹338 crores at a 15.6% margin. The company also achieved an all-time high order backlog of ₹29,872 crores, boosted by strong order inflows. Management eyes significant growth from data centers, energy transition, and increased exports.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:13:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698dee35e8013a522e77a3a5_1770909492079.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Deep Industries Q3 Profit Soars 50%, Eyes 30% FY27 Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Deep-Industries-Q3-Profit-Soars-50percent-Eyes-30percent-FY27-Growth/698dedc0e8013a522e77a27f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Deep-Industries-Q3-Profit-Soars-50percent-Eyes-30percent-FY27-Growth/698dedc0e8013a522e77a27f</guid><description>Deep Industries posted a stellar Q3 FY'26 with revenue up 43.1% to ₹221.5 Cr and PAT surging 49.8% to ₹71.3 Cr. Nine-month performance also saw robust growth. The company projects over 30% revenue growth for FY'27, targeting ₹1,150 Cr. However, a gas leakage incident at Rajahmundry caused a 2-3 month delay for a project and destroyed a rig, with insurance expected to cover losses.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:12:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698dedc0e8013a522e77a27e_1770909328171.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>WeWork India Wins IPO Legal Battle, Investor Confidence Reaffirmed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/WeWork-India-Wins-IPO-Legal-Battle-Investor-Confidence-Reaffirmed/698dedafe8013a522e77a26f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/WeWork-India-Wins-IPO-Legal-Battle-Investor-Confidence-Reaffirmed/698dedafe8013a522e77a26f</guid><description>WeWork India Management Limited has achieved a significant legal victory with the Bombay High Court disposing of the final writ petition related to its IPO. The petitioner unconditionally withdrew the case, and previous dismissals affirmed WeWork India's transparent disclosures. Management termed the legal challenges 'orchestrated harassment,' but the resolution validates the company's governance and bolsters investor confidence.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:11:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698dedafe8013a522e77a26e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coal India Profit Skyrockets 203%, But Compliance Lapses Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Coal-India-Profit-Skyrockets-203percent-But-Compliance-Lapses-Loom/698ded6ce8013a522e77a229</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Coal-India-Profit-Skyrockets-203percent-But-Compliance-Lapses-Loom/698ded6ce8013a522e77a229</guid><description>Coal India reported a spectacular Q3 FY26 with consolidated net profit soaring 202.78% year-on-year to ₹25,709.57 crore, driven by a 36.79% jump in revenue to ₹1,26,956.76 crore. The company also declared a ₹5.50 per share interim dividend. However, the independent auditor flagged compliance deficiencies, including SEBI Regulation 17(1) related to independent directors, potentially attracting penalties, and non-compliance by subsidiaries SECL and MCL with the woman director mandate.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:10:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698ded6ce8013a522e77a228_1770909347143.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Singer India Q3 Revenue Soars 52%, PAT Jumps 456% on Sewing Machine Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Singer-India-Q3-Revenue-Soars-52percent-PAT-Jumps-456percent-on-Sewing-Machine-Demand/698ded0ae8013a522e77a130</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Singer-India-Q3-Revenue-Soars-52percent-PAT-Jumps-456percent-on-Sewing-Machine-Demand/698ded0ae8013a522e77a130</guid><description>Singer India Limited posted stellar Q3 FY26 results, with revenue climbing 52.3% year-on-year to ₹16,101 lakhs and Profit After Tax skyrocketing 456.0% to ₹839 lakhs. The surge was primarily fuelled by a 75.7% revenue jump in the sewing machines segment. The company also raised funds via preferential allotment for manufacturing expansion and has applied for NSE listing.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:08:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698ded0ae8013a522e77a12f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Frontier Springs Surges 154% Revenue YoY, Profit Dips QoQ</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Frontier-Springs-Surges-154percent-Revenue-YoY-Profit-Dips-QoQ/698dec7fe8013a522e779f54</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Frontier-Springs-Surges-154percent-Revenue-YoY-Profit-Dips-QoQ/698dec7fe8013a522e779f54</guid><description>Frontier Springs Ltd. reported stellar Q3 FY26 results, with revenue jumping 154.44% YoY to ₹14.32 crore and Net Profit growing 63.54% YoY to ₹14.28 crore. Nine-month figures also show robust growth. However, the company saw a 9.08% sequential decline in Net Profit QoQ, and noted internal calculation discrepancies in its filing. No future guidance was provided.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:06:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698dec7fe8013a522e779f53.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SMT Engineering Q3: Standalone Plunge Masks Explosive Acquisition-Led Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SMT-Engineering-Q3-Standalone-Plunge-Masks-Explosive-Acquisition-Led-Growth/698debebe8013a522e779dc2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SMT-Engineering-Q3-Standalone-Plunge-Masks-Explosive-Acquisition-Led-Growth/698debebe8013a522e779dc2</guid><description>SMT Engineering Limited reported a drastic standalone revenue and profit decline for Q3 FY26. However, the company's consolidated performance surged dramatically, turning a loss into significant profit, driven by the recent acquisition of Sai Machine Tools Private Limited. Investors should note that consolidated figures are not strictly comparable year-over-year due to this integration.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:04:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698debebe8013a522e779dc1.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hi-Tech Pipes Surges on Revenue Growth, Faces Margin Pressure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hi-Tech-Pipes-Surges-on-Revenue-Growth-Faces-Margin-Pressure/698debaae8013a522e779d71</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hi-Tech-Pipes-Surges-on-Revenue-Growth-Faces-Margin-Pressure/698debaae8013a522e779d71</guid><description>Hi-Tech Pipes Limited reported a strong 40% year-on-year revenue growth to INR 1,070 crores in Q3 FY26, driven by a 10% rise in sales volume to 136,000 tons. However, Profit After Tax (PAT) declined by 9% to INR 17 crores due to hot-rolled coil price volatility. The company is expanding its capacity to 1 million tons and foresees margin recovery with government safeguard duties and strong demand.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:03:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698debaae8013a522e779d70.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Coal India Declares Dividend Amidst Auditor Red Flags on Compliance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Coal-India-Declares-Dividend-Amidst-Auditor-Red-Flags-on-Compliance/698deb70e8013a522e779d45</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Coal-India-Declares-Dividend-Amidst-Auditor-Red-Flags-on-Compliance/698deb70e8013a522e779d45</guid><description>Coal India Limited declared its third interim dividend of ₹5.50 per share for FY25-26. However, the latest financial update also highlighted significant concerns raised by auditors, including pending SEBI compliance regarding board composition and a substantial ₹553.31 Crore impairment for coal blocks. The company also divested 10% of its stake in BCCL.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 15:02:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698deb70e8013a522e779d44_1770908830669.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dhabriya Polywood Posts Stellar YoY Growth, But Q3 Revenue Dips Sequentially</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dhabriya-Polywood-Posts-Stellar-YoY-Growth-But-Q3-Revenue-Dips-Sequentially/698de9ade8013a522e77971e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Dhabriya-Polywood-Posts-Stellar-YoY-Growth-But-Q3-Revenue-Dips-Sequentially/698de9ade8013a522e77971e</guid><description>Dhabriya Polywood Limited has reported robust year-on-year growth for Q3 FY26, with revenue climbing 19.6% to INR 6,566.0 Lacs and Profit After Tax (PAT) more than doubling to INR 766.2 Lacs. EBITDA margin expanded significantly by 500 basis points to 21.1%. However, the company saw a marginal 2.0% sequential decline in revenue from the previous quarter. Return on Equity (ROE) also saw a dip from 7% to 5% year-on-year.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:54:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698de9ade8013a522e77971d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NHPC Invests Heavily in Future, Signals Growth Amidst Challenges</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/NHPC-Invests-Heavily-in-Future-Signals-Growth-Amidst-Challenges/698de9a4e8013a522e7796c1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/NHPC-Invests-Heavily-in-Future-Signals-Growth-Amidst-Challenges/698de9a4e8013a522e7796c1</guid><description>NHPC reported a 10% YoY revenue jump for 9M FY26 to Rs 8,800 Crore, driven by higher power generation. However, Q3 FY26 revenue fell 3% YoY due to the absence of one-off items. The company unveiled ambitious CAPEX plans and a strong pipeline of hydro and renewable projects, including solar and pumped storage, while navigating PPA signing challenges and conservative revenue recognition for new hydro assets.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:54:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698de9a4e8013a522e7796c0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Onelife Capital Rights Issue Amidst Deepening Losses and SEBI Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Onelife-Capital-Rights-Issue-Amidst-Deepening-Losses-and-SEBI-Scrutiny/698de914e8013a522e77960e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Onelife-Capital-Rights-Issue-Amidst-Deepening-Losses-and-SEBI-Scrutiny/698de914e8013a522e77960e</guid><description>Onelife Capital Advisors Limited has announced a ₹36 crore rights issue at ₹15 per share, primarily to fund its subsidiary, Dealmoney Commodities. The company reported a significant financial downturn, posting a net loss of ₹487.81 lakhs in FY25 against a profit in FY24, with EPS turning negative at ₹(3.65). This comes amid severe regulatory challenges, including SEBI penalties and promoter debarment, coupled with auditor concerns over investment recoverability, casting a long shadow over future prospects.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:52:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698de914e8013a522e77960d_1770908222394.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TACF Q3 Profit Surges 87%, But 9-Month Earnings Plunge 48% Amidst Red Flags</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/TACF-Q3-Profit-Surges-87percent-But-9-Month-Earnings-Plunge-48percent-Amidst-Red-Flags/698de8fce8013a522e7795a0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/TACF-Q3-Profit-Surges-87percent-But-9-Month-Earnings-Plunge-48percent-Amidst-Red-Flags/698de8fce8013a522e7795a0</guid><description>Tuticorin Alkali Chemicals and Fertilizers Limited (TACF) announced robust Q3 FY26 results with net profit soaring 87.22% YoY to ₹914.83 Lakhs, driven by a 19.94% revenue increase. However, the nine-month period (9M FY26) paints a concerning picture, with net profit plummeting 48.00% YoY to ₹2,858.92 Lakhs and margins contracting sharply. The company also reported a negative tangible net worth and an unusual presentation of an exceptional item affecting its profit before tax, raising significant investor concerns.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:51:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698de8fce8013a522e77959f_1770908107904.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Simplex Infrastructures D-Rated Amidst Debt Woes, Standalone Profit Soars</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Simplex-Infrastructures-D-Rated-Amidst-Debt-Woes-Standalone-Profit-Soars/698de8e7e8013a522e779564</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Simplex-Infrastructures-D-Rated-Amidst-Debt-Woes-Standalone-Profit-Soars/698de8e7e8013a522e779564</guid><description>Simplex Infrastructures Limited posted strong standalone Q3 FY26 results with revenue up 21.95% and PAT surging 64.08%. Nine-month PAT soared 103.46%. However, the company's financial health is severely questioned by a CARE D rating and ongoing debt servicing delays. Overdue debt reduced significantly, and debt-to-equity improved, but creditworthiness remains a critical concern, overshadowing operational gains.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:51:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698de8e7e8013a522e779563.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Maharashtra Reforms Spur Real Estate: Faster Approvals, New Worries</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Maharashtra-Reforms-Spur-Real-Estate-Faster-Approvals-New-Worries/698de8e2e8013a522e77955d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Maharashtra-Reforms-Spur-Real-Estate-Faster-Approvals-New-Worries/698de8e2e8013a522e77955d</guid><description>Maharashtra has dismantled the legacy Non-Agricultural (NA) land conversion requirement, integrating it directly into building plan approvals. This move accelerates project timelines by eliminating dual clearances and replaces annual taxes with a one-time premium. The removal of the 'sanad' further streamlines financing. Digital integration promises enhanced transparency. Experts anticipate a significant boost to urban expansion and housing supply, but caution looms over potential unchecked development and infrastructure strain.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:51:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698de8e2e8013a522e77955c_1770908138676.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IGL Surges on Q3 Profit Growth, But 9-Month PAT Declines</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/IGL-Surges-on-Q3-Profit-Growth-But-9-Month-PAT-Declines/698de7dee8013a522e7791be</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/IGL-Surges-on-Q3-Profit-Growth-But-9-Month-PAT-Declines/698de7dee8013a522e7791be</guid><description>Indraprastha Gas (IGL) reported a robust Q3 FY26 with standalone PAT jumping 25.45% YoY to ₹358.57 Crores, fueled by an 8.35% revenue increase and 3% volume growth. EBITDA surged 31.34% with margins expanding to 12%. However, for the nine-month period, standalone PAT declined 2.79% YoY. IGL also declared a ₹3.25 per share interim dividend amidst ongoing challenges like a contingent DDA license fee demand.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:46:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698de7dee8013a522e7791bd.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sharika Enterprises Plunges into Deep Losses as Revenues Crash</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sharika-Enterprises-Plunges-into-Deep-Losses-as-Revenues-Crash/698de7c1e8013a522e7790c1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sharika-Enterprises-Plunges-into-Deep-Losses-as-Revenues-Crash/698de7c1e8013a522e7790c1</guid><description>Sharika Enterprises Limited has reported a grim financial update, with consolidated revenue plummeting 27.30% year-on-year to ₹1,592.15 Lakhs in Q3 FY26. The company swung to a net loss of ₹292.51 Lakhs from a profit of ₹14.00 Lakhs in the prior year. Standalone figures mirrored this downturn, showing a 23.61% revenue drop and a loss of ₹244.20 Lakhs. The nine-month performance also reflects declining top-line and escalating losses, with no forward-looking guidance issued.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:46:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698de7c1e8013a522e7790c0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Synergy Green Industries Q3 Profit Dives 34%, FY26 Revenue Outlook Slashed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Synergy-Green-Industries-Q3-Profit-Dives-34percent-FY26-Revenue-Outlook-Slashed/698de734e8013a522e778fbd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Synergy-Green-Industries-Q3-Profit-Dives-34percent-FY26-Revenue-Outlook-Slashed/698de734e8013a522e778fbd</guid><description>Synergy Green Industries reported a sharp 34% YoY decline in PBDIT to ₹9.62 crore for Q3 FY2026, with margins compressing to 10.32%. For the nine months, PBDIT fell 10.2% YoY. Management cited higher outsourcing, new unit operating expenses, finance costs, and customer delays for the underperformance. Consequently, the company revised its FY2026 revenue growth projection to 5% YoY, projecting ~14% PBDIT margins. A robust FY2027 is anticipated, targeting over ₹500 crore revenue and 16-20% margins driven by expanded capacity and in-house machining.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:44:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698de734e8013a522e778fbc.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HAL Wins ₹2,312 Cr Defence Deal for 8 Coast Guard Aircraft</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HAL-Wins-2312-Cr-Defence-Deal-for-8-Coast-Guard-Aircraft/698de6fce8013a522e778f8e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HAL-Wins-2312-Cr-Defence-Deal-for-8-Coast-Guard-Aircraft/698de6fce8013a522e778f8e</guid><description>Hindustan Aeronautics Limited (HAL) has secured a significant contract valued at ₹2,312 crore from the Ministry of Defence for the supply of eight Dornier-228 aircraft to the Indian Coast Guard. Procured under the 'Buy (Indian)' category, this deal strongly supports the 'Aatmanirbhar Bharat' and 'Make-in-India' initiatives. The contract is expected to generate substantial employment and bolster India's maritime security capabilities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:43:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698de6fce8013a522e778f8d_1770907662263.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndiGrid Trust Posts 76% Profit Jump, Approves INR 4 Dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/IndiGrid-Trust-Posts-76percent-Profit-Jump-Approves-INR-4-Dividend/698de6d8e8013a522e778efc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/IndiGrid-Trust-Posts-76percent-Profit-Jump-Approves-INR-4-Dividend/698de6d8e8013a522e778efc</guid><description>IndiGrid Infrastructure Trust reported a robust Q3FY26, with profit after tax (PAT) soaring 76.33% year-on-year to INR 964.92 million. Total income grew 12.97% to INR 9,084.60 million. The Trust declared an interim distribution of INR 4.00 per unit. Earnings Per Unit (EPU) stood at INR 1.14, supported by a strong EBITDA margin of 90.96%. The Net Asset Value (NAV) per unit was INR 146.42.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:42:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698de6d8e8013a522e778efb_1770907677105.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mukta Arts Sees Strong Q3 Growth, EBITDA Soars 39% Amid Margin Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Mukta-Arts-Sees-Strong-Q3-Growth-EBITDA-Soars-39percent-Amid-Margin-Expansion/698de5cde8013a522e778af5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Mukta-Arts-Sees-Strong-Q3-Growth-EBITDA-Soars-39percent-Amid-Margin-Expansion/698de5cde8013a522e778af5</guid><description>Mukta Arts Limited reported strong Q3 FY26 financials, with consolidated EBITDA surging 39% year-on-year to Rs. 1,552 lacs and margins expanding significantly. Key subsidiaries, including Mukta A2 Cinemas and Whistling Woods International, showcased impressive operational turnarounds and revenue growth. While management highlighted strategic execution and efficiency, specific forward-looking guidance was notably absent.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:38:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698de5cde8013a522e778af4.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Yashraj Containeurs Posts Loss in CIRP, Omits Revenue Figures</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Yashraj-Containeurs-Posts-Loss-in-CIRP-Omits-Revenue-Figures/698de580e8013a522e778a0e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Yashraj-Containeurs-Posts-Loss-in-CIRP-Omits-Revenue-Figures/698de580e8013a522e778a0e</guid><description>Yashraj Containeurs Ltd., under Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP), has reported a narrowed net loss of ₹14.85 Lacs for Q3 FY26, an improvement from the previous year. However, the nine-month period saw a significant shift from profit to a ₹59.30 Lacs loss. Critically, the company failed to disclose its total revenue from operations for both periods, raising serious concerns about its financial health and the 'Going Concern Basis' of its financial statements, which is contingent on successful CIRP and promoter funding.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:36:48 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698de580e8013a522e778a0d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MTNL Faces Auditor's Severe Warning Amidst Deepening Losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/MTNL-Faces-Auditors-Severe-Warning-Amidst-Deepening-Losses/698de57de8013a522e7789ec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/MTNL-Faces-Auditors-Severe-Warning-Amidst-Deepening-Losses/698de57de8013a522e7789ec</guid><description>Mahanagar Telephone Nigam Limited (MTNL) reported a stark financial downturn in Q3 FY26, with revenues plunging 25.6% YoY and net losses widening to ₹898.38 Cr. The company's net worth is fully eroded, and it has defaulted on significant loan repayments, leading to NPA classification. Auditors have issued an adverse conclusion, citing accounting anomalies and unreconciled balances with BSNL and DOT. Despite this, the government is pushing a revival plan including debt restructuring and a potential BSNL merger to keep the company afloat.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 14:36:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698de57de8013a522e7789eb.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>