<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:47:25 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India's Trade Pacts: Growth Tailwinds Meet Competitive Realities</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Trade-Pacts-Growth-Tailwinds-Meet-Competitive-Realities/69985502057e346edab43515</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Trade-Pacts-Growth-Tailwinds-Meet-Competitive-Realities/69985502057e346edab43515</guid><description>India's economy is poised for sustained growth, bolstered by recently concluded trade agreements with the EU and an interim pact with the US. These deals aim to enhance market access and integrate Indian firms into global value chains. Foreign portfolio investment has shown a rebound, reflecting renewed investor confidence. However, the narrative of unbridled optimism must contend with structural challenges, including intense global competition, evolving tariff landscapes, and the delicate balance of fiscal consolidation against growth imperatives.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:35:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69985502057e346edab43514_1771591097632.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Unilever Promoter Group Takes Control of Kwality Wall's India Post Demerger</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Unilever-Promoter-Group-Takes-Control-of-Kwality-Walls-India-Post-Demerger/6998548a057e346edab4346e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Unilever-Promoter-Group-Takes-Control-of-Kwality-Walls-India-Post-Demerger/6998548a057e346edab4346e</guid><description>Unilever Plc's promoter group has acquired a controlling 61.90% stake in Kwality Wall's (India) Limited, following the demerger of Hindustan Unilever's (HUL) ice cream business. The transaction, which involved the allotment of over 1.45 billion shares, was completed on December 12, 2025. Kwality Wall's (India) Limited shares commenced trading on February 16, 2026. The acquisition was made under a SEBI exemption, avoiding a public open offer. This move consolidates control within the Unilever ecosystem and sets Kwality Wall's up as a standalone entity in India's competitive ice cream market.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:33:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6998548a057e346edab4346d_1771590925123.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>LIC Buys More Cipla Shares as Stock Faces Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/LIC-Buys-More-Cipla-Shares-as-Stock-Faces-Headwinds/69985484057e346edab43458</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/LIC-Buys-More-Cipla-Shares-as-Stock-Faces-Headwinds/69985484057e346edab43458</guid><description>State-owned Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC) has significantly increased its shareholding in Cipla Limited, raising its stake from 5.025% to 7.055% through market purchases between July and November 2025. This move by India's largest institutional investor signals growing confidence in the pharmaceutical major, even as Cipla navigates a challenging market characterized by margin pressures and declining sales of key products like gRevlimid.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:33:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69985484057e346edab43457_1771590898645.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NCLT Oks Asian Granito Demerger Amidst ₹104Cr Tax Dispute</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCLT-Oks-Asian-Granito-Demerger-Amidst-104Cr-Tax-Dispute/69985391057e346edab43361</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCLT-Oks-Asian-Granito-Demerger-Amidst-104Cr-Tax-Dispute/69985391057e346edab43361</guid><description>The National Company Law Tribunal (NCLT), Ahmedabad Bench, has approved Asian Granito India Limited's (AGIL) corporate demerger scheme involving its subsidiaries. This key approval allows AGIL to proceed with integrating operations and expanding market reach. The decision comes despite objections from the Income Tax Department over a ₹104.73 crore disputed tax liability, which the NCLT ruled does not impede the scheme's sanctioning.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:29:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69985391057e346edab43360_1771590649573.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI's 'Optimum Regulation' Faces Tech Arms Race Against Rising Fraud</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBIs-Optimum-Regulation-Faces-Tech-Arms-Race-Against-Rising-Fraud/699852ca057e346edab43282</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBIs-Optimum-Regulation-Faces-Tech-Arms-Race-Against-Rising-Fraud/699852ca057e346edab43282</guid><description>Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) Chairman Tuhin Kanta Pandey has reiterated the regulator's commitment to 'optimum regulation,' balancing market innovation with investor protection. Amidst a multi-fold increase in India's investor base to approximately 14 crore, Pandey highlighted the escalating threat of cyber fraud driven by digital adoption. SEBI is deploying advanced technological tools and new initiatives, such as the SEBI Check facility and validated UPI handles, to combat these risks. However, a persistent gap in investor awareness leaves many vulnerable to mis-selling and scams, signaling an ongoing challenge for the regulator in maintaining market integrity.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:25:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699852ca057e346edab43281_1771590477809.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IRB Infra Seeks Nod for Bonus Shares, Huge Project Deal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/IRB-Infra-Seeks-Nod-for-Bonus-Shares-Huge-Project-Deal/699851b3057e346edab4315c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/IRB-Infra-Seeks-Nod-for-Bonus-Shares-Huge-Project-Deal/699851b3057e346edab4315c</guid><description>IRB Infrastructure Developers Ltd. is asking shareholders for approval on four key matters through a postal ballot. These include issuing bonus shares in a 1:1 ratio, increasing the company's authorized share capital, approving a substantial related party transaction valued at up to ₹1,866.55 Crore, and re-appointing a director. The related party deal, for the TOT-18 project, represents over 20% of the company's projected annual turnover.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:21:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699851b3057e346edab4315b_1771590211997.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Patel Engineering Cuts Debt, Eyes Growth Amidst Fierce Bidding Wars</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Patel-Engineering-Cuts-Debt-Eyes-Growth-Amidst-Fierce-Bidding-Wars/699851af057e346edab43146</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Patel-Engineering-Cuts-Debt-Eyes-Growth-Amidst-Fierce-Bidding-Wars/699851af057e346edab43146</guid><description>Patel Engineering is cutting debt using its INR 400 crore rights issue, aiming for over INR 5,000 crore revenue this fiscal year. While its order book is strong, management faces tough competition and investor questions about high promoter share pledges and rights issue costs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:21:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699851af057e346edab43145.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Starbucks India Expands Aggressively Amidst Widening Losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Starbucks-India-Expands-Aggressively-Amidst-Widening-Losses/69985162057e346edab430c5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Starbucks-India-Expands-Aggressively-Amidst-Widening-Losses/69985162057e346edab430c5</guid><description>Starbucks' Indian joint venture is accelerating store openings and diversifying its menu with localized offerings and health-conscious options. Despite claims of operational cash positivity, the venture reported a significant widening of net losses to ₹135.7 crore in FY25, even as revenue grew marginally by 5%. This aggressive growth strategy unfolds against a backdrop of intense competition from nimble local players and broader market slowdowns, raising questions about the long-term profitability of its India expansion.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:19:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69985162057e346edab430c4_1771590084734.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Core Sector Growth Skewed by Steel, Cement; Risks Mount</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Core-Sector-Growth-Skewed-by-Steel-Cement-Risks-Mount/699850f9057e346edab43035</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Core-Sector-Growth-Skewed-by-Steel-Cement-Risks-Mount/699850f9057e346edab43035</guid><description>India's eight core sectors expanded by 4% year-on-year in January 2026, primarily driven by robust performances in steel and cement output. However, this concentrated growth masks a broader economic picture, with significant expansion in these key sectors raising concerns about oversupply and margin pressures. While manufacturing activity shows overall expansion, persistent challenges in other core industries and macro-economic headwinds create a complex outlook for sustained industrial momentum.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:18:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699850f9057e346edab43034.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Accenture's AI Promotion Mandate Creates Internal Talent Divide</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Accentures-AI-Promotion-Mandate-Creates-Internal-Talent-Divide/699850c6057e346edab42ff6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Accentures-AI-Promotion-Mandate-Creates-Internal-Talent-Divide/699850c6057e346edab42ff6</guid><description>Accenture is now requiring associate directors and senior managers to regularly use its AI tools to be considered for leadership promotions. This policy, driven by a broad AI-focused restructuring, mandates a significant reskilling effort across its 779,000-strong workforce. While aiming to bolster AI competency and client services, it introduces internal talent segmentation and execution risks amid broader industry shifts.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:17:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699850c6057e346edab42ff5_1771589951417.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lumax Auto Sets New Revenue Record, Boosts FY26 Outlook on Strong OEM Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Lumax-Auto-Sets-New-Revenue-Record-Boosts-FY26-Outlook-on-Strong-OEM-Demand/69984fd6057e346edab42efa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Lumax-Auto-Sets-New-Revenue-Record-Boosts-FY26-Outlook-on-Strong-OEM-Demand/69984fd6057e346edab42efa</guid><description>Lumax Auto Technologies Ltd. achieved its highest-ever quarterly revenue of INR 1,271 crore in the third quarter of fiscal year 2025-26, marking a significant 40% year-on-year increase. The company also hit a milestone with EBITDA margins reaching 15% for the first time. Driven by robust demand from original equipment manufacturers (OEMs) across vehicle segments and a strong order book, management has revised its full-year revenue growth guidance upwards to 30%. The company is also progressing with mergers and new product supplies for key automotive players.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:13:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69984fd6057e346edab42ef9_1771589777832.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Khazanchi Jewellers Retail Push Fuels 49% Q3 Sales Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Khazanchi-Jewellers-Retail-Push-Fuels-49percent-Q3-Sales-Growth/69984f59057e346edab42ea5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Khazanchi-Jewellers-Retail-Push-Fuels-49percent-Q3-Sales-Growth/69984f59057e346edab42ea5</guid><description>Khazanchi Jewellers reported a strong Q3 FY26 with revenue up 49.6% year-on-year to INR 589.26 crores. Their new Chennai flagship store generated INR 20 crores in its first 10 days, a testament to the company's retail expansion strategy. Management aims to boost retail's contribution to 25% of revenue, expecting significant profit margin improvements.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:11:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69984f59057e346edab42ea4.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RHI Magnesita India Hits Record Revenue, But Faces Fierce Price Wars</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/RHI-Magnesita-India-Hits-Record-Revenue-But-Faces-Fierce-Price-Wars/69984e67057e346edab42ddc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/RHI-Magnesita-India-Hits-Record-Revenue-But-Faces-Fierce-Price-Wars/69984e67057e346edab42ddc</guid><description>RHI Magnesita India achieved record revenue of INR 1,092 crores in Q3 FY26, up 8% year-on-year, and turned its debt into a net cash position of INR 35 crores. The company also reported its highest EBITDA margin of the fiscal year at 13.7%. However, management highlighted aggressive competition with rivals taking orders at negative margins, alongside structural pressures from domestic overcapacity and Chinese steel dumping. Despite these headwinds, the company is optimistic about sustained margins between 14-15% and sees growth from new contracts and increasing exports.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:07:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69984e67057e346edab42ddb_1771589339109.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Glenmark Pharma Scores 68 ESG Rating Unsolicited Amidst Past Price-Fixing Fine</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Glenmark-Pharma-Scores-68-ESG-Rating-Unsolicited-Amidst-Past-Price-Fixing-Fine/69984df2057e346edab42d73</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Glenmark-Pharma-Scores-68-ESG-Rating-Unsolicited-Amidst-Past-Price-Fixing-Fine/69984df2057e346edab42d73</guid><description>Glenmark Pharmaceuticals has been assigned an unsolicited ESG rating of "68" for FY25 by NSE Sustainability Ratings and Analytics Limited, based on publicly available data. This comes at a time when the company has faced significant regulatory challenges, including a $55 million settlement in the US related to price-fixing allegations for a generic drug. While Glenmark has its own ESG initiatives, investors will weigh this rating against its past governance issues and mixed financial performance.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:05:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69984df2057e346edab42d72_1771589278919.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Crypto SIPs: Discipline Meets Digital Asset Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Crypto-SIPs-Discipline-Meets-Digital-Asset-Volatility/69984d22057e346edab42c31</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/Crypto-SIPs-Discipline-Meets-Digital-Asset-Volatility/69984d22057e346edab42c31</guid><description>Crypto SIPs replicate mutual fund discipline for digital assets, using rupee-cost averaging to navigate extreme volatility. Platforms offer accessible entry points, but investors face significant risks, a complex global regulatory environment, and India's punitive 30% tax on gains and 1% TDS.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:01:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69984d22057e346edab42c30_1771589036663.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Markets Rebound Amidst Global Jitters, IPO Frenzy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/India-Markets-Rebound-Amidst-Global-Jitters-IPO-Frenzy/69984d18057e346edab42c19</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/India-Markets-Rebound-Amidst-Global-Jitters-IPO-Frenzy/69984d18057e346edab42c19</guid><description>Indian benchmark indices rebounded strongly on Friday, capping a volatile week. Despite global headwinds from geopolitical concerns and mixed performance in US and European markets, domestic resilience was evident. A robust calendar of upcoming IPOs, including Clean Max Enviro, Shree Ram Twistex, and PNGS Reva Diamond Jewellery, adds another layer to market activity. Investors are closely monitoring upcoming economic data releases from India, the Euro Area, and the US, alongside ongoing geopolitical developments.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 12:01:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69984d18057e346edab42c18_1771589058330.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ceinsys Tech Lists on NSE, Shows Strong Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Ceinsys-Tech-Lists-on-NSE-Shows-Strong-Revenue-Growth/69984c99057e346edab42b23</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Ceinsys-Tech-Lists-on-NSE-Shows-Strong-Revenue-Growth/69984c99057e346edab42b23</guid><description>Ceinsys Tech Ai, already listed on the BSE since 2014, has commenced trading on the National Stock Exchange (NSE) on February 19, 2026. The company showcased a strong financial performance, with revenues growing consistently since FY14-15 and significantly in the first nine months of FY25-26. Its strategy focuses on deploying advanced technologies like IoT, AI, and digital twins for infrastructure development.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:59:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69984c99057e346edab42b22_1771588856713.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PPAP Automotive Exits JV for Rs 100 Cr, Eyes Debt Cut Amidst Sales Slump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/PPAP-Automotive-Exits-JV-for-Rs-100-Cr-Eyes-Debt-Cut-Amidst-Sales-Slump/69984c8d057e346edab42b07</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/PPAP-Automotive-Exits-JV-for-Rs-100-Cr-Eyes-Debt-Cut-Amidst-Sales-Slump/69984c8d057e346edab42b07</guid><description>PPAP Automotive Limited has exited its joint venture with Tokai Kogyo, securing ₹100 crore. The company plans to use these funds to slash its debt and invest in capital expenditure, aiming to cut interest costs by 30%. While the aftermarket and battery businesses are showing strong growth, the core automotive segment faced demand challenges in Q3 FY26, impacting capacity utilization and profitability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:59:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69984c8d057e346edab42b06.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Quality Power subsidiary wins ₹18 Cr transformer order</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Quality-Power-subsidiary-wins-18-Cr-transformer-order/69984c86057e346edab42ae1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Quality-Power-subsidiary-wins-18-Cr-transformer-order/69984c86057e346edab42ae1</guid><description>Quality Power Electrical Equipments Limited's material subsidiary, Mehru Electrical and Mechanical Engineers Private Limited (MEMEPL), has secured a Letter of Award (LOA) for supplying instrument transformers worth approximately ₹18 Crores. The order, with an 8-month execution timeline, bolsters MEMEPL's position in the high-voltage equipment sector and aligns with Quality Power's strategic growth in the energy transition segment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:59:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69984c86057e346edab42ae0_1771588867586.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tira Adds Medicube: K-Beauty Hype Meets Indian Premium Skincare Race</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Tira-Adds-Medicube-K-Beauty-Hype-Meets-Indian-Premium-Skincare-Race/69984b9f057e346edab429f1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Tira-Adds-Medicube-K-Beauty-Hype-Meets-Indian-Premium-Skincare-Race/69984b9f057e346edab429f1</guid><description>Reliance Retail's beauty platform Tira has partnered with South Korean dermo-cosmetic brand Medicube, aiming to bolster its premium skincare offerings. This move taps into India's rapidly growing premium and K-beauty markets, driven by ingredient-aware Gen Z and millennials. Medicube brings clinically proven, viral-popular formulations to India, aligning with Tira's strategy to curate high-efficacy global brands. However, the partnership faces the challenge of translating social media momentum into sustained consumer loyalty in a price-sensitive market, while competing against established players like Nykaa.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:55:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69984b9f057e346edab429f0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JSW Infra Plans Massive Fundraise For Port Expansion &amp; Appoints New Director</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/JSW-Infra-Plans-Massive-Fundraise-For-Port-Expansion-and-Appoints-New-Director/6998494a057e346edab428cd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/JSW-Infra-Plans-Massive-Fundraise-For-Port-Expansion-and-Appoints-New-Director/6998494a057e346edab428cd</guid><description>JSW Infrastructure's board has greenlit a substantial equity fundraising plan, aiming to issue up to 25 crore shares. This capital will fuel its ₹39,000 crore expansion drive to reach 400 MTPA port capacity by FY2030 and meet SEBI's Minimum Public Shareholding (MPS) norms. Additionally, Mr. Kartick Maheshwari joins as a Non-Executive Independent Director. The company anticipates doubling its operating EBITDA by FY2028.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:45:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6998494a057e346edab428cc_1771588019699.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lumax Industries Hits Record Revenue on Strong LED Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Lumax-Industries-Hits-Record-Revenue-on-Strong-LED-Demand/69984866057e346edab42814</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Lumax-Industries-Hits-Record-Revenue-on-Strong-LED-Demand/69984866057e346edab42814</guid><description>Lumax Industries reported its highest-ever quarterly revenue of INR 1,053 crores, up 18.7% year-on-year. The company's successful shift to LED lighting, now contributing 61% of revenue, is fueling growth, supported by a strong INR 1,759 crore order book. Management guides for over 20% top-line growth next fiscal and aims for 12% EBITDA margins within two years, despite investments and import concentration risks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:41:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69984866057e346edab42813.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NTPC Green Energy Adds 158 MW Solar Power, Boosts Green Capacity to 9151 MW</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/NTPC-Green-Energy-Adds-158-MW-Solar-Power-Boosts-Green-Capacity-to-9151-MW/699847e2057e346edab42773</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/NTPC-Green-Energy-Adds-158-MW-Solar-Power-Boosts-Green-Capacity-to-9151-MW/699847e2057e346edab42773</guid><description>NTPC Green Energy Limited, a unit of NTPC, has successfully started commercial operations for a 158.4 MW solar power project in Andhra Pradesh. This development, effective February 14, 2026, increases the NTPC Green Energy Group's total installed renewable capacity to 9151.08 MW. The project is part of the Ayana Kadapa Renewable Power Private Limited initiative, boosting India's significant push towards cleaner energy sources.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:39:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699847e2057e346edab42772_1771587713307.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Edible Oil Command Faces Price Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Edible-Oil-Command-Faces-Price-Volatility/69984708057e346edab42638</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Edible-Oil-Command-Faces-Price-Volatility/69984708057e346edab42638</guid><description>India's position as a global edible oil trade driver is increasingly reliant on narrow price arbitrage, creating market instability. Recent import surges were opportunistic, but fluctuating biofuel policies and geopolitical factors amplify price sensitivity. A $50-60 per tonne price shift can significantly alter India's import volumes, highlighting a reliance on arbitrage that may not sustain its market dominance. Projections indicate continued high import dependence, but structural volatility is intensifying.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:35:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69984708057e346edab42637.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JASUB Holdings &amp; Allies Trim Cohance Lifesciences Stake</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/JASUB-Holdings-and-Allies-Trim-Cohance-Lifesciences-Stake/699846f2057e346edab4261d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/JASUB-Holdings-and-Allies-Trim-Cohance-Lifesciences-Stake/699846f2057e346edab4261d</guid><description>JASUB Property Holdings LLP and its associated entities have adjusted their stake in Cohance Lifesciences Limited, formerly Suven Pharmaceuticals. Through inter-se transfers in block deals on February 18, 2026, the aggregate shareholding of JASUB and Persons Acting in Concert (PACs) decreased to 6.36% from 6.59%. This comes amid recent regulatory disclosures for Cohance Lifesciences, including a US FDA warning and an RBI compounding fee.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:35:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699846f2057e346edab4261c.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JSW Infra OKs Big Fund Raise, Appoints Ex-Chief As Independent Director</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/JSW-Infra-OKs-Big-Fund-Raise-Appoints-Ex-Chief-As-Independent-Director/699846e9057e346edab42606</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/JSW-Infra-OKs-Big-Fund-Raise-Appoints-Ex-Chief-As-Independent-Director/699846e9057e346edab42606</guid><description>JSW Infrastructure's board has approved an equity fund-raise of up to 25 crore shares, aiming to fuel its massive multi-year expansion program and meet SEBI's minimum public shareholding rules. The company also appointed Mr. Kartick Maheshwari, former Joint MD &amp; CEO, as a Non-Executive, Independent Director. This move signals a strategic push for growth funded by capital infusion, balancing expansion needs with regulatory compliance.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:35:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699846e9057e346edab42605.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BEL's Top Credit Rating Confirmed by ICRA, Signals Financial Strength</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BELs-Top-Credit-Rating-Confirmed-by-ICRA-Signals-Financial-Strength/69984675057e346edab4256b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/BELs-Top-Credit-Rating-Confirmed-by-ICRA-Signals-Financial-Strength/69984675057e346edab4256b</guid><description>Bharat Electronics Limited (BEL) has received a strong endorsement from credit rating agency ICRA, which has reaffirmed its highest ratings for the company's debt facilities. This reaffirmation underscores BEL's robust financial health, dominant position in the defense sector, and significant order book, signaling continued stability and strength for the state-owned enterprise.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:33:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69984675057e346edab4256a_1771587292211.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Premier Explosives Promoter Group Restructures, AKS Trust Takes Control</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Premier-Explosives-Promoter-Group-Restructures-AKS-Trust-Takes-Control/69984674057e346edab42555</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Premier-Explosives-Promoter-Group-Restructures-AKS-Trust-Takes-Control/69984674057e346edab42555</guid><description>Premier Explosives Limited's promoter group has undergone a significant restructuring, with AKS Family Trust acquiring a 41.33% stake through a settlement. While the overall promoter holding remains constant, this move consolidates control under the family trust. The transaction occurred under a SEBI exemption order. This development comes as the company reported a sharp year-on-year decline in its third-quarter revenue and profit, though its nine-month performance shows growth. Investors are also watching a SEBI inquiry into suspected insider trading and potential penalties for delivery delays.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:33:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69984674057e346edab42554.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Diamond Power Fined ₹10 Lakh for Shareholding Rule Breach</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Diamond-Power-Fined-10-Lakh-for-Shareholding-Rule-Breach/69984581057e346edab42434</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Diamond-Power-Fined-10-Lakh-for-Shareholding-Rule-Breach/69984581057e346edab42434</guid><description>Diamond Power Infrastructure Limited has been hit with a penalty of ₹10.85 lakh by the BSE and NSE for failing to meet Minimum Public Shareholding (MPS) norms for the quarter ending December 31, 2025. The company has paid the fines, but faces risks of further exchange actions if compliance isn't restored soon. The board is committed to fixing the issue.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:29:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69984581057e346edab42433.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TIL Limited Plans Big Buy &amp; More Loans Ahead of March EGM</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TIL-Limited-Plans-Big-Buy-and-More-Loans-Ahead-of-March-EGM/69984580057e346edab4241e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/TIL-Limited-Plans-Big-Buy-and-More-Loans-Ahead-of-March-EGM/69984580057e346edab4241e</guid><description>TIL Limited has called an Extraordinary General Meeting (EGM) for March 14, 2026, to get shareholder nod for acquiring a 60% stake in Tulip Compression Private Limited (TCPL) for about ₹119 crore. TCPL operates in CNG, LNG, and Hydrogen infrastructure. The company also plans to increase its borrowing limit from ₹400 crore to ₹600 crore to fund this deal and future expansion, signaling a push for growth in the energy infrastructure sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:29:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69984580057e346edab4241d_1771587053908.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>McNally Bharat Posts Narrower Loss Post-Insolvency, Revenue Falls 13%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/McNally-Bharat-Posts-Narrower-Loss-Post-Insolvency-Revenue-Falls-13percent/69984491057e346edab42344</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/McNally-Bharat-Posts-Narrower-Loss-Post-Insolvency-Revenue-Falls-13percent/69984491057e346edab42344</guid><description>McNally Bharat has reported a much smaller net loss for the quarter ended December 31, 2025, thanks to drastically reduced finance costs following its insolvency resolution. However, the company's revenue declined by 13% year-on-year. The firm is still navigating post-insolvency challenges, including operational deficits, write-offs of international investments, and ongoing disputes, signaling a critical but complex turnaround phase.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:25:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69984491057e346edab42343_1771586824242.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Max India Expands Senior Care Business, But Losses Deepen</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Max-India-Expands-Senior-Care-Business-But-Losses-Deepen/69984418057e346edab422cf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Max-India-Expands-Senior-Care-Business-But-Losses-Deepen/69984418057e346edab422cf</guid><description>Max India Limited presented a bold strategy for its Antara senior care business, aiming for pan-India presence with new residential communities and care homes. Despite a 27% year-on-year rise in revenue for Q3 FY26, the company's operating losses (EBITDA) and net losses widened, highlighting the significant investment required for its expansion plans.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:23:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69984418057e346edab422ce.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Crypto Giant's Gold Hoard Reshapes Market Dynamics</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Crypto-Giants-Gold-Hoard-Reshapes-Market-Dynamics/69984344057e346edab4217a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Crypto-Giants-Gold-Hoard-Reshapes-Market-Dynamics/69984344057e346edab4217a</guid><description>Tether Holdings has dramatically expanded its physical gold reserves, amassing approximately 148 tonnes valued at $23 billion by late January 2026. This aggressive accumulation, conducted from a Swiss mountain bunker, positions the stablecoin issuer as one of the world's largest private gold buyers, outmaneuvering numerous nations and significantly influencing global gold demand, which itself hit record highs in 2025. The move signals a structural shift, blending traditional safe-haven assets with digital finance infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:19:32 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69984344057e346edab42179_1771586511658.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata Hotels' IHCL Gets Top AAA Credit Rating Upgrade</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Hotels-IHCL-Gets-Top-AAA-Credit-Rating-Upgrade/6998432c057e346edab4215a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-Hotels-IHCL-Gets-Top-AAA-Credit-Rating-Upgrade/6998432c057e346edab4215a</guid><description>The Indian Hotels Company Limited (IHCL) has earned a prestigious upgrade in its long-term credit rating from ICRA to AAA (Stable), the highest possible. This reflects its robust financial performance, market leadership in Indian hospitality, and strong backing from Tata Sons. Despite impressive revenue and margin growth, and an aggressive asset-light expansion plan targeting over 700 hotels by 2030, IHCL faces a significant risk from a protracted lease rental dispute with the Mumbai Port Trust over the iconic Taj Mahal Palace hotel.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:19:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6998432c057e346edab42159_1771586458492.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndusInd Bank Doubles Gold Loan Network Amid Market Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IndusInd-Bank-Doubles-Gold-Loan-Network-Amid-Market-Push/699842bc057e346edab42096</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IndusInd-Bank-Doubles-Gold-Loan-Network-Amid-Market-Push/699842bc057e346edab42096</guid><description>IndusInd Bank is nearly doubling its gold loan network to 500 branches, signaling a strategic push to tap into the rapidly growing, secure gold loan market. This move aims to enhance accessible credit for customers and strengthen the bank's retail lending portfolio, especially as gold loans have seen substantial growth and favorable regulatory commentary from the RBI. The expansion aligns with a broader industry trend where banks are increasing their share in this segment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:17:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699842bc057e346edab42095.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kiri Industries Directors Set for Re-appointment Amidst Financial Turnaround</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Kiri-Industries-Directors-Set-for-Re-appointment-Amidst-Financial-Turnaround/699842b1057e346edab4207f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Kiri-Industries-Directors-Set-for-Re-appointment-Amidst-Financial-Turnaround/699842b1057e346edab4207f</guid><description>Kiri Industries Limited is seeking shareholder approval through a postal ballot for the re-appointment of its Chairman &amp; Managing Director, Mr. Manish Kiri, and two Whole Time Directors, Mr. Girish Tandel and Mr. Yagnesh Mankad. The company reported a significant financial turnaround for FY 2024-25, with its standalone EBITDA turning positive after a period of losses, driven by factors including the resolution of its long-standing legal dispute concerning its stake in DyStar.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:17:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699842b1057e346edab4207e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jagran Prakashan Fights Shareholder Move to Remove 8 Directors</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Jagran-Prakashan-Fights-Shareholder-Move-to-Remove-8-Directors/69984238057e346edab4200a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Jagran-Prakashan-Fights-Shareholder-Move-to-Remove-8-Directors/69984238057e346edab4200a</guid><description>Jagran Prakashan Limited (JPL) has initiated legal proceedings to prevent a shareholder from holding an Extra-Ordinary General Meeting (EGM). The shareholder's notice seeks to remove seven Independent Directors and one Whole-Time Director, citing alleged invalid appointments due to a voting rights dispute. JPL's application aims to block the requisition and the proposed EGM, highlighting a significant corporate governance conflict within the media company.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:15:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69984237057e346edab42009.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UPL Restructuring Sparks Skepticism Amid Debt Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/UPL-Restructuring-Sparks-Skepticism-Amid-Debt-Concerns/69983ff4057e346edab41e7a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/UPL-Restructuring-Sparks-Skepticism-Amid-Debt-Concerns/69983ff4057e346edab41e7a</guid><description>Indian agrochemical giant UPL announced a significant restructuring to split its operations into two publicly traded companies, aiming for simplified structures and focused platforms. The plan involves multiple mergers and demergers, with UPL Sustainable Agri Solutions merging into UPL and the India crop protection business demerging into a new entity. Despite recent positive Q3 earnings, shares dipped 1.7% on February 20, 2026, as investors digest the intricate process and UPL's substantial debt load, a lingering concern from past acquisitions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:05:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69983ff4057e346edab41e79.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kopran Ltd. Server Data Breached; Company Probes Cyber Incident</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Kopran-Ltd-Server-Data-Breached-Company-Probes-Cyber-Incident/69983fe0057e346edab41e58</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Kopran-Ltd-Server-Data-Breached-Company-Probes-Cyber-Incident/69983fe0057e346edab41e58</guid><description>Kopran Ltd. has reported a significant security incident, revealing that an unauthorized individual gained access to its computer server data at the Khopoli factory. The pharmaceutical company has initiated an investigation with cybersecurity experts to determine the extent of the breach and its root cause. This disclosure comes under SEBI regulations, highlighting the operational and governance challenges companies face in safeguarding sensitive data.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:05:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69983fe0057e346edab41e57_1771585609590.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Premier Energies Eyes Export Growth, Bets on Copper Tech</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Premier-Energies-Eyes-Export-Growth-Bets-on-Copper-Tech/69983ec6057e346edab41d03</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Premier-Energies-Eyes-Export-Growth-Bets-on-Copper-Tech/69983ec6057e346edab41d03</guid><description>Premier Energies is pivoting from its domestic focus to export markets, capitalizing on Western supply chain diversification away from China. A joint venture with Heliene will establish a 1 GW solar cell plant in the US, aiming to leverage Inflation Reduction Act incentives. Concurrently, the company is pursuing research to replace silver with copper in solar cells, targeting cost stability and reduced reliance on volatile materials, with initial results expected within 18 months. This strategic shift addresses evolving global trade dynamics and technological innovation in the solar sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:00:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69983ec6057e346edab41d02.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>