<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 06:27:42 +0000</pubDate><item><title>SML Mahindra Skyrockets: December Sales Boom Triggers 5% Upper Circuit!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/SML-Mahindra-Skyrockets-December-Sales-Boom-Triggers-5percent-Upper-Circuit/69560f134342f77179f44969</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/SML-Mahindra-Skyrockets-December-Sales-Boom-Triggers-5percent-Upper-Circuit/69560f134342f77179f44969</guid><description>SML Mahindra Limited shares surged to a 5% upper circuit, closing at ₹4,174.25 on the BSE. This jump followed the company's announcement of strong December auto sales figures, showing a significant 67% year-on-year increase. The company sold 1,044 units, with cargo and passenger vehicles contributing significantly. This positive sales momentum is expected to be further reflected in the upcoming unaudited financial results for Q3 FY2023-24, due for board approval on January 16, 2024.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 05:56:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69560f134342f77179f44968_1767247728930.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Steel Strips Wheels Skyrockets 8% After SMASHING Record Sales! Investors Cheer Highest-Ever Monthly Performance!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Steel-Strips-Wheels-Skyrockets-8percent-After-SMASHING-Record-Sales-Investors-Cheer-Highest-Ever-Monthly-Performance/69560f074342f77179f4492e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Steel-Strips-Wheels-Skyrockets-8percent-After-SMASHING-Record-Sales-Investors-Cheer-Highest-Ever-Monthly-Performance/69560f074342f77179f4492e</guid><description>Steel Strips Wheels Ltd. shares surged nearly 8% after announcing its highest-ever monthly sales for December 2025. Strong domestic demand across tractor, aluminium, and truck wheel segments, coupled with record turnover and improved average selling prices, fueled the rally. Net turnover jumped 22.44% year-on-year to ₹446.59 crore, despite muted export volumes.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 05:56:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69560f074342f77179f4492d_1767247729693.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Blue Dart Shares Skyrocket: Massive Tax Victory &amp; Future Price Hikes Ignites Rally!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Blue-Dart-Shares-Skyrocket-Massive-Tax-Victory-and-Future-Price-Hikes-Ignites-Rally/69560e434342f77179f445a9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Blue-Dart-Shares-Skyrocket-Massive-Tax-Victory-and-Future-Price-Hikes-Ignites-Rally/69560e434342f77179f445a9</guid><description>Blue Dart Express Ltd. shares jumped nearly 9% on Thursday following two major positive developments. Tax authorities significantly reduced a demand from ₹421 crore to ₹64.98 lakh, which the company has paid. Additionally, Blue Dart announced an average shipment price increase of 9-12% effective January 1, 2026, to counter rising costs and invest in growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 05:56:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69560e434342f77179f445a8_1767247506838.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ITC Plunges on Tax Hike! Voda Idea Surges, Rupee Dips as Markets React to Key Indian News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ITC-Plunges-on-Tax-Hike-Voda-Idea-Surges-Rupee-Dips-as-Markets-React-to-Key-Indian-News/69560ecb4342f77179f4484c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ITC-Plunges-on-Tax-Hike-Voda-Idea-Surges-Rupee-Dips-as-Markets-React-to-Key-Indian-News/69560ecb4342f77179f4484c</guid><description>Indian markets saw significant movement as ITC Ltd. shares dropped to a 33-month low following a government excise duty hike on cigarettes. Meanwhile, Vodafone Idea Ltd. shares gained nearly 9% after securing a revised agreement with promoters for ₹5,836 crore in receivables. The Indian Rupee also started the year weaker, depreciating 11 paise against the US dollar due to foreign fund outflows. Gold and silver began 2026 cautiously after strong prior-year gains.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 05:56:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Rs 86 Cr to Rs 32,000 Cr: Info Edge's Zomato Masterstroke Unveiled!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Rs-86-Cr-to-Rs-32000-Cr-Info-Edges-Zomato-Masterstroke-Unveiled/69560e3c4342f77179f4455c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Rs-86-Cr-to-Rs-32000-Cr-Info-Edges-Zomato-Masterstroke-Unveiled/69560e3c4342f77179f4455c</guid><description>Info Edge, parent of Naukri.com, has seen its initial Rs 86 crore investment in food delivery firm Eternal (formerly Zomato) skyrocket to over Rs 32,000 crore. This exceptional growth highlights Info Edge's successful venture capital strategy and Eternal's significant stock market gains since its 2021 IPO.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 05:51:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Motilal Oswal's Bold Call: Kotak Mahindra Bank Stock Set for Massive Surge to ₹2500? Investor Frenzy Builds!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Motilal-Oswals-Bold-Call-Kotak-Mahindra-Bank-Stock-Set-for-Massive-Surge-to-2500-Investor-Frenzy-Builds/69560dd34342f77179f44390</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Motilal-Oswals-Bold-Call-Kotak-Mahindra-Bank-Stock-Set-for-Massive-Surge-to-2500-Investor-Frenzy-Builds/69560dd34342f77179f44390</guid><description>Motilal Oswal has issued a strong 'Buy' recommendation for Kotak Mahindra Bank, setting a target price of ₹2,500. The brokerage highlights the bank's disciplined growth framework, focusing on retail and SME segments, which is expected to drive robust return ratios. Despite near-term NIM fluctuations due to yield distortions and liquidity deployment, the report projects stable earnings growth and estimates Return on Assets (RoA) and Return on Equity (RoE) at 2% and 12.7% respectively by FY27E. The target price is based on 2.5 times FY27E Adjusted Book Value plus subsidiary value.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 05:51:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Kia India Shatters Records: December Sales Skyrocket Over 200%!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Kia-India-Shatters-Records-December-Sales-Skyrocket-Over-200percent/69560c354342f77179f43c4b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Kia-India-Shatters-Records-December-Sales-Skyrocket-Over-200percent/69560c354342f77179f43c4b</guid><description>Kia India achieved its best-ever December, selling 18,659 units, a more than double increase from 8,957 units in December 2024. For the full calendar year 2025, wholesale volumes rose 15% to 2,80,286 units compared to 2,45,000 units in 2024. The company attributes this growth to strong customer focus, positive consumer sentiment, strategic product launches like the Carens Clavis, and optimized models such as the Seltos, Carens, and Sonet, supported by favourable economic conditions and government policies.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 05:47:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>January 2026: India's Q3 Earnings Rush! TCS Dividend, HDFC Bank &amp; 10+ Stocks in Focus!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/January-2026-Indias-Q3-Earnings-Rush-TCS-Dividend-HDFC-Bank-and-10-Stocks-in-Focus/69560c784342f77179f43d7e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/January-2026-Indias-Q3-Earnings-Rush-TCS-Dividend-HDFC-Bank-and-10-Stocks-in-Focus/69560c784342f77179f43d7e</guid><description>January 2026 marks the start of India Inc's crucial Q3 FY26 earnings season. Investors will closely watch major companies, including IT giants like TCS and Infosys, banks like HDFC Bank and ICICI Bank, and firms across cement, pharma, FMCG, and auto sectors, as they unveil their quarterly results and potential dividend announcements. These results are vital for assessing corporate performance amid evolving economic conditions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 05:46:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69560c784342f77179f43d7d_1767247044971.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Auto Giants Surge! M&amp;M, Kia India Smash December Sales Records - What's Driving This Explosive Growth?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Auto-Giants-Surge-MandM-Kia-India-Smash-December-Sales-Records-Whats-Driving-This-Explosive-Growth/69560bcd4342f77179f43a71</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Auto-Giants-Surge-MandM-Kia-India-Smash-December-Sales-Records-Whats-Driving-This-Explosive-Growth/69560bcd4342f77179f43a71</guid><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra (M&amp;M) reported a 23% jump in domestic vehicle sales for December 2025, dispatching 50,946 units. Kia India also achieved its best-ever December with a 105% year-on-year growth, selling 18,659 units. M&amp;M marked its highest-ever volumes in SUVs and LCVs for calendar year 2025. Tractor sales for M&amp;M and Escorts Kubota also surged by 37% and 36.1% respectively, driven by positive rural sentiment and government support.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 05:45:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_69560bcd4342f77179f43a70_1767247385476.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Piccadily Agro Shares Skyrocket 13%! Chhattisgarh Unit Powers Massive Rally - What's Behind the Surge?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Piccadily-Agro-Shares-Skyrocket-13percent-Chhattisgarh-Unit-Powers-Massive-Rally-Whats-Behind-the-Surge/695608064342f77179f42c8d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Piccadily-Agro-Shares-Skyrocket-13percent-Chhattisgarh-Unit-Powers-Massive-Rally-Whats-Behind-the-Surge/695608064342f77179f42c8d</guid><description>Piccadily Agro Industries shares surged by nearly 13%, reaching an intra-day high of ₹639.35 on the BSE. This rally is driven by the company's commencement of commercial production at its new Chhattisgarh unit, boasting a capacity of 200 kilolitres per day (KLPD). The expansion is expected to boost its manufacturing capabilities in its core distillery and sugar segments.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 05:23:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695608064342f77179f42c8c_1767247137570.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Escorts Kubota Stock Surges 3.5% on Stellar Tractor Sales Growth!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Escorts-Kubota-Stock-Surges-35percent-on-Stellar-Tractor-Sales-Growth/695607904342f77179f427ac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Escorts-Kubota-Stock-Surges-35percent-on-Stellar-Tractor-Sales-Growth/695607904342f77179f427ac</guid><description>Escorts Kubota Limited announced a significant 38.5% year-on-year growth in tractor sales for December 2025, selling 7,577 units compared to 5,472 in December 2024. This strong business update propelled the company's share price up by 3.52% on the NSE. Domestic sales increased by 36.1% and export sales by 64.3%, driven by supportive government policies and positive rural sentiment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 05:23:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695607904342f77179f427ab_1767245775085.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bharti Airtel Stock Soars: Nirmal Bang's Bold 'BUY' Call &amp; ₹2,525 Target! 🚀</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Bharti-Airtel-Stock-Soars-Nirmal-Bangs-Bold-BUY-Call-and-2525-Target/695607eb4342f77179f42c03</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Bharti-Airtel-Stock-Soars-Nirmal-Bangs-Bold-BUY-Call-and-2525-Target/695607eb4342f77179f42c03</guid><description>Brokerage firm Nirmal Bang has issued a 'Buy' recommendation for Bharti Airtel, citing strong Average Revenue Per User (ARPU) of ₹256, robust 4G/5G subscriber growth, and expansion in digital and home segments. They have set a target price of ₹2,525 per share, indicating a potential 20% upside from current levels, driven by strategic investments in data centers and future growth prospects.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 05:23:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695607eb4342f77179f42c02_1767245920619.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Reliance Industries Stock Rockets Near All-Time High! See What's Driving This Massive 3% Rally!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Reliance-Industries-Stock-Rockets-Near-All-Time-High-See-Whats-Driving-This-Massive-3percent-Rally/695606d44342f77179f4254e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Reliance-Industries-Stock-Rockets-Near-All-Time-High-See-Whats-Driving-This-Massive-3percent-Rally/695606d44342f77179f4254e</guid><description>Reliance Industries (RIL) shares have rallied 3% in two days, hitting a 52-week high and nearing its all-time peak. Analysts from India Ratings and Research and BNP Paribas India are positive, citing strong cash flow generation from O2C and digital businesses, growth in Jio's ARPU, and expansion of Reliance Retail. RIL's new green energy ventures are also seen as promising. The stock has significantly outperformed the BSE Sensex over the past year.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 05:23:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695606d44342f77179f4254d_1767245676811.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hindustan Copper Shares Soar 3% on NSE Fine Exemption Hope – What Investors Need to Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Hindustan-Copper-Shares-Soar-3percent-on-NSE-Fine-Exemption-Hope-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/695607964342f77179f427e5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Hindustan-Copper-Shares-Soar-3percent-on-NSE-Fine-Exemption-Hope-What-Investors-Need-to-Know/695607964342f77179f427e5</guid><description>Hindustan Copper shares jumped 3.04% to ₹534.1 on NSE, driven by the company's announcement that its board will seek exemption from a ₹9.77 lakh fine imposed by the NSE. The fine was for non-compliance with SEBI LODR regulations regarding board composition for the September 2025 quarter. Hindustan Copper, a government company, is seeking the Ministry of Mines' intervention for this exemption.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 05:23:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695607964342f77179f427e4_1767246191824.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Somany Ceramics Target Slashed! Antique Sees Trouble Ahead, But Is There a Hidden Gem?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Somany-Ceramics-Target-Slashed-Antique-Sees-Trouble-Ahead-But-Is-There-a-Hidden-Gem/695606604342f77179f42128</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Somany-Ceramics-Target-Slashed-Antique-Sees-Trouble-Ahead-But-Is-There-a-Hidden-Gem/695606604342f77179f42128</guid><description>Antique Stock Broking has reduced its target price for Somany Ceramics Ltd. by cutting earnings estimates, citing concerns over slower volume growth and margin recovery. Despite near-term demand challenges, particularly in metro cities, the brokerage maintains a 'Buy' rating, believing the stock's attractive valuation outweighs current issues. Operations are normalizing, and a shift towards glazed vitrified tiles is expected to drive future growth.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 05:23:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695606604342f77179f42127_1767246129367.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rupee Plunges on New Year's Day: 11 Paise Lost Against Dollar Amid Outflows!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Plunges-on-New-Years-Day-11-Paise-Lost-Against-Dollar-Amid-Outflows/6956062a4342f77179f4200d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Rupee-Plunges-on-New-Years-Day-11-Paise-Lost-Against-Dollar-Amid-Outflows/6956062a4342f77179f4200d</guid><description>The Indian Rupee began 2026 on a weak note, depreciating by 11 paise to trade at 89.99 against the US dollar in early Thursday trade. This decline was primarily driven by persistent foreign fund outflows, although strong macroeconomic fundamentals and ample forex reserves offer some stability against global uncertainties.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 05:22:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956062a4342f77179f4200c_1767245487512.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Bubble Fears Fade: Is THIS Metal Poised for a Massive Crash? Investors Beware!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/AI-Bubble-Fears-Fade-Is-THIS-Metal-Poised-for-a-Massive-Crash-Investors-Beware/695605fc4342f77179f41f75</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/AI-Bubble-Fears-Fade-Is-THIS-Metal-Poised-for-a-Massive-Crash-Investors-Beware/695605fc4342f77179f41f75</guid><description>Silver has surged to an all-time high of $77.92, marking a 140% gain this year. However, Ned Davis Research warns the rally exhibits bubble-like characteristics and that the metal is overbought. A market correction is anticipated, suggesting potential risks for investors chasing the recent gains.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 05:22:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695605fc4342f77179f41f74_1767245881849.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IREDA Shares Soar on Massive Loan Growth! Investors Rejoice as Renewable Energy Giant Reports Stellar Q3 Update.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/IREDA-Shares-Soar-on-Massive-Loan-Growth-Investors-Rejoice-as-Renewable-Energy-Giant-Reports-Stellar-Q3-Update/695605ac4342f77179f41e79</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/IREDA-Shares-Soar-on-Massive-Loan-Growth-Investors-Rejoice-as-Renewable-Energy-Giant-Reports-Stellar-Q3-Update/695605ac4342f77179f41e79</guid><description>Indian Renewable Energy Development Agency (IREDA) shares gained 2% following a strong provisional Q3 FY26 business update. Loan disbursements surged 44% year-on-year to ₹24,903 crore, while sanctioned loans grew 29% year-on-year to ₹40,100 crore. The company's loan book also expanded by 28% YoY to ₹87,975 crore.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 05:18:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695605ac4342f77179f41e78_1767247550994.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Muthoot Microfin: Is This NBFC-MFI's Turnaround Story Just Beginning? Key Factors Revealed!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Muthoot-Microfin-Is-This-NBFC-MFIs-Turnaround-Story-Just-Beginning-Key-Factors-Revealed/6956050d4342f77179f41c31</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Muthoot-Microfin-Is-This-NBFC-MFIs-Turnaround-Story-Just-Beginning-Key-Factors-Revealed/6956050d4342f77179f41c31</guid><description>Muthoot Microfin is showing strong recovery signs in H1 FY26, with loan growth picking up and asset quality stabilizing. Analysts expect profitability to surge in H2 FY26 due to falling credit costs and lower funding expenses. With management's encouraging guidance and attractive valuations compared to peers, this micro-finance player presents a compelling recovery play for investors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 05:17:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6956050d4342f77179f41c30_1767245219428.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's UPI Records STUNNING December Highs: Rs 28 Lakh Crore In Digital Payments!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-UPI-Records-STUNNING-December-Highs-Rs-28-Lakh-Crore-In-Digital-Payments/695604f84342f77179f41bc4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-UPI-Records-STUNNING-December-Highs-Rs-28-Lakh-Crore-In-Digital-Payments/695604f84342f77179f41bc4</guid><description>Unified Payments Interface (UPI) achieved record highs in December 2025, processing 21.6 billion transactions worth ₹28 lakh crore. This caps a monumental year where annual volumes reached 228.3 billion transactions valued at ₹299.7 lakh crore. The average transaction size has decreased to ₹1,293, highlighting UPI's growing use for everyday small purchases, signaling deep digital penetration across India's retail and merchant payments landscape.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 05:17:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695604f84342f77179f41bc3_1767245131373.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra SUV Sales Skyrocket 23% in December! Demand Surge Fueled by Tax Cuts - Is This Just the Beginning?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Mahindra-and-Mahindra-SUV-Sales-Skyrocket-23percent-in-December-Demand-Surge-Fueled-by-Tax-Cuts-Is-This-Just-the-Beginning/695604494342f77179f419a5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Mahindra-and-Mahindra-SUV-Sales-Skyrocket-23percent-in-December-Demand-Surge-Fueled-by-Tax-Cuts-Is-This-Just-the-Beginning/695604494342f77179f419a5</guid><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra reported a strong 23% increase in its sports utility vehicle (SUV) sales to dealers in December. This significant growth is attributed to sustained demand, boosted by recent tax reductions on SUVs with engines above 1500 cc, which came into effect in September. The automotive giant's performance sets a positive tone as competitors like Maruti Suzuki, Hyundai India, and Tata Motors are yet to release their figures.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 05:13:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695604494342f77179f419a4_1767245138120.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mahindra SUVs Soar! 23% December Sales Surge Fueled by Tax Cuts - What Investors Need to Know NOW!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Mahindra-SUVs-Soar-23percent-December-Sales-Surge-Fueled-by-Tax-Cuts-What-Investors-Need-to-Know-NOW/695603e84342f77179f4188e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Mahindra-SUVs-Soar-23percent-December-Sales-Surge-Fueled-by-Tax-Cuts-What-Investors-Need-to-Know-NOW/695603e84342f77179f4188e</guid><description>Mahindra &amp; Mahindra reported a significant 23% year-on-year increase in December sales for its sports utility vehicles (SUVs) delivered to dealers. This strong performance is largely attributed to renewed demand after the Indian government reduced taxes on SUVs with engines exceeding 1500 cc in September. This policy change has positively impacted most of Mahindra's SUV lineup, boosting sales figures for the month. Major competitors like Maruti Suzuki, Hyundai India, and Tata Motors have yet to announce their December sales data.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 05:12:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695603e84342f77179f4188d_1767244848841.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold &amp; Silver Set for Bullish Surge: Expert Forecasts Massive New Year Rally! See Price Targets Now!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-Set-for-Bullish-Surge-Expert-Forecasts-Massive-New-Year-Rally-See-Price-Targets-Now/695603814342f77179f41711</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-and-Silver-Set-for-Bullish-Surge-Expert-Forecasts-Massive-New-Year-Rally-See-Price-Targets-Now/695603814342f77179f41711</guid><description>Experts predict gold and silver prices will continue their bullish trend in the New Year, with dips acting as buying opportunities. MCX Gold is expected to target 140,000, supported at 132,000. MCX Silver could advance to 260,000, with support at 221,000. The overall sentiment remains positive, favoring trend continuation.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 05:07:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_695603814342f77179f41710_1767246905815.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vodafone Idea Skyrockets? Rs 15 Target After HUGE Govt Relief Package!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vodafone-Idea-Skyrockets-Rs-15-Target-After-HUGE-Govt-Relief-Package/6955feac4342f77179f40ae0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vodafone-Idea-Skyrockets-Rs-15-Target-After-HUGE-Govt-Relief-Package/6955feac4342f77179f40ae0</guid><description>Vodafone Idea shares are expected to see action after the Union Cabinet approved a major relief package. The government has frozen Adjusted Gross Revenue (AGR) dues at ₹87,695 crore, rescheduling payments until FY41. Additionally, analyst Kunal Bothra initiated a BUY rating with a ₹15 target price, influencing investor sentiment for the debt-laden telecom operator.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:49:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955feac4342f77179f40adf_1767243502961.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shockwave Hits Tobacco Stocks! Govt Tax Hike Triggers Massive Sell-off - What Investors MUST Know!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Shockwave-Hits-Tobacco-Stocks-Govt-Tax-Hike-Triggers-Massive-Sell-off-What-Investors-MUST-Know/6955fe674342f77179f40a19</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Shockwave-Hits-Tobacco-Stocks-Govt-Tax-Hike-Triggers-Massive-Sell-off-What-Investors-MUST-Know/6955fe674342f77179f40a19</guid><description>Godfrey Phillips India and ITC shares plunged today after the government notified a significant hike in excise duty on cigarettes and tobacco products, set to take effect from February 1, 2026. The new measure includes a 40% GST, prompting concerns about potential price increases and future tax burdens for investors.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:48:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955fe674342f77179f40a18_1767243439688.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vodafone Idea Surges 4% on Rs 5,836 Crore Payout and Potential Govt AGR Moratorium!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vodafone-Idea-Surges-4percent-on-Rs-5836-Crore-Payout-and-Potential-Govt-AGR-Moratorium/6955fd594342f77179f40763</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/Vodafone-Idea-Surges-4percent-on-Rs-5836-Crore-Payout-and-Potential-Govt-AGR-Moratorium/6955fd594342f77179f40763</guid><description>Vodafone Idea shares jumped over 4% on January 1 following news that it will receive approximately ₹5,836 crore from Vodafone Group as part of a revised settlement agreement. Additionally, reports suggest the Union Cabinet may have approved a five-year moratorium on the company's Adjusted Gross Revenue (AGR) dues, offering significant financial breathing room.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:44:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955fd594342f77179f40762_1767243162513.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Business Shock: Commercial LPG Jumps ₹111! Airlines Get Relief as ATF Prices Drop</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Business-Shock-Commercial-LPG-Jumps-111-Airlines-Get-Relief-as-ATF-Prices-Drop/6955fca94342f77179f40554</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Business-Shock-Commercial-LPG-Jumps-111-Airlines-Get-Relief-as-ATF-Prices-Drop/6955fca94342f77179f40554</guid><description>On the first day of 2026, commercial LPG cylinder prices surged by ₹111 across major Indian metros, significantly increasing operating costs for hotels, restaurants, and service businesses. However, domestic LPG rates remained unchanged. In contrast, Aviation Turbine Fuel (ATF) prices saw a decrease, offering relief to airlines struggling with elevated costs.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:40:41 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955fca94342f77179f40553_1767243012807.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Defence Production Surges Past FY26 Target: Record Growth &amp; Exports Signal Manufacturing Boom!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Indias-Defence-Production-Surges-Past-FY26-Target-Record-Growth-and-Exports-Signal-Manufacturing-Boom/6955fc174342f77179f4038c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Indias-Defence-Production-Surges-Past-FY26-Target-Record-Growth-and-Exports-Signal-Manufacturing-Boom/6955fc174342f77179f4038c</guid><description>India's defence production is set to surpass its fiscal year 2026 target of ₹1.75 lakh crore, achieving an all-time high of ₹1.54 lakh crore in FY25 with 18% growth. Indigenous production reached ₹1.27 lakh crore in FY24, and exports hit a record ₹23,622 crore in FY25. The private sector's participation has significantly increased to 23%, supported by government reforms and substantial capital acquisition approvals, positioning India for ambitious long-term defence manufacturing goals.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:38:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955fc174342f77179f4038b_1767244761073.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Mid-Tier Banks Lagging? Elara Capital Reveals Top Picks for Bigger Gains!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Mid-Tier-Banks-Lagging-Elara-Capital-Reveals-Top-Picks-for-Bigger-Gains/6955f8b44342f77179f3f7ed</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Mid-Tier-Banks-Lagging-Elara-Capital-Reveals-Top-Picks-for-Bigger-Gains/6955f8b44342f77179f3f7ed</guid><description>Elara Capital predicts a slower valuation increase for mid-tier private banks due to stretched valuations. The firm favors large private lenders like ICICI Bank and Kotak Mahindra Bank, citing their stronger earnings resilience and attractive prices. State Bank of India is preferred among public sector banks, though sustained re-rating may take longer. Elara emphasizes the critical role of a strong liability franchise for success in FY27 amid rising competition and deposit cost pressures.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:16:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955f8b44342f77179f3f7ec_1767242002317.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cement Stocks Surge? PL Capital Initiates Coverage with Major 'Buy' Ratings and Bullish Targets!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cement-Stocks-Surge-PL-Capital-Initiates-Coverage-with-Major-Buy-Ratings-and-Bullish-Targets/6955f7ae4342f77179f3f26b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cement-Stocks-Surge-PL-Capital-Initiates-Coverage-with-Major-Buy-Ratings-and-Bullish-Targets/6955f7ae4342f77179f3f26b</guid><description>PL Capital has initiated coverage on JK Cement, JK Lakshmi Cement, and JSW Cement, assigning 'Accumulate' or 'Buy' ratings with attractive price targets. The brokerage anticipates a 6.5% CAGR in cement demand over three years, driven by rural housing, though industry capacity expansion might cap utilization rates below 70%.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:16:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955f7ae4342f77179f3f26a_1767241729761.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Market Magic! Indian Stocks Start Year with Major Rally: Sensex &amp; Nifty Soar!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Market-Magic-Indian-Stocks-Start-Year-with-Major-Rally-Sensex-and-Nifty-Soar/6955f7b34342f77179f3f298</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Market-Magic-Indian-Stocks-Start-Year-with-Major-Rally-Sensex-and-Nifty-Soar/6955f7b34342f77179f3f298</guid><description>Indian stock markets began the year on a high note, with early trading seeing significant gains. The benchmark Sensex climbed 223.54 points, reaching 85,444.14, while the Nifty index rose by 65.75 points to trade at 26,195.35. This positive start suggests investor confidence early in the trading year.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:15:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955f7b34342f77179f3f297_1767241748389.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Kalpataru Projects Lands Mega ₹719 Crore Thane Metro Order – Stock Surges!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kalpataru-Projects-Lands-Mega-719-Crore-Thane-Metro-Order-Stock-Surges/6955f6f44342f77179f3f02a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kalpataru-Projects-Lands-Mega-719-Crore-Thane-Metro-Order-Stock-Surges/6955f6f44342f77179f3f02a</guid><description>Kalpataru Projects International Ltd. shares rose after securing new orders worth ₹719 crore for the Thane Metro elevated rail project. The company highlighted this order win as strengthening its position in the urban transportation EPC business in India. Management expressed confidence in achieving growth targets due to a strong order book and robust execution, despite ongoing challenges with payments in the Jal Jeevan Mission.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:15:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955f6f44342f77179f3f029_1767245368060.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ITC Stock CRASHES! 21-Month Low Hit as India Slaps Massive Tax Hike on Cigarettes!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ITC-Stock-CRASHES-21-Month-Low-Hit-as-India-Slaps-Massive-Tax-Hike-on-Cigarettes/6955f6984342f77179f3ef5c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/ITC-Stock-CRASHES-21-Month-Low-Hit-as-India-Slaps-Massive-Tax-Hike-on-Cigarettes/6955f6984342f77179f3ef5c</guid><description>ITC shares plummeted to a 21-month low on Thursday, January 1, after the Finance Ministry announced a 40% Goods and Services Tax (GST) on cigarettes and tobacco products, effective February 1, 2026. This move, which includes subsuming excise duties, comes alongside a significant block deal where over 4 crore shares traded at ₹400 each, totaling ₹1,614.5 crore.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:15:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955f6984342f77179f3ef5b_1767241477030.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Health Insurance Revolution: Insurers Prioritize YOU with Preventive Care &amp; Big Savings!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indias-Health-Insurance-Revolution-Insurers-Prioritize-YOU-with-Preventive-Care-and-Big-Savings/6955f6f74342f77179f3f055</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Indias-Health-Insurance-Revolution-Insurers-Prioritize-YOU-with-Preventive-Care-and-Big-Savings/6955f6f74342f77179f3f055</guid><description>Indian health insurers, led by Mayank Bathwal of Aditya Birla Health Insurance, are shifting focus from just hospital stays to preventive care. With over 60% of healthcare costs still out-of-pocket for households, this move aims to make everyday health expenses predictable and reduce costly hospitalizations. Innovations in digital platforms and wellness rewards are key to making insurance more accessible and trusted.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:15:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955f6f74342f77179f3f054_1767242583027.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Midcap Stocks Poised for Explosive Growth? Up to 40% Revenue Surge Forecasted for FY26!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Midcap-Stocks-Poised-for-Explosive-Growth-Up-to-40percent-Revenue-Surge-Forecasted-for-FY26/6955f5594342f77179f3eca3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Midcap-Stocks-Poised-for-Explosive-Growth-Up-to-40percent-Revenue-Surge-Forecasted-for-FY26/6955f5594342f77179f3eca3</guid><description>In a market where bargains are scarce, investors are scrutinizing management guidance. This analysis highlights midcap stocks offering revenue growth forecasts of up to 40% for FY26. Companies like Netweb Technologies India, Genus Power Infrastructures, Waaree Renewable Technologies, Krishna Defence and Allied Industries, and Shakti Pumps are identified, showcasing strong performance and clear growth signals backed by recent results and solid order books.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:10:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955f5594342f77179f3eca2_1767241114146.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>New Year, New Rally? Indian Markets Kick Off 2026 with a Bang! What Experts Predict Next!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/New-Year-New-Rally-Indian-Markets-Kick-Off-2026-with-a-Bang-What-Experts-Predict-Next/6955f35f4342f77179f3e67a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/New-Year-New-Rally-Indian-Markets-Kick-Off-2026-with-a-Bang-What-Experts-Predict-Next/6955f35f4342f77179f3e67a</guid><description>Indian stock markets, including Nifty50 and BSE Sensex, began the first trading day of 2026 on a positive note, opening in green. Nifty50 surpassed 26,150 while BSE Sensex rose over 100 points. Experts anticipate measured market gains throughout 2026, fueled by improving corporate earnings, increased private capital expenditure, and supportive government policies. Despite mixed global signals and net selling by foreign investors, domestic institutional investors provided market support.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 04:00:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955f35f4342f77179f3e679_1767240609606.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Auto Stocks Surge as December Sales Jump 67%! SML Mahindra Leads Charge – Is Your Portfolio Ready?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Auto-Stocks-Surge-as-December-Sales-Jump-67percent-SML-Mahindra-Leads-Charge-Is-Your-Portfolio-Ready/6955eeac4342f77179f3dba8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Auto-Stocks-Surge-as-December-Sales-Jump-67percent-SML-Mahindra-Leads-Charge-Is-Your-Portfolio-Ready/6955eeac4342f77179f3dba8</guid><description>December auto sales for 2025 showed robust growth, with SML Mahindra reporting a 67% year-on-year increase to 1,044 units, driven by strong cargo and passenger vehicle sales. VAHAN data indicated a 9% overall registration rise in December, though two-wheelers lagged. Key players like Maruti Suzuki and Mahindra &amp; Mahindra are set to launch new models in January 2026, while the Nifty Auto index ended 2025 with a significant 21.8% gain.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 03:42:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955eeac4342f77179f3dba7_1767239415384.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global Markets Shut, But India's Dalal Street OPEN on New Year's Day 2026! Traders Rejoice!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Global-Markets-Shut-But-Indias-Dalal-Street-OPEN-on-New-Years-Day-2026-Traders-Rejoice/6955ee624342f77179f3db05</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/Global-Markets-Shut-But-Indias-Dalal-Street-OPEN-on-New-Years-Day-2026-Traders-Rejoice/6955ee624342f77179f3db05</guid><description>Indian stock markets, including the Bombay Stock Exchange (BSE) and National Stock Exchange (NSE), will operate as usual on New Year's Day, January 1, 2026. This contrasts sharply with most global equity markets which will remain closed. Commodity markets will also be functional during daytime hours, though evening sessions are suspended. Investors can plan accordingly, as exchanges have released the full 2026 holiday calendar listing 15 trading holidays.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 03:39:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955ee624342f77179f3db04_1767239341510.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Factories Roar Back: Will November's Record Surge Ignite a 2026 Turnaround?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Factories-Roar-Back-Will-Novembers-Record-Surge-Ignite-a-2026-Turnaround/6955edc74342f77179f3d9ea</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Factories-Roar-Back-Will-Novembers-Record-Surge-Ignite-a-2026-Turnaround/6955edc74342f77179f3d9ea</guid><description>India's industrial production surged 6.7% year-on-year in November 2025, its highest since October 2023, with manufacturing up 8%. Capital goods and consumer goods also showed strong growth, and only three manufacturing sectors contracted. However, consumer durables show long-term stagnation, and the sustainability of consumption demand and capital expenditure is key. A new IIP series in 2026 will provide a clearer picture of India's industrial future.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 03:37:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955edc74342f77179f3d9e9_1767239181473.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global Giants Unleash $15 Trillion: Tech's Next Big Boom Ignited!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Global-Giants-Unleash-15-Trillion-Techs-Next-Big-Boom-Ignited/6955e99d4342f77179f3cd96</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Global-Giants-Unleash-15-Trillion-Techs-Next-Big-Boom-Ignited/6955e99d4342f77179f3cd96</guid><description>Global sovereign wealth funds (SWFs) reached a record $15 trillion in assets under management in 2025. They significantly increased technology investments, ploughing $66 billion into artificial intelligence and digitalization. Middle Eastern SWFs, including Abu Dhabi's Mubadala Investment Co., Kuwait Investment Authority, and Qatar Investment Authority, led this surge. The United States emerged as the primary destination for these substantial state-owned investments.</description><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 03:10:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_6955e99d4342f77179f3cd95_1767238168317.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>