<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:43:10 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Embassy REIT Leases Surge, But Growth Hinges on Development</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Embassy-REIT-Leases-Surge-But-Growth-Hinges-on-Development/698633d304125efaa8b09728</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Embassy-REIT-Leases-Surge-But-Growth-Hinges-on-Development/698633d304125efaa8b09728</guid><description>Embassy Office Parks REIT reported its strongest quarter ending December 2025, with record revenue of ₹1,193 crore and Net Operating Income (NOI) of ₹985 crore, driven by 1.1 million sq ft of leasing and 17% re-leasing spreads. The REIT is strategically expanding its portfolio through acquisitions and development projects, signaling a focus on future growth drivers beyond current market recovery. Despite robust performance, challenges from rising interest costs and competition persist, as indicated by analyst sentiment and peer valuations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:32:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Purple Finance Eyes ₹693 Cr Capital Infusion, Diversifies into Mutual Funds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Purple-Finance-Eyes-693-Cr-Capital-Infusion-Diversifies-into-Mutual-Funds/698633bc04125efaa8b09606</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Purple-Finance-Eyes-693-Cr-Capital-Infusion-Diversifies-into-Mutual-Funds/698633bc04125efaa8b09606</guid><description>Purple Finance Limited is seeking shareholder approval for a significant corporate restructuring. The company plans to raise ₹693 crore through a preferential issue of convertible warrants to bolster its capital base for growth and lending activities. In a strategic diversification move, it aims to enter the mutual fund distribution business. The capital raise will also trigger a mandatory open offer for up to 26% of its expanded share capital, potentially impacting existing shareholders and the promoter group.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:32:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RBI Holds Rates Steady; Banks Cheer, MSMEs Face Borrowing Pain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Holds-Rates-Steady-Banks-Cheer-MSMEs-Face-Borrowing-Pain/698633aa04125efaa8b09530</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Holds-Rates-Steady-Banks-Cheer-MSMEs-Face-Borrowing-Pain/698633aa04125efaa8b09530</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has opted to maintain its benchmark repo rate at 5.25%, a decision largely anticipated and welcomed by major banking institutions. Governor Sanjay Malhotra highlighted regulatory and developmental policies aimed at enhancing customer protection, digital payments, and MSME support. However, a dissenting view emerged from CapitalXB, which expressed disappointment, arguing the conservative rate stance ignores the severe impact of high borrowing costs on Indian entrepreneurs and small businesses, especially given inflation's multi-year lows. The RBI also projected a robust GDP growth of 7.4% for FY26, while keeping inflation expectations at a low 2.1%.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:32:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Budget 2026: Interest Deduction on Investment Loans Ends</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Budget-2026-Interest-Deduction-on-Investment-Loans-Ends/6986335d04125efaa8b093be</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Budget-2026-Interest-Deduction-on-Investment-Loans-Ends/6986335d04125efaa8b093be</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 proposes a significant shift in investment taxation by disallowing interest deductions on loans used for acquiring shares and mutual fund units. This move marks a departure from previous tax principles, aiming to curb tax arbitrage and tax investment income on a gross basis.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:30:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Multi-Asset Funds: Diversification's Manager Risk Illusion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Multi-Asset-Funds-Diversifications-Manager-Risk-Illusion/6986334b04125efaa8b09305</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Multi-Asset-Funds-Diversifications-Manager-Risk-Illusion/6986334b04125efaa8b09305</guid><description>In an uncertain global economic climate, multi-asset funds are marketed as robust portfolio anchors. While they blend equities, debt, and gold for stability, their effectiveness is critically tied to fund manager allocation expertise. The recent parabolic rise in gold prices introduces significant concentration risk, potentially overshadowing the intended diversification benefits. Investors must look beyond the asset mix to scrutinize manager decision-making and mandate specifics.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:30:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Excelsoft Technologies Posts Strong Nine-Month Growth, IPO Funds Allocated</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Excelsoft-Technologies-Posts-Strong-Nine-Month-Growth-IPO-Funds-Allocated/6986333204125efaa8b0923c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Excelsoft-Technologies-Posts-Strong-Nine-Month-Growth-IPO-Funds-Allocated/6986333204125efaa8b0923c</guid><description>Excelsoft Technologies announced strong financial results for the nine months ended December 31, 2025, with consolidated revenue up 17.13% YoY to ₹1,913.59 million and consolidated profit after tax surging 88.38% YoY to ₹267.81 million. Q3FY26 consolidated revenue grew 29.45% YoY to ₹710.34 million, though PAT saw a more modest 7.67% YoY increase to ₹102.96 million, impacted by exceptional items related to new Labour Codes. The company detailed its IPO proceeds utilization plan, allocating over ₹1.6 billion towards capital expenditure and facility upgrades, with ₹1,267.88 million remaining unutilized.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:30:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lemon Tree Hotels Posts Record Revenue, Eyes Margin Boost Post-FY28</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Lemon-Tree-Hotels-Posts-Record-Revenue-Eyes-Margin-Boost-Post-FY28/698632ea04125efaa8b084f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Lemon-Tree-Hotels-Posts-Record-Revenue-Eyes-Margin-Boost-Post-FY28/698632ea04125efaa8b084f9</guid><description>Lemon Tree Hotels reported its highest-ever Q3 revenue and EBITDA, up 15% and 12% YoY respectively. Despite a 2% PAT increase, EBITDA margins dipped 133 bps due to investments and GST. The company added 1,855 rooms to its pipeline and opened 816 rooms in Q3, focusing on asset-light expansion. Management projects margin recovery by FY28 as cost pressures ease.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:28:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Dish TV India Faces Existential Threat from ₹7,203 Cr Levy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Dish-TV-India-Faces-Existential-Threat-from-7203-Cr-Levy/698632d304125efaa8b08413</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/Dish-TV-India-Faces-Existential-Threat-from-7203-Cr-Levy/698632d304125efaa8b08413</guid><description>Dish TV India Limited is confronting an immediate existential challenge with a fresh ₹7,203 crore license fee demand from the Ministry of Information and Broadcasting, which includes substantial interest. This demand exacerbates the company's already precarious financial state, marked by accumulated losses exceeding equity, significant asset impairments, and a negative net worth. Despite ongoing legal disputes and declining revenues, the company asserts its ability to continue operations on a going concern basis, though its financial footing remains highly uncertain.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:28:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>KPIT Tech Posts 9.4% Revenue Growth, Eyes AI-Led Solutions for Future</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/KPIT-Tech-Posts-94percent-Revenue-Growth-Eyes-AI-Led-Solutions-for-Future/698632c004125efaa8b08373</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/KPIT-Tech-Posts-94percent-Revenue-Growth-Eyes-AI-Led-Solutions-for-Future/698632c004125efaa8b08373</guid><description>KPIT Technologies reported a 9.4% year-on-year revenue growth in Q3 FY'26 to ₹[revenue_value] billion, with EBITDA up 6.8%. However, net profit remained flat quarter-on-quarter at ₹1.53 billion after excluding a one-time labor code impact of ₹469 million. The company declared an interim dividend and maintains a cash reserve of ₹9 billion. Management forecasts Q4 FY'26 as the highest growth quarter with improved profitability, driven by a strategic pivot towards AI, agentic solutions, and specialized automotive segments, supported by recent acquisitions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:28:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Shifts Deposit Insurance to Risk-Based Premiums</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Shifts-Deposit-Insurance-to-Risk-Based-Premiums/6986327904125efaa8b07609</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Shifts-Deposit-Insurance-to-Risk-Based-Premiums/6986327904125efaa8b07609</guid><description>Effective April 1, 2026, India will implement a risk-based premium (RBP) framework for deposit insurance, replacing the long-standing flat-rate system. The Deposit Insurance and Credit Guarantee Corporation (DICGC), with Reserve Bank of India approval, aims to align insurance costs with a bank's risk profile. This reform is expected to encourage robust risk management practices by penalizing riskier institutions with higher premiums and rewarding stronger ones with lower costs. The framework introduces tiered assessment models and includes incentives for long-standing contributions. Certain banks, like local area and payment banks, will retain the flat rate due to data limitations. This move signals a maturation of the Indian banking sector towards greater accountability and systemic stability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:27:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Kalpataru IPO Funds Use Verified by CARE Ratings; Debt Paid Early</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kalpataru-IPO-Funds-Use-Verified-by-CARE-Ratings-Debt-Paid-Early/6986326904125efaa8b06934</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kalpataru-IPO-Funds-Use-Verified-by-CARE-Ratings-Debt-Paid-Early/6986326904125efaa8b06934</guid><description>Kalpataru Limited's IPO proceeds of Rs. 1,590 crore have been monitored by CARE Ratings, confirming utilization aligns with its Offer Document. The company fully utilized Rs. 1,192.50 crore for debt repayment ahead of schedule. While Rs. 166.24 crore was deployed for General Corporate Purposes (GCP) during the quarter, an internal report inconsistency regarding GCP totals warrants attention. Rs. 54.82 crore was spent on issue expenses, leaving Rs. 168.77 crore unutilized overall as of December 31, 2025.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:26:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RBI Holds Rates, But Bond Market Eyes Liquidity Over Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Holds-Rates-But-Bond-Market-Eyes-Liquidity-Over-Growth/6986324504125efaa8b05c9a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Holds-Rates-But-Bond-Market-Eyes-Liquidity-Over-Growth/6986324504125efaa8b05c9a</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's Monetary Policy Committee maintained its repo rate at 5.25% and a neutral stance, projecting strong FY27 GDP growth at 6.9% and 7.0% for Q1/Q2. However, bond markets reacted negatively, with G-sec yields hardening as investors scrutinized the central bank's liquidity management strategy amidst significant government borrowing and global uncertainties. Enhanced MSME loan limits and digital fraud compensation measures were also announced.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:26:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Mfg Ambition Faces Trade Tightrope: FTAs vs. Scale</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Mfg-Ambition-Faces-Trade-Tightrope-FTAs-vs-Scale/698631f804125efaa8b0434d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Mfg-Ambition-Faces-Trade-Tightrope-FTAs-vs-Scale/698631f804125efaa8b0434d</guid><description>India aims to elevate manufacturing's GDP contribution from 17% to 25%, leveraging new FTAs with the EU and US alongside budget measures. While the EU trade deal promises significant export growth, the US agreement faces scrutiny for potentially harming Indian exports. Experts caution that achieving scale, particularly for MSMEs, and managing import competition, especially from China, remain critical hurdles. The strategy balances boosting tech-intensive sectors with labor-intensive ones, but the path to enhanced global competitiveness is fraught with geopolitical and economic complexities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:24:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Reliance Infra Shares Plunge as ED Attaches Subsidiaries Worth ₹1,575 Crore</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Reliance-Infra-Shares-Plunge-as-ED-Attaches-Subsidiaries-Worth-1575-Crore/698631d804125efaa8b03650</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Reliance-Infra-Shares-Plunge-as-ED-Attaches-Subsidiaries-Worth-1575-Crore/698631d804125efaa8b03650</guid><description>Reliance Infrastructure Limited has disclosed receipt of a Provisional Attachment Order from the Enforcement Directorate (ED) on January 28, 2026. The order provisionally attaches the company's shareholding in subsidiaries BSES Yamuna Power Limited, BSES Rajdhani Power Limited, and Mumbai Metro One Private Limited, valued at approximately ₹1,575 crore. The ED cited alleged violations of the Prevention of Money Laundering Act (PMLA) between 2017-2019. R-Infra is consulting legal counsel and will take steps to protect shareholder interests.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:24:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RBI Sees Strong Growth, Low Rates Amidst Global Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Sees-Strong-Growth-Low-Rates-Amidst-Global-Risks/698631cc04125efaa8b02a1a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Sees-Strong-Growth-Low-Rates-Amidst-Global-Risks/698631cc04125efaa8b02a1a</guid><description>Reserve Bank of India Governor Sanjay Malhotra projected an improving Indian economy, citing robust growth and controlled inflation, while signaling continued low policy rates. The central bank revised GDP forecasts upward by 20 basis points. However, significant government borrowing plans, though deemed manageable by the RBI, have caused some market jitters, with bond yields hardening. The recent US-India trade deal and insurance sector reforms are seen as positive catalysts, but global economic uncertainties and trade shifts remain factors to monitor.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:24:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Lemon Tree Restructures, Q3 PAT Dips 18.75% Amidst One-Off Costs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Lemon-Tree-Restructures-Q3-PAT-Dips-1875percent-Amidst-One-Off-Costs/6986318404125efaa8b0247d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Lemon-Tree-Restructures-Q3-PAT-Dips-1875percent-Amidst-One-Off-Costs/6986318404125efaa8b0247d</guid><description>Lemon Tree Hotels announced its Q3 FY26 results, showcasing robust underlying performance with Profit Before Exceptional Items and Tax surging 61.69% standalone and 133.19% consolidated YoY. However, reported Net Profit After Tax (PAT) saw a decline of 18.75% standalone and a marginal 2.49% rise consolidated, heavily influenced by significant exceptional items totaling ₹18.78 Cr standalone and ₹31.33 Cr consolidated. These included adjustments for new Labour Codes, ex-gratia payments, property tax settlement, and restructuring expenses. Concurrently, the Board approved a Composite Scheme of Arrangement to demerge the hotel ownership and development business into a separate entity, "Fleur Hotels," while retaining the hotel management and brand business under Lemon Tree, aiming to create focused platforms and unlock value.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:23:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RBI Lifts Debt Cap: India Bond Market Poised for Inflow Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Lifts-Debt-Cap-India-Bond-Market-Poised-for-Inflow-Surge/6986316604125efaa8b02374</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Lifts-Debt-Cap-India-Bond-Market-Poised-for-Inflow-Surge/6986316604125efaa8b02374</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has abolished the ₹2.5 trillion investment ceiling for foreign portfolio investors (FPIs) via the Voluntary Retention Route (VRR). This significant policy adjustment is designed to deepen India's domestic bond markets and attract more stable, long-term capital. By removing the cap, investments will now adhere to general security ceilings, offering foreign investors greater flexibility. This move, coupled with proposed derivative frameworks for corporate bonds, aims to enhance market liquidity, improve risk management, and potentially translate into more accessible and efficiently priced credit for businesses, including MSMEs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:22:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Pee Safe Secures $32M for Profitable Expansion into New Wellness Frontiers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Pee-Safe-Secures-32M-for-Profitable-Expansion-into-New-Wellness-Frontiers/6986314f04125efaa8b0230a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Pee-Safe-Secures-32M-for-Profitable-Expansion-into-New-Wellness-Frontiers/6986314f04125efaa8b0230a</guid><description>Pee Safe has secured $32 million in Series C funding, led by OrbiMed, to accelerate its expansion in offline retail and quick commerce. The women's hygiene and wellness brand, currently generating over ₹150 crore in annualized revenue and operating profitably, plans to deepen its market penetration across India and internationally. A key strategic focus includes expanding its product portfolio into the menopause-related category, leveraging a favorable regulatory environment and growing consumer demand for comprehensive women's health solutions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:22:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Spending Spree Sparks Tech Valuation Jitters; India Holds Steady</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Spending-Spree-Sparks-Tech-Valuation-Jitters-India-Holds-Steady/698630fb04125efaa8b02184</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/AI-Spending-Spree-Sparks-Tech-Valuation-Jitters-India-Holds-Steady/698630fb04125efaa8b02184</guid><description>Global markets are unsettled by US tech giants' unprecedented AI capital expenditure, leading to valuation strains. Amazon alone pledges $200 billion, pushing combined outlays for Alphabet, Meta, and Microsoft near $660 billion. Despite this, Indian equities demonstrate resilience, with the Sensex and Nifty posting gains. The Reserve Bank of India maintained its repo rate at 5.25%, simultaneously revising GDP growth forecasts upwards to 7.4% for FY26 and projecting inflation at 2.1%. This domestic stability contrasts sharply with a global outlook clouded by escalating US layoffs and concerns over AI's disruptive impact on traditional software businesses, which triggered a significant sell-off in the Nifty IT index.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:20:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Prataap Snacks Posts Profit Turnaround, Eyes Growth with ₹425 Cr Plant Amid Fire Setback</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Prataap-Snacks-Posts-Profit-Turnaround-Eyes-Growth-with-425-Cr-Plant-Amid-Fire-Setback/698630e904125efaa8b0208c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Prataap-Snacks-Posts-Profit-Turnaround-Eyes-Growth-with-425-Cr-Plant-Amid-Fire-Setback/698630e904125efaa8b0208c</guid><description>Prataap Snacks Limited reported a significant turnaround in its Q3 FY26 results, posting a net profit of ₹3.25 Cr against a loss of ₹37.93 Cr last year, with revenue up 3.7% to ₹459.25 Cr. The company announced a major ₹425 Cr investment for a new Indore plant and detailed a ₹34.34 Cr loss from a Jammu plant fire.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:20:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Purple Finance on Radar: Acquirers Announce Substantial Stake Bid</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Purple-Finance-on-Radar-Acquirers-Announce-Substantial-Stake-Bid/698630da04125efaa8b01fb6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Purple-Finance-on-Radar-Acquirers-Announce-Substantial-Stake-Bid/698630da04125efaa8b01fb6</guid><description>Purple Finance Limited has been notified of a Public Announcement by Allied Commodities Private Limited and Mr. Sandeep Jindal regarding a substantial acquisition. The move, made in accordance with SEBI's Takeover Regulations, involves parties acting in concert including Intellect Stock Broking Limited and others. This signals a potential change in shareholding or control, prompting regulatory scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:20:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Prataap Snacks Hits Record Revenue, Turns Profitable, Plans ₹425 Cr Plant</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Prataap-Snacks-Hits-Record-Revenue-Turns-Profitable-Plans-425-Cr-Plant/6986308f04125efaa8b01de5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Prataap-Snacks-Hits-Record-Revenue-Turns-Profitable-Plans-425-Cr-Plant/6986308f04125efaa8b01de5</guid><description>Prataap Snacks Limited (PSL) reported its highest-ever quarterly revenue of ₹461.6 crore in Q3 FY26, marking a 3.8% year-on-year growth. The company achieved a significant turnaround in profitability, with PAT turning positive to ₹5.7 crore from a loss last year. Operating EBITDA improved to ₹20.3 crore. Despite margin contraction due to input costs and strategic investments in quick commerce, PSL's board approved a ₹425 crore state-of-the-art manufacturing facility near Indore to boost capacity and efficiency.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:18:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RBI's Risk-Based Insurance: Banks Face New Premium Reality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-Risk-Based-Insurance-Banks-Face-New-Premium-Reality/6986307804125efaa8b01d59</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-Risk-Based-Insurance-Banks-Face-New-Premium-Reality/6986307804125efaa8b01d59</guid><description>Effective April 1, 2026, the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) will transition deposit insurance premiums to a risk-based framework, replacing the long-standing flat-rate system. Banks will be categorized into risk tiers (A-D), with premiums ranging from 8 to 12 paise per ₹100 assessable deposits, offering up to a 33.3% discount to well-managed institutions. This significant regulatory shift aims to incentivize sound risk management, potentially widening the performance gap between stronger and weaker banks and bolstering the stability of the Deposit Insurance and Credit Guarantee Corporation (DICGC) fund, even as the overall insured deposit ratio has declined.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:18:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Rajasthan Syntex Faces Going Concern Doubt Despite Reduced Losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Rajasthan-Syntex-Faces-Going-Concern-Doubt-Despite-Reduced-Losses/6986306304125efaa8b01c68</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Rajasthan-Syntex-Faces-Going-Concern-Doubt-Despite-Reduced-Losses/6986306304125efaa8b01c68</guid><description>Shree Rajasthan Syntex reported a 3.8% YoY revenue rise to ₹3.52 Crore but a net loss of ₹2.22 Crore for Q3 FY26. Crucially, auditors flagged a 'material uncertainty related to going concern' due to accumulated losses and high liabilities. The company completed a PPIRP and plans investor funding to continue operations. Net loss reduction was 38% YoY.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:18:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>JK Tyre Posts Stellar Q3 Results, PAT Surges 264% on Margin Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/JK-Tyre-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Results-PAT-Surges-264percent-on-Margin-Gains/6986301504125efaa8b01b24</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/JK-Tyre-Posts-Stellar-Q3-Results-PAT-Surges-264percent-on-Margin-Gains/6986301504125efaa8b01b24</guid><description>JK Tyre &amp; Industries Ltd. reported robust financial performance in Q3 FY26, with consolidated PAT soaring 264% YoY to ₹209 Crore. Total income rose 15% to ₹4,235 Crore, driven by a significant 74% EBITDA jump and 4.7 percentage point margin expansion to 13.8%. The company also highlighted its new EV and smart tyre offerings and strong ESG commitments, signaling future growth potential.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:16:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>IITM &amp; UIV Launch ₹600Cr Deep Tech Fund for India's Sovereignty</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/IITM-and-UIV-Launch-600Cr-Deep-Tech-Fund-for-Indias-Sovereignty/69862ff804125efaa8b019d7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/IITM-and-UIV-Launch-600Cr-Deep-Tech-Fund-for-Indias-Sovereignty/69862ff804125efaa8b019d7</guid><description>IIT Madras Research Park (IITMRP) and Unicorn India Ventures (UIV) have launched the 'IIT Madras Unicorn Frontier Fund I', a ₹600 crore initiative to propel India's deep technology sector. With a ₹400 crore greenshoe option, the fund targets over 25 early-stage startups focused on areas like AI, semiconductors, and defense tech. Directors V. Kamakoti and CEO Natarajan Malupillai emphasized the fund's role in achieving technological sovereignty and accelerating indigenous innovation, marking a significant step in bridging academic research with industrial application.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:16:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Embassy REIT Hits Record Revenue, Boosts NOI Amidst Expansion Drive</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Embassy-REIT-Hits-Record-Revenue-Boosts-NOI-Amidst-Expansion-Drive/69862feb04125efaa8b0191e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Embassy-REIT-Hits-Record-Revenue-Boosts-NOI-Amidst-Expansion-Drive/69862feb04125efaa8b0191e</guid><description>Embassy Office Parks REIT (Embassy REIT) reported its strongest-ever quarterly performance, with revenue soaring 17% YoY to ₹1,193 crores and Net Operating Income (NOI) jumping 19% YoY to ₹985 crores for Q3 FY2026. The REIT declared distributions of ₹613 crores (+10% YoY). Key growth drivers include leasing 1.1 msf, receiving an offer for Embassy Zenith acquisition, acquiring Pinehurst for ₹852 crores, and launching a new redevelopment project. Embassy REIT reaffirmed its FY2026 NOI and DPU guidance.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:16:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RBI Holds Rates: Navigating Growth Amidst Inflationary Winds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Holds-Rates-Navigating-Growth-Amidst-Inflationary-Winds/69862f2c04125efaa8aeef63</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Holds-Rates-Navigating-Growth-Amidst-Inflationary-Winds/69862f2c04125efaa8aeef63</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's Monetary Policy Committee (MPC) held the benchmark repo rate steady at 5.25%, a move anticipated amidst a complex economic environment. While domestic growth shows resilience, the central bank has revised inflation forecasts upward for fiscal year 2026-27, citing global geopolitical tensions and commodity price volatility. Concurrently, the agricultural sector faces significant headwinds, with unseasonal rains impacting Robusta coffee, arecanut, and rubber harvests, threatening foreign exchange earnings and highlighting an urgent need for specialized crop insurance.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bengaluru Mandates Greener Construction Processes, Not Just Buildings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Bengaluru-Mandates-Greener-Construction-Processes-Not-Just-Buildings/69862f0c04125efaa8aee5e7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Bengaluru-Mandates-Greener-Construction-Processes-Not-Just-Buildings/69862f0c04125efaa8aee5e7</guid><description>Bengaluru's Chief Commissioner is now scrutinizing the construction process itself for environmental impact, demanding stricter management of emissions, debris handling, and material reuse. This regulatory pivot, supported by evolving national C&amp;D waste rules mandating recycling targets and responsible disposal, places new compliance burdens and operational considerations directly on construction firms, moving beyond traditional green building certifications. Firms must adapt to lifecycle requirements or face increased costs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:12:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Fractal Analytics Bags ₹1,248 Cr Anchor Funding for IPO</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Fractal-Analytics-Bags-1248-Cr-Anchor-Funding-for-IPO/69862efc04125efaa8aee150</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Fractal-Analytics-Bags-1248-Cr-Anchor-Funding-for-IPO/69862efc04125efaa8aee150</guid><description>Fractal Analytics, India's first pure-play artificial intelligence company, has secured ₹1,248.26 crore from anchor investors ahead of its proposed Initial Public Offering. Shares were allocated at the upper price band of ₹900, reflecting robust institutional demand. The anchor book saw significant participation from domestic mutual funds and insurance companies, alongside global marquee investors, signaling strong confidence.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:12:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Fusion Finance Recovers: Posts ₹14 Cr Profit, Asset Quality Surges</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Fusion-Finance-Recovers-Posts-14-Cr-Profit-Asset-Quality-Surges/69862eb304125efaa8aed81b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Fusion-Finance-Recovers-Posts-14-Cr-Profit-Asset-Quality-Surges/69862eb304125efaa8aed81b</guid><description>Fusion Finance Limited has staged a significant comeback, reporting a Profit After Tax (PAT) of ₹14 Cr for Q3 FY26. This marks a substantial recovery from a ₹719 Cr loss last year and a ₹22 Cr loss in the previous quarter. The turnaround is attributed to improved asset quality, with Gross NPAs falling to 4.38% and Net NPAs at 0.63%. Net Interest Margins (NIM) expanded by 246 bps YoY to 11.32%, and disbursements grew 23% QoQ.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:10:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Kalpataru Faces Auditor Red Flag On Subsidiaries Amidst Losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kalpataru-Faces-Auditor-Red-Flag-On-Subsidiaries-Amidst-Losses/69862e9c04125efaa8aed750</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Kalpataru-Faces-Auditor-Red-Flag-On-Subsidiaries-Amidst-Losses/69862e9c04125efaa8aed750</guid><description>Kalpataru Limited reported a mixed financial quarter. Standalone Q3 FY26 saw a profit turnaround to ₹281 Lakhs, but nine-month standalone results swung to a ₹1,502 Lakhs loss. Consolidated, the company posted a ₹6,704 Lakhs net loss for Q3 FY26, an improvement from last year's loss but indicating ongoing challenges. Crucially, auditors issued an Emphasis of Matter regarding 13 subsidiaries operating under the 'going concern' assumption despite losses. The company also secured Board approval to raise ₹350 Crores via NCDs.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:10:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Prataap Snacks Turns Profitable, Approves ₹425 Cr Indore Plant</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Prataap-Snacks-Turns-Profitable-Approves-425-Cr-Indore-Plant/69862e8104125efaa8aed640</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Prataap-Snacks-Turns-Profitable-Approves-425-Cr-Indore-Plant/69862e8104125efaa8aed640</guid><description>Prataap Snacks Limited has staged a remarkable financial turnaround, reporting a net profit of ₹3.25 Cr for Q4 FY25 against a net loss of ₹37.93 Cr last year. The company also posted a net profit of ₹3.58 Cr for the nine months ended December 31, 2025, a significant reversal from the prior period's loss. Expenses were controlled, with a 2.17% YoY reduction in Q4. Further fueling growth, the Board approved a ₹425 crore greenfield manufacturing plant near Indore, Madhya Pradesh, with a planned capacity of 60,000 MTPA, slated for commissioning by March 2027.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:10:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Embassy REIT Declares ₹613 Cr Distribution Amidst Regulatory Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Embassy-REIT-Declares-613-Cr-Distribution-Amidst-Regulatory-Scrutiny/69862e6004125efaa8aed521</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Embassy-REIT-Declares-613-Cr-Distribution-Amidst-Regulatory-Scrutiny/69862e6004125efaa8aed521</guid><description>Embassy Office Parks REIT reported its Q3 FY26 unaudited results, declaring a distribution of ₹6,132.87 million (₹6.47 per Unit). The REIT is evaluating a potential acquisition of Embassy Zenith in Bengaluru and has completed the sale of two strata blocks at MPPL for ₹5,300 million. However, the announcement also highlighted ongoing regulatory matters with SEBI, including settlement orders for past issues and income tax survey proceedings, raising investor caution.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:09:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Universal Cables Surges 93% PAT, Expands Capex and Enters HTLS Market</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Universal-Cables-Surges-93percent-PAT-Expands-Capex-and-Enters-HTLS-Market/69862e37e769d12df1db949c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Universal-Cables-Surges-93percent-PAT-Expands-Capex-and-Enters-HTLS-Market/69862e37e769d12df1db949c</guid><description>Universal Cables Limited posted a stellar Q3 FY26, with net profit after tax (PAT) surging 93% year-on-year to ₹18.74 crore on a 26.4% revenue increase to ₹767.92 crore. For the nine months, PAT soared 147% to ₹74.78 crore, while EBITDA margins improved to 9.64%. The company is increasing its organic expansion outlay to ₹550 crore and strategically entering the High Performance Conductors (HTLS) market via a partnership with TS Conductor Corp, USA. Management forecasts revenue growth over 25% for FY26 and a consistent 20-25% CAGR for the next two fiscals, backed by a robust order book of approximately ₹2,950 crore.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:08:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Aditya Birla Lifestyle Brands Posts Strong Q3 Growth, Eyes Double-Digit Momentum</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Aditya-Birla-Lifestyle-Brands-Posts-Strong-Q3-Growth-Eyes-Double-Digit-Momentum/69862e0be769d12df1db938a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Aditya-Birla-Lifestyle-Brands-Posts-Strong-Q3-Growth-Eyes-Double-Digit-Momentum/69862e0be769d12df1db938a</guid><description>Aditya Birla Lifestyle Brands Limited (ABLBL) delivered a robust Q3 FY26 performance, with revenue climbing 10% year-on-year to ₹2,343 crores. EBITDA surged 21% to ₹431 crores, expanding margins by 180 basis points to 18.4%. The company reported a PAT of ₹69 crores and reduced net debt to ₹800 crores. Management expressed confidence in sustaining double-digit growth, backed by aggressive store expansion and strategic focus on emerging brands, aiming for them to contribute one-fourth of the business within 4-5 years.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:08:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's Digital Fraud: New Tech Fuels Consumer Losses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Digital-Fraud-New-Tech-Fuels-Consumer-Losses/69862dc2e769d12df1db765b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Digital-Fraud-New-Tech-Fuels-Consumer-Losses/69862dc2e769d12df1db765b</guid><description>Online scams have become a pervasive threat across India, with nearly nine in ten individuals encountering fraudulent schemes daily. A significant portion, 51%, have lost an average of Rs 93,195 to these attacks. The alarming speed of scams, often resolved in minutes, is compounded by evolving tactics like deepfakes and voice clones, which nearly a third of the population struggles to identify. This escalating digital fraud erodes consumer wealth and highlights a critical vulnerability in India's rapidly digitizing economy.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:06:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's EM Index Weight Shrinks as Tech Rally Sidelines New Delhi</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-EM-Index-Weight-Shrinks-as-Tech-Rally-Sidelines-New-Delhi/69862da7e769d12df1db7592</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-EM-Index-Weight-Shrinks-as-Tech-Rally-Sidelines-New-Delhi/69862da7e769d12df1db7592</guid><description>India's standing in the MSCI Emerging Markets Index has diminished to 13.34% by end-January 2026, slipping to fourth position. This decline stems from global investors chasing artificial intelligence and semiconductor rallies, areas where India has limited exposure compared to technology-centric markets like Taiwan and South Korea. Sustained foreign fund outflows have further pressured Indian equities, widening the performance gap with peers that are benefiting from the current tech-driven investment narrative.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:06:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ram Ratna Wires Q3 Beat: Valuation Premium Sparks Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ram-Ratna-Wires-Q3-Beat-Valuation-Premium-Sparks-Scrutiny/69862d97e769d12df1db74e2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ram-Ratna-Wires-Q3-Beat-Valuation-Premium-Sparks-Scrutiny/69862d97e769d12df1db74e2</guid><description>Ram Ratna Wires reported a significant Q3 FY26 performance, with net profit soaring 74% year-on-year to ₹31.3 crore and revenue climbing 43.8% to ₹1,277.9 crore. This robust growth, driven by healthy demand and operational efficiencies, propelled EBITDA by 85.1% to ₹72 crore, with margins expanding to 5.6%. However, the company's elevated P/E ratio of approximately 38-40x, significantly above industry peers, prompts scrutiny regarding the sustainability of its premium valuation, especially amidst noted margin pressures and potential debt concerns. A leadership transition with a new CFO appointment effective April 1, 2026, also forms part of the disclosed corporate actions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:06:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Universal Cables Posts 93% Profit Jump, Expands Capex to ₹550 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Universal-Cables-Posts-93percent-Profit-Jump-Expands-Capex-to-550-Cr/69862d45e769d12df1db72f8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Universal-Cables-Posts-93percent-Profit-Jump-Expands-Capex-to-550-Cr/69862d45e769d12df1db72f8</guid><description>Universal Cables Limited reported a robust Q3 FY26, with standalone net profit surging 93.2% year-on-year to ₹18.74 crore on a 26.4% revenue jump to ₹767.92 crore. Margins improved across standalone and consolidated segments. The company raised its capital outlay to ₹550 crore for organic expansion and secured a ₹2,950 crore order book, anticipating consistent revenue CAGR of 20-25%.</description><pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 18:04:53 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>