<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 01:49:27 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India's Retirement Planning: The Hidden Cost of Product Over Purpose</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-Retirement-Planning-The-Hidden-Cost-of-Product-Over-Purpose/698d296bba46a4833be08ef0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/Indias-Retirement-Planning-The-Hidden-Cost-of-Product-Over-Purpose/698d296bba46a4833be08ef0</guid><description>The pervasive Indian approach to retirement planning centers on accumulating investment products like EPF, NPS, SIPs, and FDs, rather than aligning them with specific financial purposes such as stability or growth. This product-centric mindset leads to a "purpose gap," masking true risk exposure and fostering misaligned expectations. Compounding issues arise from automatic allocations into low-risk instruments and a focus on returns over sustainable retirement income, creating a systemic misallocation of capital that could jeopardize long-term financial security.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 01:14:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>RBI Mulls CRR Shift: A New Liquidity Paradigm?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Mulls-CRR-Shift-A-New-Liquidity-Paradigm/698d28d8ba46a4833be08ea4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Mulls-CRR-Shift-A-New-Liquidity-Paradigm/698d28d8ba46a4833be08ea4</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India is reportedly evaluating the Cash Reserve Ratio (CRR) as a liquidity management tool, a move that could signify a strategic pivot. This consideration comes as existing instruments like Open Market Operations (OMOs) face increasing limitations due to regulatory shifts and market dynamics. The CRR, a non-interest-bearing reserve that imposes a direct cost on banks, could offer a less collateral-dependent infusion method, potentially empowering banks to lower lending rates. This exploration highlights the RBI's proactive approach to ensuring system liquidity while navigating complex financial market conditions, including hardening bond yields and a widening credit-deposit gap.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 01:11:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Nifty 50 Tests 26,000 Amid Expiry; Earnings Divergence Widens</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-50-Tests-26000-Amid-Expiry-Earnings-Divergence-Widens/698d269dba46a4833be08ce3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-50-Tests-26000-Amid-Expiry-Earnings-Divergence-Widens/698d269dba46a4833be08ce3</guid><description>The Nifty 50 index is probing the 26,000 resistance level as monthly derivatives expiry approaches, marked by elevated volatility. While broad market indices show strength and foreign investor inflows resume, a sharp divergence is evident, with the IT sector facing headwinds against robust performance in financials and PSU banks. Investors await key Q3 earnings reports, seeking clarity amidst mixed signals and a cautious global economic backdrop. The Reserve Bank of India's stable monetary policy and controlled inflation provide underlying support.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 01:02:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>USV Pharma Nears Rs 1,600 Crore Deal for Wellbeing Nutrition Stake</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/USV-Pharma-Nears-Rs-1600-Crore-Deal-for-Wellbeing-Nutrition-Stake/698d2690ba46a4833be08c3f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/USV-Pharma-Nears-Rs-1600-Crore-Deal-for-Wellbeing-Nutrition-Stake/698d2690ba46a4833be08c3f</guid><description>USV Pharma is reportedly leading the race to acquire an 85% stake in D2C supplements brand Wellbeing Nutrition for ₹1,600 crore. The deal would see early investors Hindustan Unilever and Fireside Ventures exit with substantial returns, having invested three years ago at a ₹350 crore valuation. Founder Avnish Chhabria will retain a significant stake and continue leading the business.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 01:02:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Fractal Analytics IPO Completes Amidst Valuation &amp; Debut Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Fractal-Analytics-IPO-Completes-Amidst-Valuation-and-Debut-Concerns/698d24fbba46a4833be0882d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Fractal-Analytics-IPO-Completes-Amidst-Valuation-and-Debut-Concerns/698d24fbba46a4833be0882d</guid><description>The Fractal Analytics IPO concluded its subscription period with full oversubscription, driven by late Qualified Institutional Buyer (QIB) demand. Allotment is expected today, February 12, 2026. However, a subdued market sentiment is indicated by a near-zero or negative Grey Market Premium (GMP), suggesting potential listing day tepidness. Concerns linger around the company's aggressive valuation multiples and significant client concentration risks, despite its positioning as a pure-play enterprise AI provider.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 00:55:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698d24fbba46a4833be0882c_1770858137749.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Agrawal's Microcap Gambit: Profitable NBFC Meets Troubled SaaS</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Agrawals-Microcap-Gambit-Profitable-NBFC-Meets-Troubled-SaaS/698d24c5ba46a4833be086af</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Agrawals-Microcap-Gambit-Profitable-NBFC-Meets-Troubled-SaaS/698d24c5ba46a4833be086af</guid><description>Ace investor Mukul Agrawal has deployed ₹25 crore into two contrasting microcap stocks: Laxmi India Finance, a non-deposit taking NBFC with strong AUM growth but a recent revenue dip, and Tracxn Technologies, a market intelligence platform struggling with profitability but undergoing strategic investment. This move signals Agrawal's characteristic pursuit of undervalued assets and turnaround potential in the high-risk microcap segment.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 00:54:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>W Health Ventures Secures ₹550 Cr for Fund II, Bets on AI-Driven Healthcare Builders</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/W-Health-Ventures-Secures-550-Cr-for-Fund-II-Bets-on-AI-Driven-Healthcare-Builders/698d2452ba46a4833be085bb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/W-Health-Ventures-Secures-550-Cr-for-Fund-II-Bets-on-AI-Driven-Healthcare-Builders/698d2452ba46a4833be085bb</guid><description>W Health Ventures has completed an initial close of its second fund at ₹550 crore, nearing its target corpus, signaling a renewed commitment to its 'company creation' model. The fund will invest ₹30-50 crore per company, aiming to build 8-10 AI-enabled healthcare ventures over four years, focusing on both India's underserved markets and the US-India service corridor. This strategy targets complex healthcare challenges, moving beyond traditional venture capital investments to actively building businesses from inception.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 00:52:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India Eyes Empowering Women Farmers Amidst UN's 2026 Declaration</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/India-Eyes-Empowering-Women-Farmers-Amidst-UNs-2026-Declaration/698d23d9ba46a4833be08587</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/India-Eyes-Empowering-Women-Farmers-Amidst-UNs-2026-Declaration/698d23d9ba46a4833be08587</guid><description>The United Nations has declared 2026 the International Year of the Woman Farmer, spotlighting critical gender disparities in India's agricultural sector. Women, despite forming over 40% of the workforce, hold only about 14% of land and face significant barriers in accessing credit and participating in collectives. Policy interventions are now crucial to address these gaps and harness the full potential of female agricultural labor.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 00:50:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>India's GVC Ambition: Task vs. Reality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-GVC-Ambition-Task-vs-Reality/698d23bcba46a4833be0857b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-GVC-Ambition-Task-vs-Reality/698d23bcba46a4833be0857b</guid><description>India's strategy to ascend global value chains (GVCs) from assembly to higher-value tasks, aiming for "strategic indispensability," faces formidable challenges. Despite policy intent outlined in the Economic Survey 2025-26, structural weaknesses, intense competition from regional peers like Vietnam and China, and the fragmentation of GVC tasks present significant impediments. The transition necessitates more than participation; it requires deep integration into critical choke-point functions, a feat complicated by weak backward linkages and the imperative to synergize manufacturing with advanced services. Failure to address these fundamental issues risks India remaining a peripheral player, despite its economic ambitions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 00:50:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698d23bcba46a4833be0857a_1770857755853.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sagility Defies Tech Slump with Niche Healthcare AI Edge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Sagility-Defies-Tech-Slump-with-Niche-Healthcare-AI-Edge/698d23bcba46a4833be08573</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Sagility-Defies-Tech-Slump-with-Niche-Healthcare-AI-Edge/698d23bcba46a4833be08573</guid><description>Sagility Limited is bucking the IT sector downturn, attracting significant FII and DII investment due to its specialized healthcare IT services. The company reported a 36% revenue surge and 35% profit growth in Q3FY26, driven by US healthcare outsourcing demand and AI integration. While return ratios lag industry averages, a low PEG ratio suggests potential valuation upside as the industry shifts towards efficiency and margin repair.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 00:50:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698d23bcba46a4833be08572_1770857764329.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Neogen Chemicals Bets Big on Battery JV, PAT Surges 63% on Strong Quarter</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Neogen-Chemicals-Bets-Big-on-Battery-JV-PAT-Surges-63percent-on-Strong-Quarter/698d196cba46a4833be08250</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Neogen-Chemicals-Bets-Big-on-Battery-JV-PAT-Surges-63percent-on-Strong-Quarter/698d196cba46a4833be08250</guid><description>Neogen Chemicals reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated revenue growing 9% YoY to INR 220 crore and consolidated PAT surging 63% YoY to INR 4 crore, despite transitory cost headwinds. Standalone PAT increased 39% YoY to INR 9 crore. The company highlighted significant progress in its strategic battery chemicals business, including a new Indo-Japan joint venture with Morita Investment Limited and substantial capacity expansions. It also received INR 83.48 crore in insurance claims for a past fire incident and secured board approval for a INR 150 crore preferential issue to the Promoter Group.</description><pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 00:06:04 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>