<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:45:29 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Lufthansa's Premium Push: High Stakes in a Thin-Margin Aviation World</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Lufthansas-Premium-Push-High-Stakes-in-a-Thin-Margin-Aviation-World/699cf9c604a25a58c84e3256</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Lufthansas-Premium-Push-High-Stakes-in-a-Thin-Margin-Aviation-World/699cf9c604a25a58c84e3256</guid><description>Deutsche Lufthansa AG is aggressively upgrading its premium cabins, exemplified by the Allegris product, to capitalize on India's burgeoning luxury travel market. Despite significant investment and a competitive landscape dominated by airlines like Emirates, the efficacy and cost-benefit of these upgrades are under scrutiny. While the broader European aviation sector forecasts profit growth, individual airlines like Lufthansa operate on razor-thin margins, facing persistent cost pressures from supply chain issues, labor, and fuel. Lufthansa's current valuation suggests investor caution, balancing aggressive expansion against a backdrop of operational complexities and mixed analyst sentiment.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:07:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699cf9c604a25a58c84e3255_1771895360023.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cyber Stocks Plunge on AI Fears; Adaptation Key</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Cyber-Stocks-Plunge-on-AI-Fears-Adaptation-Key/699cf8cd04a25a58c84e3131</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Cyber-Stocks-Plunge-on-AI-Fears-Adaptation-Key/699cf8cd04a25a58c84e3131</guid><description>Major cybersecurity firms, including CrowdStrike and Datadog, experienced significant sell-offs on Monday, with shares dropping up to 11%. The catalyst was Anthropic's introduction of Claude Code Security, designed to detect and patch open-source vulnerabilities. Investors are weighing AI's potential impact, driving a narrative-led sell-off. However, some analysts suggest this could be an overreaction, with AI more likely to augment than replace existing security solutions, creating an inflection point for sector adaptation and innovation.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:03:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699cf8cd04a25a58c84e3130_1771895155650.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Infrastructure Push: Spending Soars, Execution Stalls</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Infrastructure-Push-Spending-Soars-Execution-Stalls/699cf86604a25a58c84e3048</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Infrastructure-Push-Spending-Soars-Execution-Stalls/699cf86604a25a58c84e3048</guid><description>Despite a substantial increase in public capital expenditure for infrastructure, India faces a significant execution gap. The Union Budget's strategy, while aiming to stimulate growth, is hampered by delays in land acquisition, regulatory hurdles, weak project preparation, and insufficient focus on operations and maintenance. Analysts caution that without addressing these systemic delivery issues, higher spending risks creating stranded assets and falling short of economic goals.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:01:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699cf86604a25a58c84e3047_1771894998748.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Leverages Tariff Ruling to Fortify Energy Security, Trade</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Leverages-Tariff-Ruling-to-Fortify-Energy-Security-Trade/699cf85404a25a58c84e302e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Leverages-Tariff-Ruling-to-Fortify-Energy-Security-Trade/699cf85404a25a58c84e302e</guid><description>India's energy strategy is recalibrating following the US Supreme Court's invalidation of President Trump's sweeping tariffs. While this removes a significant trade weapon, the US retains other pressure points. India is leveraging this moment to solidify its commitment to strategic autonomy, diversify its energy basket, and renegotiate trade terms from a stronger position, even as geopolitical risks persist.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:01:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699cf85404a25a58c84e302d_1771895004790.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Global Markets Brace for Enduring Geopolitical Drag</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Global-Markets-Brace-for-Enduring-Geopolitical-Drag/699cf85204a25a58c84e3017</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Global-Markets-Brace-for-Enduring-Geopolitical-Drag/699cf85204a25a58c84e3017</guid><description>The Russia-Ukraine conflict, now in its fourth year, has evolved into a chronic drag on global economic stability. Stalled peace talks over territory mask deeper structural shifts: a sustained surge in defense spending due to heightened geopolitical risk, ongoing energy market volatility, and a recalibration of global supply chains. Sanctions continue to impact Russia's economy and trade patterns. Investor sentiment reflects a move towards defensive assets amidst this enduring uncertainty.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 01:01:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699cf85204a25a58c84e3016_1771894999104.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Suraj Estate Buys Prabhadevi Land for ₹30.4 Cr, Plans ₹200 Cr GDV Project</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Suraj-Estate-Buys-Prabhadevi-Land-for-304-Cr-Plans-200-Cr-GDV-Project/699ceb2f04a25a58c84e2c0a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Suraj-Estate-Buys-Prabhadevi-Land-for-304-Cr-Plans-200-Cr-GDV-Project/699ceb2f04a25a58c84e2c0a</guid><description>Suraj Estate Developers Limited has acquired Hally Pacific Private Limited for ₹30.40 crore, gaining a vacant land parcel in Mumbai's prime Prabhadevi area. The company plans to develop this land into a project with an estimated Gross Development Value (GDV) of ₹200 crore, significantly bolstering its development pipeline and medium-term revenue visibility in a sought-after micro-market.</description><pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 00:05:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ceb2f04a25a58c84e2c09_1771891612143.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>