<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:37:00 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India's Premium Grocers Bet on Quality, Not Speed</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Premium-Grocers-Bet-on-Quality-Not-Speed/699331432e6a0b8ae17d47de</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Premium-Grocers-Bet-on-Quality-Not-Speed/699331432e6a0b8ae17d47de</guid><description>While quick-commerce leaders like Blinkit and Zepto focus on speed, premium Indian grocery startups FirstClub and Pluckk are carving out a niche by emphasizing quality, clean labels, and transparency. FirstClub reports 45% month-on-month growth and a leading ₹1,170 average order value, while Pluckk leverages direct farmer sourcing for its ₹800-1,000 AOV. These companies aim to democratize premium offerings, appealing to an expanding consumer base willing to pay for ingredient assurance, and positioning themselves for quicker profitability through higher basket sizes and gross margins.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 15:01:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699331432e6a0b8ae17d47dd.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sical Logistics Rights Issue: ₹930 Cr Raise Amidst High Debt &amp; MPS Deadline</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Sical-Logistics-Rights-Issue-930-Cr-Raise-Amidst-High-Debt-and-MPS-Deadline/699330b92e6a0b8ae17d474f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Sical-Logistics-Rights-Issue-930-Cr-Raise-Amidst-High-Debt-and-MPS-Deadline/699330b92e6a0b8ae17d474f</guid><description>Sical Logistics is launching a ₹930.3 crore rights issue at ₹64 per share to address high borrowings and general corporate needs. A crucial aspect is the promoter group waiving their rights entitlement to meet Minimum Public Shareholding norms by February 2026, highlighting past compliance issues. Investors must weigh this capital raise against substantial existing debt, ongoing litigation, and a history of financial distress.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:59:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699330b92e6a0b8ae17d474e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bimetal Bearings Sees Profit Drop 28% Quarter-on-Quarter</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bimetal-Bearings-Sees-Profit-Drop-28percent-Quarter-on-Quarter/6993303f2e6a0b8ae17d46e5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Bimetal-Bearings-Sees-Profit-Drop-28percent-Quarter-on-Quarter/6993303f2e6a0b8ae17d46e5</guid><description>Bimetal Bearings Limited reported a 17.89% year-on-year increase in total income for the third quarter ended December 31, 2025. However, profit after tax saw a significant sequential decline of 28.50% compared to the previous quarter, raising concerns about margin pressure. For the nine months, profit growth was minimal despite strong revenue gains.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:57:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6993303f2e6a0b8ae17d46e4_1771253946631.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Marathon Realty Raises ₹900 Cr, Achieves Net Cash; Q3 Revenue at ₹178 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Marathon-Realty-Raises-900-Cr-Achieves-Net-Cash-Q3-Revenue-at-178-Cr/69932e632e6a0b8ae17d461f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Marathon-Realty-Raises-900-Cr-Achieves-Net-Cash-Q3-Revenue-at-178-Cr/69932e632e6a0b8ae17d461f</guid><description>Marathon Nextgen Realty Limited has successfully raised ₹900 crore through a Qualified Institutional Placement (QIP), achieving a net cash position and significantly reducing debt. For the third quarter ending December 31, 2025 (Q3 FY26), the company reported adjusted total revenues of ₹178 crore and a profit after tax (PAT) of ₹33 crore. The nine-month period (9M FY26) saw revenues of ₹656 crore and PAT of ₹161 crore. Strategic initiatives include an ongoing amalgamation and expansion of its project pipeline.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:49:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69932e632e6a0b8ae17d461e_1771253452343.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>PSU Bonds Soar Amidst Debt Market Flight to Quality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSU-Bonds-Soar-Amidst-Debt-Market-Flight-to-Quality/69932cfc2e6a0b8ae17d455d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/PSU-Bonds-Soar-Amidst-Debt-Market-Flight-to-Quality/69932cfc2e6a0b8ae17d455d</guid><description>India's debt markets are exhibiting a clear flight to quality. National Bank for Agriculture and Rural Development (Nabard) successfully raised ₹6,779 crore at 7.01% for its three-year bonds, a rate seen as favorable amidst elevated sovereign yields. This contrasts with the broader corporate bond market's subdued activity, where non-bank lenders like IIFL Finance must offer significantly higher coupon rates of up to 9% to attract capital. REC Ltd's upcoming issuance further signals robust demand for AAA-rated public sector paper.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:43:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69932cfc2e6a0b8ae17d455c_1771253137593.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RCB Stake Sale Eyes $2 Billion, Signaling IPL's Asset Class Evolution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/RCB-Stake-Sale-Eyes-2-Billion-Signaling-IPLs-Asset-Class-Evolution/69932c082e6a0b8ae17d446e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Media-and-Entertainment/RCB-Stake-Sale-Eyes-2-Billion-Signaling-IPLs-Asset-Class-Evolution/69932c082e6a0b8ae17d446e</guid><description>Nine to ten bidders are advancing in the sale process for a stake in Royal Challengers Bengaluru (RCB), with valuations potentially reaching $1.5 to $2 billion. This surge highlights the Indian Premier League's (IPL) evolution into a prime alternative asset class, attracting significant global investor interest amid a broader wave of M&amp;A activity across multiple franchises. Due diligence is now underway, with final bids expected after further review.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:39:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69932c082e6a0b8ae17d446d_1771252885944.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pace Digitek Revenue Jumps, But Margins Dip on Project Mix</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Pace-Digitek-Revenue-Jumps-But-Margins-Dip-on-Project-Mix/69932aa02e6a0b8ae17d439c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Pace-Digitek-Revenue-Jumps-But-Margins-Dip-on-Project-Mix/69932aa02e6a0b8ae17d439c</guid><description>Pace Digitek reported a strong 13.5% year-on-year revenue growth to ₹644.0 crore in Q3 FY2026. However, gross and EBITDA margins saw a decline due to a shift in project mix. The company is aggressively expanding its Battery Energy Storage Systems (BESS) capacity and order book, targeting significant contributions from this segment by FY2027.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:33:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69932aa02e6a0b8ae17d439b_1771252500451.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rama Paper Mills in Deep Crisis: Auditors Flag Going Concern Risk Amidst CIRP</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rama-Paper-Mills-in-Deep-Crisis-Auditors-Flag-Going-Concern-Risk-Amidst-CIRP/699327102e6a0b8ae17d4152</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rama-Paper-Mills-in-Deep-Crisis-Auditors-Flag-Going-Concern-Risk-Amidst-CIRP/699327102e6a0b8ae17d4152</guid><description>Rama Paper Mills Limited has announced its Q3 FY26 results, revealing significant financial distress. The company is undergoing Corporate Insolvency Resolution Process (CIRP), with auditors raising serious concerns about its ability to continue as a going concern. Key issues include unprovided interest, unverified inventory, and MSME disclosure violations, compounded by the NCLT setting aside a prior resolution plan.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:17:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699327102e6a0b8ae17d4151_1771251574333.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Expands Forex Derivative Reporting</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Expands-Forex-Derivative-Reporting/699326af2e6a0b8ae17d4068</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/RBI-Expands-Forex-Derivative-Reporting/699326af2e6a0b8ae17d4068</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has proposed new reporting requirements for Authorised Dealer Category-I (AD Cat-I) banks, compelling them to disclose all over-the-counter (OTC) foreign exchange derivative contracts involving the rupee that are transacted globally by their related parties. This expansion of reporting mandates, with comments due by March 9, 2026, aims to bolster transparency in the offshore rupee derivative market and provides for a phased implementation over 24 months, with thresholds increasing from 70% to 90% of notional value.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:16:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699326af2e6a0b8ae17d4067_1771251608825.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Audit Warns: Small Firm's Numbers Unreliable Amidst Revenue Drop</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Audit-Warns-Small-Firms-Numbers-Unreliable-Amidst-Revenue-Drop/6993269c2e6a0b8ae17d3fdf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Audit-Warns-Small-Firms-Numbers-Unreliable-Amidst-Revenue-Drop/6993269c2e6a0b8ae17d3fdf</guid><description>A micro-cap company has reported a significant year-on-year decline in revenue and a surge in expenses for the quarter ending December 31, 2025. However, the most alarming development is a 'Basis for Disclaimer of Opinion' from its auditors, Chandabhoy &amp; Jassoobhoy Chartered Accountants, citing lack of crucial supporting documents for sales, expenses, and loans.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:15:56 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6993269c2e6a0b8ae17d3fde_1771251475436.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Vedanta Promoter Pledges More Shares for $350M Loan</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Vedanta-Promoter-Pledges-More-Shares-for-350M-Loan/699326962e6a0b8ae17d3fc9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Vedanta-Promoter-Pledges-More-Shares-for-350M-Loan/699326962e6a0b8ae17d3fc9</guid><description>Vedanta Resources Limited (VRL) has secured a new US$350 million credit facility, leading to further encumbrances on shares of its subsidiary, Vedanta Limited (VEDL). This move, aimed at managing VRL Group's debt, involves significant portions of the promoter's VEDL stake being used as collateral. The disclosure under SEBI's Takeover Regulations highlights potential risks related to debt servicing and control maintenance for the group.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:15:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699326962e6a0b8ae17d3fc8.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Restaurant Firm's Revenue Jumps 9% Amid Strong Margin Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Restaurant-Firms-Revenue-Jumps-9percent-Amid-Strong-Margin-Gains/699326902e6a0b8ae17d3fb3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Restaurant-Firms-Revenue-Jumps-9percent-Amid-Strong-Margin-Gains/699326902e6a0b8ae17d3fb3</guid><description>An Indian restaurant company reported a solid 9% year-on-year revenue increase for Q3 FY26, alongside significant improvements in EBITDA and gross margins. The firm is pushing a strategy focused on enhancing the dine-in experience and undertaking international expansion in Saudi Arabia and the UAE, alongside domestic growth. Capital spending will be self-funded, with new outlets favoring smaller footprints.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:15:44 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699326902e6a0b8ae17d3fb2_1771251519122.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Alkem Labs Bets Big on Global MedTech With Occlutech Buy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Alkem-Labs-Bets-Big-on-Global-MedTech-With-Occlutech-Buy/699326892e6a0b8ae17d3f7e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Alkem-Labs-Bets-Big-on-Global-MedTech-With-Occlutech-Buy/699326892e6a0b8ae17d3f7e</guid><description>Alkem Laboratories is making a bold move into the global medical technology (MedTech) market by acquiring a majority stake in Occlutech Holding AG, a leading European player in cardiovascular devices. The ₹19,516 crore deal, funded by Alkem's internal cash, signals a strategic push beyond its traditional pharmaceutical business into higher-growth, technologically advanced healthcare segments like orthopedics and cardiovascular solutions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:15:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699326892e6a0b8ae17d3f7d_1771251444174.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MSME Credit Gap Widens: RBI Focus vs. Market Reality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/MSME-Credit-Gap-Widens-RBI-Focus-vs-Market-Reality/6993264e2e6a0b8ae17d3eae</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/MSME-Credit-Gap-Widens-RBI-Focus-vs-Market-Reality/6993264e2e6a0b8ae17d3eae</guid><description>Reserve Bank of India Governor Sanjay Malhotra highlighted the critical role of MSMEs and the central bank's priority in improving their formal credit access. However, recent data indicates significant challenges persist, with a widening credit gap and a bearish technical outlook for the BSE SME IPO index. Recent regulatory measures aim to ease collateral requirements, but practical implementation and underlying structural issues continue to impede seamless financing for the sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:14:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6993264e2e6a0b8ae17d3ead_1771251434936.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Cash Surge: Digital Dominance in Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Cash-Surge-Digital-Dominance-in-Growth/6993264b2e6a0b8ae17d3e97</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Cash-Surge-Digital-Dominance-in-Growth/6993264b2e6a0b8ae17d3e97</guid><description>India's currency in circulation reached an unprecedented ₹40 lakh crore by January 2026, a 11.1% year-on-year rise. Despite this nominal increase, cash's relative economic importance is shrinking, evidenced by a declining cash-to-GDP ratio to 11%. SBI Research highlights that incremental GDP growth is increasingly funded by digital payments like UPI, not cash. This trend is driven by lower interest rates, behavioral responses to policy signals like GST notices, and liquidity recycling. The rise in cash reflects complex economic dynamics rather than a retreat from digital transformation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:14:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6993264b2e6a0b8ae17d3e96.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>REC Ltd's Green Hydrogen Gambit Leverages PFC Synergy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/REC-Ltds-Green-Hydrogen-Gambit-Leverages-PFC-Synergy/6993262c2e6a0b8ae17d3e7a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/REC-Ltds-Green-Hydrogen-Gambit-Leverages-PFC-Synergy/6993262c2e6a0b8ae17d3e7a</guid><description>REC Ltd's subsidiary, Vizag Power Transmission, is established for green hydrogen infrastructure in Andhra Pradesh. This move leverages REC's strategic consolidation under Power Finance Corporation (PFC), aiming to tap into India's burgeoning green hydrogen sector. The incorporation signifies a commitment to critical transmission development for decarbonization goals, supported by a merged entity poised for enhanced project financing capacity.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:14:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6993262c2e6a0b8ae17d3e79_1771251406780.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Highway Infra Stock Dips Amid NHAI Contract Win</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Highway-Infra-Stock-Dips-Amid-NHAI-Contract-Win/699325ef2e6a0b8ae17d3df7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Highway-Infra-Stock-Dips-Amid-NHAI-Contract-Win/699325ef2e6a0b8ae17d3df7</guid><description>Highway Infrastructure Ltd announced a ₹154.6 crore contract win from the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) for toll operations in Gujarat. However, the company's shares closed down 2.15% on February 16, 2026. This muted reaction contrasts with previous rallies following similar contract awards, suggesting investors are scrutinizing the short-term nature of the project and the company's valuation relative to its larger peers.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:13:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699325ef2e6a0b8ae17d3df6.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Madhur Industries Suffers Steep Revenue Fall, Equity Wiped Out</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Madhur-Industries-Suffers-Steep-Revenue-Fall-Equity-Wiped-Out/699325782e6a0b8ae17d3d06</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Madhur-Industries-Suffers-Steep-Revenue-Fall-Equity-Wiped-Out/699325782e6a0b8ae17d3d06</guid><description>Madhur Industries Ltd. reported a dismal Q3 FY26 with revenue plunging 36.8% year-on-year to ₹3.88 Lakhs and net losses widening to ₹14.54 Lakhs. For the nine months, revenue crashed 98% YoY. Critically, the company's reserves have been completely wiped out, standing at ₹0, indicating severe erosion of its equity base. The company also has a past SEBI regulatory issue concerning scrip manipulation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:11:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699325782e6a0b8ae17d3d05.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Shree Ram Twistex IPO: Powering Growth with Green Energy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Shree-Ram-Twistex-IPO-Powering-Growth-with-Green-Energy/699325182e6a0b8ae17d3c39</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Shree-Ram-Twistex-IPO-Powering-Growth-with-Green-Energy/699325182e6a0b8ae17d3c39</guid><description>Shree Ram Twistex, a Gujarat-based cotton yarn manufacturer, is set to launch its Initial Public Offering (IPO) on February 23, 2026. The IPO, a fresh issue of 1.06 crore equity shares, aims to raise capital for establishing captive solar and wind power plants, repaying debt, and bolstering working capital. The company reported a profit of ₹8 crore on revenue of ₹255 crore in FY25, indicating steady financial performance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:09:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699325182e6a0b8ae17d3c38.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US-India Trade Deal: Tariff Cut Offers Relief Amidst Global Friction</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-India-Trade-Deal-Tariff-Cut-Offers-Relief-Amidst-Global-Friction/699325052e6a0b8ae17d3c1b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-India-Trade-Deal-Tariff-Cut-Offers-Relief-Amidst-Global-Friction/699325052e6a0b8ae17d3c1b</guid><description>The United States and India have agreed to an interim trade framework, reducing reciprocal tariffs on Indian goods to 18% and aiming to finalize a comprehensive legal agreement by March. This recalibration follows a period of significant trade friction and aims to address non-tariff barriers across sectors including industrial goods, agriculture, and pharmaceuticals. While offering immediate tariff relief, the deal's long-term impact is debated amid broader geopolitical shifts and existing trade imbalances.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:09:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699325052e6a0b8ae17d3c1a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bajaj Sugar Plans ₹13,000 Cr Capital Hike, Debt-for-Equity Swap</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Bajaj-Sugar-Plans-13000-Cr-Capital-Hike-Debt-for-Equity-Swap/699324882e6a0b8ae17d3b5b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Bajaj-Sugar-Plans-13000-Cr-Capital-Hike-Debt-for-Equity-Swap/699324882e6a0b8ae17d3b5b</guid><description>Bajaj Hindusthan Sugar is calling an Extraordinary General Meeting (EGM) on March 10, 2026, to seek shareholder approval for a significant ₹13,000 Cr capital increase and a debt restructuring plan. This plan involves converting over ₹3,400 Cr of lender debt into equity and preference shares, significantly diluting the promoters' stake and placing lenders in a dominant shareholder position. The company is battling severe financial distress.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:07:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699324882e6a0b8ae17d3b5a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Mid-Cap Access Via GIFT City: Sundaram Launches Offshore USD Fund</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Mid-Cap-Access-Via-GIFT-City-Sundaram-Launches-Offshore-USD-Fund/699323a12e6a0b8ae17d3a1e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Mid-Cap-Access-Via-GIFT-City-Sundaram-Launches-Offshore-USD-Fund/699323a12e6a0b8ae17d3a1e</guid><description>Sundaram Asset Management Company has launched the Sundaram India Mid Cap GIFT, a USD-denominated offshore feeder fund. Leveraging GIFT City's International Financial Services Centre (IFSC), the fund aims to simplify global investors' access to India's mid-cap segment by investing substantially in the Sundaram Mid Cap Fund, which boasts a 23-year track record. This initiative highlights GIFT City's growing role as a financial gateway and the continued investor appetite for Indian equities, particularly mid-sized companies poised for expansion.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:03:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699323a12e6a0b8ae17d3a1d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Green Steel Push: Scrap Quality Challenges Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Green-Steel-Push-Scrap-Quality-Challenges-Loom/6993239d2e6a0b8ae17d3a07</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Green-Steel-Push-Scrap-Quality-Challenges-Loom/6993239d2e6a0b8ae17d3a07</guid><description>Indian steel giants like Tata Steel, JSW Steel, and ArcelorMittal Nippon Steel are accelerating investments in scrap recycling and green steel production following the government's introduction of a green steel taxonomy. This regulatory shift, coupled with a mandate for Public Sector Undertakings (PSUs) to procure certified green steel, aims to curb carbon emissions. However, persistent challenges with domestic scrap quality and the inherent cost premium of green steel present significant operational and market integration hurdles for the sector's ambitious decarbonization targets.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:03:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6993239d2e6a0b8ae17d3a06.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Challenge: Job Growth Pressure Mounts as IT Stocks Dive</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-AI-Challenge-Job-Growth-Pressure-Mounts-as-IT-Stocks-Dive/699323262e6a0b8ae17d3964</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-AI-Challenge-Job-Growth-Pressure-Mounts-as-IT-Stocks-Dive/699323262e6a0b8ae17d3964</guid><description>Chief Economic Advisor V. Anantha Nageswaran has cautioned that India faces significant risks of increased inequality and social instability if artificial intelligence adoption is not strategically aligned with job creation and mass employability. His remarks come as the Nifty IT index has experienced a sharp decline, shedding over 15% in recent weeks, reflecting investor anxieties about AI-driven disruption. This backdrop also saw Fractal Analytics, a pure-play enterprise AI firm, debut on the stock market at a discount, highlighting valuation concerns in the burgeoning AI sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:01:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699323262e6a0b8ae17d3963.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tenneco India Q3 Profit Dips 5% But Revenue &amp; Ebidta Surge Ahead</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tenneco-India-Q3-Profit-Dips-5percent-But-Revenue-and-Ebidta-Surge-Ahead/699322c72e6a0b8ae17d38ec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tenneco-India-Q3-Profit-Dips-5percent-But-Revenue-and-Ebidta-Surge-Ahead/699322c72e6a0b8ae17d38ec</guid><description>Tenneco Clean Air India announced robust Q3 FY2025-26 results with revenue up 14.2% and EBITDA soaring 24.8%. However, reported Profit After Tax saw a 5.3% decline due to a one-time charge. The company also highlighted significant new business wins and expansion plans. The audio recording of the earnings call is now available for investors seeking deeper insights.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:59:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699322c72e6a0b8ae17d38eb.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Canara HSBC Life Seeks Shareholder Vote on Promoter Board Seats, Key Deals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Canara-HSBC-Life-Seeks-Shareholder-Vote-on-Promoter-Board-Seats-Key-Deals/699321432e6a0b8ae17d37cf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/Canara-HSBC-Life-Seeks-Shareholder-Vote-on-Promoter-Board-Seats-Key-Deals/699321432e6a0b8ae17d37cf</guid><description>Canara HSBC Life Insurance has issued a postal ballot notice to shareholders, seeking approval for two crucial proposals. The first involves amending its Articles of Association to formalize nomination rights for its promoters, Canara Bank and HSBC Insurance (Asia-Pacific) Holdings Limited, to its Board of Directors. The second proposal seeks approval for material related party transactions (RPTs) with Canara Bank and The Hongkong and Shanghai Banking Corporation Limited for the financial year 2025-26. E-voting will take place from February 18 to March 19, 2026.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:53:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699321432e6a0b8ae17d37ce.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>StarSource Multitrade Zero Revenue, Posts ₹118 Cr Loss on Financial Instruments</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/StarSource-Multitrade-Zero-Revenue-Posts-118-Cr-Loss-on-Financial-Instruments/699321402e6a0b8ae17d37b9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/StarSource-Multitrade-Zero-Revenue-Posts-118-Cr-Loss-on-Financial-Instruments/699321402e6a0b8ae17d37b9</guid><description>StarSource Multitrade Limited reported a dire Q3 FY26 with zero revenue from operations and a net loss of ₹0.87 crore. The situation worsened over nine months, with a staggering ₹118.14 crore net loss, significantly driven by the 'Fair Valuation of Financial Instruments'. This reliance on volatile market valuations, rather than core business, raises serious concerns for investors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:53:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699321402e6a0b8ae17d37b8.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Texmaco Rail Wins ₹219 Cr Mumbai Suburban Signalling Order</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Texmaco-Rail-Wins-219-Cr-Mumbai-Suburban-Signalling-Order/699320512e6a0b8ae17d3705</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Texmaco-Rail-Wins-219-Cr-Mumbai-Suburban-Signalling-Order/699320512e6a0b8ae17d3705</guid><description>Texmaco Rail &amp; Engineering Limited has secured a significant INR 219.18 crore order from Mumbai Railway Vikas Corporation Ltd. for signalling equipment on the Borivali-Virar section under the MUTP-IIIA project. The 36-month project aims to enhance Mumbai's suburban railway network, boosting the company's order book and future revenue streams.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:49:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699320512e6a0b8ae17d3704.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Reliance Bets Big on Africa, Health Foods: A Dual-Stage Growth Play</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Reliance-Bets-Big-on-Africa-Health-Foods-A-Dual-Stage-Growth-Play/69931eed2e6a0b8ae17d360b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Reliance-Bets-Big-on-Africa-Health-Foods-A-Dual-Stage-Growth-Play/69931eed2e6a0b8ae17d360b</guid><description>Reliance Consumer Products (RCPL) is aggressively pursuing a two-pronged growth strategy. The company will form a majority-owned joint venture with Nigeria's TGI Group to tap into Africa's fastest-growing FMCG market, while simultaneously acquiring Indian health food maker Southern Health Foods (SHFPL) to fortify its domestic offerings. This dual approach signals a deliberate effort to balance high-potential emerging market penetration with targeted consolidation in high-growth domestic segments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:43:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69931eed2e6a0b8ae17d360a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Slice SFB Appoints Bajaj CEO Amidst Tech-Driven Banking Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Slice-SFB-Appoints-Bajaj-CEO-Amidst-Tech-Driven-Banking-Shift/69931e082e6a0b8ae17d3501</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Slice-SFB-Appoints-Bajaj-CEO-Amidst-Tech-Driven-Banking-Shift/69931e082e6a0b8ae17d3501</guid><description>Rajan Bajaj, founder of the fintech firm Slice, has been officially appointed as the new Managing Director and CEO of Slice Small Finance Bank (SSFB), effective February 17, 2026, following Reserve Bank of India approval. This pivotal leadership change occurs as the bank solidifies its transition from a digital credit platform to a licensed deposit-taking institution. Slice SFB has ambitious plans to leverage artificial intelligence for personalized customer experiences and operational efficiency, aiming to capture market share in the competitive small finance banking sector. The bank has reported opening over four million savings accounts in its first year of full banking operations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:39:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69931e082e6a0b8ae17d3500.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lemon Tree Hotels Q3 Revenue Jumps 15%, Margins Dip Due to Investments; Demerger on Track</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Lemon-Tree-Hotels-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-15percent-Margins-Dip-Due-to-Investments-Demerger-on-Track/69931df92e6a0b8ae17d34e8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Lemon-Tree-Hotels-Q3-Revenue-Jumps-15percent-Margins-Dip-Due-to-Investments-Demerger-on-Track/69931df92e6a0b8ae17d34e8</guid><description>Lemon Tree Hotels reported a strong 15% year-on-year revenue growth to ₹407.8 crore for Q3 FY26, with PAT rising 2% to ₹81.8 crore. However, EBITDA margins compressed by 133 basis points to 50.6% due to increased investments in renovations and technology. The company highlighted robust expansion plans and the upcoming demerger, which aims to create a debt-free, asset-light Lemon Tree.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:39:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69931df92e6a0b8ae17d34e7.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SKF India's ₹653 Cr Pune Plant: A 'Factory of Future' Vision</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SKF-Indias-653-Cr-Pune-Plant-A-Factory-of-Future-Vision/69931d7f2e6a0b8ae17d343a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SKF-Indias-653-Cr-Pune-Plant-A-Factory-of-Future-Vision/69931d7f2e6a0b8ae17d343a</guid><description>SKF India is investing ₹653 crore to establish a 'Factory of the Future' manufacturing plant in Pune, set for completion by 2030. This strategic move reinforces its commitment to digitalization, sustainability, and resilient supply chains, aiming to bolster support for critical industries. The investment signals a strong conviction in India's manufacturing growth trajectory, contrasting with the company's recent stock underperformance and market pressures.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:37:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69931d7f2e6a0b8ae17d3439.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Unemployment Rate Inches Up to 5%; Rural Factors Dominate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Unemployment-Rate-Inches-Up-to-5percent-Rural-Factors-Dominate/69931cc92e6a0b8ae17d3370</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Unemployment-Rate-Inches-Up-to-5percent-Rural-Factors-Dominate/69931cc92e6a0b8ae17d3370</guid><description>India's unemployment rate increased to 5% in January 2026, a marginal rise from 4.8% in December 2025, according to the Statistics Ministry. This uptick was primarily concentrated in rural areas, attributed to seasonal factors like post-harvest slack and winter slowdowns in activities such as construction and agriculture. Urban areas remained relatively stable. The Periodic Labour Force Survey (PLFS) also indicated lower labour force participation rates (LFPR) and worker population ratios (WPR), suggesting a potential increase in discouraged workers. While male unemployment remained stable, female unemployment saw a marginal increase but was deemed a short-term fluctuation by the Ministry.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:34:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69931cc92e6a0b8ae17d336f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Samvardhana Motherson Hits Record Revenue, Profit Jumps 21%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Samvardhana-Motherson-Hits-Record-Revenue-Profit-Jumps-21percent/69931c902e6a0b8ae17d32fa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Samvardhana-Motherson-Hits-Record-Revenue-Profit-Jumps-21percent/69931c902e6a0b8ae17d32fa</guid><description>Samvardhana Motherson International achieved its highest-ever quarterly revenue of approximately ₹31,409 crores, a 14% increase year-on-year. Normalized profit after tax (PAT) surged 21% to ₹1,061 crores, driven by margin improvements across segments and strong growth in non-automotive businesses like consumer electronics. The company maintains robust financial discipline with a net leverage of 1.1x, while investing heavily in 12 greenfield projects and strategic acquisitions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:33:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69931c902e6a0b8ae17d32f9.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Ambition vs. Infrastructure Reality: The Path to Sovereign Compute</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-vs-Infrastructure-Reality-The-Path-to-Sovereign-Compute/69931c492e6a0b8ae17d322e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Ambition-vs-Infrastructure-Reality-The-Path-to-Sovereign-Compute/69931c492e6a0b8ae17d322e</guid><description>India aims to be an AI powerhouse, driven by initiatives like the IndiaAI Mission and treated digital infrastructure as paramount. Despite a seven-fold increase in data center capacity over seven years, projections indicate a significant shortfall against burgeoning domestic and global AI demand. Achieving sovereign AI leadership necessitates overcoming substantial infrastructure deficits, integrating hybrid and indigenous models, and navigating complex data governance frameworks like the DPDP Rules, which may unlock strategic 'data corridors'. The nation's ambition is clear, but the execution of this vision hinges on bridging vast investment gaps and contending with global competitive pressures.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:31:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69931c492e6a0b8ae17d322d_1771248811149.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ValleyNXT Launches Deep Tech Fund with Accelerator Model</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/ValleyNXT-Launches-Deep-Tech-Fund-with-Accelerator-Model/69931c1a2e6a0b8ae17d320b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/ValleyNXT-Launches-Deep-Tech-Fund-with-Accelerator-Model/69931c1a2e6a0b8ae17d320b</guid><description>ValleyNXT Ventures has launched the SEBI-registered Bharat Breakthrough Fund–I, a ₹400 crore venture capital fund targeting seed to pre-Series A deep-tech and technology-first startups. The fund differentiates itself through a 'VC-plus-accelerator' model, integrating capital with hands-on mentorship and business connections to address critical early-stage failure points beyond mere financial backing. This initiative aims to support companies in crucial sectors like AI, space, defence tech, and biotech, navigating the challenging validation-to-scale phase.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:31:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69931c1a2e6a0b8ae17d320a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NCL Industries Profit Soars 14% Despite Revenue Dip; Rs 10,000 Cr Expansion Planned</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCL-Industries-Profit-Soars-14percent-Despite-Revenue-Dip-Rs-10000-Cr-Expansion-Planned/69931ab42e6a0b8ae17d30ff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NCL-Industries-Profit-Soars-14percent-Despite-Revenue-Dip-Rs-10000-Cr-Expansion-Planned/69931ab42e6a0b8ae17d30ff</guid><description>NCL Industries Limited saw its net profit jump 14.41% year-on-year to ₹127 crore in the third quarter of FY26, driven by operational efficiencies. However, revenue declined 22.44% to ₹197 crore. For the nine months of FY26, revenue grew 48.56% to ₹4082.77 crore, but net profit fell 13.93% to ₹173.96 crore. The company also announced ambitious expansion plans worth ₹10,000 crore, focusing on debt optimization.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:25:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69931ab42e6a0b8ae17d30fe.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Marathon Realty Hits Record Profit, Becomes Debt-Free</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Marathon-Realty-Hits-Record-Profit-Becomes-Debt-Free/699319c12e6a0b8ae17d3039</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Marathon-Realty-Hits-Record-Profit-Becomes-Debt-Free/699319c12e6a0b8ae17d3039</guid><description>Marathon Nextgen Realty Ltd. has achieved a significant financial milestone, reporting its highest-ever nine-month profit after tax (PAT) of ₹161 crore for the period ended December 31, 2025. The company also successfully eliminated its debt, maintaining a net debt-free position. This strong performance is driven by robust sales from its commercial projects and steady progress in its residential developments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:21:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699319c12e6a0b8ae17d3038_1771248238624.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Juniper Hotels Profit Skyrockets 101% on Record Sales and Margin Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Juniper-Hotels-Profit-Skyrockets-101percent-on-Record-Sales-and-Margin-Gains/699319562e6a0b8ae17d2fbf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Juniper-Hotels-Profit-Skyrockets-101percent-on-Record-Sales-and-Margin-Gains/699319562e6a0b8ae17d2fbf</guid><description>Juniper Hotels reported a stellar Q3 FY'26, with profit after tax soaring 101% year-on-year to INR65 crore, driven by a 15% revenue increase and expanding EBITDA margins. The luxury hotel chain highlighted strong demand across its portfolio, progress on key expansion projects in Bengaluru and Guwahati, and a healthy financial position with a debt-to-EBITDA ratio of 1.3x. Management remains confident in achieving full-year targets, bolstered by the Indian hospitality market's robust growth prospects.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:19:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699319562e6a0b8ae17d2fbe.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>H.G. Infra Wins ₹154 Cr Gujarat Toll Contract Amidst CBI Probe Shadows</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HG-Infra-Wins-154-Cr-Gujarat-Toll-Contract-Amidst-CBI-Probe-Shadows/699318d22e6a0b8ae17d2f5f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/HG-Infra-Wins-154-Cr-Gujarat-Toll-Contract-Amidst-CBI-Probe-Shadows/699318d22e6a0b8ae17d2f5f</guid><description>H.G. Infra Engineering Limited (HGINFRA) has secured a significant Letter of Acceptance (LOA) from the National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) for operations at the Moti Naroli Fee Plaza in Gujarat. The contract is valued at ₹154.6 Crores. This award offers a revenue visibility boost, but comes amidst growing concerns over the company's high debt levels, slow-moving order book, and a recent Central Bureau of Investigation (CBI) probe.</description><pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 13:17:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699318d22e6a0b8ae17d2f5e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>