<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:44:09 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Nifty Breach Signals Near-Term Weakness: Target Sectors</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Nifty-Breach-Signals-Near-Term-Weakness-Target-Sectors/6997e310057e346edab3ae96</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Nifty-Breach-Signals-Near-Term-Weakness-Target-Sectors/6997e310057e346edab3ae96</guid><description>The Nifty index has fallen below its 20-day moving average, marking a potential turn in market sentiment. Analysts point to critical support levels at 25,100 and 24,718 for the Nifty, while Bank Nifty faces headwinds. Investors are advised to target underperforming sectors like Information Technology, Real Estate, and Fast-Moving Consumer Goods, and consider hedging strategies as global geopolitical tensions and FII outflows increase market volatility. The India VIX has seen a notable jump, reinforcing cautious sentiment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:29:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997e310057e346edab3ae95.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nvidia-OpenAI Deal Reshapes AI Investment Landscape</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nvidia-OpenAI-Deal-Reshapes-AI-Investment-Landscape/6997e2a2057e346edab3ae11</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nvidia-OpenAI-Deal-Reshapes-AI-Investment-Landscape/6997e2a2057e346edab3ae11</guid><description>Nvidia is finalizing a $30 billion investment in OpenAI, revising a prior $100 billion commitment. This move is part of OpenAI's broader $100 billion+ funding round, valuing the AI leader at approximately $730 billion pre-money. The investment prioritizes OpenAI's direct reinvestment into Nvidia hardware, reflecting a strategic recalibration amid AI market caution and escalating compute demands. Despite broader tech sector headwinds, analysts maintain a bullish stance on Nvidia, citing its dominant market position and strong fundamentals.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:27:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997e2a2057e346edab3ae10.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dabur India: Bullish Call vs. Market Doubt?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Dabur-India-Bullish-Call-vs-Market-Doubt/6997e29e057e346edab3adf7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Dabur-India-Bullish-Call-vs-Market-Doubt/6997e29e057e346edab3adf7</guid><description>Dabur India's stock is under scrutiny following Nuvama Institutional Equities' 'Buy' rating and a ₹605 target price, implying a 17% potential upside. This bullish stance contrasts with a mixed analyst consensus, recent profit declines, and tepid stock performance, raising questions about the efficacy of growth catalysts and the company's ability to overcome market headwinds.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:27:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997e29e057e346edab3adf6_1771561772007.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GC Unleashes $5B India Bet, Signaling AI &amp; Global Resilience Push</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/GC-Unleashes-5B-India-Bet-Signaling-AI-and-Global-Resilience-Push/6997e1c3057e346edab3acdf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Startups-VC/GC-Unleashes-5B-India-Bet-Signaling-AI-and-Global-Resilience-Push/6997e1c3057e346edab3acdf</guid><description>Venture capital giant General Catalyst announced a landmark $5 billion investment in India's startup ecosystem on February 20, 2026. This substantial commitment, following an $8 billion global fund raise, signifies an accelerated strategic focus on India's artificial intelligence capabilities and its unique potential to address large-scale societal challenges. The pledge highlights India's growing stature as a global innovation hub, bolstered by its young talent pool and expanding technological infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:23:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997e1c3057e346edab3acde_1771561513227.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SBI General Insurance: Growth Surge Amid Cost Pressures</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/SBI-General-Insurance-Growth-Surge-Amid-Cost-Pressures/6997e137057e346edab3ac46</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Insurance/SBI-General-Insurance-Growth-Surge-Amid-Cost-Pressures/6997e137057e346edab3ac46</guid><description>SBI General Insurance has posted a robust 14.5% growth in gross direct premium for the first nine months of FY26, significantly outpacing the industry's 8.7%. Driven by strong performance in health, motor, and personal accident segments, the company also improved its loss ratio and maintained a healthy solvency ratio. However, this expansion occurs against a backdrop of escalating industry-wide distribution costs and increasing regulatory attention on commission structures.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 04:21:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997e137057e346edab3ac45_1771561396006.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Pharma &amp; Hospitals: Bullish Bets Face Valuation Puzzles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Pharma-and-Hospitals-Bullish-Bets-Face-Valuation-Puzzles/6997dbc2057e346edab3a9be</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Pharma-and-Hospitals-Bullish-Bets-Face-Valuation-Puzzles/6997dbc2057e346edab3a9be</guid><description>Axis Securities maintains a bullish stance on the pharma and hospital sectors, highlighting Lupin, Aurobindo Pharma, Max Healthcare, and Fortis Healthcare as top picks due to robust fundamentals and growth prospects. However, the report contrasts emerging US market strengths and domestic pharma growth with significant valuation concerns in the hospital segment and potential margin pressures from capacity expansion. Pharmaceutical sector growth is projected, but declining US FDA filings suggest evolving product development strategies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 03:57:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997dbc2057e346edab3a9bd.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IndusInd Bank: Turnaround Hype Meets Reality Check</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IndusInd-Bank-Turnaround-Hype-Meets-Reality-Check/6997dbb0057e346edab3a9a5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IndusInd-Bank-Turnaround-Hype-Meets-Reality-Check/6997dbb0057e346edab3a9a5</guid><description>Emkay Global has upgraded IndusInd Bank to 'Buy' with a ₹1,100 target, citing a new CEO and turnaround potential. However, the bank exhibits a negative trailing twelve-month P/E ratio, indicating current unprofitability, and faces significant liabilities. Its valuation metrics, while lower than major peers, are weighed against a history of governance issues and intense competition in the Indian banking sector.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 03:57:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997dbb0057e346edab3a9a4_1771559962999.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Luggage Wars: Safari's Premium Soars, VIP Eyes Turnaround</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/India-Luggage-Wars-Safaris-Premium-Soars-VIP-Eyes-Turnaround/6997dbae057e346edab3a98e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/India-Luggage-Wars-Safaris-Premium-Soars-VIP-Eyes-Turnaround/6997dbae057e346edab3a98e</guid><description>India's luggage industry faces heightened discounting and demand softness, but a recovery is anticipated in the first half of FY27. Safari Industries demonstrates robust revenue growth driven by volume, bolstered by a significant QIP for expansion. In contrast, VIP Industries reported a revenue decline, with its outlook dependent on a turnaround strategy under new private equity-backed leadership. While Safari commands a premium valuation, VIP's negative P/E ratio highlights its current financial challenges and reliance on future performance improvements.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 03:57:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997dbae057e346edab3a98d.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RIL's $110B AI Bet: Growth Pivot or Funding Risk?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/RILs-110B-AI-Bet-Growth-Pivot-or-Funding-Risk/6997db23057e346edab3a8e0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/RILs-110B-AI-Bet-Growth-Pivot-or-Funding-Risk/6997db23057e346edab3a8e0</guid><description>Reliance Industries announced a monumental ₹10 lakh crore ($110 billion) investment over seven years to build India's AI ecosystem. Morgan Stanley tagged it a 'top pick' with an 18% upside target. However, the sheer scale of this ambition, while positioning Reliance for future growth, also presents significant funding and execution challenges amidst intense global competition.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 03:55:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997db23057e346edab3a8df.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>CSB Bank: Gold Loan Strength Outshines Earnings Dip, Valuation Attracts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/CSB-Bank-Gold-Loan-Strength-Outshines-Earnings-Dip-Valuation-Attracts/6997daa0057e346edab3a830</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/CSB-Bank-Gold-Loan-Strength-Outshines-Earnings-Dip-Valuation-Attracts/6997daa0057e346edab3a830</guid><description>CSB Bank's stock has experienced a significant decline following muted Q3 FY26 earnings, impacted by asset quality concerns and elevated credit costs. Despite these near-term pressures, the bank's robust gold loan portfolio, outperforming advance growth compared to industry peers, and an attractive valuation relative to competitors, suggest underlying strength. While margin expansion faces competition headwinds, strategic growth in gold loans and future operational efficiencies may drive a valuation re-rating.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 03:53:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997daa0057e346edab3a82f_1771559747837.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Small Caps Face Earnings Gap: Valuations Still Stretched?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Small-Caps-Face-Earnings-Gap-Valuations-Still-Stretched/6997da9f057e346edab3a819</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Small-Caps-Face-Earnings-Gap-Valuations-Still-Stretched/6997da9f057e346edab3a819</guid><description>Recent market corrections have led to nearly half of Indian small-cap stocks trading approximately 40% below their all-time highs. However, analysis reveals a significant disconnect: while large-cap earnings are robust, small-cap companies exhibit a higher miss rate in quarterly results. This, coupled with still elevated P/E multiples for small caps relative to their earnings consistency, presents a complex investment scenario requiring careful assessment of risk and reward.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 03:53:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997da9f057e346edab3a818_1771559713667.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Solar Open Access Record: Waiver Rush Masks Real Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Solar-Open-Access-Record-Waiver-Rush-Masks-Real-Demand/6997d93c057e346edab3a714</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Solar-Open-Access-Record-Waiver-Rush-Masks-Real-Demand/6997d93c057e346edab3a714</guid><description>India's corporate solar open access segment posted a record 7.8 GW of installations in 2025, marginally surpassing 2024. However, this growth was front-loaded, driven by a rush before the ISTS charge waiver expiry in June. The fourth quarter saw a 29% sequential decline, indicating regulatory influence rather than demand weakness. Despite a robust pipeline, the phasing out of the ISTS waiver and volatility in green energy certificates signal underlying market recalibration and emerging risks for sustained growth.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 03:47:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997d93c057e346edab3a713_1771559437925.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cement Rally Faces Pricing Test Amid Capacity Spree</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cement-Rally-Faces-Pricing-Test-Amid-Capacity-Spree/6997d760057e346edab3a627</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Cement-Rally-Faces-Pricing-Test-Amid-Capacity-Spree/6997d760057e346edab3a627</guid><description>Indian cement prices have seen a modest recovery, boosted by seasonal demand and infrastructure spending. Major players are aggressively expanding capacity, aiming for significant volume growth. However, signs of demand plateauing and intense competition raise concerns about sustained pricing power, potentially complicating earnings recovery despite strong volume outlooks for FY26.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 03:39:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997d760057e346edab3a626_1771558895950.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Cement Sector Faces Expansion Boom: Oversupply Fears Mount</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Cement-Sector-Faces-Expansion-Boom-Oversupply-Fears-Mount/6997d41d057e346edab3a478</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Cement-Sector-Faces-Expansion-Boom-Oversupply-Fears-Mount/6997d41d057e346edab3a478</guid><description>India's cement sector is poised for substantial capacity growth, with 158 million tonnes planned by FY28. While consolidation is ongoing, the sheer scale of new additions, particularly in the North, raises concerns about potential oversupply, pricing pressure, and margin erosion despite operational efficiencies. Brokerage analyses highlight a complex outlook, balancing growth potential against risks of increased competition and weaker profitability, with specific scrutiny on companies like JSW Cement.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 03:25:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997d41d057e346edab3a477_1771558065392.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ABB India's Order Surge Met by Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ABB-Indias-Order-Surge-Met-by-Valuation-Concerns/6997d416057e346edab3a461</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ABB-Indias-Order-Surge-Met-by-Valuation-Concerns/6997d416057e346edab3a461</guid><description>ABB India's fourth-quarter results revealed a significant 52% year-on-year surge in orders, reaching ₹4,096 crore, and a 6% increase in revenue to ₹3,557 crore. However, profitability declined, with Profit After Tax (PAT) falling 18.4% to ₹434 crore due to inflationary pressures and higher labor costs. Analysts are divided, with a consensus target price suggesting a potential downside, citing the stock's high valuation multiples.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 03:25:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997d416057e346edab3a460_1771558065133.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ola Electric Halves Stores Amidst Deepening Investor Crisis</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electric-Halves-Stores-Amidst-Deepening-Investor-Crisis/6997d415057e346edab3a44a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Ola-Electric-Halves-Stores-Amidst-Deepening-Investor-Crisis/6997d415057e346edab3a44a</guid><description>Ola Electric Mobility is drastically reducing its physical store count to 550 by March, a stark reversal from its previous aggressive expansion. This move coincides with a wave of analyst downgrades, including 'Sell' ratings from Citi and Emkay, citing market share erosion, persistent service issues, and intense competition. The company's stock has plummeted nearly 50% in six months, reflecting deep investor concern over its financial viability and competitive positioning in India's expanding EV market.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 03:25:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997d415057e346edab3a449_1771558048090.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nvidia Shifts $100B Commitment to $30B Stake in OpenAI</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nvidia-Shifts-100B-Commitment-to-30B-Stake-in-OpenAI/6997d328057e346edab3a36b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nvidia-Shifts-100B-Commitment-to-30B-Stake-in-OpenAI/6997d328057e346edab3a36b</guid><description>Nvidia is finalizing a $30 billion equity investment in OpenAI, a significant pivot from its previously announced $100 billion long-term infrastructure commitment. This strategic adjustment is part of OpenAI's latest $100 billion funding round, which values the AI powerhouse at approximately $830 billion post-investment. The change suggests a recalibration of capital deployment strategies amidst evolving AI market dynamics and concerns over sustainability.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 03:21:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997d328057e346edab3a36a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Oil Shock Rattles Markets; ABB India Navigates Margin Squeeze</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Oil-Shock-Rattles-Markets-ABB-India-Navigates-Margin-Squeeze/6997d1bb057e346edab3a2ab</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Oil-Shock-Rattles-Markets-ABB-India-Navigates-Margin-Squeeze/6997d1bb057e346edab3a2ab</guid><description>Indian equity benchmarks are poised for a flat opening, weighed down by a six-month high in oil prices driven by US-Iran tensions and continued foreign investor outflows. ABB India's December quarter saw profits decline 18% year-on-year despite revenue growth, citing input cost inflation. Meanwhile, Texmaco Rail &amp; Engineering and Rail Vikas Nigam (RVNL) have inked a strategic joint venture to bolster railway manufacturing and EPC projects, aiming to capture future infrastructure demand.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 03:15:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997d1bb057e346edab3a2aa.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>₹1 Crore Goal: Inflation's Hidden Tax vs. Investment Reality</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/1-Crore-Goal-Inflations-Hidden-Tax-vs-Investment-Reality/6997cfdc057e346edab3a1e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Personal-Finance/1-Crore-Goal-Inflations-Hidden-Tax-vs-Investment-Reality/6997cfdc057e346edab3a1e1</guid><description>The widely promoted goal of accumulating a ₹1 crore corpus is presented as attainable through disciplined savings and moderate investment returns. However, persistent inflation significantly diminishes the real value of this target, while behavioral challenges like lifestyle creep and inconsistent investment discipline pose substantial execution risks. Achieving this milestone requires a more realistic outlook than simplistic calculations often suggest.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 03:07:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997cfdc057e346edab3a1e0_1771556953194.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ICICI Pru AMC: Premium Valuation Tested Amidst Growth &amp; Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/ICICI-Pru-AMC-Premium-Valuation-Tested-Amidst-Growth-and-Risks/6997cd35057e346edab3a085</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/ICICI-Pru-AMC-Premium-Valuation-Tested-Amidst-Growth-and-Risks/6997cd35057e346edab3a085</guid><description>Antique Stock Broking launched coverage on ICICI Prudential Asset Management Company (AMC) with a 'Buy' rating and a ₹3,600 target, citing superior execution and growth prospects. The company's Q3FY26 net profit jumped 45% to ₹917 crore, driven by robust AUM growth and strong SIP flows. However, its current TTM P/E of around 46.4x is elevated compared to peers, even as it leads in hybrid and passive segments and demonstrates strong fund performance.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:55:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997cd35057e346edab3a084_1771556246336.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Banks: Structural Savings Shift Outpaces RBI Liquidity</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Banks-Structural-Savings-Shift-Outpaces-RBI-Liquidity/6997cd29057e346edab3a06c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Banks-Structural-Savings-Shift-Outpaces-RBI-Liquidity/6997cd29057e346edab3a06c</guid><description>Indian banks are navigating a complex liquidity environment, with RBI interventions largely offset by forex sales. However, deeper structural shifts in household savings away from bank deposits towards mutual funds and equities, coupled with diminishing regulatory liquidity buffers, present a more significant long-term challenge. This dynamic is expected to constrain future deposit accretion and loan growth, potentially widening the performance gap between private and public sector banks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:55:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997cd29057e346edab3a06b_1771556246056.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TCS Bets Big on AI: OpenAI Partnership Sparks Valuation Debate</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TCS-Bets-Big-on-AI-OpenAI-Partnership-Sparks-Valuation-Debate/6997cc97057e346edab39fa8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TCS-Bets-Big-on-AI-OpenAI-Partnership-Sparks-Valuation-Debate/6997cc97057e346edab39fa8</guid><description>Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) has forged a strategic alliance with OpenAI, positioning itself for an AI-driven future. Morgan Stanley maintains an 'Overweight' rating, seeing parallels to cloud adoption's impact and highlighting the long-term optionality of TCS's data center business. Despite recent stock depreciation amid AI disruption fears, the partnership aims to leverage AI infrastructure and develop industry-specific solutions, potentially shifting investor valuation models to a sum-of-the-parts approach. TCS's market capitalization is approximately ₹9.8 lakh crore, with a P/E ratio around 35.20x.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:53:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997cc97057e346edab39fa7.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Lenskart: Can Sky-High Valuation Withstand Retail Headwinds?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Lenskart-Can-Sky-High-Valuation-Withstand-Retail-Headwinds/6997cc94057e346edab39f8e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Lenskart-Can-Sky-High-Valuation-Withstand-Retail-Headwinds/6997cc94057e346edab39f8e</guid><description>Eyewear giant Lenskart Solutions posted robust Q3 FY26 results, with revenue up 38% and net profit surging multifold, leading to a 12-13% stock rally and new target prices. Analysts are optimistic, projecting substantial growth. However, Lenskart's market capitalization of over ₹83,000 crore and a P/E ratio exceeding 200x raise concerns about valuation sustainability, especially when contrasted with sector peers and evolving consumer spending patterns.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:53:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997cc94057e346edab39f8d_1771556125710.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gaudium IVF IPO Launches: Growth Ambitions Meet High Attrition Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Gaudium-IVF-IPO-Launches-Growth-Ambitions-Meet-High-Attrition-Risk/6997ca3f057e346edab39e2d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Gaudium-IVF-IPO-Launches-Growth-Ambitions-Meet-High-Attrition-Risk/6997ca3f057e346edab39e2d</guid><description>Gaudium IVF is launching its ₹165 crore Initial Public Offering, aiming to fund the establishment of 19 new IVF centers and repay debt. The company operates within India's rapidly expanding fertility services market, driven by declining birth rates and increasing awareness. Anchor investors have already committed ₹49.5 crore. While the IPO exhibits strong financial metrics and a promising market opportunity, potential investors must weigh the aggressive expansion against significant employee attrition rates and operational complexities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:43:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997ca3f057e346edab39e2c_1771555514268.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Market Divergence: Bulls Back Select Stocks Amidst Index Weakness</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Market-Divergence-Bulls-Back-Select-Stocks-Amidst-Index-Weakness/6997c8d5057e346edab39d67</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Indian-Market-Divergence-Bulls-Back-Select-Stocks-Amidst-Index-Weakness/6997c8d5057e346edab39d67</guid><description>Indian equity indices Nifty and Bank Nifty showed sharp declines, signalling increased selling pressure and cautious near-term bias. Despite this, Bajaj Broking Research has recommended IndusInd Bank and UPL for purchase, targeting significant returns over three months. This divergence highlights potential sector-specific resilience or unique catalysts at play within specific stocks, contrasting with the broader market's bearish sentiment.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:37:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997c8d5057e346edab39d66.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Defense Procurement: Escalating Costs, Stagnant Capabilities</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Defense-Procurement-Escalating-Costs-Stagnant-Capabilities/6997c513057e346edab3842f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Defense-Procurement-Escalating-Costs-Stagnant-Capabilities/6997c513057e346edab3842f</guid><description>India's pursuit of an modernized air force is mired in systemic procurement inefficiencies, leading to escalating costs and strategic vulnerability. Despite significant spending, the Indian Air Force (IAF) remains critically understrength, with indigenous programs facing chronic delays and foreign dependence persisting. The recurring cycles of tenders, exorbitant enhancement costs, and failure to secure genuine technology transfer highlight a pattern of financial drain and compromised defense capabilities. With a new 114-jet tender on the horizon, the risk of repeating these costly missteps and perpetuating strategic dependency looms large.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:21:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997c513057e346edab3842e_1771554200121.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HFCL Acquisition Buzz Meets Valuation Reality Check</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/HFCL-Acquisition-Buzz-Meets-Valuation-Reality-Check/6997c2ed057e346edab382a1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/HFCL-Acquisition-Buzz-Meets-Valuation-Reality-Check/6997c2ed057e346edab382a1</guid><description>HFCL's stock has seen speculative interest flagged as a potential acquisition target, pushing its price near ₹73. However, this optimism contrasts sharply with its extremely high P/E ratio, which hovers around 200-300x, significantly above historical averages and peers. Despite recent quarterly revenue growth, the company's FY25 profits and EBITDA declined year-on-year, and key profitability metrics like ROE remain low, signaling underlying financial pressures that investors may be overlooking amid the acquisition speculation.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 02:11:57 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997c2ed057e346edab382a0.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US-Indonesia Trade Deal: Critical Minerals Fuel Geopolitical Gambit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Indonesia-Trade-Deal-Critical-Minerals-Fuel-Geopolitical-Gambit/6997be3e057e346edab3813f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Indonesia-Trade-Deal-Critical-Minerals-Fuel-Geopolitical-Gambit/6997be3e057e346edab3813f</guid><description>The United States and Indonesia have concluded a comprehensive trade agreement, finalizing terms that include significant reductions in US tariffs on Indonesian goods and a commitment for Jakarta to facilitate substantial purchases of American products, totaling an estimated $33 billion. A key, strategic element of the accord focuses on critical minerals, aligning with the US objective to diversify supply chains away from China. This move, however, places Indonesia in a delicate geopolitical position, potentially exacerbating its existing economic fragilities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 01:51:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997be3e057e346edab3813e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Boosts Offshore Wind Subsidies Amidst Cost Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/India-Boosts-Offshore-Wind-Subsidies-Amidst-Cost-Hurdles/6997bb7a057e346edab38002</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/India-Boosts-Offshore-Wind-Subsidies-Amidst-Cost-Hurdles/6997bb7a057e346edab38002</guid><description>New Delhi is considering a substantial increase to its Viability Gap Funding (VGF) scheme for offshore wind energy projects, tasking the World Bank and KPMG to assess financial needs. This move follows a failed tender for a 1 GW project and aims to attract greater investor participation. However, offshore wind's inherently high capital expenditure and operational costs continue to pose significant challenges against cheaper energy alternatives, raising questions about the long-term viability despite enhanced subsidies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 01:40:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997bb7a057e346edab38001.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>HUL's India Pivot: Premium Push Meets Growth Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/HULs-India-Pivot-Premium-Push-Meets-Growth-Headwinds/6997b4ad057e346edab37df7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/HULs-India-Pivot-Premium-Push-Meets-Growth-Headwinds/6997b4ad057e346edab37df7</guid><description>Hindustan Unilever (HUL) is reorienting its strategy to elevate the US and India's combined revenue contribution to 45%, from the current 33%. This involves a strong emphasis on premiumizing its Indian portfolio to 50% of offerings and expanding digital commerce. The company has also signaled intent for strategic acquisitions in India and is under new leadership with Priya Nair at the helm. However, despite these initiatives, analysts highlight concerns over decelerating earnings growth and increasing market competition, leading to target price revisions and a cautious outlook for the consumer giant.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 01:11:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997b4ad057e346edab37df6.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Atul Auto's EV Pivot: Rural Bet Faces Fierce Competition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Atul-Autos-EV-Pivot-Rural-Bet-Faces-Fierce-Competition/6997b3c1057e346edab37cfb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Atul-Autos-EV-Pivot-Rural-Bet-Faces-Fierce-Competition/6997b3c1057e346edab37cfb</guid><description>Atul Auto has merged its electric vehicle (EV) business into the parent company, aiming for sales synergy and balance sheet clarity. While investor Vijay Kedia's long-term conviction highlights the company's rural focus and engineering heritage, the transition is set against a backdrop of escalating competition from Bajaj Auto and Mahindra &amp; Mahindra, and significant volatility in battery material costs. The company's target of 30% volume growth for FY27 will test its ability to navigate these demanding market dynamics.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 01:07:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997b3c1057e346edab37cfa_1771549868184.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Trio: Divergent Paths in a Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Trio-Divergent-Paths-in-a-Boom/6997b3c0057e346edab37ce4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-AI-Trio-Divergent-Paths-in-a-Boom/6997b3c0057e346edab37ce4</guid><description>As India champions its sovereign AI ecosystem with a ₹10,300 crore mission, three companies—Netweb Technologies, Aurionpro Solutions, and E2E Networks—are carving distinct niches. Netweb drives AI hardware innovation, Aurionpro redefines enterprise software, and E2E Networks builds critical cloud infrastructure. Their vastly different financial metrics and strategic plays reveal a spectrum of opportunities and risks in India's AI gold rush.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 01:07:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997b3c0057e346edab37ce3.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Electronics Boom: Profitability Under Pressure?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Electronics-Boom-Profitability-Under-Pressure/6997b3bc057e346edab37ccd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indias-Electronics-Boom-Profitability-Under-Pressure/6997b3bc057e346edab37ccd</guid><description>India's electronics manufacturing sector is experiencing robust growth, fueled by Production Linked Incentive (PLI) schemes and global supply chain realignments. Companies like Dixon Technologies, Syrma SGS, Kaynes Technology, and Netweb Technologies are rapidly expanding production and investing heavily in new capacities. However, this expansion comes with significant risks. Persistent margin pressures, escalating input costs, and increasingly demanding valuations suggest that the sector's rapid growth may not translate directly into sustainable profitability, posing a critical challenge for investors.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 01:07:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997b3bc057e346edab37ccc_1771549883134.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Accenture Bets AI on Growth, Redefining Markets for SMEs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Accenture-Bets-AI-on-Growth-Redefining-Markets-for-SMEs/6997b258057e346edab37bc6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Accenture-Bets-AI-on-Growth-Redefining-Markets-for-SMEs/6997b258057e346edab37bc6</guid><description>Accenture's strategic pivot emphasizes AI's role in driving enterprise growth, not just efficiency. CEO Julie Sweet highlighted Large Language Models (LLMs) as new marketplaces enabling Small and Medium-sized Enterprises (SMEs) global access. The company faces significant adoption hurdles and evolving market dynamics within the IT services sector, with analysts offering a mixed but generally positive outlook on its AI-centric transformation. Accenture's fiscal year 2025 performance showed strong revenue growth driven by substantial AI investments, though market sentiment has seen recent volatility.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 01:01:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997b258057e346edab37bc5_1771549392969.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Stocks Dip as Financial Fears, Geopolitics Spark Caution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/US-Stocks-Dip-as-Financial-Fears-Geopolitics-Spark-Caution/6997b077057e346edab37abe</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/US-Stocks-Dip-as-Financial-Fears-Geopolitics-Spark-Caution/6997b077057e346edab37abe</guid><description>US equities declined on Thursday, pushing the S&amp;P 500 near flat year-to-date. Financials led losses after Blue Owl Capital tightened liquidity, fueling private credit jitters. Tech stocks remained under pressure from AI disruption fears, while geopolitical tensions and a cautious retail outlook from Walmart added to investor unease. This market pullback confirms a shift in leadership, as investors recalibrate portfolios amid rising systemic risks.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:53:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997b077057e346edab37abd.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI's Ethics Mandate: Indian Banks Face Sales Overhaul</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-Ethics-Mandate-Indian-Banks-Face-Sales-Overhaul/6997ae1c057e346edab379b9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBIs-Ethics-Mandate-Indian-Banks-Face-Sales-Overhaul/6997ae1c057e346edab379b9</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India (RBI) is elevating banking ethics from a 'soft theme' to a core operational imperative, introducing stringent draft guidelines on product advertising and sales. This regulatory shift compels financial institutions to embed transparency and 'inward honesty' across all functions, from frontline staff interactions to digital lending processes. The move targets historical mis-selling issues and aggressive sales tactics, signaling increased compliance burdens and a potential recalibration of revenue models heavily reliant on product commissions.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:43:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997ae1c057e346edab379b8_1771548328798.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Reboots AI Race: Local Intel Trumps Global Scale</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Reboots-AI-Race-Local-Intel-Trumps-Global-Scale/6997adad057e346edab37912</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Reboots-AI-Race-Local-Intel-Trumps-Global-Scale/6997adad057e346edab37912</guid><description>India's AI sector is undergoing a strategic transformation, moving beyond sheer parameter counts to prioritize deep linguistic and cultural relevance. Companies like Sarvam AI and BharatGen are launching sophisticated models tailored for India's diverse populace, aiming for a "sovereign AI" capability. This approach, bolstered by government initiatives like the IndiaAI Mission and significant funding, positions India to lead not just in AI development, but in creating AI that truly understands and serves its unique 1.4 billion population, potentially offering a competitive edge over globally focused giants.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:41:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997adad057e346edab37911.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Qualcomm Taps India for Global Auto Modules: Resilience Play</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Qualcomm-Taps-India-for-Global-Auto-Modules-Resilience-Play/6997ad2c057e346edab378b9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Qualcomm-Taps-India-for-Global-Auto-Modules-Resilience-Play/6997ad2c057e346edab378b9</guid><description>Qualcomm is expanding its manufacturing footprint in India by partnering to produce and source automotive modules, aiming to bolster global supply chain resilience and leverage the nation's R&amp;D capabilities. This strategic move diversifies production away from traditional East Asian hubs, aligning with India's growing semiconductor ecosystem and government incentives. While the company faces headwinds from memory chip shortages impacting its core smartphone business, the India initiative signals a long-term commitment to growth in automotive and AI sectors. Qualcomm's valuation, with a P/E ratio of approximately 29x, positions it favorably against semiconductor industry averages, though execution risks and competitive pressures remain key considerations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:39:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6997ad2c057e346edab378b8_1771548144468.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Infosys Chief: Use Cases, Not Tech Race, Key for India's AI Lead</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-Chief-Use-Cases-Not-Tech-Race-Key-for-Indias-AI-Lead/6997a81b057e346edab3773f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-Chief-Use-Cases-Not-Tech-Race-Key-for-Indias-AI-Lead/6997a81b057e346edab3773f</guid><description>Infosys Chairman Nandan Nilekani has cautioned that uncontrolled AI proliferation could alienate white-collar workers, potentially triggering an "AI train wreck." He advocates for India to seize leadership in developing beneficial AI use cases, emphasizing responsible diffusion and societal integration over a purely technological race. This strategic pivot is critical for the Indian IT sector amidst intensifying AI disruption and macroeconomic headwinds impacting valuations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:17:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-6997a81b057e346edab3773e.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>