<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:39:22 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India Budget 2026: Tech Bets, STT Hike Rattles Bourses</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Budget-2026-Tech-Bets-STT-Hike-Rattles-Bourses/697f45ee47db7081af636665</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-Budget-2026-Tech-Bets-STT-Hike-Rattles-Bourses/697f45ee47db7081af636665</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman unveiled the 2026-27 Union Budget, emphasizing technology sectors like AI, deep tech, and semiconductors as drivers for 'Viksit Bharat'. Key initiatives include Bharat-VISTAAR for agri-tech and an expanded India Semiconductor Mission 2.0. However, an increase in the Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on derivative trades led to immediate market turbulence, with the BSE experiencing a significant price drop. This signals investor caution despite ambitious growth plans.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:28:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f45ee47db7081af636664_1769948866058.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Solar Ambitions Soar: Budget 2026 Fuels Homes &amp; Farms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Solar-Ambitions-Soar-Budget-2026-Fuels-Homes-and-Farms/697f44a447db7081af636377</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Indias-Solar-Ambitions-Soar-Budget-2026-Fuels-Homes-and-Farms/697f44a447db7081af636377</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-2027 champions India's solar energy push with a ₹28,000 crore allocation towards household autonomy and agricultural resilience. Key initiatives include substantial funding for rooftop solar installations and farmer energy security, alongside critical customs duty reductions on raw materials for solar glass manufacturing. This strategic fiscal manoeuvre aims to bolster domestic renewable manufacturing and advance scientific research infrastructure in solar technology.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:26:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f44a447db7081af636376_1769948810621.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026-27: Retail Sector Gears Up for Growth Reforms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Budget-2026-27-Retail-Sector-Gears-Up-for-Growth-Reforms/697f448b47db7081af6362aa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Budget-2026-27-Retail-Sector-Gears-Up-for-Growth-Reforms/697f448b47db7081af6362aa</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 proposes a comprehensive strategy to invigorate India's retail sector. Key initiatives include bolstering grassroots entrepreneurship via SHE Marts, accelerating digital integration by removing e-commerce value caps, and stimulating consumer spending through tariff reductions on personal imports and tax relief. Infrastructure upgrades and dedicated MSME support funds are also slated to professionalize and scale retail operations nationwide.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:24:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f448b47db7081af6362a9_1769948637317.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Energy Security, Green Push Drive Infrastructure Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Budget-2026-Energy-Security-Green-Push-Drive-Infrastructure-Growth/697f439547db7081af6360a8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Budget-2026-Energy-Security-Green-Push-Drive-Infrastructure-Growth/697f439547db7081af6360a8</guid><description>India's Budget 2026-27 champions energy security and a green transition, treating energy as a strategic economic pillar. Significant allocations target solar power expansion and grid-scale storage, alongside extended incentives for nuclear energy and carbon capture technologies. The budget aims to enhance infrastructure financing and grid stability, steering investment towards companies focused on integrated energy systems and clean fuel economics.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:22:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f439547db7081af6360a7_1769948534199.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Bond Market Braces for Record Supply</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Budget-2026-Bond-Market-Braces-for-Record-Supply/697f42ba47db7081af635e8b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/India-Budget-2026-Bond-Market-Braces-for-Record-Supply/697f42ba47db7081af635e8b</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 shifts India's fiscal anchor to the debt-to-GDP ratio, targeting 50% by FY31, while projecting a fiscal deficit of 4.3% for FY27. Concurrently, the bond market faces a significant supply surge, with combined central and state government security issuances estimated at ₹30.2 trillion. This comes as bank deposit growth lags credit demand, pushing the credit-to-deposit ratio to a record 82%, constraining investor appetite. Analysts anticipate continued pressure on yields, with the Reserve Bank of India expected to play a crucial role in managing market liquidity.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:20:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f42ba47db7081af635e8a_1769948403687.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Market Slumps Amidst Opposition Barrage</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Market-Slumps-Amidst-Opposition-Barrage/697f42a547db7081af635df0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Market-Slumps-Amidst-Opposition-Barrage/697f42a547db7081af635df0</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026-27 has been met with widespread criticism from opposition parties, who deem it out of touch with ground realities. While Prime Minister Modi hailed it as a milestone, market indices reacted sharply. The Sensex plummeted over 1,500 points, and the Nifty 50 saw significant losses, largely attributed to an increase in the Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on derivatives trading. Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman highlighted a record capital expenditure target of ₹12.2 lakh crore for FY27 and projected a fiscal deficit of 4.3% of GDP.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:17:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f42a547db7081af635def_1769948261898.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026 Allocates ₹9,000 Cr for MSME Credit Lifeline</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Allocates-9000-Cr-for-MSME-Credit-Lifeline/697f41c847db7081af635be1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Allocates-9000-Cr-for-MSME-Credit-Lifeline/697f41c847db7081af635be1</guid><description>In its Union Budget 2026, the government has earmarked ₹9,000 crore for the Guaranteed Emergency Credit Line (GECL) facility. This allocation aims to bolster micro, small, and medium enterprises (MSMEs) facing ongoing liquidity challenges stemming from global trade disruptions and domestic economic shifts. The GECL is a successor to the highly impactful Emergency Credit Line Guarantee Scheme (ECLGS), which provided significant succor during the pandemic years.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:15:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f41c847db7081af635be0_1769948133854.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian Defence Stocks Tumble Post-Budget Despite Spending Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Indian-Defence-Stocks-Tumble-Post-Budget-Despite-Spending-Surge/697f41b347db7081af635afa</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Indian-Defence-Stocks-Tumble-Post-Budget-Despite-Spending-Surge/697f41b347db7081af635afa</guid><description>The Union Budget FY2026-27 boosts India's defence outlay to ₹7.85 lakh crore, a 15.3% increase, with capital expenditure rising 21.8% to ₹2.19 lakh crore. Despite this, key defence stocks like Data Patterns, BEL, and HAL saw significant declines post-announcement, reversing pre-budget rallies. The budget emphasizes indigenisation, private sector R&amp;D via a ₹5,000 crore Deep-Tech Fund, and customs duty exemptions for aircraft parts, aiming to foster domestic manufacturing and modernization.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:13:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f41b347db7081af635af9_1769947999366.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Imposes Steep Penalties on Crypto Reporting</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/India-Imposes-Steep-Penalties-on-Crypto-Reporting/697f413e47db7081af635981</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Crypto/India-Imposes-Steep-Penalties-on-Crypto-Reporting/697f413e47db7081af635981</guid><description>India's Budget 2026 has enacted strict penalties for crypto-asset reporting non-compliance. Effective April 2, 2026, daily fines of Rs 200 and Rs 50,000 for inaccurate information will target undeclared virtual digital assets, following the CBDT's identification of Rs 888.82 crore in undeclared income.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:11:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f413e47db7081af635980_1769947877364.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Moody's: India Budget 'Tactical', Fiscal Gains Insufficient for Rating Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Moodys-India-Budget-Tactical-Fiscal-Gains-Insufficient-for-Rating-Boost/697f404147db7081af6355b1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Moodys-India-Budget-Tactical-Fiscal-Gains-Insufficient-for-Rating-Boost/697f404147db7081af6355b1</guid><description>Moody's Ratings characterized India's latest federal budget as "tactical" rather than a "breakthrough." The agency noted that planned fiscal consolidation, reducing the deficit from 4.4% to 4.3% of GDP, will not impact the nation's credit profile. Senior vice president Christian de Guzman stated that despite deficit consolidation efforts, the current deficit remains wider than pre-pandemic levels, and fiscal metrics have not improved sufficiently to warrant a rating change.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:08:50 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f404147db7081af6355b0_1769947726337.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026 Fuels Infra Boom: Road Spend Jumps 8%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Budget-2026-Fuels-Infra-Boom-Road-Spend-Jumps-8percent/697f402a47db7081af63547c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Budget-2026-Fuels-Infra-Boom-Road-Spend-Jumps-8percent/697f402a47db7081af63547c</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 allocates ₹3.09 lakh crore to the Ministry of Road Transport and Highways, an 8% increase from the prior fiscal, signaling sustained focus on national infrastructure. The National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) receives ₹1.87 lakh crore, as it targets debt reduction below ₹2 lakh crore. This substantial fiscal push, part of a ₹12.2 lakh crore total capital expenditure for the sector in FY27, aims to bolster economic activity and logistical efficiency. Initial market reactions saw infrastructure stocks, including Larsen &amp; Toubro and IRB Infrastructure Developers, experience gains.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:06:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f402a47db7081af63547b_1769947517632.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Union Budget Signals Strategic Boost for Tourism and Healthcare</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Union-Budget-Signals-Strategic-Boost-for-Tourism-and-Healthcare/697f400247db7081af635399</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Union-Budget-Signals-Strategic-Boost-for-Tourism-and-Healthcare/697f400247db7081af635399</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 has been met with positive reactions from key industry players. Brigade Hotel Ventures Ltd noted the 'strategic recognition' given to the tourism sector, emphasizing infrastructure and skilled human capital development. Meanwhile, Aarthi Scans and Labs lauded the budget for strengthening healthcare capacity, particularly in diagnostics and allied health professionals, signaling a robust investment-led approach.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:05:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f400247db7081af635398_1769947517517.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Tax Hikes on Derivatives, Buybacks Announced</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Tax-Hikes-on-Derivatives-Buybacks-Announced/697f3fb647db7081af6351f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Tax-Hikes-on-Derivatives-Buybacks-Announced/697f3fb647db7081af6351f9</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 signals a fiscal shift towards increased tax enforcement and procedural clarity. Key measures include a substantial increase in Securities Transaction Tax (STT) for derivatives, reimposing share buyback proceeds taxation as capital gains, and the enactment of a new Income Tax Act from April 1, 2026. Reductions in Tax Collection at Source (TCS) for overseas remittances and a one-time foreign asset disclosure window are also notable. These changes aim to refine tax collection and compliance for the upcoming assessment cycle.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:04:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f3fb647db7081af6351f8_1769947373091.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>MSME, Textile Sectors Get Budget Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/MSME-Textile-Sectors-Get-Budget-Boost/697f3f8d47db7081af6350ee</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/MSME-Textile-Sectors-Get-Budget-Boost/697f3f8d47db7081af6350ee</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 introduced substantial financial support for Micro, Small, and Medium Enterprises (MSMEs) with a ₹10,000-crore growth fund. The government also bolstered the Self-Reliant India Fund by ₹4,000 crore for 2026-27 and proposed an integrated textile program to address sector-specific challenges. Further measures include developing a 'corporate mitras' cadre for MSME support and initiatives for high-value agriculture.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 12:00:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f3f8d47db7081af6350ed_1769947235501.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Budget 2026: Fiscal Prudence Fuels Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-2026-Fiscal-Prudence-Fuels-Growth/697f3f5f47db7081af634fd3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-2026-Fiscal-Prudence-Fuels-Growth/697f3f5f47db7081af634fd3</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 outlines a strategic roadmap balancing fiscal discipline with ambitious growth targets and significant capital expenditure. Key initiatives aim to propel India towards becoming the world's third-largest economy by bolstering MSMEs, reforming capital markets, advancing clean energy, enhancing infrastructure, and simplifying compliance. The budget proposes sustained capital expenditure of ₹12.2 lakh crore and targets a fiscal deficit of 4.3% of GDP, signaling stability for long-term investors.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:58:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f3f5f47db7081af634fd2_1769947111952.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's INR 10,000 crore Mfg Push Targets China's Container Dominance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-INR-10000-crore-Mfg-Push-Targets-Chinas-Container-Dominance/697f3d9747db7081af634c74</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-INR-10000-crore-Mfg-Push-Targets-Chinas-Container-Dominance/697f3d9747db7081af634c74</guid><description>New Delhi has committed INR 10,000 crore to establish a domestic container manufacturing industry, a sector currently dominated by China with a 95% market share. This strategic move aims to reduce import dependency, create employment, and enhance India's logistics capabilities by bolstering its railway network and cargo mobility. The initiative targets key demand drivers in food, pharmaceuticals, and automotive sectors.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:54:46 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f3d9747db7081af634c73_1769946883218.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Unveils Critical Mineral Reforms, Eyes Self-Reliance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Unveils-Critical-Mineral-Reforms-Eyes-Self-Reliance/697f3d7d47db7081af634bc9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/India-Unveils-Critical-Mineral-Reforms-Eyes-Self-Reliance/697f3d7d47db7081af634bc9</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 signals a significant strategic shift for India's critical mineral sector. Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman announced the establishment of dedicated rare earth corridors in mineral-rich states and a zero basic customs duty on monazite. These measures, alongside exemptions on capital goods for mineral processing, aim to enhance domestic extraction, processing, and manufacturing, thereby reducing import reliance for vital high-tech and green energy components. This initiative builds upon the existing National Critical Mineral Mission, which has a substantial outlay to strengthen the entire value chain.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:53:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f3d7d47db7081af634bc8_1769946808480.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 2026 Budget Aims for Tourism Overhaul</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Indias-2026-Budget-Aims-for-Tourism-Overhaul/697f3d0a47db7081af634a37</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Indias-2026-Budget-Aims-for-Tourism-Overhaul/697f3d0a47db7081af634a37</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 signals a strategic pivot to elevate India's tourism sector, moving beyond its established religious and spiritual appeal. Key initiatives include establishing a National Institute of Hospitality, upskilling 10,000 guides, and creating a digital knowledge grid for heritage sites. The budget also champions the development of diverse tourism products like mountain trails, archaeological site experiences, and medical tourism hubs, while reducing the TCS on outbound travel to 2%.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:51:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f3d0a47db7081af634a36_1769946673229.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budgets ₹10K Cr Fund to Ignite MSME Champions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budgets-10K-Cr-Fund-to-Ignite-MSME-Champions/697f3ca647db7081af63488d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budgets-10K-Cr-Fund-to-Ignite-MSME-Champions/697f3ca647db7081af63488d</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 targets MSME transformation with a ₹10,000 crore SME Growth Fund for equity infusion and strengthened TReDS liquidity mechanisms. Initiatives include mandated CPSE settlement via TReDS, a CGTMSE guarantee, GeM integration, and securitization of receivables to foster growth, professionalization via 'Corporate Mitras', and enhanced risk capital access for micro-enterprises.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:48:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f3ca647db7081af63488c_1769946519824.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budgets Shift to Debt-to-GDP Anchor</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budgets-Shift-to-Debt-to-GDP-Anchor/697f3c8d47db7081af6347e2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budgets-Shift-to-Debt-to-GDP-Anchor/697f3c8d47db7081af6347e2</guid><description>India's Union Budget for 2026-27 marks a significant fiscal strategy shift, prioritizing the debt-to-Gross Domestic Product (GDP) ratio over the fiscal deficit as the primary anchor. The government aims to lower the debt-to-GDP ratio to 55.6% in FY27, supported by an assumed 10% nominal GDP growth projected at Rs 393 lakh crore. This recalibration occurs as central government borrowing is set to surge to Rs 17.2 lakh crore, driven by substantial debt repayments, while interest payments are projected to reach Rs 14.04 lakh crore, consuming a significant portion of expenditure. This strategic move aims to provide greater fiscal flexibility and transparency amid a volatile global economic environment.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:48:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f3c8d47db7081af6347e1_1769946387758.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: SHE Marts to Boost Women Entrepreneurs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-SHE-Marts-to-Boost-Women-Entrepreneurs/697f3b9d47db7081af6345e9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-SHE-Marts-to-Boost-Women-Entrepreneurs/697f3b9d47db7081af6345e9</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 unveiled the 'Self Help Entrepreneurs - SHE Marts' initiative, establishing community-owned retail outlets run by women's self-help groups. This program aims to bolster grassroots entrepreneurship by providing direct market access for products made by women. It signifies a strategic step to transition women from credit-linked livelihoods to enterprise ownership, building on the proven success of the Lakhpati Didi Programme.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:44:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f3b9d47db7081af6345e8_1769946291467.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: Auto Sector Fuels on Capex, Infra Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Budget-2026-Auto-Sector-Fuels-on-Capex-Infra-Boost/697f3aaf47db7081af6343d6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/Budget-2026-Auto-Sector-Fuels-on-Capex-Infra-Boost/697f3aaf47db7081af6343d6</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 signals a significant push towards higher capital expenditure, infrastructure development, and manufacturing-led growth. Industry leaders anticipate these measures will invigorate India's automotive sector, driving demand for vehicles and components. Key allocations include ₹12.2 lakh crore for capital expenditure and focused initiatives for electric vehicle (EV) ecosystems, advanced manufacturing, and supply chain resilience. This strategic direction aims to bolster macroeconomic stability and competitiveness amid global economic shifts.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:42:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f3aaf47db7081af6343d5_1769946121828.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: AI, Infra Drive Growth, Markets React Cautiously</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-AI-Infra-Drive-Growth-Markets-React-Cautiously/697f3a3847db7081af634260</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-AI-Infra-Drive-Growth-Markets-React-Cautiously/697f3a3847db7081af634260</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman's Union Budget 2026-27 prioritizes economic growth through substantial capital expenditure increases and a strong focus on technology like AI, alongside infrastructure development and manufacturing initiatives. While the budget signals fiscal prudence with a targeted deficit, initial market reactions were mixed, marked by volatility following changes to Securities Transaction Tax. The repeated emphasis on 'Income Tax', 'services', 'AI', and 'infrastructure' highlights key policy directions for the coming fiscal year.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:40:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f3a3847db7081af63425f_1769946003571.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: SHE-Marts to Empower Rural Women</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-SHE-Marts-to-Empower-Rural-Women/697f394247db7081af634066</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-SHE-Marts-to-Empower-Rural-Women/697f394247db7081af634066</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 introduces SHE-Marts, a nationwide network of community-owned retail outlets designed to elevate women-led enterprises. Building on the success of programs like Lakhpati Didi, this initiative aims to transition women from micro-credit dependent livelihoods to robust, sustained entrepreneurship. SHE-Marts will operate through federations, offering market access and institutional support, thereby formalizing retail platforms and increasing value capture for women producers. This strategic intervention aligns with broader rural development goals to boost household income and local employment.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:38:33 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f394247db7081af634065_1769945909785.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026: Rs 10,000 Crore Scheme to Revolutionize Container Manufacturing</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Budget-2026-Rs-10000-Crore-Scheme-to-Revolutionize-Container-Manufacturing/697f38f947db7081af633e94</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Budget-2026-Rs-10000-Crore-Scheme-to-Revolutionize-Container-Manufacturing/697f38f947db7081af633e94</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman's Budget 2026 proposals include a significant ₹10,000 crore allocation over five years for a global-standard container manufacturing ecosystem. The budget also champions the expansion of crucial infrastructure, announcing plans for a new Dedicated Freight Corridor and the operationalization of 20 new National Waterways, aiming to bolster India's logistics and trade capabilities.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:36:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f38f947db7081af633e93_1769945789806.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Venezuela Opens Oil Sector, Reshaping Global Energy Flows</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Venezuela-Opens-Oil-Sector-Reshaping-Global-Energy-Flows/697f38d047db7081af633dbf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Venezuela-Opens-Oil-Sector-Reshaping-Global-Energy-Flows/697f38d047db7081af633dbf</guid><description>Venezuela has undertaken sweeping reforms to its hydrocarbons law, dismantling decades of state control to attract foreign investment and boost production. Concurrently, the US Treasury has eased sanctions, allowing American companies to engage in Venezuelan oil activities and facilitating a significant shift in global crude export routes. This policy pivot is rerouting oil away from China towards US refiners and storage, with major commodity traders playing a key role. The changes are expected to boost Venezuela's output and cash flow, potentially impacting global oil supply dynamics.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:35:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f38d047db7081af633dbe_1769945709640.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Textile Sector Roars: Budget 2026 Fuels Parks, FTA Boosts Stocks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Indias-Textile-Sector-Roars-Budget-2026-Fuels-Parks-FTA-Boosts-Stocks/697f38a047db7081af633ca1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Indias-Textile-Sector-Roars-Budget-2026-Fuels-Parks-FTA-Boosts-Stocks/697f38a047db7081af633ca1</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026 has launched a comprehensive policy framework for India's textile sector, featuring Mega Textile Parks, enhanced export timelines, and support for technical textiles and man-made fibers. This strategic push, combined with the India-EU Free Trade Agreement, has spurred substantial gains across major listed companies. While export-oriented, well-capitalized players are poised to benefit most, smaller and cotton-reliant manufacturers may see a more gradual impact.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:34:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f38a047db7081af633ca0_1769945588801.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Studds Accessories Posts Strong Q3 Profit, Eyes Global Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Studds-Accessories-Posts-Strong-Q3-Profit-Eyes-Global-Expansion/697f387447db7081af633b41</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Studds-Accessories-Posts-Strong-Q3-Profit-Eyes-Global-Expansion/697f387447db7081af633b41</guid><description>Studds Accessories reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with revenue rising 9.4% YoY to ₹163 Cr and Profit After Tax surging 26.3% to ₹20.7 Cr. The company saw significant margin improvements to 18.8% for EBITDA and 12.7% for PAT, driven by favorable raw material prices and operational efficiencies. Strategic initiatives, including international diversification and product premiumization, are underway.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:32:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f387447db7081af633b40_1769945468016.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Logistics Sector Gears Up for Infra Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Budget-2026-Logistics-Sector-Gears-Up-for-Infra-Boost/697f385c47db7081af633a84</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/India-Budget-2026-Logistics-Sector-Gears-Up-for-Infra-Boost/697f385c47db7081af633a84</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman's Union Budget 2026-27 allocates ₹5,98,520 crore to the transport sector, prioritizing greener freight routes, faster clearances, and manufacturing-linked logistics. Key initiatives include new Dedicated Freight Corridors (DFC) from Dankuni to Surat, operationalization of 20 National Waterways, and a ₹10,000 crore container manufacturing scheme. These measures aim to bolster India's supply chain reliability and export competitiveness.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:31:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f385c47db7081af633a83_1769945474998.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Studds Accessories Posts Strong Q3 Growth; Margins Expand Significantly YoY</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Studds-Accessories-Posts-Strong-Q3-Growth-Margins-Expand-Significantly-YoY/697f37e147db7081af6338c7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Studds-Accessories-Posts-Strong-Q3-Growth-Margins-Expand-Significantly-YoY/697f37e147db7081af6338c7</guid><description>Studds Accessories reported a strong Q3 FY26, with consolidated revenue up 9.4% YoY to ₹163 Cr. EBITDA and PAT saw substantial YoY jumps of 20.1% and 26.3% respectively, driven by margin expansion to 18.8% (EBITDA) and 12.7% (PAT). Management cited steady demand and favorable raw material costs, despite increased marketing spends, and highlighted progress on its Spanish subsidiary and a slightly deferred capacity expansion.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:29:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f37e147db7081af6338c6_1769945339341.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's FY27 Budget: Fiscal Tightrope Walk Amidst Bond Supply Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-FY27-Budget-Fiscal-Tightrope-Walk-Amidst-Bond-Supply-Surge/697f371a47db7081af63368c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-FY27-Budget-Fiscal-Tightrope-Walk-Amidst-Bond-Supply-Surge/697f371a47db7081af63368c</guid><description>India's Union Budget for FY27 targets a fiscal deficit of 4.3% of GDP and shifts its anchor to the debt-to-GDP ratio, aiming for 50% by FY31. However, a substantial increase in government securities supply, coupled with constrained investor demand, presents a significant challenge for the bond market. State governments' worsening fiscal health adds to the supply pressure, creating a complex demand-supply dynamic requiring potential central bank intervention. Global fiscal pressures and elevated US Treasury yields further complicate the outlook.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:26:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f371a47db7081af63368b_1769945187257.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget FY27: States Take Capex Lead Amidst Market Jitters</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-FY27-States-Take-Capex-Lead-Amidst-Market-Jitters/697f36ed47db7081af633597</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-FY27-States-Take-Capex-Lead-Amidst-Market-Jitters/697f36ed47db7081af633597</guid><description>India's Union Budget for fiscal year 2027 (FY27) prioritizes a substantial capital expenditure (capex) boost, projecting Rs. 12.2 trillion, an 11.5% rise. A key strategic shift places greater execution responsibility on state governments, supported by enhanced interest-free loans and grants. The budget aims for fiscal prudence with a projected 4.3% deficit, but higher market borrowing plans signal potential bond market stress. Initiatives target manufacturing, though disinvestment targets remain historically conservative.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:24:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f36ed47db7081af633596_1769945061295.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget Sparks Infrastructure Boom, Markets Flinch</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-Sparks-Infrastructure-Boom-Markets-Flinch/697f367547db7081af6333f0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-Sparks-Infrastructure-Boom-Markets-Flinch/697f367547db7081af6333f0</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman unveiled the Union Budget 2026-27 with a significant ₹12.2 lakh crore allocation for capital expenditure, aiming to fuel infrastructure development and economic growth. The budget also highlighted initiatives for the biopharmaceutical sector and digital infrastructure, alongside fiscal consolidation targets. However, the equity markets experienced a sharp downturn, largely attributed to an increase in Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on derivatives trading.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:22:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f367547db7081af6333ef_1769944920039.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026 Eases Tax: Deadlines Extended, Small Biz Compliance Simplified</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Eases-Tax-Deadlines-Extended-Small-Biz-Compliance-Simplified/697f360447db7081af633267</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Eases-Tax-Deadlines-Extended-Small-Biz-Compliance-Simplified/697f360447db7081af633267</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 introduces significant tax compliance reforms, extending the income tax return filing deadline for small businesses and professionals not requiring audits to August 31st. The window for revised returns is now 12 months, and a rule-based automated scheme aims to simplify filing for small taxpayers. These measures are lauded as practical, taxpayer-friendly, and part of a broader effort to modernize the tax framework and enhance transparency.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:20:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f360447db7081af633266_1769944817771.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Railway Stocks Tumble Despite Budget Allocation Hike</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Railway-Stocks-Tumble-Despite-Budget-Allocation-Hike/697f35b347db7081af6330d2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Railway-Stocks-Tumble-Despite-Budget-Allocation-Hike/697f35b347db7081af6330d2</guid><description>Indian railway stocks experienced a notable decline on February 1, 2026, despite the Union Budget allocating ₹2.93 lakh crore to the Ministry of Railways, a 10% increase year-on-year. The market's negative reaction was driven by the absence of concrete announcements regarding new train orders and specific growth catalysts, suggesting the increased allocation was largely anticipated and priced in by investors.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:18:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f35b347db7081af6330d1_1769944707820.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Budget 2026: Bold Push for Global Services Hub</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-2026-Bold-Push-for-Global-Services-Hub/697f358747db7081af632fef</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Budget-2026-Bold-Push-for-Global-Services-Hub/697f358747db7081af632fef</guid><description>Union Budget 2026 signals a decisive shift, prioritizing India's services sector to achieve 10% of global services output by 2047. The budget introduces a raft of measures across health, education, and tourism, alongside significant infrastructure development including a new freight corridor and city economic regions. Manufacturing continuity and targeted tax reforms aim to attract foreign investment and reduce pain points. However, the market reacted with volatility, partly due to increased transaction taxes.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:18:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f358747db7081af632fee_1769944593598.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Unveils Risk Fund to Spur Infra Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Unveils-Risk-Fund-to-Spur-Infra-Boom/697f349947db7081af632e56</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Unveils-Risk-Fund-to-Spur-Infra-Boom/697f349947db7081af632e56</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman announced the creation of an Infrastructure Risk Guarantee Fund in Budget 2026, designed to offer partial credit guarantees to lenders for infrastructure projects. This initiative aims to mitigate risks during the construction and early operational phases, encouraging greater bank and private sector financing. The announcement coincides with a significant increase in government capital expenditure, targeting ₹12.2 lakh crore for FY27, signaling a robust commitment to infrastructure-led economic growth.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:12:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f349947db7081af632e55_1769944324588.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Budget 2026 Expands Tax Revision Window</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Expands-Tax-Revision-Window/697f32b747db7081af632c6b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Budget-2026-Expands-Tax-Revision-Window/697f32b747db7081af632c6b</guid><description>Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman announced in Budget 2026 an extension of the income tax return revision deadline to March 31, providing taxpayers with an extended 12-month window from the end of the tax year. This policy change, effective from the upcoming fiscal year, aims to offer greater flexibility for correcting errors and omissions in original filings. A nominal fee will apply for revisions submitted after the initial nine-month period. This move underscores a broader governmental push towards facilitating taxpayer compliance and reducing potential disputes.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:04:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f32b747db7081af632c6a_1769943851208.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Seafood Sector: Budget Boost Meets Trade Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Seafood-Sector-Budget-Boost-Meets-Trade-Headwinds/697f324247db7081af632b18</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Seafood-Sector-Budget-Boost-Meets-Trade-Headwinds/697f324247db7081af632b18</guid><description>India's Union Budget 2026 introduces measures to bolster the aquaculture industry, including increased duty-free import limits and value chain enhancements. Despite record seafood exports in FY25, driven by demand from the US and China, the sector faces significant pressure from a 50% US tariff on shrimp. The newly signed India-EU Free Trade Agreement provides a critical strategic hedge, aiming to ensure industry resilience and European market access. Key players like Avanti Feeds and Apex Frozen Foods are positioned to benefit from these policy shifts and market diversification efforts.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:02:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f324247db7081af632b17_1769943754633.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Tax Law Overhauled, Not Rates; STT Hiked</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Tax-Law-Overhauled-Not-Rates-STT-Hiked/697f30de47db7081af6328d0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Tax-Law-Overhauled-Not-Rates-STT-Hiked/697f30de47db7081af6328d0</guid><description>India's fiscal year 2026-27 budget heralds a significant overhaul of the income tax framework with the Income Tax Act, 2025, replacing the old law. While direct tax rates and slabs remain unchanged, the focus is on simplifying compliance, reducing litigation, and enhancing transparency. Key changes include stricter penalties for misreporting, an extended deadline for revised tax returns, and a new six-month foreign asset disclosure window. For investors, the budget brings increased Securities Transaction Tax (STT) on futures and options, and a shift in buyback taxation to capital gains, while reducing Tax Collected at Source (TCS) on education and medical remittances.</description><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 10:58:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_697f30de47db7081af6328cf_1769943358917.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>