<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:55:10 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Tata Comms &amp; RailTel Ally for India's AI Digital Infrastructure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tata-Comms-and-RailTel-Ally-for-Indias-AI-Digital-Infrastructure/699bd974ee97f501b0eb1509</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Tata-Comms-and-RailTel-Ally-for-Indias-AI-Digital-Infrastructure/699bd974ee97f501b0eb1509</guid><description>Tata Communications and RailTel have joined forces in a strategic partnership aimed at fortifying India's digital infrastructure, with a significant focus on Artificial Intelligence (AI). This collaboration seeks to modernize network infrastructure, bolster cybersecurity, and promote secure cloud adoption. By integrating RailTel's extensive national telecom network with Tata Communications' global digital capabilities, the alliance is poised to deliver faster connectivity and improved digital services for government entities and citizens across India.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:37:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bd974ee97f501b0eb1508_1771821533355.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nifty-500 Earnings Surge 19%; Focus Shifts to Sustainability</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-500-Earnings-Surge-19percent-Focus-Shifts-to-Sustainability/699bd822ee97f501b0eb13ab</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Nifty-500-Earnings-Surge-19percent-Focus-Shifts-to-Sustainability/699bd822ee97f501b0eb13ab</guid><description>The Nifty-500 index experienced its strongest earnings expansion in eight quarters during Q3 FY26, with aggregate profits climbing 19% year-on-year. This broad-based performance, bolstered by an 11% revenue increase, is attributed partly to GST 2.0 reforms, yet an elevated valuation premium and emerging sectoral divergences prompt closer scrutiny from investors.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:31:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bd822ee97f501b0eb13aa_1771821286842.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Capital Goods Rally Faces Commodity Headwinds &amp; Selective Capex</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Capital-Goods-Rally-Faces-Commodity-Headwinds-and-Selective-Capex/699bd81eee97f501b0eb1394</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Capital-Goods-Rally-Faces-Commodity-Headwinds-and-Selective-Capex/699bd81eee97f501b0eb1394</guid><description>The capital goods and defence sectors are exhibiting robust Q3 FY26 performance, driven by government capital expenditure and steady order inflows. However, a deeper analysis reveals significant risks. Surging commodity prices, particularly steel and copper, pose a threat to profit margins for manufacturers. Private sector capital expenditure, while increasing, remains concentrated and selective, relying heavily on government initiatives. Analyst sentiment varies, with some recommending specific large-cap execution leaders while others express caution on valuations and sector-wide headwinds.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:31:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bd81eee97f501b0eb1393_1771821361127.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AU Small Finance Bank: Market Overreaction or Regulatory Warning?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/AU-Small-Finance-Bank-Market-Overreaction-or-Regulatory-Warning/699bd7b0ee97f501b0eb1290</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/AU-Small-Finance-Bank-Market-Overreaction-or-Regulatory-Warning/699bd7b0ee97f501b0eb1290</guid><description>AU Small Finance Bank experienced a significant share price decline following the Haryana government's decision to de-empanel its accounts, citing a fraud incident involving government funds. Despite the bank's clarification that transactions were government-authorized and preliminary reviews indicate no financial impact, the stock plunged 7.4%. Government deposits with AU SFB fell by approximately 26%, though this represents only 0.4% of overall deposits. The market's sharp reaction may reflect broader concerns about regulatory scrutiny and contagion within the small finance bank sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:29:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bd7b0ee97f501b0eb128f_1771821079448.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Block Deal Boost Masks Cohance Lifesciences' Deepening Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Block-Deal-Boost-Masks-Cohance-Lifesciences-Deepening-Woes/699bd737ee97f501b0eb11c5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Block-Deal-Boost-Masks-Cohance-Lifesciences-Deepening-Woes/699bd737ee97f501b0eb11c5</guid><description>Cohance Lifesciences Ltd. saw its shares climb up to 8% on Monday, February 23, following a substantial block deal where approximately 7.7 million shares changed hands for ₹235.6 crore. This immediate price appreciation contrasts sharply with the company's year-to-date performance, which shows a significant decline of over 40% in 2026. The block transaction, involving unknown buyers and sellers, occurs against a backdrop of recent management changes, including an MD resignation, and persistent regulatory concerns like a USFDA warning letter impacting its manufacturing facility. Despite the positive intraday movement, the underlying structural issues and recent financial headwinds suggest the block deal's impact may be temporary.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:27:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bd737ee97f501b0eb11c4_1771821079656.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Wage Code Forces ₹13K Cr Balance Sheet Reset</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Wage-Code-Forces-13K-Cr-Balance-Sheet-Reset/699bd726ee97f501b0eb1191</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Wage-Code-Forces-13K-Cr-Balance-Sheet-Reset/699bd726ee97f501b0eb1191</guid><description>Corporate India's payroll systems underwent a substantial recalibration in Q3 FY26, marked by a ₹13,161 crore one-time provisioning impact across large listed employers. This adjustment stems from the Code on Wages' mandate to redefine 'wages,' capping exclusions at 50% of total remuneration and consequently expanding the base for statutory benefits. The financial charge reflects actuarial re-estimations of long-term liabilities, signaling a strategic shift in how companies manage compensation and compliance.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:27:18 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bd726ee97f501b0eb1190_1771820978560.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Dual IPO Launch: Clean Max GMP Cools, Shree Ram Twistex Holds Steady</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Dual-IPO-Launch-Clean-Max-GMP-Cools-Shree-Ram-Twistex-Holds-Steady/699bd6a7ee97f501b0eb1081</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/IPO/Dual-IPO-Launch-Clean-Max-GMP-Cools-Shree-Ram-Twistex-Holds-Steady/699bd6a7ee97f501b0eb1081</guid><description>Two Indian IPOs, Clean Max Enviro Energy Solutions (₹3,100 crore) and Shree Ram Twistex (₹110.24 crore), commenced subscription today, February 23, 2026. While Shree Ram Twistex exhibits a stronger listing gain potential based on its stable grey market premium (GMP), Clean Max's GMP has seen a sharp decline, signaling cooling investor sentiment. This divergence highlights distinct market perceptions driven by company structure, sector dynamics, and valuation considerations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:25:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bd6a7ee97f501b0eb1080_1771820854363.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aether Industries Site 3++ Operational, Eyes Future Capacity Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Aether-Industries-Site-3-Operational-Eyes-Future-Capacity-Boost/699bd6a1ee97f501b0eb106a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Aether-Industries-Site-3-Operational-Eyes-Future-Capacity-Boost/699bd6a1ee97f501b0eb106a</guid><description>Aether Industries Limited has commenced commercial operations at its new Manufacturing Site 3++ effective February 22, 2026. This expansion is a key step in the company's strategy to enhance production capacities and drive future revenue growth. The facility is expected to significantly contribute to the company's scaling-up efforts in the competitive specialty chemicals market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:25:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bd6a1ee97f501b0eb1069_1771820843716.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sensex, Nifty Rally on Tariff News; Focus Shifts to Fundamentals</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Sensex-Nifty-Rally-on-Tariff-News-Focus-Shifts-to-Fundamentals/699bd632ee97f501b0eb0f95</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Sensex-Nifty-Rally-on-Tariff-News-Focus-Shifts-to-Fundamentals/699bd632ee97f501b0eb0f95</guid><description>Indian benchmarks Sensex and Nifty surged nearly 1% Monday, reacting to the US Supreme Court's voiding of tariffs, which reduced trade uncertainty. Axis Bank shares rose 2% amidst this broad market optimism. However, the rally's long-term trajectory will likely hinge on domestic economic fundamentals and sector-specific resilience rather than external trade event resolution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:23:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bd632ee97f501b0eb0f94_1771820742130.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Torrent Power Pivots to Contracted Assets, Eyes Long-Term Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Torrent-Power-Pivots-to-Contracted-Assets-Eyes-Long-Term-Growth/699bd632ee97f501b0eb0f7e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/Torrent-Power-Pivots-to-Contracted-Assets-Eyes-Long-Term-Growth/699bd632ee97f501b0eb0f7e</guid><description>Torrent Power is executing a significant strategic shift, acquiring Nabha Power for ₹3,660 crore and bolstering thermal and renewable capacity. This move aims to decrease its dependence on volatile gas power assets, which currently face underutilization and earnings fluctuations. The company is adding 1,400 MW thermal capacity through Nabha, constructing another 1,600 MW thermal plant, and developing 4,000 MW in solar and wind projects. These new capacities, backed by long-term power purchase agreements (PPAs), are designed to provide revenue visibility and mitigate market demand vagaries, though full earnings benefits will accrue over several years.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:23:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bd632ee97f501b0eb0f7d_1771820713580.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Tariff Turmoil Creates Market Divergence</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/US-Tariff-Turmoil-Creates-Market-Divergence/699bd44bee97f501b0eb0def</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/US-Tariff-Turmoil-Creates-Market-Divergence/699bd44bee97f501b0eb0def</guid><description>Indian equities anticipate a positive open Monday, reacting to a US Supreme Court ruling against President Trump's tariffs. However, Trump's swift increase of import tariffs to 15% injects significant uncertainty, delaying India's trade talks. While export-oriented sectors may see a short-term boost, the market grapples with conflicting signals and underlying corporate risks, exemplified by IDFC First Bank's investigation into a $65 million fraud. IDFC First Bank shares declined pre-market due to the allegations.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:15:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bd44bee97f501b0eb0dee_1771820259068.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Tariffs: Court Voids, Trump Re-Imposes; Indian Markets Brace for Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Tariffs-Court-Voids-Trump-Re-Imposes-Indian-Markets-Brace-for-Volatility/699bd368ee97f501b0eb0d32</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/US-Tariffs-Court-Voids-Trump-Re-Imposes-Indian-Markets-Brace-for-Volatility/699bd368ee97f501b0eb0d32</guid><description>Indian equities surged initially as the US Supreme Court invalidated President Trump's sweeping tariffs. However, this relief was short-lived. Trump immediately enacted new, temporary tariffs under a different legal provision, raising them to 15%. This creates lingering uncertainty for global trade and investor sentiment. Crude oil prices remain sensitive to US-Iran nuclear talks, adding another layer of geopolitical risk. While domestic institutional investors showed confidence, foreign investors continued net selling. The Nifty 50 trades at a P/E of approximately 22.4, suggesting a fairly valued market amidst this complex global backdrop.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:11:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bd368ee97f501b0eb0d31_1771820050436.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IDFC First Bank Stock Plummets on ₹590 Cr Fraud; Haryana Gov Bans Bank</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Stock-Plummets-on-590-Cr-Fraud-Haryana-Gov-Bans-Bank/699bd26aee97f501b0eb0c50</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Stock-Plummets-on-590-Cr-Fraud-Haryana-Gov-Bans-Bank/699bd26aee97f501b0eb0c50</guid><description>IDFC First Bank's stock plunged 10% to ₹75.16 on Monday after revealing a ₹590 crore fraud involving Haryana government accounts at its Chandigarh branch. The lender's operational integrity is now under intense scrutiny. The Haryana government immediately de-empanelled IDFC First Bank for state business, citing lapses. Despite some analysts downplaying the financial impact, the market has reacted severely, highlighting concerns over the bank's premium valuation and internal controls.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:07:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bd26aee97f501b0eb0c4f_1771819752928.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Stallion India Fluorochemicals plans ₹200 Cr Rajasthan HFO plant, eyes 35% revenue CAGR</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Stallion-India-Fluorochemicals-plans-200-Cr-Rajasthan-HFO-plant-eyes-35percent-revenue-CAGR/699bd1f1ee97f501b0eb0bdd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Stallion-India-Fluorochemicals-plans-200-Cr-Rajasthan-HFO-plant-eyes-35percent-revenue-CAGR/699bd1f1ee97f501b0eb0bdd</guid><description>Stallion India Fluorochemicals (SIFL) has received approval for land allotment in Rajasthan for a new Hydrofluoroolefin (HFO) manufacturing plant. The ₹200 crore expansion aims to strengthen its product portfolio with low-GWP refrigerants and support a projected 30-35% revenue CAGR. The project, slated to commence in 2027, underscores the company's growth strategy in sustainable cooling solutions.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 04:05:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bd1f1ee97f501b0eb0bdc_1771819658804.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Delphi World Money Q3 EBITDA Turns Positive; FY26 Outlook Eyes ₹240 Mn Profit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Delphi-World-Money-Q3-EBITDA-Turns-Positive-FY26-Outlook-Eyes-240-Mn-Profit/699bd087ee97f501b0eb0b13</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Delphi-World-Money-Q3-EBITDA-Turns-Positive-FY26-Outlook-Eyes-240-Mn-Profit/699bd087ee97f501b0eb0b13</guid><description>Delphi World Money reported a significant turnaround in Q3 FY26, with its adjusted EBITDA turning positive at ₹52.54 Mn, driven by a 24% quarter-on-quarter revenue growth to ₹547 Mn. The company anticipates processing ₹68 Bn in GMV and achieving approximately ₹240 Mn in full-year FY26 adjusted EBITDA, signalling a strong recovery. Despite positive financial momentum, the company faces scrutiny over past regulatory and auditor issues.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 03:59:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bd087ee97f501b0eb0b12_1771819350638.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Tariff Ruling: India Exports Gain, But Fed Rate Path Uncertain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/US-Tariff-Ruling-India-Exports-Gain-But-Fed-Rate-Path-Uncertain/699bcf9aee97f501b0eb0a67</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/International-News/US-Tariff-Ruling-India-Exports-Gain-But-Fed-Rate-Path-Uncertain/699bcf9aee97f501b0eb0a67</guid><description>A US Supreme Court decision has temporarily reduced universal tariffs, offering Indian exporters like Welspun Living, Trident, and SRF a window of opportunity. However, US economic growth slowed to 1.4% in Q4 2025, and Federal Reserve rate cut expectations are becoming more cautious, focusing on domestic demand over trade policy shifts. Lingering uncertainties about future tariff reinstatements and fiscal implications create a complex outlook.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 03:55:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bcf9aee97f501b0eb0a66_1771819058560.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Solar Industries: MS Bullish Case Meets High Valuation Headwinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Solar-Industries-MS-Bullish-Case-Meets-High-Valuation-Headwinds/699bce31ee97f501b0eb0905</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Solar-Industries-MS-Bullish-Case-Meets-High-Valuation-Headwinds/699bce31ee97f501b0eb0905</guid><description>Morgan Stanley initiated coverage on Solar Industries India Ltd. with an 'Overweight' rating and a price target of ₹16,151, implying over 21% upside. This bullish stance is anchored in the company's dual-engine growth strategy across defense and explosives, projecting strong CAGRs. However, the stock's stratospheric valuation, evidenced by a TTM P/E exceeding 80x, coupled with sector-specific risks and mixed technical indicators, necessitates a cautious investor perspective amidst the prevailing optimism.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 03:49:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bce31ee97f501b0eb0904_1771818707655.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Garment Mantra Lifestyle: Recycled Tees for Africa/UAE; Export Sales Hit ₹100 Cr.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Garment-Mantra-Lifestyle-Recycled-Tees-for-AfricaUAE-Export-Sales-Hit-100-Cr/699bce30ee97f501b0eb08ee</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Textile/Garment-Mantra-Lifestyle-Recycled-Tees-for-AfricaUAE-Export-Sales-Hit-100-Cr/699bce30ee97f501b0eb08ee</guid><description>Garment Mantra Lifestyle is venturing into sustainable fashion with a new line of men's T-shirts made from recycled fabrics, targeting export markets in Africa and the UAE. This initiative aligns with global sustainability trends and the company's recent success in achieving record export sales of ₹100 crore. The company expects positive buyer response to its eco-friendly and affordable apparel offerings.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 03:49:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bce30ee97f501b0eb08ed_1771818687668.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEPC Order Book Hits Record ₹10,455 Crore; FY26 Inflows Bolster Future</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SEPC-Order-Book-Hits-Record-10455-Crore-FY26-Inflows-Bolster-Future/699bcdb8ee97f501b0eb0855</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/SEPC-Order-Book-Hits-Record-10455-Crore-FY26-Inflows-Bolster-Future/699bcdb8ee97f501b0eb0855</guid><description>SEPC Limited has announced a record consolidated order book of ₹10,455 crore as of December 31, 2025, driven by robust order accretion and improved execution. The company secured ₹5,954 crore in fresh orders during FY26 up to the reporting date. This expanded order book provides strong multi-year revenue visibility and enhances operating leverage for the infrastructure solutions provider.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 03:47:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bcdb8ee97f501b0eb0854_1771818544902.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Morepen Labs Bags ₹825 Cr CDMO Mandate; Eyes Global Pharma Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Morepen-Labs-Bags-825-Cr-CDMO-Mandate-Eyes-Global-Pharma-Growth/699bcdb8ee97f501b0eb0842</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Morepen-Labs-Bags-825-Cr-CDMO-Mandate-Eyes-Global-Pharma-Growth/699bcdb8ee97f501b0eb0842</guid><description>Morepen Laboratories has secured a multi-year Contract Development and Manufacturing Organization (CDMO) mandate valued at approximately ₹825 crore ($91 million). This significant deal marks an expansion into the high-growth CDMO segment, leveraging the company's API manufacturing expertise and accreditations like USFDA and WHO-GMP. Supplies are slated to begin within 4-5 months, with full execution kicking off next financial year.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 03:47:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bcdb8ee97f501b0eb0841_1771818558255.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IDFC First Bank Fraud: Governance Test Amidst Reassurance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Fraud-Governance-Test-Amidst-Reassurance/699bccccee97f501b0eb0772</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/IDFC-First-Bank-Fraud-Governance-Test-Amidst-Reassurance/699bccccee97f501b0eb0772</guid><description>IDFC First Bank disclosed a significant Rs 590 crore fraud stemming from unauthorized transactions at its Chandigarh branch impacting Haryana government accounts. CEO V Vaidyanathan characterized the event as an isolated incident, the first major operational setback in a decade, while assuring stakeholders of continued investor support from entities like Warburg Pincus. The bank has appointed KPMG to conduct an independent forensic audit to ascertain the full scope and impact. The disclosed fraud amount exceeds the bank's net profit for the October-December quarter of fiscal year 2025-26, raising questions about internal controls.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 03:43:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bccccee97f501b0eb0771_1771818415268.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Haryana Fraud Probe: IDFC First Bank Faces Govt Ban, Audit</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Haryana-Fraud-Probe-IDFC-First-Bank-Faces-Govt-Ban-Audit/699bcbe0ee97f501b0eb066f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Haryana-Fraud-Probe-IDFC-First-Bank-Faces-Govt-Ban-Audit/699bcbe0ee97f501b0eb066f</guid><description>Haryana has de-empanelled IDFC First Bank and AU Small Finance Bank from handling state government business following the detection of a ₹590 crore suspected fraud. IDFC First Bank disclosed unauthorized activities by employees at its Chandigarh branch, leading to suspensions and the appointment of KPMG for a forensic audit. The state's finance department also cited broader issues with bank deposit management and reconciliation, alongside this specific fraud case, impacting government fund handling.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 03:39:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bcbe0ee97f501b0eb066e_1771818075084.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NSE Investor Pace Slows Despite Record Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/NSE-Investor-Pace-Slows-Despite-Record-Growth/699bcb71ee97f501b0eb05fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/NSE-Investor-Pace-Slows-Despite-Record-Growth/699bcb71ee97f501b0eb05fb</guid><description>The National Stock Exchange (NSE) investor base expanded to 12.7 crore by January 2026, a four-fold increase since FY2020 with a 27.3% CAGR. However, the pace of new investor additions has decelerated, with the latest crore taking eight months versus previous five-to-six month periods. This slowdown is attributed to tariff-related shocks and global economic headwinds. January 2026 saw 17.7 lakh new investors, a 13% month-on-month rise, marking the third-highest sequential increase in FY2025-26. Unique client codes surpassed 25 crore by February 12, 2026.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 03:37:21 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bcb71ee97f501b0eb05fa_1771817974128.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Max Financial, Delhivery: Growth Catalysts Meet Valuation Puzzles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Max-Financial-Delhivery-Growth-Catalysts-Meet-Valuation-Puzzles/699bca6fee97f501b0eb0524</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Max-Financial-Delhivery-Growth-Catalysts-Meet-Valuation-Puzzles/699bca6fee97f501b0eb0524</guid><description>Max Financial Services continues its expansion driven by product mix and distribution strength, targeting significant growth in the Indian life insurance sector. Delhivery, post-Ecom Express acquisition, shows network enhancement and margin improvement. However, both companies face scrutiny regarding high valuations and underlying profitability metrics, alongside sector-specific challenges. Analysts remain largely positive, projecting upside for both, but a deeper dive reveals potential headwinds beneath the surface.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 03:33:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bca6fee97f501b0eb0523_1771817753912.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Disrupts IT Services: FIIs Flee as Valuations Face Structural Test</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Disrupts-IT-Services-FIIs-Flee-as-Valuations-Face-Structural-Test/699bc6b9ee97f501b0eb0385</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Disrupts-IT-Services-FIIs-Flee-as-Valuations-Face-Structural-Test/699bc6b9ee97f501b0eb0385</guid><description>Foreign institutional investors have significantly reduced their stakes in major Indian IT firms, mirroring a broad retreat from the sector. This exodus is fueled by escalating concerns over artificial intelligence's disruptive potential, which threatens traditional IT service revenue models and margin structures. While global IT spending is booming in AI infrastructure, Indian IT service providers face pressure to adapt rapidly to an AI-native paradigm, a shift that analysts suggest may not be fully reflected in current valuations. The Nifty IT index has seen substantial declines, with analysts warning of persistent headwinds and a need for strategic reorientation to navigate the evolving technological landscape.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 03:17:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bc6b9ee97f501b0eb0384_1771816756801.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>UPL Stock Tumbles on Downgrade Amid Restructuring Ambitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/UPL-Stock-Tumbles-on-Downgrade-Amid-Restructuring-Ambitions/699bc63dee97f501b0eb0312</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/UPL-Stock-Tumbles-on-Downgrade-Amid-Restructuring-Ambitions/699bc63dee97f501b0eb0312</guid><description>UPL Ltd. is undertaking a significant reorganization to spin off its crop protection operations into a dedicated entity, UPL Global. However, Nuvama Institutional Equities has downgraded the stock to 'Hold,' citing unresolved leverage concerns and potential dilution risks. This move casts a shadow over the company's strategic ambitions to create a focused agricultural solutions powerhouse, prompting investors to weigh execution risks against long-term value creation prospects.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 03:15:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bc63dee97f501b0eb0311_1771816667260.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold's Rally Fueled by Structural Shifts, Not Just Tensions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Golds-Rally-Fueled-by-Structural-Shifts-Not-Just-Tensions/699bc54fee97f501b0eb01f3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Golds-Rally-Fueled-by-Structural-Shifts-Not-Just-Tensions/699bc54fee97f501b0eb01f3</guid><description>Gold prices are underpinned by significant structural shifts, extending beyond temporary geopolitical concerns. Record central bank accumulation, sustained ETF inflows, and the prospect of persistently low real interest rates are creating a durable demand environment. While short-term price action remains sensitive to geopolitical flares and currency movements, analysts foresee 2026 prices potentially reaching $6,000 per ounce, driven by these fundamental economic realignments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 03:11:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bc54fee97f501b0eb01f2_1771816433334.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Google Locks In Bengaluru: Record Campus Lease Signals India Ambitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Google-Locks-In-Bengaluru-Record-Campus-Lease-Signals-India-Ambitions/699bc4dbee97f501b0eb0184</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Google-Locks-In-Bengaluru-Record-Campus-Lease-Signals-India-Ambitions/699bc4dbee97f501b0eb0184</guid><description>Google IT Services India has secured approximately 2.6 million square feet of prime office space at Alembic City in Bengaluru's Whitefield, a move underscoring a significant, long-term commitment to the region. This expansive lease, which includes exclusive rights to three additional towers, positions it as one of the largest single-campus occupancies by a global tech firm in India. The deal signifies Google's deep confidence in Bengaluru as a core technology and product development base, while also reflecting a strategic prioritization of expansion certainty and scalability in a competitive Grade A market.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 03:09:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bc4dbee97f501b0eb0183_1771816329325.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>NHPC Faces ₹227 Cr Arbitration Award; Counter-Claim Stands at ₹738 Cr</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NHPC-Faces-227-Cr-Arbitration-Award-Counter-Claim-Stands-at-738-Cr/699bc27bee97f501b0eb0059</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/NHPC-Faces-227-Cr-Arbitration-Award-Counter-Claim-Stands-at-738-Cr/699bc27bee97f501b0eb0059</guid><description>NHPC Limited has received an arbitration award pronounced in favour of Hindustan Construction Company (HCC) for the Kishanganga HE Project. The award is for ₹227.82 crore plus other charges and interest. Simultaneously, NHPC has a significant counter-claim of ₹738.67 crore, on which arguments are yet to commence. The company is currently examining the award, pronounced on 21.02.2026 (a future date, noted for clarification).</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 02:59:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bc27bee97f501b0eb0058_1771815659312.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tech Breakout, Insurance Resilience, Bank Momentum Signal Gains</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Tech-Breakout-Insurance-Resilience-Bank-Momentum-Signal-Gains/699bbf33ee97f501b0eafe6b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Tech-Breakout-Insurance-Resilience-Bank-Momentum-Signal-Gains/699bbf33ee97f501b0eafe6b</guid><description>Choice Equity Broking's Aakash Shah identifies three key technical setups: Netweb Technologies' powerful breakout after extended consolidation, SBI Life Insurance's sustained uptrend supported by key moving averages, and IDBI Bank's broad bullish alignment following a range breach. These patterns suggest continued upward potential, supported by sector-specific strength and accumulation signals, though valuation metrics for the technology stock warrant careful observation.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 02:45:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bbf33ee97f501b0eafe6a_1771814880781.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Passive Sector ETFs: Structure vs. Alpha Capture</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Passive-Sector-ETFs-Structure-vs-Alpha-Capture/699bbed9ee97f501b0eafda4</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Stock-Investment-Ideas/Passive-Sector-ETFs-Structure-vs-Alpha-Capture/699bbed9ee97f501b0eafda4</guid><description>The allure of sector and thematic investing lies in its potential for rapid, large gains. However, its inherent volatility and complexity often lead investors to passive vehicles like ETFs and Funds of Funds (FoFs) for a structured approach. While these passive tools mitigate behavioral risks and offer cost efficiencies, their rigid index construction and rebalancing schedules can create a significant challenge: alpha leakage. This rigidity may prevent them from capitalizing on fleeting market leadership shifts and rapid thematic rotations, potentially trapping investors in lagging exposures and hindering true alpha capture.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 02:43:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bbed9ee97f501b0eafda3_1771814901048.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Rolls-Royce Signals Shareholder Return Amidst Valuation Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rolls-Royce-Signals-Shareholder-Return-Amidst-Valuation-Scrutiny/699bbec3ee97f501b0eafd8d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Rolls-Royce-Signals-Shareholder-Return-Amidst-Valuation-Scrutiny/699bbec3ee97f501b0eafd8d</guid><description>Rolls-Royce Holdings is poised to return over £1 billion to shareholders, headlined by a potential £1.5 billion share buyback, coinciding with its annual results on February 26. The aerospace giant anticipates record profits, underscoring a remarkable turnaround. However, its current valuation metrics and a history of significant past financial penalties warrant closer investor scrutiny regarding future growth sustainability.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 02:43:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bbec3ee97f501b0eafd8c_1771814752508.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Axis Bank Denies CreditAccess Grameen Bid, Valuation Focus Shifts</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Axis-Bank-Denies-CreditAccess-Grameen-Bid-Valuation-Focus-Shifts/699bbebaee97f501b0eafd73</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Axis-Bank-Denies-CreditAccess-Grameen-Bid-Valuation-Focus-Shifts/699bbebaee97f501b0eafd73</guid><description>Axis Bank Ltd. definitively stated it has no current or planned bid for CreditAccess Grameen Ltd., quashing prior market speculation and analyst projections. This clarification arrives despite bullish sentiment from brokerages like CLSA, which saw a "win-win" in a potential deal. While Axis Bank's denial may temper acquisition-driven upside for CreditAccess Grameen, the microfinance firm's robust business model and positive underlying analyst ratings persist, albeit with scrutiny over its high valuation (P/E of ~42.4x) in a sector facing asset quality concerns. Axis Bank, meanwhile, continues to garner strong analyst support with multiple 'buy' ratings and a positive outlook from Fitch.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 02:43:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bbebaee97f501b0eafd72_1771814759460.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Markets Navigate Tariffs, Geopolitics, Oil Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-Navigate-Tariffs-Geopolitics-Oil-Volatility/699bbc68ee97f501b0eaf4ce</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Markets-Navigate-Tariffs-Geopolitics-Oil-Volatility/699bbc68ee97f501b0eaf4ce</guid><description>Indian stock markets, including the Sensex and Nifty, are bracing for turbulence as renewed U.S. tariff policies and escalating geopolitical tensions in West Asia create a complex economic environment. A recent Supreme Court ruling struck down key tariff measures, only for President Trump to announce a revised 15% global tariff, leading to the deferral of critical India-U.S. trade talks. Simultaneously, rising Brent crude oil prices, driven by U.S.-Iran tensions, pose a significant risk to India's import-reliant economy, threatening inflation, currency stability, and corporate profit margins. The Nifty 50 trades with a P/E of 22.4 and the Sensex at 22.7, reflecting current market valuations amidst these crosscurrents.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 02:33:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bbc68ee97f501b0eaf4cd_1771814125328.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Infra Stocks: Axis Bets Big, But Risks Emerge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Infra-Stocks-Axis-Bets-Big-But-Risks-Emerge/699bbc65ee97f501b0eaf483</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Infra-Stocks-Axis-Bets-Big-But-Risks-Emerge/699bbc65ee97f501b0eaf483</guid><description>Axis Securities champions Kalpataru Projects, RITES, and Ahluwalia Contracts for expected infrastructure sector growth, citing robust order books and government capex. Targets suggest significant upside, yet varying analyst views and sector-specific risks, from regulatory bans to high valuations, demand investor caution.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 02:33:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bbc65ee97f501b0eaf482_1771814189378.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Derivatives: RBI Funding Curbs Spark Pivot &amp; Risk</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Derivatives-RBI-Funding-Curbs-Spark-Pivot-and-Risk/699bb7c3ee97f501b0eae28d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Derivatives-RBI-Funding-Curbs-Spark-Pivot-and-Risk/699bb7c3ee97f501b0eae28d</guid><description>The Reserve Bank of India's April 1 directives banning bank funding for proprietary trading and demanding 100% collateral for broker loans are poised to reshape India's massive derivatives market. Expect halved profit margins, a potential 20% drop in trading volumes, and a strategic pivot for firms. Smaller players face closure, while larger ones may seek offshore capital. This regulatory tightening aims to curb speculative excesses and protect retail investors, who have suffered significant losses.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 02:13:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bb7c3ee97f501b0eae28c_1771812992783.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Bangladesh: Ambitious Growth Targets Mask Deep Economic Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Bangladesh-Ambitious-Growth-Targets-Mask-Deep-Economic-Risks/699bb7b8ee97f501b0eae275</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Bangladesh-Ambitious-Growth-Targets-Mask-Deep-Economic-Risks/699bb7b8ee97f501b0eae275</guid><description>Bangladesh's economy, once compared to Asian Tigers, now grapples with subdued GDP growth (around 4-5%), high inflation (~9-10.5%), and declining foreign investment. Prime Minister Tarique Rahman has pledged to double the nation's GDP by 2034, a target requiring sustained growth rates near 9% annually, significantly exceeding current projections of 4-6%. While pursuing ASEAN membership to bolster economic diplomacy, investor confidence remains fragile due to ongoing political instability and structural weaknesses, including a stressed banking sector. Achieving these lofty goals hinges on deep-seated reforms, not just policy pronouncements.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 02:13:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bb7b8ee97f501b0eae274_1771812935962.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ICICI Pru: Tactical Sector ETFs Key for Navigating Cycles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/ICICI-Pru-Tactical-Sector-ETFs-Key-for-Navigating-Cycles/699bb74cee97f501b0eae1b5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/ICICI-Pru-Tactical-Sector-ETFs-Key-for-Navigating-Cycles/699bb74cee97f501b0eae1b5</guid><description>ICICI Prudential Asset Management Company is advocating for the strategic use of passive investment vehicles, specifically sector-specific ETFs and index funds, to gain tactical exposure. This approach aims to mitigate single-stock risk and navigate dynamic market leadership shifts driven by economic factors. The company identifies banking, energy, consumer, and technology as sectors with long-term drivers, but cautions that careful allocation and diversification are paramount, especially within volatile thematic strategies. The focus is on enhancing portfolio resilience and capturing targeted sector gains in a complex macro environment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 02:11:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bb74cee97f501b0eae1b4_1771812875596.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold, Silver Surge on Policy Chaos; Analyst Bets on Continued Upside</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Surge-on-Policy-Chaos-Analyst-Bets-on-Continued-Upside/699bb748ee97f501b0eae19e</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Gold-Silver-Surge-on-Policy-Chaos-Analyst-Bets-on-Continued-Upside/699bb748ee97f501b0eae19e</guid><description>Gold and silver prices climbed sharply as renewed uncertainty over U.S. trade policy and escalating geopolitical tensions drove investors to safe-haven assets. Despite mixed U.S. economic signals, the Federal Reserve's easing rate cut probability, and a weakening dollar supported bullion. Analysts highlight persistent policy instability and structural demand shifts, projecting continued upside for precious metals, though risks from potential Fed hawkishness and tariff impacts remain.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 02:11:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bb748ee97f501b0eae19d_1771812817278.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Gold Loans Rise as 'Bridge Asset' Strategy Unfolds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Gold-Loans-Rise-as-Bridge-Asset-Strategy-Unfolds/699bb73cee97f501b0eae184</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Gold-Loans-Rise-as-Bridge-Asset-Strategy-Unfolds/699bb73cee97f501b0eae184</guid><description>Record gold prices are transforming Indian household finance, fueling both investment demand and a surge in gold-backed borrowing. While jewelry demand fell 12% in 2025, investment demand jumped 73%, with gold loans expanding by 41.9% year-on-year by November 2025. Average loan sizes increased, and larger loan origination grew, indicating a strategic shift towards using gold for significant financial needs rather than outright sale. This trend positions gold as a 'bridge asset' for short-term liquidity, mitigating the need to liquidate long-term investments.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 02:11:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699bb73cee97f501b0eae183_1771812813550.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>