<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 01:16:50 +0000</pubDate><item><title>India Supercharges Auto Sector! Govt Nearly Doubles EV Funds – Big Wins or Missed Opportunities Ahead?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Supercharges-Auto-Sector-Govt-Nearly-Doubles-EV-Funds-Big-Wins-or-Missed-Opportunities-Ahead/694c8d80e10c98d078889839</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Supercharges-Auto-Sector-Govt-Nearly-Doubles-EV-Funds-Big-Wins-or-Missed-Opportunities-Ahead/694c8d80e10c98d078889839</guid><description>India's government plans to nearly double funding for its auto and auto component Production Linked Incentive (PLI) scheme to ₹5,500 crore in FY27, reinforcing its commitment to electric vehicle (EV) manufacturing and advanced automotive tech. Despite the increased allocation, new EV makers like Ather Energy are unlikely to get their application window reopened, as the scheme's eligibility criteria continue to favour established players. The move aims to boost domestic production, attract investment, and create jobs in the rapidly growing EV market.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 00:53:00 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c8d80e10c98d078889838_1766624845857.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>BSNL STUNNER: 3G to VANISH! Is YOUR phone ready for the BIG 4G upgrade?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/BSNL-STUNNER-3G-to-VANISH-Is-YOUR-phone-ready-for-the-BIG-4G-upgrade/694c8c80e10c98d07888977a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Telecom/BSNL-STUNNER-3G-to-VANISH-Is-YOUR-phone-ready-for-the-BIG-4G-upgrade/694c8c80e10c98d07888977a</guid><description>State-owned telecom operator Bharat Sanchar Nigam Ltd (BSNL) is shutting down its 3G mobile services nationwide as part of a major cost-cutting and network upgrade initiative. The company will also terminate maintenance contracts with vendors like Nokia and ZTE for 3G sites. This move allows BSNL to reallocate crucial 2100 MHz spectrum entirely for its 4G network, aiming to boost capacity and performance. Users with 3G-only SIM cards or older handsets may need to upgrade to ensure continued service.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 00:52:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c8c80e10c98d078889779_1766624494274.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Indian IT Giant in $500M US Patent War: Will Core Tech Ideas Be Blocked?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Giant-in-500M-US-Patent-War-Will-Core-Tech-Ideas-Be-Blocked/694c8ce8e10c98d0788897c2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Indian-IT-Giant-in-500M-US-Patent-War-Will-Core-Tech-Ideas-Be-Blocked/694c8ce8e10c98d0788897c2</guid><description>Hexaware Technologies has asked a US court to dismiss a $500 million patent infringement lawsuit filed by Natsoft. Hexaware argues the inventions, related to application modernization and GenAI, are abstract ideas not eligible for patents under US law. Natsoft claims Hexaware used software covered by nine of its patents, seeking damages that could significantly impact Hexaware's finances. The case highlights ongoing legal battles over software innovation patents.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 00:52:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c8ce8e10c98d0788897c1_1766624736166.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SEBI Unlocks Simpler Investing: Major Demat Account Shake-up Coming!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Unlocks-Simpler-Investing-Major-Demat-Account-Shake-up-Coming/694c8b72e10c98d07888967c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/SEBI-Exchange/SEBI-Unlocks-Simpler-Investing-Major-Demat-Account-Shake-up-Coming/694c8b72e10c98d07888967c</guid><description>India's market regulator, SEBI, is simplifying Basic Services Demat Account (BSDA) rules effective March 31, 2026. Zero Coupon Zero Principal (ZCZP) bonds and delisted securities will no longer count towards the eligibility threshold for BSDA, making it easier for small investors. Depository Participants must now review accounts quarterly and convert eligible ones to BSDA by default unless investors actively opt out. This aims to reduce compliance burdens and enhance the BSDA facility.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 00:47:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c8b72e10c98d07888967b_1766624345868.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Agri-Derivatives Market in Crisis: Why Key Futures Suspension Led to Sharp Decline!</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Agri-Derivatives-Market-in-Crisis-Why-Key-Futures-Suspension-Led-to-Sharp-Decline/694c8afbe10c98d0788895f9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Commodities/Indias-Agri-Derivatives-Market-in-Crisis-Why-Key-Futures-Suspension-Led-to-Sharp-Decline/694c8afbe10c98d0788895f9</guid><description>India's agricultural derivatives market is facing a severe downturn, with turnover declining significantly since the suspension of seven liquid agri-futures in December 2021. SEBI and NCDEX data show a sharp drop in notional turnover and reduced participation from farmers and value chain partners. Experts are calling for a review of market microstructure and a potential revocation of suspensions to restore vitality and crucial risk management functions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 00:46:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c8afbe10c98d0788895f8_1766624098816.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Growth Secret: Tackle Air Pollution &amp; Boost Economy Together! EVs &amp; New Cities Key.</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-Secret-Tackle-Air-Pollution-and-Boost-Economy-Together-EVs-and-New-Cities-Key/694c8b72e10c98d0788896a7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-Growth-Secret-Tackle-Air-Pollution-and-Boost-Economy-Together-EVs-and-New-Cities-Key/694c8b72e10c98d0788896a7</guid><description>India faces a high Air Quality Index (AQI) problem, with policymakers fearing environmental action might hinder economic growth. However, an economist suggests this is an exaggerated fear. Solutions include subsidizing Electric Vehicles (EVs) and developing new urban centers to reduce pollution and congestion in big cities. These strategies can lower AQI without sacrificing GDP growth, while also improving public health and long-term economic potential.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 00:46:01 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c8b72e10c98d0788896a6_1766624180925.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI's Paradox: IT Giants TCS, Accenture See Revenue Growth, But Is It New Money?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AIs-Paradox-IT-Giants-TCS-Accenture-See-Revenue-Growth-But-Is-It-New-Money/694c85fee10c98d078889418</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AIs-Paradox-IT-Giants-TCS-Accenture-See-Revenue-Growth-But-Is-It-New-Money/694c85fee10c98d078889418</guid><description>Major IT services companies like Tata Consultancy Services and Accenture are reporting impressive revenue growth from Artificial Intelligence. However, experts and company leaders suggest this growth may be cannibalizing existing revenue streams, improving efficiency rather than adding net new income. This trend raises questions about AI's true financial contribution beyond internal productivity gains.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 00:24:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://news-whales.s3.ap-south-1.amazonaws.com/images/thumbnail_694c85fee10c98d078889417_1766622815357.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>