<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 01:48:00 +0000</pubDate><item><title>AXISCADES Subsidiary Wins ₹25 Cr HAL Order for Single Board Computers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/AXISCADES-Subsidiary-Wins-25-Cr-HAL-Order-for-Single-Board-Computers/699baf45ee97f501b0eadc85</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/AXISCADES-Subsidiary-Wins-25-Cr-HAL-Order-for-Single-Board-Computers/699baf45ee97f501b0eadc85</guid><description>AXISCADES Technologies' subsidiary, Mistral Solutions Private Limited, has secured a domestic supply order worth approximately ₹25 crores from Hindustan Aeronautics Limited (HAL). The contract for Single Board Computers is slated for execution over multiple years, bolstering the company's order book and providing multi-year revenue visibility. This strategic win underscores Mistral's capabilities in critical defence electronics.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 01:37:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699baf45ee97f501b0eadc84_1771810979032.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>FIIs Return Selectively Amidst Geopolitical Crosswinds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/FIIs-Return-Selectively-Amidst-Geopolitical-Crosswinds/699ba65dee97f501b0ead8df</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/FIIs-Return-Selectively-Amidst-Geopolitical-Crosswinds/699ba65dee97f501b0ead8df</guid><description>Foreign institutional investors (FIIs) have re-entered Indian markets in February, injecting approximately ₹16,900 crore after consistent selling in prior months. This inflow is attributed to improving corporate earnings, particularly a 13.4% year-on-year growth in Nifty 50 earnings for Q3 FY26. However, a significant sectoral rotation is underway: FIIs offloaded nearly ₹11,000 crore in IT stocks due to AI disruption concerns while increasing allocations to financial services and capital goods. This cautious optimism unfolds against a backdrop of escalating US-Iran tensions and lingering uncertainty over US tariffs, which temper broader market enthusiasm.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:59:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ba65dee97f501b0ead8de_1771808524858.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Avendus Scales Up Fundraise to ₹4,000 Cr Amidst Private Credit Boom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Avendus-Scales-Up-Fundraise-to-4000-Cr-Amidst-Private-Credit-Boom/699ba5f9ee97f501b0ead83b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Avendus-Scales-Up-Fundraise-to-4000-Cr-Amidst-Private-Credit-Boom/699ba5f9ee97f501b0ead83b</guid><description>Avendus Group's Structured Credit Fund III (ASCF III) secured over ₹2,200 crore in commitments, triggering its greenshoe option and setting a target corpus of ₹4,000 crore. This marks a fourfold increase from its predecessor and highlights substantial investor confidence and a growing allocation towards private credit. The fund has already deployed 60% of its capital across diverse sectors, tracking an 18% gross IRR, consistent with Avendus's established performance. The expansion underscores the rapid growth and increasing sophistication of India's private credit sector.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:57:29 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ba5f9ee97f501b0ead83a_1771808390241.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tariff Turmoil Fuels Election Battleground</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Tariff-Turmoil-Fuels-Election-Battleground/699ba5ebee97f501b0ead821</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Tariff-Turmoil-Fuels-Election-Battleground/699ba5ebee97f501b0ead821</guid><description>The US Supreme Court's rejection of IEEPA tariffs and the administration's subsequent Section 122 impositions have intensified economic anxieties. With inflation and the wealth gap as focal points, and the President's approval rating below 40%, historical midterm trends point to significant political shifts. Vulnerable Republicans face constituent pressure as Democrats aim to capitalize on economic discontent, potentially reshaping US trade policy.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:57:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ba5ebee97f501b0ead820_1771808525392.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>US Tech Giants Pour Billions into India's Data Centers</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/US-Tech-Giants-Pour-Billions-into-Indias-Data-Centers/699ba570ee97f501b0ead79a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/US-Tech-Giants-Pour-Billions-into-Indias-Data-Centers/699ba570ee97f501b0ead79a</guid><description>US technology leaders are committing a staggering $67.5 billion to India's data center and AI infrastructure, a move driven by the nation's significant data storage deficit and burgeoning digital economy. This strategic investment by Microsoft, Amazon, and Google, among others, positions India as a critical global hub for AI development and data processing, far outweighing transient political concerns over energy costs. The influx aims to bridge India's vast data production-to-storage gap, projected to fuel substantial economic growth and solidify the subcontinent's role in the future of artificial intelligence.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:55:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699ba570ee97f501b0ead799_1771808273119.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Apple's India Exports Hit $23B Amid Trade Shifts: Can India Close the Gap?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Apples-India-Exports-Hit-23B-Amid-Trade-Shifts-Can-India-Close-the-Gap/699b9f6aee97f501b0ead436</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Apples-India-Exports-Hit-23B-Amid-Trade-Shifts-Can-India-Close-the-Gap/699b9f6aee97f501b0ead436</guid><description>India's smartphone exports soared to $30.13 billion in 2025, with Apple's iPhones accounting for $23 billion, primarily destined for the U.S. market. This growth was fueled by manufacturing incentives and temporary tariff advantages on Chinese imports. However, the recent abolition of U.S. fentanyl tariffs on Chinese goods, coupled with India's persistent cost disability compared to China, signals a complex future for the nation's electronics manufacturing ambitions. Apple's strategic pivot to India now faces deeper structural competition beyond trade policy.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:29:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699b9f6aee97f501b0ead435_1771806754012.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Sector Breakouts Clash with Rising Market Volatility</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/India-Sector-Breakouts-Clash-with-Rising-Market-Volatility/699b9f67ee97f501b0ead41f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/India-Sector-Breakouts-Clash-with-Rising-Market-Volatility/699b9f67ee97f501b0ead41f</guid><description>Indian markets are witnessing a divergence, with Nifty PSU Bank and Defence indices charting strong breakouts amidst robust derivatives momentum and FII long additions. However, elevated India VIX levels and a cautious FII stance on broader index futures indicate rising near-term uncertainty. This analysis probes the sustainability of sector strength against a backdrop of increased volatility and potential market headwinds. While sector-specific data points to bullish conviction, the broader market's risk aversion calls for a discerning view on the longevity of these rallies.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:29:27 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699b9f67ee97f501b0ead41e_1771806787337.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>DIIs Bet on CONCOR Amid PSE Weakness, Banking on Infrastructure</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/DIIs-Bet-on-CONCOR-Amid-PSE-Weakness-Banking-on-Infrastructure/699b9f53ee97f501b0ead408</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/DIIs-Bet-on-CONCOR-Amid-PSE-Weakness-Banking-on-Infrastructure/699b9f53ee97f501b0ead408</guid><description>Domestic institutional investors (DIIs) injected approximately ₹7 lakh crore into Indian equities in 2025, demonstrating sustained confidence. CONCOR, a key Public Sector Enterprise (PSE), is a notable recipient of this domestic capital, with DIIs raising their stake despite the company's negative one-year stock returns (-8.6%) and a decline in recent net profit. This contrarian move appears driven by expectations of operational efficiency gains and the catalytic impact of upcoming infrastructure projects like the Western Dedicated Freight Corridor (WDFC) link to JNPT.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:29:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699b9f53ee97f501b0ead407_1771806726002.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Space Boom: High Valuations Cloud Ambitious Growth Trajectory</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Indias-Space-Boom-High-Valuations-Cloud-Ambitious-Growth-Trajectory/699b9f51ee97f501b0ead3f1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Aerospace-&amp;-Defense/Indias-Space-Boom-High-Valuations-Cloud-Ambitious-Growth-Trajectory/699b9f51ee97f501b0ead3f1</guid><description>India aims to scale its space economy to ₹4 lakh crore by 2033, fueled by policy reforms and private investment. MTAR Technologies, Data Patterns, and Apollo Micro Systems are identified as key beneficiaries. However, despite a 'Strong Buy' consensus from analysts, these companies trade at premium valuations, often outstripping their current profitability and growth metrics, signaling a potential disconnect between market exuberance and fundamental value.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:29:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699b9f51ee97f501b0ead3f0_1771806710948.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ozempic Effect: Indian Eateries &amp; Speciality Restaurants Adjust to New Consumer</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Ozempic-Effect-Indian-Eateries-and-Speciality-Restaurants-Adjust-to-New-Consumer/699b9f51ee97f501b0ead3da</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Ozempic-Effect-Indian-Eateries-and-Speciality-Restaurants-Adjust-to-New-Consumer/699b9f51ee97f501b0ead3da</guid><description>A significant rise in weight-loss drug usage in urban India is compelling restaurants to revise menus, focusing on smaller portions and lighter options, dubbed the 'Size O' trend. This shift coincides with the impending March 2026 patent expiry of semaglutide (Ozempic), expected to drastically reduce drug prices and broaden consumer access. Speciality Restaurants, a prominent player, faces both opportunities from adapting to evolving dietary preferences and challenges from its current market valuation and analyst sentiment.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:29:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699b9f51ee97f501b0ead3d9_1771806676311.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Godrej Properties inks Thane JDA for ₹7,500 Cr revenue potential</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Godrej-Properties-inks-Thane-JDA-for-7500-Cr-revenue-potential/699b9c81ee97f501b0ead270</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Godrej-Properties-inks-Thane-JDA-for-7500-Cr-revenue-potential/699b9c81ee97f501b0ead270</guid><description>Godrej Properties Limited (GPL) has announced a significant joint development agreement (JDA) for an 18-acre land parcel in Thane, Mumbai. The project is expected to generate over ₹7,500 crore in revenue, marking GPL's fourth development in the rapidly growing Thane micro-market. This strategic move expands the company's footprint in the Mumbai Metropolitan Region, aligning with its growth strategy.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:17:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699b9c81ee97f501b0ead26f_1771805955537.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's AI Ambition Meets Digital Governance Failures</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-AI-Ambition-Meets-Digital-Governance-Failures/699b9aa2ee97f501b0ead186</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-AI-Ambition-Meets-Digital-Governance-Failures/699b9aa2ee97f501b0ead186</guid><description>Despite India's ambitious push towards an AI-driven future, recent Comptroller and Auditor General (CAG) reports reveal systemic fraud and mismanagement within existing digital governance systems, particularly Direct Benefit Transfers (DBTs). Audits from late 2025 and early 2026 highlight significant lapses, including missing verification checks and flawed beneficiary data, totaling hundreds of crores. This points to a critical disconnect: the nation's digital foundations appear insufficient for the envisioned AI leap, risking fraud amplification rather than corruption-free governance. The IT sector, while showing resilience, faces investor caution amid these systemic issues and global economic headwinds.</description><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:09:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699b9aa2ee97f501b0ead185_1771805494461.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>