<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:42:05 +0000</pubDate><item><title>Karnataka Bank Profit Dips 9% QoQ; NIM Eyes 3% Amidst Asset Quality Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Karnataka-Bank-Profit-Dips-9percent-QoQ-NIM-Eyes-3percent-Amidst-Asset-Quality-Concerns/699584fad25eafd9cdfd4986</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Karnataka-Bank-Profit-Dips-9percent-QoQ-NIM-Eyes-3percent-Amidst-Asset-Quality-Concerns/699584fad25eafd9cdfd4986</guid><description>Karnataka Bank reported a 9% sequential drop in its Q3 FY26 net profit to ₹290.79 crore, though it saw a modest 2.5% year-on-year growth. While Net Interest Margins (NIM) improved quarter-on-quarter to 2.92%, they remain below last year's levels. The bank aims to bring NIM back above 3% and strengthen its retail and MSME (RAM) segments. However, Gross Non-Performing Assets (GNPA) edged up slightly year-on-year to 3.32%, and the bank has a history of regulatory penalties and past fraud exposures.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:23:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699584fad25eafd9cdfd4985_1771406715199.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jyoti CNC Automation's Q3 Beats Expectations With 28% Revenue Jump</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jyoti-CNC-Automations-Q3-Beats-Expectations-With-28percent-Revenue-Jump/69958390d25eafd9cdfd489a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Jyoti-CNC-Automations-Q3-Beats-Expectations-With-28percent-Revenue-Jump/69958390d25eafd9cdfd489a</guid><description>Jyoti CNC Automation posted strong Q3 FY'26 results, with revenue soaring 28.1% year-over-year to ₹576 Crores and EBITDA growing 37.3%. The company is aggressively expanding its manufacturing capacity in India and France and is investing heavily in R&amp;D for next-generation products like semiconductor equipment. A healthy order book provides visibility for future growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:17:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69958390d25eafd9cdfd4899_1771406370879.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Accord Transformer IPO: Growth Fuels SME Debut on Feb 23</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Accord-Transformer-IPO-Growth-Fuels-SME-Debut-on-Feb-23/69958328d25eafd9cdfd4840</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Accord-Transformer-IPO-Growth-Fuels-SME-Debut-on-Feb-23/69958328d25eafd9cdfd4840</guid><description>Accord Transformer &amp; Switchgear is launching its ₹25.59 crore IPO on February 23, 2026, with shares priced between ₹43-₹46. The company, established in 2014, designs and manufactures electrical transformers and equipment. It reported a significant financial leap in FY25, with revenues soaring 62% to ₹79 crore and PAT reaching ₹6.05 crore. Proceeds will fund machinery purchases and working capital. Unlisted market sentiment shows an ₹8 premium.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:15:20 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69958328d25eafd9cdfd483f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ISA's AI Mission: Scaling Digital Energy Amidst Infrastructure Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ISAs-AI-Mission-Scaling-Digital-Energy-Amidst-Infrastructure-Hurdles/6995822cd25eafd9cdfd46b9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/ISAs-AI-Mission-Scaling-Digital-Energy-Amidst-Infrastructure-Hurdles/6995822cd25eafd9cdfd46b9</guid><description>The International Solar Alliance (ISA) has initiated a global mission to integrate Artificial Intelligence (AI) into clean energy systems across its member nations, aiming to accelerate the energy transition through digital infrastructure. Announced on February 17, 2026, the initiative highlights India's digital power sector model. However, the ambitious goal confronts significant hurdles, including the massive energy consumption of AI technologies, the strain on existing grid infrastructure, and the complex financial and technical demands of widespread digital adoption, particularly in developing economies. This push comes as the global AI in renewable energy market is projected for substantial growth, signaling both opportunity and considerable execution risk.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:11:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995822cd25eafd9cdfd46b8_1771406049761.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nvidia Deepens India AI Push with VC, Data Center Alliances</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nvidia-Deepens-India-AI-Push-with-VC-Data-Center-Alliances/6995822bd25eafd9cdfd46a2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Nvidia-Deepens-India-AI-Push-with-VC-Data-Center-Alliances/6995822bd25eafd9cdfd46a2</guid><description>Nvidia is significantly expanding its artificial intelligence footprint in India by forging strategic partnerships with major venture capital firms like Peak XV, Elevation Capital, Nexus Venture, and Accel India to fund AI startups. Concurrently, the chip giant is supplying its latest Blackwell Ultra GPUs to data centre operators Yotta Data Services and AI cloud firm E2E Networks Ltd., reinforcing India's high-performance computing infrastructure. This aggressive strategy aims to cultivate India's AI ecosystem, align with national AI ambitions, and solidify Nvidia's market position amidst escalating competition.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:11:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995822bd25eafd9cdfd46a1_1771405996911.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SC Slams RERA: Real Estate Watchdog Faces Reform Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/SC-Slams-RERA-Real-Estate-Watchdog-Faces-Reform-Demand/69958229d25eafd9cdfd468b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/SC-Slams-RERA-Real-Estate-Watchdog-Faces-Reform-Demand/69958229d25eafd9cdfd468b</guid><description>India's Real Estate Regulatory Authorities (RERA) face severe criticism from the Supreme Court, with observations suggesting they primarily facilitate defaulting builders rather than protect homebuyers. This judicial reprimand highlights widespread implementation failures and inconsistent enforcement across states, raising concerns about investor confidence. While the real estate sector anticipates disciplined growth in 2026, experts emphasize the urgent need for robust reforms and stricter oversight to rebuild credibility, rather than abolishing the framework.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:11:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69958229d25eafd9cdfd468a_1771406002745.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jefferies Picks: Financial Stocks Face Valuation Hurdles</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Jefferies-Picks-Financial-Stocks-Face-Valuation-Hurdles/699580c7d25eafd9cdfd44ba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Jefferies-Picks-Financial-Stocks-Face-Valuation-Hurdles/699580c7d25eafd9cdfd44ba</guid><description>Brokerage firm Jefferies has identified Cholamandalam Investment and Finance Company, Shriram Finance, and Bajaj Finance as top picks, citing strong profit growth, steady loan expansion, and improving margins. However, a deeper look reveals these companies are trading at elevated valuations, and persistent stress in unsecured loan segments poses a significant risk. While earnings momentum is projected to continue, further substantial re-ratings may be constrained, suggesting investors should balance optimism with caution regarding potential asset quality headwinds.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:05:11 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699580c7d25eafd9cdfd44b9_1771405715589.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India AI Summit Boom Meets IT Sector Disruption Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-AI-Summit-Boom-Meets-IT-Sector-Disruption-Fears/699580c6d25eafd9cdfd44a3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/India-AI-Summit-Boom-Meets-IT-Sector-Disruption-Fears/699580c6d25eafd9cdfd44a3</guid><description>The India AI Impact Summit 2026 saw record attendance and an extended run, signaling robust enthusiasm for the nation's AI ambitions. This surge, marked by a Guinness World Record for student pledges, occurred as India projects significant AI market growth. However, major Indian IT firms like Infosys (P/E ~20, MCap ~₹5.6L Cr) [7, 12], TCS (P/E ~19-21, MCap ~₹9.8L Cr) [14, 29], and Wipro (P/E ~17, MCap ~₹2.3L Cr) [13, 34] have recently navigated significant investor concerns regarding AI-driven disruption to traditional services, leading to a sharp sector sell-off and subsequent cautious rebound.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:05:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699580c6d25eafd9cdfd44a2_1771405645705.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's Steel Boom: Capacity Surge Risks Overshadow Demand</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Steel-Boom-Capacity-Surge-Risks-Overshadow-Demand/699580c5d25eafd9cdfd448c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Indias-Steel-Boom-Capacity-Surge-Risks-Overshadow-Demand/699580c5d25eafd9cdfd448c</guid><description>India stands alone in the global steel market with robust demand growth, fueled by economic expansion and infrastructure projects. Domestic consumption has surged over 50% in five years, prompting substantial capacity additions. However, the rapid pace of expansion, combined with global demand stagnation and the complexities of integrating advanced technologies like AI across a fragmented industry, presents a nuanced outlook that warrants caution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 09:05:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699580c5d25eafd9cdfd448b_1771405664005.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ARAPL Turns Profitable on Cost Cuts; Humro Unit Targets US Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ARAPL-Turns-Profitable-on-Cost-Cuts-Humro-Unit-Targets-US-Growth/69957c89d25eafd9cdfd42cd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/ARAPL-Turns-Profitable-on-Cost-Cuts-Humro-Unit-Targets-US-Growth/69957c89d25eafd9cdfd42cd</guid><description>Affordable Robotic and Automation Limited (ARAPL) has swung to profitability in the nine months of FY26, thanks to aggressive cost-cutting measures that reduced material and employee expenses by around 30% each. Despite a dip in revenue, improved operating efficiency led to a significant margin expansion. The company is now focusing on its subsidiary Humro's growth in the US autonomous vehicle market and monetizing its technology stack, while navigating execution risks tied to funding.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:47:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69957c89d25eafd9cdfd42cc_1771404571154.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Power Sector: Demand Rebounds, But Discom Health Looms Large</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Power-Sector-Demand-Rebounds-But-Discom-Health-Looms-Large/69957c18d25eafd9cdfd4223</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/India-Power-Sector-Demand-Rebounds-But-Discom-Health-Looms-Large/69957c18d25eafd9cdfd4223</guid><description>India's power demand surged 5% in January 2026, recovering from a Q3 dip. Antique Stock Broking reiterates a constructive outlook, with 'Buy' ratings on JSW Energy (target ₹648) and Adani Power (target ₹187), citing strong execution. However, the Draft National Electricity Policy 2026 highlights significant challenges, particularly the financial distress of distribution companies (discoms), which carry substantial debt and losses. While renewable energy additions continue, the sector's sustainable growth hinges on resolving these systemic issues. JSW Energy trades at a higher P/E (33.71x) compared to Adani Power (24.64x), reflecting differing growth trajectories and risk profiles.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:45:12 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69957c18d25eafd9cdfd4222_1771404896663.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Telangana Courts Global Pharma Giants With New Policy &amp; Funding</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Telangana-Courts-Global-Pharma-Giants-With-New-Policy-and-Funding/69957bb7d25eafd9cdfd415c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Telangana-Courts-Global-Pharma-Giants-With-New-Policy-and-Funding/69957bb7d25eafd9cdfd415c</guid><description>Telangana's 'Next-Gen Life Sciences Policy 2026-2030' aims to elevate Hyderabad into a top global life sciences cluster. Launched at Davos, the policy aligns with the ₹10,000 crore 'Biopharma SHAKTI' initiative, focusing on biologics and biosimilars. BioAsia 2026 saw significant investment pledges, including France's Opella Healthcare expanding its Global Capability Centre and Indonesia's Vaksindo Animal Health establishing a BSL-3 vaccine facility. The state is actively promoting advanced manufacturing and R&amp;D to drive value-led growth.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:43:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69957bb7d25eafd9cdfd415b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>TCS Bets Big on AI Amid Market AI-Disruption Fears</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TCS-Bets-Big-on-AI-Amid-Market-AI-Disruption-Fears/69957baad25eafd9cdfd4142</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/TCS-Bets-Big-on-AI-Amid-Market-AI-Disruption-Fears/69957baad25eafd9cdfd4142</guid><description>Tata Consultancy Services (TCS) CEO K Krithivasan is aggressively pivoting the company towards artificial intelligence, announcing substantial investments in AI infrastructure and dismissing fears of job displacement. He projects AI will expand opportunities and drive demand for services. However, this bullish outlook contrasts with recent market sentiment; IT stocks, including TCS, have experienced significant value erosion amidst widespread concerns that AI could disrupt traditional IT outsourcing models. While TCS plans significant data center expansion and acquisitions, investors are grappling with the potential for automation-driven margin compression and changing revenue streams, despite generally positive analyst price targets.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:43:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69957baad25eafd9cdfd4141_1771404323545.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>FedEx Bets ₹2,500 Cr on India Logistics Boom at NMIA</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/FedEx-Bets-2500-Cr-on-India-Logistics-Boom-at-NMIA/69957b9bd25eafd9cdfd412a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/FedEx-Bets-2500-Cr-on-India-Logistics-Boom-at-NMIA/69957b9bd25eafd9cdfd412a</guid><description>FedEx is committing over ₹2,500 crore to establish a 300,000 sq ft automated air cargo hub at the newly operational Navi Mumbai International Airport (NMIA). This strategic move positions FedEx as a pioneer cargo operator at the greenfield facility, aiming to capture substantial share in India's rapidly growing logistics market. The investment highlights Adani Airports' significant infrastructure development and intensifies competition with global rivals like DHL Group and domestic players such as Blue Dart Express, who are also scaling up operations across India.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:43:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69957b9bd25eafd9cdfd4129_1771404383373.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Auto Capacity Surge: A Race for Dominance Amidst Margin Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Auto-Capacity-Surge-A-Race-for-Dominance-Amidst-Margin-Risks/69957b26d25eafd9cdfd4090</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/India-Auto-Capacity-Surge-A-Race-for-Dominance-Amidst-Margin-Risks/69957b26d25eafd9cdfd4090</guid><description>India's automotive sector is undergoing a massive capacity expansion, with key players like Maruti Suzuki, Toyota, Mahindra &amp; Mahindra, Tata Motors, and JSW MG Motor lining up investments nearing Rs 1 lakh crore. This build-up, spurred by GST policy clarity and sustained demand, aims to increase annual passenger vehicle output by 65% to 9 million units. However, this race for scale intensifies competition, presenting potential risks of margin erosion and strategic rebalancing for market share.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:41:10 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69957b26d25eafd9cdfd408f.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India-UK Taskforce: Unlocking India's 70GW Offshore Wind Potential</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/India-UK-Taskforce-Unlocking-Indias-70GW-Offshore-Wind-Potential/699579dcd25eafd9cdfd3f46</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/India-UK-Taskforce-Unlocking-Indias-70GW-Offshore-Wind-Potential/699579dcd25eafd9cdfd3f46</guid><description>The newly formed India-UK Offshore Wind Taskforce aims to accelerate India's massive offshore wind development, tapping into over 70 GW of potential. The collaboration leverages the UK's established expertise in supply chains and market maturity to overcome India's execution and financing hurdles. This strategic partnership targets enhanced energy security and sustainable growth, building on decades of bilateral energy cooperation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:35:40 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699579dcd25eafd9cdfd3f45.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Microsoft Bets $50B on Global South AI to Secure Future Dominance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Microsoft-Bets-50B-on-Global-South-AI-to-Secure-Future-Dominance/699579c1d25eafd9cdfd3f2c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Microsoft-Bets-50B-on-Global-South-AI-to-Secure-Future-Dominance/699579c1d25eafd9cdfd3f2c</guid><description>Microsoft announced a $50 billion investment by 2030 to bolster AI infrastructure and skilling across the Global South. This significant capital infusion, detailed at the India AI Impact Summit, signals a strategic imperative to secure future market share, talent, and competitive positioning in emerging economies. While framed as bridging an AI divide, the move positions Microsoft to preempt rivals, shape regulatory frameworks, and lock in long-term growth prospects in regions poised for significant digital expansion.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:35:13 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699579c1d25eafd9cdfd3f2b.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>AI Investment Surge: Productivity Boom or Investor Bubble?</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Investment-Surge-Productivity-Boom-or-Investor-Bubble/699574b2d25eafd9cdfd3cec</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/AI-Investment-Surge-Productivity-Boom-or-Investor-Bubble/699574b2d25eafd9cdfd3cec</guid><description>AI investment, particularly in data centers, is projected to reach nearly $1 trillion. Global tech leaders debate whether this signals a genuine productivity boom or an unsustainable bubble. While advanced AI agents are now performing real-world tasks, investors seek clearer return-on-investment goals. The discussion highlights the shift from AI experiments to tangible economic contributions, but questions linger about the timeline for recouping massive capital outlays, especially with private capital bearing much of the risk.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:13:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699574b2d25eafd9cdfd3ceb_1771402536462.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Power Mech's ₹1000 Cr Orders Mask Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Power-Mechs-1000-Cr-Orders-Mask-Valuation-Concerns/69957493d25eafd9cdfd3cba</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Power-Mechs-1000-Cr-Orders-Mask-Valuation-Concerns/69957493d25eafd9cdfd3cba</guid><description>Power Mech Projects Ltd's shares saw a notable uplift, trading near ₹2,097, following the announcement of two substantial orders totaling approximately ₹1,000 crore from Adani Power subsidiaries. Mirzapur Thermal Energy (UP) Private Limited awarded a ₹515 crore contract, and Mahan Energen Limited a ₹490 crore contract, both for ultra-supercritical thermal power projects set for 36-month execution. However, this near-term revenue visibility is juxtaposed against recent analyst downgrades, a significant gap from its 52-week high, and the broader sector's energy transition towards renewables.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:13:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69957493d25eafd9cdfd3cb9_1771402553192.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Wipro Exec: India's AI Path Beats Western Compliance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Wipro-Exec-Indias-AI-Path-Beats-Western-Compliance/69957445d25eafd9cdfd3c01</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Wipro-Exec-Indias-AI-Path-Beats-Western-Compliance/69957445d25eafd9cdfd3c01</guid><description>Ivana Bartoletti, Wipro's Global Chief Privacy &amp; AI Governance Officer, advocates for India to bypass Western AI governance models, championing a unique "techno-legal" approach focused on long-term innovation and accountable deployment. She highlighted potential ROI failures from misaligned AI models and India's strength in digital infrastructure to scale its own path, distinct from Europe's compliance-heavy EU AI Act.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:11:49 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69957445d25eafd9cdfd3c00_1771402438534.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Infosys: AI Gamble Amidst Market Skepticism</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-AI-Gamble-Amidst-Market-Skepticism/6995743ed25eafd9cdfd3be0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Infosys-AI-Gamble-Amidst-Market-Skepticism/6995743ed25eafd9cdfd3be0</guid><description>Infosys is executing a dual AI strategy—AI-first for new demand and AI-augmented for existing services—targeting a $300-400 billion market. Despite ongoing AI projects and a partnership with Anthropic, the company's stock has depreciated significantly, reflecting investor skepticism about AI's disruptive impact on traditional IT models and concerns over margin compression. Competitors like TCS pursue infrastructure-heavy AI plays, while Infosys focuses on productivity and AI agents, raising questions about scaling and profitability.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:11:42 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995743ed25eafd9cdfd3bdf_1771402405307.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Microfinance Showdown: Muthoot's Value vs. CreditAccess's Speculative Premium</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Microfinance-Showdown-Muthoots-Value-vs-CreditAccesss-Speculative-Premium/6995739fd25eafd9cdfd3b28</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Microfinance-Showdown-Muthoots-Value-vs-CreditAccesss-Speculative-Premium/6995739fd25eafd9cdfd3b28</guid><description>The micro-finance sector shows signs of recovery, with CreditAccess Grameen (CAGL) and Muthoot Microfin (MML) reporting improved Q3 FY26 earnings. MML trades at a steep discount, evidenced by its negative P/E ratio, suggesting a potentially favorable risk-reward for value investors. Conversely, CAGL commands a premium valuation, partly fueled by its promoter's potential stake sale, but faces scrutiny over its high P/E and concentration in Karnataka. Both entities are actively managing asset quality and loan growth amidst evolving sector dynamics and regulatory shifts.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:09:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_6995739fd25eafd9cdfd3b27_1771402299232.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Valeo's India EV Push: €200M Investment Faces Fierce Competition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Valeos-India-EV-Push-200M-Investment-Faces-Fierce-Competition/699572c4d25eafd9cdfd399d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Valeos-India-EV-Push-200M-Investment-Faces-Fierce-Competition/699572c4d25eafd9cdfd399d</guid><description>Valeo is injecting over €200 million into its Indian operations, targeting a threefold increase in sales to €700 million by 2028. This aggressive expansion builds on a significant $1 billion electric powertrain supply agreement with Mahindra &amp; Mahindra for its 'Born Electric' platform. However, the strategy unfolds amidst intense competition in India's rapidly growing but complex electric vehicle market, alongside questions regarding Valeo's valuation and market positioning.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:05:24 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699572c4d25eafd9cdfd399c_1771402083203.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Yotta Deploys Nvidia Blackwell for Asia's Mega AI Hub</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Yotta-Deploys-Nvidia-Blackwell-for-Asias-Mega-AI-Hub/699572b3d25eafd9cdfd3986</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Yotta-Deploys-Nvidia-Blackwell-for-Asias-Mega-AI-Hub/699572b3d25eafd9cdfd3986</guid><description>Yotta Data Services is constructing one of Asia's largest AI computing hubs, investing over $2 billion in Nvidia's latest Blackwell Ultra GPUs. The project includes a $1 billion Nvidia DGX Cloud cluster, set to launch by August. This initiative positions India as a critical AI infrastructure node, but faces intense competition from global hyperscalers and raises questions about market sustainability and execution risks. Yotta's parent company is also pursuing a NASDAQ listing to fund its aggressive expansion.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 08:05:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_699572b3d25eafd9cdfd3985_1771402132301.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Trade, Mfg Policies Shift to Trust, Digital</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Trade-Mfg-Policies-Shift-to-Trust-Digital/69957101d25eafd9cdfd381a</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/India-Budget-2026-Trade-Mfg-Policies-Shift-to-Trust-Digital/69957101d25eafd9cdfd381a</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 signals a strategic shift in India's indirect tax policy, moving from control to confidence. Proposals aim to simplify tariffs, bolster domestic manufacturing, and enhance export competitiveness through calibrated duty rationalization and a digital-first customs approach. Key sectors like seafood, footwear, textiles, aviation, and renewable energy are slated for benefits from extended exemptions and duty reductions. A significant amendment reclassifies intermediary services under GST as exports, potentially improving global competitiveness. However, underlying complexities in customs litigation and the transition to a trust-based system present areas for ongoing scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:57:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69957101d25eafd9cdfd3819_1771401542232.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Genus Power Profit Doubles, But ED Probe Casts Shadow</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Genus-Power-Profit-Doubles-But-ED-Probe-Casts-Shadow/699570ced25eafd9cdfd37e5</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Genus-Power-Profit-Doubles-But-ED-Probe-Casts-Shadow/699570ced25eafd9cdfd37e5</guid><description>Genus Power Infrastructures Limited delivered stellar Q3 FY26 results, with net profit rocketing 117% year-on-year to INR 148 Crores, fueled by an 86% revenue surge to INR 1,122 Crores. The company boasts a substantial INR 27,000 Crore order book, ensuring multi-year visibility. However, a search by the Enforcement Directorate (ED) in December 2024, investigating alleged corruption, introduces a significant governance risk, despite management's claims of unaffected operations and full cooperation.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:57:02 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-699570ced25eafd9cdfd37e4.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Neogen Chemicals' Profit Tumbles 63% Despite 9% Revenue Gain</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Neogen-Chemicals-Profit-Tumbles-63percent-Despite-9percent-Revenue-Gain/69957057d25eafd9cdfd3775</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Neogen-Chemicals-Profit-Tumbles-63percent-Despite-9percent-Revenue-Gain/69957057d25eafd9cdfd3775</guid><description>Neogen Chemicals reported a 9% year-on-year revenue growth to ₹220 crore for Q3 FY26. However, profit after tax (PAT) fell sharply by 63% to ₹4 crore. This decline was attributed to increased finance costs related to capital expenditure for the Dahej plant reconstruction and Neogen Ionics ramp-up, alongside temporary operational expenses from interim toll manufacturing. The company is making progress on its strategic pivot towards battery chemicals, including a joint venture with Japan's Morita Investment Limited and nearing completion of its Dahej replacement plant.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:55:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69957057d25eafd9cdfd3774_1771401450742.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>L&amp;T, NVIDIA Forge Mega Deal for India's Largest AI Factory</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/LandT-NVIDIA-Forge-Mega-Deal-for-Indias-Largest-AI-Factory/69956fe4d25eafd9cdfd36fc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/LandT-NVIDIA-Forge-Mega-Deal-for-Indias-Largest-AI-Factory/69956fe4d25eafd9cdfd36fc</guid><description>Engineering giant Larsen &amp; Toubro (L&amp;T) is joining forces with AI leader NVIDIA to build India's largest Gigawatt-scale AI factory. This landmark initiative, aligned with the IndiaAI Mission, aims to significantly enhance India's standing as a global AI powerhouse by developing robust, scalable, and sovereign AI infrastructure.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:53:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69956fe4d25eafd9cdfd36fb_1771401294509.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Power Mech Gains on Orders Amid India's Energy Shift</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Power-Mech-Gains-on-Orders-Amid-Indias-Energy-Shift/69956d8dd25eafd9cdfd35f7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Power-Mech-Gains-on-Orders-Amid-Indias-Energy-Shift/69956d8dd25eafd9cdfd35f7</guid><description>Power Mech Projects Ltd. shares jumped on securing over ₹1,000 crore in thermal power projects from Adani Power subsidiaries, bolstered by strong Q3 results showing a 14.6% profit increase. However, the company operates within a dynamic Indian energy sector rapidly transitioning towards renewables, posing long-term strategic questions for its thermal-centric order book and past regulatory scrutiny.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:43:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69956d8dd25eafd9cdfd35f6_1771400736250.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India's 2047 Goal: Unpaid Female Labor Drains Trillions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2047-Goal-Unpaid-Female-Labor-Drains-Trillions/69956d14d25eafd9cdfd3545</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Economy/Indias-2047-Goal-Unpaid-Female-Labor-Drains-Trillions/69956d14d25eafd9cdfd3545</guid><description>India's 'Viksit Bharat @2047' vision is critically undermined by its low female labor force participation rate (FLFPR). The immense burden of unpaid domestic and care work on women represents a significant economic drain, costing trillions in lost GDP potential and jeopardizing the nation's demographic dividend. Despite recent policy efforts showing a rise in FLFPR, deep-rooted social norms and structural barriers indicate substantial untapped economic potential remains unrealized.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:41:08 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69956d14d25eafd9cdfd3544_1771400600225.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Qualcomm Bets $150M on India for Edge AI Leadership</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Qualcomm-Bets-150M-on-India-for-Edge-AI-Leadership/69956ca2d25eafd9cdfd349c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Qualcomm-Bets-150M-on-India-for-Edge-AI-Leadership/69956ca2d25eafd9cdfd349c</guid><description>Qualcomm Incorporated announced a $150 million strategic investment fund targeting Indian AI startups, specifically focusing on edge Artificial Intelligence. This initiative, deployed through Qualcomm Ventures, signals a significant push to bolster on-device intelligence and diversify beyond its traditional mobile base. The fund aims to tap into India's growing deep tech ecosystem and engineering talent to lead the next wave of AI integration into everyday devices and industrial systems, positioning Qualcomm as a key player in the rapidly expanding edge AI hardware market.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:39:14 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69956ca2d25eafd9cdfd349b_1771400509584.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sarvam AI Eyes Hardware with Kaze Glasses, Faces Fierce Competition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Sarvam-AI-Eyes-Hardware-with-Kaze-Glasses-Faces-Fierce-Competition/69956bc0d25eafd9cdfd33a7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Sarvam-AI-Eyes-Hardware-with-Kaze-Glasses-Faces-Fierce-Competition/69956bc0d25eafd9cdfd33a7</guid><description>Sarvam AI has launched Sarvam Kaze, its first AI-powered smart glasses, aiming to challenge global dominance with a "Made-In-India" approach focused on local languages. The device integrates cameras and voice command capabilities, leveraging Sarvam's proprietary AI models trained on Indian data. Despite a high-profile unveiling, crucial details on pricing, battery life, and hardware specifications remain undisclosed, while the company faces established players like Meta and significant consumer adoption hurdles.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:35:28 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69956bc0d25eafd9cdfd33a6_1771400288598.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Anthropic Eyes India as AI 'Development Crucible' Amidst Fierce Competition</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Anthropic-Eyes-India-as-AI-Development-Crucible-Amidst-Fierce-Competition/69956b35d25eafd9cdfd3302</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/Anthropic-Eyes-India-as-AI-Development-Crucible-Amidst-Fierce-Competition/69956b35d25eafd9cdfd3302</guid><description>Anthropic is strategically advancing its 'AI for Development' vision in India, ranking second globally in Claude usage. With a new India MD and a focus on education and enterprise partnerships like Pratham and Cognizant, the company aims to embed safe, beneficial AI. However, challenges remain in broad adoption beyond the tech sector and intense competition from global players eyeing India's burgeoning AI market.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:33:09 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69956b35d25eafd9cdfd3301_1771400193849.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Tata AutoComp Unifies European Brand, Expands Engineering Hub</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-AutoComp-Unifies-European-Brand-Expands-Engineering-Hub/69956b32d25eafd9cdfd32eb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Tata-AutoComp-Unifies-European-Brand-Expands-Engineering-Hub/69956b32d25eafd9cdfd32eb</guid><description>Tata AutoComp Systems has finalized the acquisition of IAC Group (Slovakia) s.r.o., now rebranded as Artifex Systems Slovakia s.r.o., integrating it into its European Artifex brand. This strategic move follows the prior acquisition of IAC Sweden, now Artifex Systems AB, aimed at consolidating operations, enhancing engineering capabilities, and bolstering market position within the EU automotive sector. Coinciding with this integration, a new Artifex Engineering Center opens today in Gothenburg, Sweden, reinforcing R&amp;D and customer collaboration. The combined entity seeks to leverage synergies for improved operational efficiency and a unified approach to serving global OEMs amidst evolving industry demands.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:33:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69956b32d25eafd9cdfd32ea_1771400118710.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Oman's Expat Fees Rise: Business Cost Reckoning Looms</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Omans-Expat-Fees-Rise-Business-Cost-Reckoning-Looms/69956a43d25eafd9cdfd31a9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/Omans-Expat-Fees-Rise-Business-Cost-Reckoning-Looms/69956a43d25eafd9cdfd31a9</guid><description>Oman's Ministry of Labour has introduced a tiered fee structure for expatriate work permits, directly linking costs to Omanisation compliance. Firms meeting local hiring quotas receive a 30% discount, while non-compliant employers face doubled fees. This policy aims to accelerate national employment and reduce reliance on foreign labour. Additional administrative simplifications, such as extended licence validity, are also in effect.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:29:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69956a43d25eafd9cdfd31a8_1771399904396.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Safari Industries Secures Carlton Brand Rights for 20 Years</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Safari-Industries-Secures-Carlton-Brand-Rights-for-20-Years/69956a40d25eafd9cdfd3192</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Safari-Industries-Secures-Carlton-Brand-Rights-for-20-Years/69956a40d25eafd9cdfd3192</guid><description>Safari Industries (India) Ltd. has signed a significant 20-year licensing agreement with Carlton Retail Private Limited (CRL) to exclusively use the 'CARLTON' brand for luggage and related products in India. The deal involves a substantial Rs. 99.50 Crore interest-free security deposit and an annual license fee based on sales, aiming to bolster Safari's brand portfolio and market presence.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:29:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69956a40d25eafd9cdfd3191_1771399865650.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Cement Firm Sees 35% Revenue Jump, Turns Profitable with Solar Savings</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Cement-Firm-Sees-35percent-Revenue-Jump-Turns-Profitable-with-Solar-Savings/69956953d25eafd9cdfd30ca</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/Cement-Firm-Sees-35percent-Revenue-Jump-Turns-Profitable-with-Solar-Savings/69956953d25eafd9cdfd30ca</guid><description>A cement maker has announced impressive Q3 FY'26 results, with revenue climbing 33% year-on-year to INR 38.69 Cr and EBITDA surging 63% to INR 10.5 Cr. The company achieved a significant turnaround, posting a profit after a loss last year, boosted by a 32% rise in cement volumes and savings from its integrated solar power operations. Term debt has also been reduced by 15%. Management eyes further growth through market and product expansion.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:25:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69956953d25eafd9cdfd30c9_1771399676628.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Som Distilleries Faces Profit Drop, MP Plant License Suspended Again</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Som-Distilleries-Faces-Profit-Drop-MP-Plant-License-Suspended-Again/69956893d25eafd9cdfd2fe6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Som-Distilleries-Faces-Profit-Drop-MP-Plant-License-Suspended-Again/69956893d25eafd9cdfd2fe6</guid><description>Som Distilleries &amp; Breweries reported a challenging Q3 FY26, with net profit slumping 74.5% year-on-year to ₹5.5 crore due to a significant 24% drop in beer volumes, attributed to cold weather. The company is also grappling with the suspension of its Madhya Pradesh plant's manufacturing license, a recurring issue stemming from past legal cases. This comes on the back of a prior ₹5 lakh SEBI penalty for disclosure lapses and a past license suspension related to child labor allegations, raising governance concerns for investors. Despite these headwinds, the company is pushing forward with its large Uttar Pradesh greenfield project and a strategy focused on its growing Indian Made Foreign Liquor (IMFL) segment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:21:55 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69956893d25eafd9cdfd2fe5_1771399374531.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hotels Shine, Aviation/Luggage Struggle: Sector Divergence in Q3FY26</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Hotels-Shine-AviationLuggage-Struggle-Sector-Divergence-in-Q3FY26/69956747d25eafd9cdfd2e5b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Brokerage-Reports/Hotels-Shine-AviationLuggage-Struggle-Sector-Divergence-in-Q3FY26/69956747d25eafd9cdfd2e5b</guid><description>The hospitality sector's Q3FY26 performance revealed a distinct divergence. Luxury hotels, particularly Leela Palaces, demonstrated robust growth in room rates and revenue, benefiting from a demand-supply imbalance. In contrast, aviation carriers like IndiGo grappled with escalating fuel and currency costs, impacting profitability despite high passenger load factors. The luggage segment, exemplified by VIP Industries and Safari Industries, faced significant margin compression due to discounting, inventory issues, and competitive pressures, leading to net losses and analyst downgrades for some.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:16:23 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-69956747d25eafd9cdfd2e5a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Nisus Finance Targets ₹4000 Cr AUM Post-NCCCL Deal, Eyes UAE Expansion</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Nisus-Finance-Targets-4000-Cr-AUM-Post-NCCCL-Deal-Eyes-UAE-Expansion/69956729d25eafd9cdfd2d71</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Nisus-Finance-Targets-4000-Cr-AUM-Post-NCCCL-Deal-Eyes-UAE-Expansion/69956729d25eafd9cdfd2d71</guid><description>Nisus Finance Services Co Limited has laid out an aggressive growth plan following its acquisition of NCCCL. For FY26, the company targets ₹4,000 Cr in consolidated Assets Under Management (AUM) and significant revenue growth for both its standalone business and the newly integrated NCCCL. This strategy emphasizes an urban infrastructure platform and expansion into the UAE market.</description><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 07:15:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_69956729d25eafd9cdfd2d70_1771399044867.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>