<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Whalesbook Financial News</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/All</link><description>Latest Indian and global financial market news</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:48:24 +0000</pubDate><item><title>LTIMindtree to LTM: Company Rebrands as Business Creativity Partner</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/LTIMindtree-to-LTM-Company-Rebrands-as-Business-Creativity-Partner/698c4db6fa94ce7dec4861f2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/LTIMindtree-to-LTM-Company-Rebrands-as-Business-Creativity-Partner/698c4db6fa94ce7dec4861f2</guid><description>LTIMindtree Limited announced its Board approved changing the company's legal name to LTM Limited, pending shareholder and regulatory approvals. Concurrently, it launched its new brand identity, 'The Business Creativity Partner,' emphasizing an AI-centric global technology services approach and a creator's mindset to drive transformative client outcomes under the tagline 'It’s time to Outcreate.'</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:36:54 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c4db6fa94ce7dec4861f1_1770802859716.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>SJVN Q3 Profit Surges 80% on Tariff Gains; Declares Dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/SJVN-Q3-Profit-Surges-80percent-on-Tariff-Gains-Declares-Dividend/698c4dabfa94ce7dec4861e9</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Energy/SJVN-Q3-Profit-Surges-80percent-on-Tariff-Gains-Declares-Dividend/698c4dabfa94ce7dec4861e9</guid><description>SJVN Limited posted a stellar Q3 FY26, with standalone PAT surging 80.8% YoY to ₹251.71 Cr, driven by a 35.4% revenue jump and significant margin expansion. The company declared an interim dividend of ₹1.15 per share and approved raising up to ₹1,000 Cr via NCDs. However, consolidated debt rose and the Debt Service Coverage Ratio declined, while the Devasari project faces Supreme Court uncertainty.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:36:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c4dabfa94ce7dec4861e8_1770802904790.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IRB InvIT Q3: Revenue Soars 60%, PAT Dips 34% Amid Mega Acquisitions</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IRB-InvIT-Q3-Revenue-Soars-60percent-PAT-Dips-34percent-Amid-Mega-Acquisitions/698c4caefa94ce7dec485f23</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/IRB-InvIT-Q3-Revenue-Soars-60percent-PAT-Dips-34percent-Amid-Mega-Acquisitions/698c4caefa94ce7dec485f23</guid><description>IRB InvIT Fund reported a robust 60% YoY revenue growth to ₹411.63 Cr in Q3 FY26, fueled by strong toll collections and new asset additions. However, Profit After Tax (PAT) declined by 34.38% to ₹5.97 Cr, impacted by a significant increase in borrowings to fund major acquisitions. Despite this, EBITDA margins improved to 89.93%. The Trust declared a ₹1.50 per unit distribution.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:32:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c4caefa94ce7dec485f22_1770802644346.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>INDO SMC Lands Rs 40 Cr Bus Duct Order, Eyeing Infrastructure Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/INDO-SMC-Lands-Rs-40-Cr-Bus-Duct-Order-Eyeing-Infrastructure-Growth/698c4ba4fa94ce7dec485bdf</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/INDO-SMC-Lands-Rs-40-Cr-Bus-Duct-Order-Eyeing-Infrastructure-Growth/698c4ba4fa94ce7dec485bdf</guid><description>INDO SMC Limited has secured a major domestic purchase order valued at Rs 40.77 crore for HT Air Insulated Bus Ducts from Shree Balaji Com LLP. The contract, requiring delivery within twelve weeks, highlights the company's capabilities in specialized electrical components and adds substantial value to its existing Rs 142.45 crore order book, reinforcing its position in India's expanding power distribution sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:28:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c4ba4fa94ce7dec485bde_1770802447248.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>GNG Electronics Surges 40% Revenue, Doubles PAT, Boosts FY26 Outlook</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/GNG-Electronics-Surges-40percent-Revenue-Doubles-PAT-Boosts-FY26-Outlook/698c4ba3fa94ce7dec485bd6</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tech/GNG-Electronics-Surges-40percent-Revenue-Doubles-PAT-Boosts-FY26-Outlook/698c4ba3fa94ce7dec485bd6</guid><description>GNG Electronics Ltd. reported a stellar Q3 FY26 with revenue soaring 40.3% YoY to INR 4,872.2 million and Profit After Tax (PAT) more than doubling to INR 386.9 million. EBITDA margins improved by 200 bps to 11.2%, and PAT margins expanded to 7.9%. Driven by strong industry tailwinds in the refurbished PC market and memory shortages impacting PC prices, the company has raised its full-year FY26 revenue growth guidance to 28-30% and profitability guidance by 150-200 basis points.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:28:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c4ba3fa94ce7dec485bd5_1770802407886.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hind Rectifiers Surges on Strong Q3 Growth &amp; 1:1 Bonus Share Approval</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hind-Rectifiers-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Growth-and-11-Bonus-Share-Approval/698c4b41fa94ce7dec485afb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Hind-Rectifiers-Surges-on-Strong-Q3-Growth-and-11-Bonus-Share-Approval/698c4b41fa94ce7dec485afb</guid><description>Hind Rectifiers Limited reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with standalone revenue soaring 44.0% YoY to ₹2,432.71 million and PAT rising 37.2% YoY to ₹137.28 million. The company's board also approved a significant 1:1 bonus share issue, a ₹0.9 million investment in its subsidiary Coincade Studios, and is evaluating global acquisition opportunities, signalling a strategic push for international expansion.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:26:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c4b41fa94ce7dec485afa_1770802289118.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Avanti Feeds Q3: Margin Gains Fuel Profit Amidst Rally</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Avanti-Feeds-Q3-Margin-Gains-Fuel-Profit-Amidst-Rally/698c4b38fa94ce7dec485abc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Avanti-Feeds-Q3-Margin-Gains-Fuel-Profit-Amidst-Rally/698c4b38fa94ce7dec485abc</guid><description>Avanti Feeds reported a 10.5% net profit increase to ₹149.4 crore for Q3 FY26, significantly outpacing its 1.3% revenue growth to ₹1,383 crore. The key driver was a margin expansion to 12.7% from 11.8%, indicating strong operational efficiency or pricing power. This performance fuels Avanti Feeds' impressive stock rally, with shares up 2.8% today and 41% in the last month, continuing an 82.2% gain over six months.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:26:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c4b38fa94ce7dec485abb_1770802288493.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Aurobindo Pharma: Pen-G Dominance Masks US Generics Caution</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aurobindo-Pharma-Pen-G-Dominance-Masks-US-Generics-Caution/698c4a4efa94ce7dec4857bb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Aurobindo-Pharma-Pen-G-Dominance-Masks-US-Generics-Caution/698c4a4efa94ce7dec4857bb</guid><description>Aurobindo Pharma's upcoming year is projected to be heavily influenced by its Penicillin G (Pen-G) business, with analyst Vishal Manchanda of Systematix Group emphasizing this segment over immediate U.S. market contributions. Despite recent U.S. Food and Drug Administration (USFDA) Form 483 observations, Manchanda downplayed their significance, citing Aurobindo's history of regulatory compliance. Meanwhile, the broader Indian pharmaceutical sector sees domestic formulations outperforming, though the U.S. generics outlook remains subdued. Aurobindo's current P/E ratio of 19.22 is notably lower than its peers like Sun Pharma (37.43) and Ajanta Pharma (34.65), suggesting potential valuation differences.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:22:22 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c4a4efa94ce7dec4857ba_1770802020910.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Windlas Biotech Records Record Revenue, Eyes Growth Amidst Pharma Consolidation</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Windlas-Biotech-Records-Record-Revenue-Eyes-Growth-Amidst-Pharma-Consolidation/698c49edfa94ce7dec485572</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Windlas-Biotech-Records-Record-Revenue-Eyes-Growth-Amidst-Pharma-Consolidation/698c49edfa94ce7dec485572</guid><description>Windlas Biotech has achieved a significant milestone, reporting record revenues for the 12th consecutive quarter. In Q3 FY26, revenue from operations surged 20% year-on-year to INR 233 crores, driven by strong performance in the Generic Formulations CDMO (up 23%) and Exports (up 36%) segments. For the first nine months of FY26, revenue grew 19% YoY to INR 666 crores, with EPS increasing 12% to INR 24.02. The company is strategically positioning itself to benefit from industry consolidation driven by stringent Schedule M compliance, highlighting its robust audit readiness and quality systems as key differentiators. Management expressed strong optimism for future growth across all business verticals, with the mechanical completion of Plant 6 expected by end of FY26 to further bolster capacity.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:20:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c49edfa94ce7dec485571_1770801897514.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>IOL Chemicals PAT Flat Despite Revenue Growth; Declares Interim Dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/IOL-Chemicals-PAT-Flat-Despite-Revenue-Growth-Declares-Interim-Dividend/698c49dffa94ce7dec4854fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Other/IOL-Chemicals-PAT-Flat-Despite-Revenue-Growth-Declares-Interim-Dividend/698c49dffa94ce7dec4854fb</guid><description>IOL Chemicals and Pharmaceuticals reported a 10.91% YoY revenue increase to ₹580.39 Cr in Q3 FY26. However, consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) remained nearly flat at ₹20.58 Cr due to an exceptional item of ₹11.21 Cr related to new Labour Codes. The company declared an interim dividend of ₹1 per share. The pharmaceutical segment showed robust growth, outpacing the chemical segment.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:20:31 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c49dffa94ce7dec4854fa_1770801955052.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>RBI Ethics Push Puts Spotlight on Axis Bank's Governance</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Ethics-Push-Puts-Spotlight-on-Axis-Banks-Governance/698c4977fa94ce7dec4853d1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/RBI-Ethics-Push-Puts-Spotlight-on-Axis-Banks-Governance/698c4977fa94ce7dec4853d1</guid><description>Reserve Bank of India Deputy Governor Swaminathan J underscored the critical importance of ethics in banking, reframing it as a core discipline rather than a 'soft theme.' Speaking at the Axis Bank Champions Awards ceremony, he highlighted that robust ethical frameworks are essential for safeguarding customers, employees, and the institutions themselves. This stance suggests increased scrutiny for banks like Axis, emphasizing customer-centricity, transparency in digital dealings, and proactive mistake correction as vital for long-term credibility.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:18:47 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c4977fa94ce7dec4853d0_1770801839548.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Groww Launches Hospital ETFs Amid Sector Valuation Concerns</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Groww-Launches-Hospital-ETFs-Amid-Sector-Valuation-Concerns/698c48e0fa94ce7dec4852a7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Mutual-Funds/Groww-Launches-Hospital-ETFs-Amid-Sector-Valuation-Concerns/698c48e0fa94ce7dec4852a7</guid><description>Groww Mutual Fund has launched the Groww BSE Hospitals ETF and a related Fund of Fund, offering passive investment exposure to India's hospital sector via the BSE Hospitals Index. This launch coincides with a period of high valuations for listed hospital companies, prompting questions about the timing and value proposition of passive investments in this specialized, growth-oriented industry. Key hospital stocks like Apollo, Fortis, and Max Healthcare are trading at premium P/E multiples, reflecting strong investor confidence but also potential risks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:16:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c48e0fa94ce7dec4852a6_1770801684741.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Rejects Philip Morris E-cig Lobbying, Upholds HTP Ban</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/India-Rejects-Philip-Morris-E-cig-Lobbying-Upholds-HTP-Ban/698c48d6fa94ce7dec48529f</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/World-Affairs/India-Rejects-Philip-Morris-E-cig-Lobbying-Upholds-HTP-Ban/698c48d6fa94ce7dec48529f</guid><description>New Delhi has officially confirmed it will not relax the ban on e-cigarettes and heated tobacco products (HTPs), decisively rejecting Philip Morris International's (PMI) extensive lobbying campaign. The government cited its commitment to evidence-based tobacco control, underscoring the health risks associated with these products and maintaining the existing 2019 prohibition. This decision blocks PMI's aspirations to introduce its IQOS device into India's significant tobacco market.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:16:06 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c48d6fa94ce7dec48529e_1770801707384.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Goldi Solar Eyes $350M IPO Amid India's Crowded Green Energy Rush</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Goldi-Solar-Eyes-350M-IPO-Amid-Indias-Crowded-Green-Energy-Rush/698c487bfa94ce7dec4851a0</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/Goldi-Solar-Eyes-350M-IPO-Amid-Indias-Crowded-Green-Energy-Rush/698c487bfa94ce7dec4851a0</guid><description>Gujarat-based Goldi Solar is preparing an Initial Public Offering (IPO) that could raise up to $350 million, signaling continued momentum in India's renewable energy sector. The company, with a 14.7 GW solar module capacity, aims to file a draft prospectus by April 2026. This move occurs within a highly active IPO market for green energy firms, driven by national targets and policy support, though intense competition and valuation scrutiny are emerging.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:14:35 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c487bfa94ce7dec48519f_1770801571577.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Budget 2026: Infra Focus Boosts Real Estate, Skips Housing Stimulus</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Budget-2026-Infra-Focus-Boosts-Real-Estate-Skips-Housing-Stimulus/698c47b4fa94ce7dec484eeb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Budget-2026-Infra-Focus-Boosts-Real-Estate-Skips-Housing-Stimulus/698c47b4fa94ce7dec484eeb</guid><description>The Union Budget 2026-27 channels substantial capital into infrastructure, aiming to spur real estate growth via enhanced connectivity and urban development, particularly in Tier-2 and Tier-3 cities. However, a notable absence of direct housing demand incentives, such as increased tax deductions or GST relief for developers, suggests a strategy focused on long-term, infrastructure-driven expansion rather than immediate residential market stimulation. This could lead to varied performance across real estate segments, with commercial, industrial, and logistics potentially seeing stronger immediate traction, while residential growth hinges on the trickle-down effects of infrastructural development.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:11:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c47b4fa94ce7dec484eea_1770801325392.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Synergy Green Industries Posts Q3 Loss As Revenue Drops 21.6%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Synergy-Green-Industries-Posts-Q3-Loss-As-Revenue-Drops-216percent/698c4781fa94ce7dec484e5b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Synergy-Green-Industries-Posts-Q3-Loss-As-Revenue-Drops-216percent/698c4781fa94ce7dec484e5b</guid><description>Synergy Green Industries reported a significant financial downturn for the quarter and nine months ended December 31, 2025. Revenue declined 21.6% YoY to ₹7,200.33 Lakhs in Q3 FY26, resulting in a loss of ₹148.88 Lakhs against a profit last year. For the nine months, revenue fell 6.6% YoY, and Profit After Tax (PAT) plunged 67.5% to ₹424.91 Lakhs. The company provided no outlook or guidance, and the board approved key personnel changes effective April 1, 2026.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:10:25 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/headline-698c4781fa94ce7dec484e5a.jpg.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Enbee Trade: Revenue Plunges 99%, Profit Wiped Out; EPS Jumps 200%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Enbee-Trade-Revenue-Plunges-99percent-Profit-Wiped-Out-EPS-Jumps-200percent/698c4715fa94ce7dec484d99</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Enbee-Trade-Revenue-Plunges-99percent-Profit-Wiped-Out-EPS-Jumps-200percent/698c4715fa94ce7dec484d99</guid><description>Enbee Trade and Finance Limited reported a catastrophic Q3 FY2026, with revenue plummeting 98.95% YoY to ₹7.88 Lakhs and net profit collapsing 99.23% to ₹2.75 Lakhs. The nine-month period saw revenue drop 82.55% and profit fall 78.37%. Alarmingly, basic EPS surged 200% YoY to ₹0.15 for nine months, a stark contradiction to the financial downturn, compounded by significant impairment charges.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:08:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c4715fa94ce7dec484d98_1770801181733.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Parag Milk Foods Posts Record Revenue, But Milk Inflation Squeezes Margins</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Parag-Milk-Foods-Posts-Record-Revenue-But-Milk-Inflation-Squeezes-Margins/698c46acfa94ce7dec484bab</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Parag-Milk-Foods-Posts-Record-Revenue-But-Milk-Inflation-Squeezes-Margins/698c46acfa94ce7dec484bab</guid><description>Parag Milk Foods Limited achieved a significant milestone, crossing INR1,000 crores in revenue for the second consecutive quarter in Q3 FY26, with a 14% year-on-year growth. The 'new age' business, including Pride of Cows and Avvatar, more than doubled its revenue, growing 123% YoY to surpass INR100 crores. Despite this top-line momentum and debt reduction, the company grappled with a 20% rise in milk prices, leading to a YoY decline in gross and EBITDA margins. Management plans disciplined pricing and portfolio enhancement to navigate ongoing inflationary pressures.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:06:52 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c46acfa94ce7dec484baa_1770801086441.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Archies Q3 Loss Deepens as Auditors Raise Inventory and TDS Red Flags</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Archies-Q3-Loss-Deepens-as-Auditors-Raise-Inventory-and-TDS-Red-Flags/698c4613fa94ce7dec4848ff</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Archies-Q3-Loss-Deepens-as-Auditors-Raise-Inventory-and-TDS-Red-Flags/698c4613fa94ce7dec4848ff</guid><description>Archies Limited has posted a grim financial update for its third quarter ending December 31, 2025. Revenue from operations plunged 23% year-on-year to ₹1352.33 Lakhs. The company swung to a net loss of ₹7.46 Lakhs, a reversal from a profit in the prior year. Critically, statutory auditors raised significant concerns, stating an inability to verify inventory valuation against Net Realisable Value (NRV) and noted the non-deposit of Employees Provident Fund (EPF) and Tax Deducted at Source (TDS) for several months.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:04:19 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c4613fa94ce7dec4848fe_1770800966637.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Amanta Healthcare Turns Profitable, Targets 20% Revenue Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Amanta-Healthcare-Turns-Profitable-Targets-20percent-Revenue-Growth/698c45aefa94ce7dec4847c8</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Amanta-Healthcare-Turns-Profitable-Targets-20percent-Revenue-Growth/698c45aefa94ce7dec4847c8</guid><description>Amanta Healthcare Limited reported a significant turnaround, moving from net losses to a profit of INR 11 Cr in FY25, with 9M FY26 PAT rising 51.3% YoY to INR 9 Cr. The company reduced total debt by over INR 30 Cr, bringing the Debt-to-Equity ratio down to 0.44x. With ambitious plans for capacity expansion and a new solar power plant to cut costs, Amanta Healthcare projects over 20% revenue CAGR and EBITDA margins exceeding 25% for the next two years.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:02:38 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c45aefa94ce7dec4847c7_1770800843812.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>OneSource Eyes MENA GLP-1 Market Via Hikma Deal</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/OneSource-Eyes-MENA-GLP-1-Market-Via-Hikma-Deal/698c45adfa94ce7dec4847c1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/OneSource-Eyes-MENA-GLP-1-Market-Via-Hikma-Deal/698c45adfa94ce7dec4847c1</guid><description>OneSource Specialty Pharma Limited has obtained Saudi Food and Drug Authority (SFDA) approval for its generic semaglutide, marking a strategic entry into the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia and the broader MENA region. The company will leverage an exclusive partnership with Hikma Pharmaceuticals PLC for commercialization, utilizing OneSource's Indian manufacturing capabilities and Hikma's extensive regional distribution network to offer an affordable alternative for GLP-1 therapies. This move capitalizes on the rapidly growing demand for diabetes and weight management treatments in the Middle East.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:02:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c45adfa94ce7dec4847c0_1770800880974.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>J&amp;K Fruit Growers Face Ruin as India-US Trade Deal Slashes Tariffs</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/JandK-Fruit-Growers-Face-Ruin-as-India-US-Trade-Deal-Slashes-Tariffs/698c4535fa94ce7dec4845b7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/JandK-Fruit-Growers-Face-Ruin-as-India-US-Trade-Deal-Slashes-Tariffs/698c4535fa94ce7dec4845b7</guid><description>Jammu and Kashmir's fruit growers and sellers are bracing for economic hardship following the India-US trade deal. Reduced import duties on apples and tree nuts, including walnuts and almonds, are expected to severely impact the region's horticulture sector, which supports livelihoods for nearly 20 lakh people. While the government maintains farmer interests are protected, local representatives and officials express grave concerns, calling the tariff cuts a potential 'final nail in the coffin' for marginal farmers already struggling with rising costs and pest outbreaks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:00:37 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c4535fa94ce7dec4845b6_1770800703722.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Hospital Stocks Rally, But Capex Strain and Margin Risks Loom</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Hospital-Stocks-Rally-But-Capex-Strain-and-Margin-Risks-Loom/698c4520fa94ce7dec4844f3</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Hospital-Stocks-Rally-But-Capex-Strain-and-Margin-Risks-Loom/698c4520fa94ce7dec4844f3</guid><description>Hospital stocks surged up to 6% on Wednesday, outperforming a tepid market, driven by robust Q3FY26 earnings from Apollo Hospitals and expansion plans at Max Healthcare. While government initiatives offer tailwinds, significant capital expenditure, rising operational costs, and intense competition present considerable risks to sustained margin expansion and profitability across the sector.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 09:00:16 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c4520fa94ce7dec4844f2_1770800740879.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Sandhar Tech: Mixed Q3 Results; Slump Sale of Unit-I Approved</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sandhar-Tech-Mixed-Q3-Results-Slump-Sale-of-Unit-I-Approved/698c44bafa94ce7dec4841e1</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Sandhar-Tech-Mixed-Q3-Results-Slump-Sale-of-Unit-I-Approved/698c44bafa94ce7dec4841e1</guid><description>Sandhar Technologies announced mixed financial results for Q3 FY2026. While consolidated revenue surged 21.66% YoY to ₹1,184.64 Cr, standalone revenue saw a marginal dip of 0.37% YoY to ₹737.03 Cr. Standalone PAT declined 7.08% YoY, impacted by new Labour Codes. The company's board also approved the slump sale of its Aluminium Die Casting Unit-I to its subsidiary, Sandhar Ascast Private Limited, aiming for operational synergies and economies of scale, with completion expected by March 2026.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 08:58:34 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c44bafa94ce7dec4841e0_1770800607565.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Quest Capital Markets Skyrockets 3954% on Dividend Income Surge</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Quest-Capital-Markets-Skyrockets-3954percent-on-Dividend-Income-Surge/698c4444fa94ce7dec4840fb</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Quest-Capital-Markets-Skyrockets-3954percent-on-Dividend-Income-Surge/698c4444fa94ce7dec4840fb</guid><description>Quest Capital Markets Limited has reported a staggering 3954% year-on-year surge in revenue to ₹2,703.38 Lakhs for Q3 FY26, alongside a 6770% jump in net profit to ₹2,070.07 Lakhs. The explosive growth was primarily fueled by a significant increase in dividend income. While Q3 EPS rose to ₹20.70, detailed operational performance and future guidance were absent, raising transparency concerns for investors.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 08:56:36 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c4444fa94ce7dec4840fa_1770800486255.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>India Realty 2026: Growth Cues Meet Cautionary Winds</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Realty-2026-Growth-Cues-Meet-Cautionary-Winds/698c43f5fa94ce7dec483fbd</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/India-Realty-2026-Growth-Cues-Meet-Cautionary-Winds/698c43f5fa94ce7dec483fbd</guid><description>India's real estate market enters 2026 with cautious optimism, buoyed by enhanced housing finance access and sustained end-user demand, particularly in premium segments. While metro markets remain dominant, Tier 2 and 3 cities offer emerging potential. However, global economic uncertainties and evolving investor preferences towards institutional capital and sustainability introduce a more disciplined growth trajectory, demanding careful execution and risk management.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 08:55:17 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c43f5fa94ce7dec483fbc_1770800386110.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>ReNew Energy Taps GIFT City for $600M Green Bonds Amidst Market Growth</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/ReNew-Energy-Taps-GIFT-City-for-600M-Green-Bonds-Amidst-Market-Growth/698c43e2fa94ce7dec483f7d</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Renewables/ReNew-Energy-Taps-GIFT-City-for-600M-Green-Bonds-Amidst-Market-Growth/698c43e2fa94ce7dec483f7d</guid><description>ReNew Energy Global PLC has successfully raised $600 million through 6.5% senior secured green bonds due 2031, issued via its GIFT City subsidiary. This transaction is notable as the first international bond offering by an entity incorporated in India's GIFT City, highlighting the hub's potential for green finance. The issuance attracted significant institutional investor interest across Asia, the UK, and the US, reflecting confidence in ReNew's strategy and creditworthiness. Proceeds will likely support the company's decarbonization efforts. This move occurs as the global green bond market anticipates record issuance in 2026, driven by strong demand for renewable energy financing, despite persistent higher interest rate environments.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 08:54:58 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c43e2fa94ce7dec483f7c_1770800371373.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Enbee Trade Finance Posts 237% Net Profit Jump, But Margins Shrink</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Enbee-Trade-Finance-Posts-237percent-Net-Profit-Jump-But-Margins-Shrink/698c43ddfa94ce7dec483f75</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Banking-Finance/Enbee-Trade-Finance-Posts-237percent-Net-Profit-Jump-But-Margins-Shrink/698c43ddfa94ce7dec483f75</guid><description>Enbee Trade and Finance Limited posted a robust 237% year-on-year jump in Net Profit to ₹275.38 Lakhs for Q3 FY26, driven by a massive 247% surge in Total Revenue to ₹788.19 Lakhs. The nine-month period also showed strong growth, with Net Profit up 159% YoY. However, Profit Before Tax (PBT) margin compressed significantly in Q3 FY26 to 45.42% from 105.92% in Q3 FY25, raising concerns about cost efficiencies despite the topline explosion. Basic EPS rose to ₹0.05 from ₹0.01 YoY.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 08:54:53 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c43ddfa94ce7dec483f74_1770800487322.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Emami Realty Q3 Net Loss Widens Sharply, Revenue Halved Year-on-Year</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Emami-Realty-Q3-Net-Loss-Widens-Sharply-Revenue-Halved-Year-on-Year/698c43d5fa94ce7dec483f45</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Emami-Realty-Q3-Net-Loss-Widens-Sharply-Revenue-Halved-Year-on-Year/698c43d5fa94ce7dec483f45</guid><description>Emami Realty Limited posted a dismal Q3 FY26, with standalone revenue from operations plummeting 47% YoY to ₹489.11 Cr and consolidated revenue similarly affected. Net losses ballooned significantly; standalone net loss surged to ₹3,727.35 Cr (up from ₹3,558.05 Cr YoY), and the nine-month loss escalated to ₹12,364.05 Cr. Despite unmodified auditor opinions, the company's reserves remain deeply negative at ₹(17,999.59) Cr, signalling a severely eroded net worth. No management guidance was disclosed.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 08:54:45 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c43d5fa94ce7dec483f44_1770800400845.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ramco Industries Q3 Profit Surges 103% on Margin Boost</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ramco-Industries-Q3-Profit-Surges-103percent-on-Margin-Boost/698c4337fa94ce7dec483d19</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Ramco-Industries-Q3-Profit-Surges-103percent-on-Margin-Boost/698c4337fa94ce7dec483d19</guid><description>Ramco Industries reported a robust Q3 FY26 with consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) soaring 103.5% year-on-year to ₹21.69 Cr, fueled by operating margins expanding to 9.27%. Consolidated revenue grew 13.1% to ₹388.63 Cr. However, standalone PAT saw a modest 10.8% rise on a revenue jump of 12.2%, with standalone margins slipping slightly. The Building Products segment remains the primary revenue driver.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 08:52:07 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c4337fa94ce7dec483d18_1770800219996.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Ashok Leyland Eyes $200M for OHM Mobility Amid Valuation Scrutiny</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Ashok-Leyland-Eyes-200M-for-OHM-Mobility-Amid-Valuation-Scrutiny/698c432ffa94ce7dec483cd2</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Transportation/Ashok-Leyland-Eyes-200M-for-OHM-Mobility-Amid-Valuation-Scrutiny/698c432ffa94ce7dec483cd2</guid><description>Ashok Leyland is seeking approximately $200 million for its electric mobility services arm, OHM Global Mobility, aiming for a valuation between $800 million and $1 billion. This move into the Electric Mobility as a Service (e-MaaS) sector comes amid significant government push for EVs, but raises questions about OHM's valuation relative to its operational scale and its parent company's own EV investments. The company's robust market share in commercial vehicles and expansion plans are key, yet reliance on state transport utility payments and a highly leveraged capital structure present considerable risks.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 08:51:59 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c432ffa94ce7dec483cd1_1770800551990.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Jeevan Scientific: Stellar Q3 Standalone Profit, But 9M Consolidated Loss Widens</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Jeevan-Scientific-Stellar-Q3-Standalone-Profit-But-9M-Consolidated-Loss-Widens/698c4243fa94ce7dec483c04</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Healthcare-Biotech/Jeevan-Scientific-Stellar-Q3-Standalone-Profit-But-9M-Consolidated-Loss-Widens/698c4243fa94ce7dec483c04</guid><description>Jeevan Scientific Technology Limited reported a strong Q3 FY26 with standalone net profit soaring 614.1% YoY to ₹230.06 lakhs. However, nine-month consolidated results showed a net loss of ₹80.86 lakhs, a significant deterioration from the prior year's profit. Standalone revenue grew 42.5% YoY in the quarter, while consolidated revenue increased 52.5% YoY.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 08:48:03 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c4243fa94ce7dec483c03_1770800006440.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Wonder Electricals Q3 PAT Plummets 87% as Revenue Falls 39%</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Wonder-Electricals-Q3-PAT-Plummets-87percent-as-Revenue-Falls-39percent/698c3efdfa94ce7dec4833bc</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Wonder-Electricals-Q3-PAT-Plummets-87percent-as-Revenue-Falls-39percent/698c3efdfa94ce7dec4833bc</guid><description>Wonder Electricals Limited reported a dramatic year-on-year decline in its Q3 FY26 financial results. Standalone revenue slumped 39.37% to ₹15,255.53 Cr, while Profit After Tax (PAT) plummeted 87.14% to ₹65.57 Cr. Consolidated figures also showed significant drops, with PAT falling 87.27% to ₹65.02 Cr. Despite the poor performance, the board declared a 10% interim dividend.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 08:34:05 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c3efdfa94ce7dec4833bb_1770799570619.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Viceroy Hotels Q3 PAT Surges 50%, Eyes Growth Via ₹206 Cr Asset Buy</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Viceroy-Hotels-Q3-PAT-Surges-50percent-Eyes-Growth-Via-206-Cr-Asset-Buy/698c3eabfa94ce7dec48337b</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Tourism/Viceroy-Hotels-Q3-PAT-Surges-50percent-Eyes-Growth-Via-206-Cr-Asset-Buy/698c3eabfa94ce7dec48337b</guid><description>Viceroy Hotels Limited reported a robust 50.38% YoY surge in consolidated Profit After Tax (PAT) for Q3 FY26, reaching ₹1,095.85 Lakhs. This uptick was fueled by lower tax expenses and increased 'other income'. However, consolidated revenue saw only a marginal 2.41% YoY rise to ₹3,866.34 Lakhs. The nine-month period presents a contrasting picture, with PAT plunging 81.89% YoY to ₹1,231.74 Lakhs due to a high base. The company also announced a significant ₹206 Crore acquisition of SLN Terminus Hotels &amp; Resorts, expanding into long-stay hospitality. Ongoing PMLA proceedings and a lack of management guidance warrant investor attention.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 08:32:43 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c3eabfa94ce7dec48337a_1770799202225.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Simplex Realty Posts Steep Q3 Loss, Auditor Flags Associate Company Risks</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Simplex-Realty-Posts-Steep-Q3-Loss-Auditor-Flags-Associate-Company-Risks/698c3daafa94ce7dec482e5c</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Real-Estate/Simplex-Realty-Posts-Steep-Q3-Loss-Auditor-Flags-Associate-Company-Risks/698c3daafa94ce7dec482e5c</guid><description>Simplex Realty Limited reported a significant financial setback for Q3 FY26, with standalone revenue falling 19.98% YoY to ₹20.86 Cr and a net loss of ₹35.11 Cr. The nine-month standalone loss widened to ₹173.03 Cr. Consolidated figures mirrored this downturn, reporting a Q3 loss of ₹36.21 Cr. Crucially, the auditor's limited review flagged "emphasis of matter" regarding associate companies whose net worth is fully eroded, raising going concern doubts, and the company's non-impairment of loans to a net-worth-negative associate.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 08:28:26 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c3daafa94ce7dec482e5b_1770799476409.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Titan Stock Hits Record High Amidst Price-Driven Sales</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titan-Stock-Hits-Record-High-Amidst-Price-Driven-Sales/698c3d3ffa94ce7dec482d04</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Consumer-Products/Titan-Stock-Hits-Record-High-Amidst-Price-Driven-Sales/698c3d3ffa94ce7dec482d04</guid><description>Titan Company's shares climbed to a record high following robust Q3 FY26 results, with net profit jumping 61% to ₹1,684 crore and revenue up 40% to ₹24,592 crore. This surge, however, masks a concerning trend of declining jewelry sales volumes, which fell 24% in 2025, driven primarily by record gold prices tempering consumer demand. The company's strategies focus on offsetting this by promoting exchanges and lower-carat options, while its premium valuation faces scrutiny against peers.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 08:26:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c3d3ffa94ce7dec482d03_1770799379118.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Wonder Electricals Profit Plummets 98.7% YoY Standalone; Declares 10% Interim Dividend</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Wonder-Electricals-Profit-Plummets-987percent-YoY-Standalone-Declares-10percent-Interim-Dividend/698c3d36fa94ce7dec482ca7</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Industrial-Goods-Services/Wonder-Electricals-Profit-Plummets-987percent-YoY-Standalone-Declares-10percent-Interim-Dividend/698c3d36fa94ce7dec482ca7</guid><description>Wonder Electricals reported a drastic YoY decline in standalone Q3 FY26 net profit, down 98.71% to ₹6.57 Lakhs, with revenue falling 29.13%. Consolidated results showed a mixed picture: Q3 revenue and PAT saw significant drops, while 9M PAT rose 34.38% due to lower tax provisions, despite a 54.45% revenue contraction. The company declared a 10% interim dividend. A discrepancy in consolidated 9M FY25 PAT figures and absence of management guidance add to investor concerns.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 08:26:30 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c3d36fa94ce7dec482ca6_1770799687465.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Godrej Agrovet Q3 Revenue Soars 11%, Strategic Portfolio Review Initiated</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Godrej-Agrovet-Q3-Revenue-Soars-11percent-Strategic-Portfolio-Review-Initiated/698c3cc7fa94ce7dec482bac</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Agriculture/Godrej-Agrovet-Q3-Revenue-Soars-11percent-Strategic-Portfolio-Review-Initiated/698c3cc7fa94ce7dec482bac</guid><description>Godrej Agrovet (GAVL) reported robust Q3 FY26 results, with consolidated revenues climbing 11% YoY. Profit before tax jumped 23% YoY. Key drivers included Animal Feed volume growth (+12%), stellar Vegetable Oil revenue (+27%), and Crop Protection revenue increase (+37%). Astec Life Sciences showed a strong turnaround. GAVL is undertaking a deep strategic review of its business portfolio, with decisions expected by April.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 08:24:39 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c3cc7fa94ce7dec482bab_1770799140095.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>JSW Warns of Car Launch Delay Over China Parts Import Snag</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/JSW-Warns-of-Car-Launch-Delay-Over-China-Parts-Import-Snag/698c3ca4fa94ce7dec482b83</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Auto/JSW-Warns-of-Car-Launch-Delay-Over-China-Parts-Import-Snag/698c3ca4fa94ce7dec482b83</guid><description>JSW Motors is flagging a potential delay to its highly anticipated first car launch, expected in the second half of this year. The automotive venture, part of the JSW Group's $3 billion investment in Maharashtra, requires expedited licenses for critical Chinese-sourced components, such as safety glass. India's stringent quality control regulations, designed to curb low-quality imports, are creating a bottleneck for suppliers needing local certification, jeopardizing timelines.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 08:24:04 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c3ca4fa94ce7dec482b82_1770799437193.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item><item><title>Fairchem Organics Q3 Revenue Misses Estimates, Profit Plummets Amidst Import Woes</title><link>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Fairchem-Organics-Q3-Revenue-Misses-Estimates-Profit-Plummets-Amidst-Import-Woes/698c3c37fa94ce7dec482a74</link><guid>https://www.whalesbook.com/news/English/Chemicals/Fairchem-Organics-Q3-Revenue-Misses-Estimates-Profit-Plummets-Amidst-Import-Woes/698c3c37fa94ce7dec482a74</guid><description>Fairchem Organics reported a challenging Q3 FY26, with revenue at ₹100 crore (12% YoY decline) missing analyst estimates and adjusted PAT at ₹60 lakhs significantly underperforming projections. Impacted by import competition and lower paint sector off-take, EBITDA margins compressed to 4.2%. Management sees the worst behind them, targeting export recovery and new product launches for sequential growth from Q4 FY26.</description><pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 08:22:15 +0000</pubDate><enclosure url="https://images.whalesbook.com/images/thumbnail_698c3c37fa94ce7dec482a73_1770799356242.jpeg" type="image/jpeg" /></item></channel></rss>